TOKEN	NE
1a	O
-1179	O
.	O
Sponge	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
at	O
fishers	B-place
Island	I-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
stone	O
of	O
it	O
thrown	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
.	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Winthorpe	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
New	B-place
England	I-place
.	O
202	O
-1180	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
globose	O
lapis	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Haines	I-pers
-1181	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
growing	O
upon	O
an	O
East	O
India	O
pearl	O
oyster	O
shell	O
,	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
solid	O
&	O
the	O
holes	O
of	O
various	O
figures	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hodson	I-pers
from	O
Mocha	B-place
.	O
vid	O
Shells	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
205	O
208	O
.	O
-1182	O
.	O
Fungus	O
saxeus	O
from	O
Mocha	B-place
.	O
Id	O
.	O
205	O
-1183	O
.	O
A	O
smaller	O
bra	O
n	O
ched	O
,	O
solid	O
tho	O
it	O
hath	O
cavities	O
alongst	O
its	O
branches	O
.	O
Id	O
200	O
-1184	O
Rete	O
marinum	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
shell	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
-1185	O
.	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
dichotom	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
larger	O
sort	O
from	O
Witney	B-place
quarry	O
.	O
200	O
15	O
q	O
-1186	O
.	O
Astroites	O
fossil	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
75	O
200	O
-1187	O
.	O
Calix	O
corallinus	O
in	O
saxo	O
arenario	O
.	O
From	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Breynius	I-pers
from	O
Dantzig	B-place
.	O
32	O
15	O
q	O
-1188	O
.	O
Spongia	O
spuria	O
dura	O
hollow	O
&	O
of	O
a	O
Conicall	O
figure	O
growing	O
on	O
white	O
corall	O
.	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Laurie	I-pers
from	O
Campeche	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1189	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
mamillæ.Id	O
.	O
200	O
-1190	O
.	O
Flatt	O
white	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
starry	O
cavities	O
thick	O
sett	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
205	O
-1191	O
.	O
Branchedcorall	O
from	O
the	O
quarry	O
at	O
Witney	B-place
.	O
43	O
1192	O
.	O
Broad	O
corallium	O
porosum	O
of	O
a	O
blew	O
colour	O
from	O
sumatra	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
32	O
-1193	O
.	O
Astroites.Id	O
.	O
32	O
-1194	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
190.	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Swymmor	I-pers
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
petrified	O
bone	O
from	O
the	O
Western	O
shore	O
of	O
Cheseapeak	B-place
bay	I-place
189	O
248	O
1195	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
elation	O
ramisla	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
colore	O
dilute	O
purpureo	O
from	O
the	O
shores	O
of	O
Georgia	B-place
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
208	O
1196.	O
cof	O
lore	O
sulphures	O
wt	O
.	O
bustard	O
sponge	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
208	O
1197.	O
lactuca	O
marina	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1198.	O
bastard	O
sponge	O
&	O
fucus	O
feniculaceus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1199.	O
color	O
dilute	O
sulphurec	O
wt	O
lacti	O
mar	O
.	O
Id	O
1200.	O
spec	O
.	O
feniculaceus	O
Id	O
.	O
1201.	O
wt	O
a	O
solid	O
corall	O
white	O
Id	O
2	O
Coralls	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
207	O
LXXIIII	O
2	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
?	O
Rete	O
marin	O
.	O
branched	O
?	O
LXXVI	O
3	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
maxi=	O
=mum	O
striatum	O
&	O
stellatum	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Canaries	B-place
.	O
208	O
4	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
elatior	O
ramis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
teretibus	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
3.	O
upon	O
207	O
LXXXVIII	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
No	O
.	O
3.	O
with	O
barnacles	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
208	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
208	O
7	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
?	O
Vid	O
the	O
same	O
growing	O
in	O
the	O
soundings	O
No	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
LXXIX	O
upon	O
206	O
8	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adult	O
=erinum	O
.	O
J.B	O
?	O
upon	O
200	O
C	O
V.	O
206	O
9	O
.	O
A	O
bottle	O
covered	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
207	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
wreck	O
ship	O
covered	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
207	O
11	O
.	O
Red	O
corall	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
rock	O
wt	O
.	O
shells	O
.	O
206	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
without	O
shells	O
.	O
Vid	O
Imperat	O
Edit	O
Nariol	O
1590.	O
p.	O
714	O
.	O
Venet	O
.	O
1672.	O
pag	O
.	O
622	O
.	O
Latin	O
pag	O
8	O
.	O
Vid	O
Aldrovand	O
Mus	O
.	O
Metall	O
.	O
206	O
13	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
punctatum	O
Stellatum	O
?	O
/	O
From	O
Carber	B-place
Vid	O
Ferr	O
ad	O
Imperat	O
.	O
upon	O
207	O
2a	O
1202	O
.	O
A	O
foot	O
long	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
covered	O
here	O
&	O
there	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
thin	O
gray	O
crust	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
center	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
brown	O
woody	O
substance	O
such	O
as	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
large	O
corallines	O
.	O
This	O
woody	O
-	O
substance	O
is	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
midle	O
of	O
the	O
branches	O
some	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
solid	O
.	O
Given	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Francin	I-pers
✓	O
207	O
.	O
1203	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
elatior	O
ramis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
crasta	O
tuberculata	O
crown	O
.	O
From	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
from	O
Georgia	B-place
208	O
1204	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
eight	O
reals	O
covered	O
wt	O
.	O
an	O
astroites	O
&	O
redish	O
crust	O
or	O
sediment	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
189	O
.	O
1205	O
.	O
A	O
sea	O
fan	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
sphondylus	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
from	O
208	O
1206.	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1207.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
sphondylus	O
&	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
No	O
868	O
173	O
.	O
CVI	O
.	O
1208	O
growing	O
on	O
its	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
the	O
crust	O
rub	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
upon	O
207	O
CVII	O
1209	O
very	O
tall	O
wt	O
its	O
purple	O
crust	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
upon	O
206	O
CVIII	O
1210.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
long	O
coralline	O
matter	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
CIX	O
1211.	O
wt.other	O
fruticose	O
corallines	O
intermix	O
'd	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
upon	O
206	O
CX	O
1212	O
.	O
Keratophyton	O
flabelliforme	O
cortice	O
verrucoso	O
abductum	O
.	O
Ray	O
ed	O
.	O
3.	O
p.	O
32	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dupuys	I-pers
.	O
the	O
wood	O
is	O
whitish	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
large	O
an	O
præced	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
CXXXIIII	O
1213.	O
the	O
same	O
blackish	O
&	O
smaller	O
the	O
crust	O
intirely	O
rubd	O
of	O
and	O
a	O
sea	O
fan	O
both	O
on	O
a	O
basis	O
of	O
corallud	O
solid	O
matter	O
.	O
from	O
Antego	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
CXXXV	O
1214	O
.	O
A	O
sea	O
fann	O
wt	O
.	O
spongia	O
dura	O
adhering	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
206	O
1215	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
infundibuli	O
forma	O
.	O
2	O
1216.	O
wt	O
.	O
large	O
cavities	O
for	O
pholades	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
200	O
1217	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
of	O
an	O
odd	O
consistence	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
horney	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
sea	O
feather	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
1218	O
more	O
branched	O
.	O
wide	O
208	O
1219.	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
corall	O
broke	O
1220	O
.	O
A	O
Sprigg	O
of	O
black	O
corall	O
sett	O
on	O
a	O
pedestall	O
.	O
3	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
upon	O
207	O
200	O
200	O
15	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
?	O
207	O
LXXVIII	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adult	O
=erinum	O
J.B.	O
flatt	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
somewhat	O
more	O
open	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
some	O
what	O
differing	O
?	O
207	O
217	O
CXI	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
grosser	O
&	O
c.	O
very	O
large	O
75	O
208	O
20	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
.	O
206	O
21	O
.	O
Corallium	O
maximum	O
porosum	O
Stellatum	O
?	O
wt.a	O
sprigg	O
of	O
red	O
Coral	O
&	O
Tubuli	O
vermium	O
208	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
No	O
.	O
13.	O
only	O
no	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
nor	O
points	O
.	O
208	O
23	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
minus	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
CXIII	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
ad=	O
=ulterinum	O
JB	O
flatt	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
sparse	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
189	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
28	O
.	O
Hippuris	O
saxea	O
Coralloides	O
Clus	O
.	O
208	O
29	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
with	O
corall	O
&	O
Sponge	O
?	O
200	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
purple	O
stalks	O
&	O
Sponge	O
?	O
208	O
31	O
.	O
Dark	O
green	O
corall	O
Gr.G	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
206	O
32	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
non	O
porosum	O
muri	O
catum	O
minus	O
?	O
206	O
3a	O
1221	O
.	O
The	O
honey	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
frutex	O
marinus	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
sphondylus	O
200	O
1222	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
long	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
sawed	O
thro	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
structure	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
?	O
208	O
.	O
288	O
1223	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
piece	O
round	O
growing	O
upon	O
coralline	O
matter	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
1224	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
severall	O
angular	O
pipes	O
.	O
194	O
1225	O
.	O
One	O
single	O
star	O
of	O
white	O
corall	O
at	O
top	O
red	O
at	O
bottoms	O
190	O
1226	O
.	O
Astroites	O
short	O
&	O
thick	O
on	O
shells	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
201	O
.	O
1227	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
chrystallin	O
fossil	O
in	O
England	O
calld	O
by	O
some	O
basaltes	O
.	O
201	O
1228	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
upon	O
which	O
are	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
&	O
c.	O
201	O
1229.	O
wt	O
.	O
very	O
fine	O
striæ	O
201	O
.	O
1230.	O
wt	O
.	O
courser	O
striæ	O
201	O
.	O
1231.	O
of	O
a	O
conicall	O
shape	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1232	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
leaves	O
of	O
from	O
China	B-place
an	O
astroites	O
or	O
or	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1233	O
.	O
Androsace	O
chameconche	O
innascens	O
.	O
C.B	O
.	O
pin	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
medi	B-place
terranean	I-place
sea	I-place
.	O
upon	O
206	O
208	O
1234	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
elatior	O
ramulis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
compressis	O
luteis	O
from	O
Antego	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	I-pers
upon	O
206	O
208	O
1235	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
humilior	O
ramulis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
teretibus	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
crust	O
raised	O
by	O
tubercles	O
wch	O
.	O
when	O
rub	O
'd	O
of	O
appear	O
so	O
many	O
holes	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1236	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
pale	O
frutex	O
marinus	O
&	O
covered	O
over	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
white	O
sediment	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1237	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
inward	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
frutex	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
sediment	O
&	O
a	O
small	O
nautilus	O
or	O
cochlea	O
marina	O
growing	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
208	O
1238	O
.	O
Long	O
twigs	O
wt	O
.	O
hard	O
coralline	O
matter	O
growing	O
on	O
them	O
from	O
Georgia	B-place
.	O
208	O
1239	O
.	O
A	O
tuft	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
hairs	O
wt	O
out	O
coralline	O
matter	O
likely	O
lost	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
208	O
1240	O
.	O
Spongia	O
minor	O
ramosa	O
from	O
Georgia	B-place
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jenkens	I-pers
.	O
200	O
1241	O
.	O
Fucus	O
feniculaceus	O
of	O
a	O
purplish	O
colour	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
1242	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
latissimum	O
muricatum	O
&	O
c.	O
rub	O
'd	O
clear	O
wt	O
.	O
red	O
corall	O
drops	O
from	O
Antego	B-place
.	O
Balanus	O
208	O
1243	O
.	O
A	O
balanus	O
coverd	O
wt	O
.	O
white	O
corall	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1244	O
.	O
Alcyonium	O
milesum	O
&	O
c.	O
Pat	O
is	O
tubuli	O
&	O
c.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
208	O
4	O
33	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
?	O
200	O
34	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
206	O
35	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
36	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
37	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
a	O
litle	O
redish	O
177.	O
upon	O
207	O
38	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
.	O
206	O
39	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
striated	O
safron	O
coloured	O
corall	O
.	O
206	O
40	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
,	O
wt	O
.	O
shells	O
red	O
corall	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
200	O
41.	O
red	O
corall	O
.	O
206	O
42	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
stellatum	O
minimum	O
.	O
206	O
201	O
43	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
upon	O
a	O
stony	O
basis	O
.	O
207	O
44	O
.	O
Tethya	O
?	O
207	O
45	O
.	O
Eschara	O
?	O
207	O
wt	O
worms	O
173	O
.	O
46	O
.	O
Eschara	O
?	O
upon	O
200	O
208	O
46	O
*	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
542	O
207	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
542	O
.	O
208	O
?	O
47	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
round	O
holes	O
or	O
starrs	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
189	O
48	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
punctatum	O
minus	O
.	O
208	O
49	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
latissimum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
the	O
murices	O
wore	O
off	O
207	O
208	O
50	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
51	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
?	O
208	O
52	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
stella	O
arborescens	O
Vid	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
206	O
53	O
.	O
Tethya	O
?	O
206	O
4a	O
-1245	O
.	O
Astroites	O
single	O
stars	O
extant	O
disjoind	O
from	O
Antego	B-place
.	O
perhaps	O
Fucus	O
Phasganoides	O
.	O
200	O
-1246	O
.	O
Fucus	O
albidus	O
membranaceus	O
like	O
dilesk	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Vid	O
.	O
Veg	O
672	O
.	O
209	O
-1247	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
minor	O
crebris	O
spongia	O
di	O
forma	O
Arborea	O
Imperati	O
p.	O
730.	O
fororm	O
inibus	O
pertise	O
.	O
from	O
Antigua	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1248	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
minima	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
200	O
-1249	O
.	O
1248	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
sphondylus	O
.	O
Id	B-place
200	O
-1250	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
round	O
a	O
fruticulus	O
marinus	O
stem	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1251	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
oblonga	O
fibris	O
paucioribus	O
.	O
Id	B-place
200	O
.	O
-1252	O
.	O
Eadem	O
plana	O
fibris	O
crebris	O
purpurascentibus	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1253	O
.	O
Eadem	O
oblongo	O
rotund	O
a	O
cava	O
fiasca	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1254	O
.	O
Ead	O
flavicuns	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
200	O
-1255	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
albida	O
subrotunda	O
fibris	O
paucioribus	O
flavicautibus	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
-1256.	O
crebrioribus	O
intus	O
cavernosa	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
-1257.	O
fibris	O
tenucoribus	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
201	O
-1258.	O
humilis	O
ramosa	O
Id	B-place
.	O
201	O
-1259.	O
loith	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
&	O
c.	O
Id	B-place
201	O
-1260	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
infundibuli	O
forma	O
flavicans	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
207	O
-1261.	O
albida	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
207	O
-1262	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
medullæ	O
panis	O
similis	O
infundibuli	O
forma	O
superficie	O
apicibus	O
innocentibus	O
extantibus	O
quaso	O
echinata	O
Id	B-place
.	O
3	O
growing	O
together	O
.	O
207	O
-1263	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
single	O
Id	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
-1264	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
opened	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
-1265	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
medullæ	O
paris	O
similis	O
fistulosa	O
superficie	O
apicibus	O
introcentibus	O
extantinus	O
quasi	O
echinata	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
7	O
together	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
root	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
-1266	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
nine	O
together	O
lower	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
-1267	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
five	O
together	O
higher	O
.	O
Id	B-place
207	O
-1268	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
two	O
together	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
museulus	O
meth	O
Id	B-place
.	O
207	O
-1269	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
medulla	O
panis	O
similis	O
fistulosa	O
fistula	O
singulari	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
208	O
-1270.	O
dapliod	O
.	O
Id	B-place
5	O
54	O
.	O
Corallÿ	O
nigri	O
ramus	O
.	O
206	O
-55	O
.	O
Astroites	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
8	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
56	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
8	O
freseed	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
189	O
water	O
.	O
-57	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
coralline	O
matter	O
precipitated	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
others	O
.	O
199	O
c.	O
58	O
.	O
Four	O
quarter	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
had	O
lain	O
59	O
years	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
vid	O
.	O
nat	O
.	O
Hist	O
of	O
Jam	O
189	O
-59	O
.	O
Beginning	O
or	O
first	O
rudiments	O
of	O
the	O
astroites	O
189	O
-60	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c	O
199	O
e	O
-61	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
62	O
.	O
Astroiteswt	O
.	O
large	O
starrs	O
,	O
upon	O
.	O
a	O
stony	O
basis	O
where	O
is	O
a	O
lesser	O
.	O
189	O
190	O
63	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
one	O
wt	O
.	O
smaller	O
starrs	O
.	O
190	O
64	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
one	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
hole	O
in	O
its	O
midle	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
65	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
round	O
one	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
&	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
worm	O
.	O
200	O
-66	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
broad	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
crooked	O
hole	O
going	O
th	O
rough	O
its	O
surface	O
for	O
a	O
solen	O
or	O
worm	O
.	O
sold	O
.	O
Given	O
me	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
of	O
Lancashire	B-place
where	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
't	O
was	O
fossil	O
.	O
}	O
0	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
67	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
piece	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
189	O
68	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
piece	O
wt	O
.	O
large	O
angular	O
starrs	O
,	O
solid	O
with	O
a	O
cavity	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
202	O
189	O
5a	O
-1271	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
flavicans	O
medullæ	O
panis	O
sinnlis	O
fistulosa	O
fistula	O
triplici	O
.	O
from	O
Antego	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
208	O
-1272.	O
fistula	O
quintuplici	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1273.	O
sextuplus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1274.	O
fistulis	O
phirmus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1275.	O
fibris	O
albidis	O
tenuibus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1276.	O
endern	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
varietas	O
.	O
208	O
-1277	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
altissima	O
e	O
luteo	O
fusca	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1278.	O
varietas	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
-1279	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
fistulosa	O
e	O
luteo	O
fusca	O
fibris	O
paucioribus	O
.	O
Id	O
208	O
-1280.	O
varietas	O
.	O
Id	O
208	O
-1281.	O
fistula	O
duplici	O
Id	O
208	O
-1282	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
medulle	O
panis	O
similis	O
infundibali	O
forma	O
flavicans	O
superficie	O
cavitatibus	O
donata	O
.	O
Id	O
208	O
1283	O
The	O
same	O
flatted	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1284	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
two	O
sticking	O
together	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1285	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
subrotunda	O
subfusca	O
caver	O
nosa	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
1286	O
.	O
A	O
varietie	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
shell	O
.	O
208	O
1287	O
.	O
Spongia	O
globosa	O
foraminibus	O
donata	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1288	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
harder	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
1289	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Id	O
208	O
-1290	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
caverns	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Id	O
200	O
208	O
1291	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
branched	O
&	O
white	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
208	O
1292	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
altissima	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.7	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
upon	O
a	O
sphondylus	O
.	O
207	O
206	O
1293.	O
upon	O
broalves	O
,	O
tubuli	O
&	O
c.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1294	O
.	O
The	O
primordia	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1295	O
.	O
Pila	O
marina	O
subrotunda	O
compressa	O
mollis	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6.	O
>	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
1296	O
.	O
Vesicaria	O
marina	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
litle	O
redish	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
207	O
1297	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
Sparia	O
globosa	O
cavernosa	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
207	O
6	O
69	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
very	O
small	O
starrs	O
small	O
&	O
of	O
a	O
darker	O
colour	O
given	O
g	O
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
202	O
70	O
The	O
same	O
smaller	O
wt	O
.	O
larger	O
starrs	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
71	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
astroites	O
solid	O
wt	O
.	O
large	O
starrs	O
.	O
154	O
202	O
72	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hickes	I-pers
.	O
D.	O
189	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
?	O
-73	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
fossil	O
?	O
189	O
15	O
q	O
-74	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
fossil	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
selfe	O
at	O
Faringdon	B-place
in	O
Barkshire	B-place
where	O
stony	O
matter	O
is	O
Joined	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
193	O
-75	O
.	O
A	O
featherd	O
agate	O
from	O
Wiltshire	B-place
or	O
flint	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
astroites-	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
flinty	O
matter	O
&	O
polishes	O
as	O
it	O
.	O
202	O
-76	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
193	O
-77	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
polished	O
.	O
84	O
.	O
78	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
71.	O
given	O
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bennet	I-pers
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
202	O
79	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
tubularia	O
purpurea	O
Imperat.|	O
Imperat	O
fol	O
.	O
Edit	O
pag	O
.	O
729	O
.	O
4to	O
Edit	O
List	O
.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
astroites	O
.	O
pa	O
822	O
n.	O
301	O
.	O
Pseudo	O
coralium	O
rubrum	O
balaincles	O
Aldrovand	O
mus	O
201	O
200	O
6a	O
-1298	O
.	O
An	O
hemisphericall	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
wt	O
.	O
very	O
fine	O
striae	O
from	O
Barbados	B-place
.	O
✓	O
208	O
-1299	O
.	O
Severall	O
astroite	O
some	O
corrugated	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
growing	O
on	O
shells	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
200	O
208	O
-1300	O
.	O
Corallines	O
very	O
small	O
(	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
pedicle	O
)	O
of	O
spheri	O
call	O
figure	O
figne	O
vid	O
.	O
seba	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
✓	O
208	O
-1301	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
yellowish	O
fungites	O
or	O
rather	O
coralloid	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
kind	O
?	O
From	O
suisserland	B-place
.	O
CXLI	O
.	O
230.	O
e	O
1302	O
.	O
Another	O
whitish	O
coloured	O
Id	B-place
.	O
CXLII	O
✓	O
207	O
-1303	O
.	O
1302	O
Another	O
corrugated	O
on	O
the	O
edges	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
CXLIII	O
-1304	O
.	O
1303	O
Another	O
of	O
a	O
conicall	O
figure	O
wt	O
.	O
out	O
any	O
cavity	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
CXLIV	O
230.	O
e	O
-1305	O
Single	O
stars	O
of	O
the	O
fungites	O
kind	O
,	O
fossil	O
?	O
small	O
?	O
200|	O
-1306.	O
larger	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
one	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
tree	O
oyster	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
200|	O
-1307.	O
black	O
&	O
crooked	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
clay	O
plestrcites	O
.	O
markd	O
414	O
.	O
200|	O
-1308.	O
gray	O
markd	O
479	O
.	O
200|	O
-1309	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
punctatum	O
minus	O
from	O
Jama	B-place
.	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
15	O
q	O
208	O
.	O
1310	O
.	O
Corallium	O
nigrum	O
reticulatum	O
.	O
From	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ranby	I-pers
.	O
208	O
.	O
-1311	O
.	O
A	O
broad	O
masse	O
of	O
Corallium	O
album	O
punctatum	O
or	O
stellatum	O
minus	O
,	O
wt	O
.	O
corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
?	O
pholades	O
,	O
bivalves	O
&	O
red	O
coraline	O
spotts	O
,	O
naturally	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
.	O
CCXXXV.III	O
.	O
upon	O
200	O
-1312	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
fossil	O
corall	O
in	O
stone	O
the	O
cavities	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
striated	O
length	O
ways	O
an	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Astroites	O
or	O
fungites	O
?	O
markd	O
formerly	O
367	O
.	O
205	O
.	O
-1313	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
an	O
astroites	O
wch	O
.	O
grew	O
on	O
a	O
concha	O
margaritifera	O
203	O
.	O
1314	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
rock	O
or	O
corall	O
roots	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
lodged	O
pholades	O
203	O
1315	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
intire	O
haemisphericall	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
-	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
Obs	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
Amsterdam	O
1674.	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
142	O
205	O
1316	O
.	O
Lithoshracion	O
.	O
205	O
16	O
J	O
.	O
1317	O
.	O
A	O
common	O
oyster	O
wt	O
.	O
common	O
coralline	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
205	O
1318	O
fucus	O
&	O
part	O
or	O
knob	O
for	O
the	O
sticking	O
of	O
a	O
rock	O
oyster	O
205	O
1319	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
astroites	O
205	O
1320	O
.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
coralls	O
.	O
205	O
7	O
80	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
,	O
a	O
smaller	O
piece	O
.	O
200	O
207	O
81	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
smaller	O
piece	O
.	O
189	O
?	O
-82	O
.	O
Large	O
tubularia	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
pipes-	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
starrs	O
.	O
Fossil	O
?	O
-83	O
.	O
Astroites	O
agate	O
unpolished	O
.	O
189	O
-84	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
polished	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
189	O
15	O
P.	O
85	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
fossil	O
with	O
pieces	O
of	O
stone	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
69	O
.	O
189	O
202	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
Round	O
pretty	O
large	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
202	O
200	O
88	O
.	O
A	O
segment	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
200	O
89	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
white	O
.	O
189	O
205	O
90	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
und=	O
=ulatus	O
more	O
solid	O
.	O
205	O
.	O
91	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
200	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
190	O
93	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
outward	O
ear	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
Obs	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
Amsterdam	O
1674.	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
142	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
205	O
94	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
very	O
large	O
striæ	O
,	O
intire	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
205	O
95	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
200	O
7a	O
-1321	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
globular	O
or	O
hemisphericall	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
wt	O
.	O
narrower	O
sulci	O
>	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
near	O
Bermudus	B-place
&	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
-	O
-1322	O
.	O
One	O
longer	O
-1323	O
.	O
Astroites	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
slate	O
stone	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barrets	I-pers
collections	O
.	O
2	O
00	O
-1324	O
.	O
Another	O
sort	O
.	O
200	O
210	O
-1325	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
200	O
-1326	O
.	O
Striated	O
pipes	O
of	O
an	O
astroites	O
in	O
a	O
yellow	O
stone	O
from	O
Arkindale	B-place
in	O
Yorkshire	B-place
200	O
-1327	O
.	O
A	O
tethya	O
from	O
Antegua	B-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
?	O
or	O
pumice	O
mart	O
17	O
....	O
200	O
.	O
1328.	O
roundish	O
wt	O
.	O
straight	O
shining	O
striæ	O
?	O
200	O
.	O
-1329	O
.	O
Small	O
astroitae	O
in	O
the	O
surface	O
of	O
chalk	O
.	O
200	O
15	O
q	O
-1330.	O
flint	O
.	O
200	O
75	O
-1331.	O
in	O
stone	O
brown	O
.	O
200	O
-1332	O
in	O
a	O
gray	O
stone	O
.	O
200	O
15	O
q	O
{	O
-1333.	O
blew	O
stone	O
.	O
200	O
15	O
q	O
{	O
-1334	O
.	O
Fungitæ	O
long	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
loose	O
.	O
202	O
15	O
P	O
1335	O
.	O
Sticking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
stone	O
.	O
markd	O
formely	O
35	O
.	O
200	O
-1336	O
.	O
Caryophyllus	O
lapideus	O
200	O
-1337	O
.	O
The	O
fungites	O
p.	O
182.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
list	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
M.	O
200	O
-1338	O
.	O
Algæ	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Georgia	B-place
?	O
200	O
-1339	O
.	O
Lithostration	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
-1340	O
.	O
159	O
Fungitæ	O
or	O
coralls	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
-1341	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
1335.	O
in	O
a	O
harder	O
stone	O
From	O
Tenby	B-place
&	O
amp	O
;	O
Caldy	B-place
Island	I-place
.	O
200	O
-1342	O
.	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
ex	O
Agro	O
Vicentino	O
from	O
fan	O
monti	O
.	O
177	O
-1343	O
.	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
ex	O
monte	O
Zibio	O
Agri	O
Mutinensis	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
-1344	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
fossilis	O
ex	O
agro	O
Vicentino	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
-1345	O
.	O
Astroites	O
chrystallo	O
in	O
interna	O
parte	O
obdictus	O
ex	O
agro	O
Veron	O
177	O
75	O
-1346	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
fossilis	O
tubulis	O
Maioribus	O
ex	O
una	O
parte	O
ex	O
polita	O
ex	O
agro	O
Vicentino	O
.	O
177	O
-1347	O
.	O
Astroites	O
laevigatue	O
stellis	O
majoribus	O
ex	O
agro	O
Veronensis	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
8	O
96	O
.	O
A	O
segment	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
long	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
Boccone	O
Recherchy	O
Obs	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
Amsterdam	O
1674	O
Fig	O
.	O
p.	O
142	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
205	O
97	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
very	O
white	O
.	O
189	O
98	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
intire	O
sea	O
rose	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
Stellated	O
pipe	O
in	O
its	O
center	O
.	O
205	O
99	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
longer	O
striæ	O
.	O
205	O
100	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
a	O
lesser	O
.	O
205	O
101	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
yet	O
lesser	O
with	O
a	O
ped=	O
=unculus	O
.	O
205	O
102	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
branched	O
.	O
205	O
103	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
more	O
solid	O
.	O
205	O
104	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
199.	O
b	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
lesser	O
cavities	O
.	O
206	O
106	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
fungus	O
lapideus	O
.	O
205	O
107	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
lesser	O
.	O
205	O
108	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
contorted	O
.	O
when	O
fluid	O
?	O
205	O
-109	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
75	O
.	O
202	O
203	O
74	O
.	O
110	O
.	O
An	O
tubularice	O
,	O
stalactitis	O
vel	O
belem=	O
=nitis	O
Species	O
?	O
|	O
tubuli	O
marini	O
.	O
190	O
189	O
189	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
201	O
8a	O
-1348	O
.	O
Astroites	O
Veronensis	O
alius	O
chrystallo	O
farctus	O
.	O
Monti	O
177	O
28	O
-1349	O
.	O
Coralloides	O
planta	O
ex	O
una	O
parte	O
plana	O
,	O
&	O
exarte	O
lavigata	O
ex	O
agro	O
Vicentino	O
.	O
177	O
-1350	O
Coralloides	O
planta	O
fossilis	O
exuna	O
parte	O
plana	O
agri	O
Vicentino	O
177	O
-1351	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
tubulis	O
tenacoribus	O
ex	O
agro	O
Vicentino	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
15	O
q	O
-1352	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
altera	O
tubulis	O
majoribus	O
ex	O
eadem	O
loco	O
.	O
177	O
1353	O
.	O
Fossile	O
ad	O
marinam	O
tubuluriam	O
nonactul	O
accedens	O
ex	O
agro	O
Veronensi	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
-1354	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
perfectly	O
round	O
from	O
Jama	B-place
.	O
178	O
.	O
177	O
15	O
P.	O
-1355	O
.	O
The	O
primordia	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
astroites	O
.	O
Id	B-place
.	O
74	O
178	O
-1356	O
.	O
Lithostration	O
in	O
sevll	O
.	O
conditions	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
-1357	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
gronove	O
?	O
177	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
-1358	O
.	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
bicorne	O
from	O
Witney	B-place
177	O
-1359	O
.	O
Two	O
fungites	O
's	O
.	O
177	O
1360	O
.	O
A	O
bushy	O
sort	O
of	O
abies	O
marina	O
?	O
Sticking	O
to	O
the	O
root	O
of	O
fucus	O
phasganoides	O
from	O
Greenland	B-place
lat	O
.	O
82.	O
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Craycoot	I-pers
.	O
200	O
.	O
-1361	O
.	O
A	O
broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Sponge	O
flatt	O
wt	O
.	O
sevll	O
.	O
tubercles	O
on	O
its	O
outside	O
&	O
upper	O
side	O
207.	O
c	O
-1362	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
tunnell	O
.	O
207.	O
c.	O
-1363	O
.	O
Corallium	O
minus	O
porosum	O
candicans	O
muricatum	O
growin	O
on	O
the	O
rete	O
marinum	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
also	O
is	O
a	O
tree	O
oyster	O
.	O
207.	O
b	O
-1364	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
upon	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
eight	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
wralkd	O
ship	O
in	O
Hispaniola	B-place
.	O
199	O
b	O
207	O
b	O
-1365	O
.	O
Sevll	O
.	O
plants	O
of	O
the	O
abies	O
marina	O
bolgica	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
pebble	O
from	O
the	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
coast	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pate	I-pers
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Buddle	O
's	O
207.	O
a	O
32	O
-1366	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
sponge	O
?	O
birds	O
nest	O
markd	O
formerly	O
200	O
?	O
1367	O
.	O
Abies	O
marina	O
bolgica	O
growing	O
on	O
an	O
urtica	O
marina	O
?	O
200	O
9	O
112	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
longer	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
206	O
207	O
113	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
shorter	O
.	O
201	O
114	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
?	O
in	O
round	O
lumps	O
from	O
the	O
Streights	O
an	O
confetti	O
di	O
Tivoli	B-place
?	O
201	O
-115	O
.	O
A	O
lesser	O
feather	O
'd	O
agate	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
75	O
.	O
189	O
75	O
116	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
black	O
corall	O
.	O
206	O
117	O
.	O
Hippuris	O
saxea	O
coralloides	O
.	O
Clus	O
.	O
upon	O
a	O
rock	O
|	O
Dr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
206	O
-118	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
?	O
CXVI	O
upon	O
206	O
119	O
.	O
CXVII	O
.	O
The	O
inward	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
an	O
black	O
corall	O
?	O
-120	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
large	O
&	O
woody	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
coralline	O
rock	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
CXVIII	O
-121	O
.	O
A	O
glasse	O
botle	O
covered	O
with	O
corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
a	O
shell	O
&	O
c.	O
207	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
A	O
sea	O
fann	O
from	O
the	O
South	B-place
seas	I-place
N.	O
D.	O
206	O
123	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
coast	O
of	O
sussex	B-place
.	O
200	O
124	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
minus	O
muricatum	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
pr	O
.	O
of	O
bivalve	O
shells	O
.	O
206	O
?	O
125	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
200	O
9a	O
1368.	O
placenta	O
hirsuta	O
forma	O
corallÿ	O
.	O
seguelt	O
.	O
p.	O
40	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
207	O
a	O
200	O
1369	O
.	O
Eadem	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
207.	O
a	O
75	O
.	O
1370	O
.	O
Arundinacea	O
spuma	O
lapidi	O
spongiæ	O
similis	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
207.	O
a	O
200	O
-1371	O
.	O
Fungus	O
Saxeus	O
Sinactus	O
or	O
corrugatus	O
from	O
Turkey	B-place
189	O
191	O
1372	O
.	O
White	O
Starry	O
corall	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Brickell	I-pers
from	O
north	B-place
Carolina	I-place
who	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
strand	O
of	O
the	O
fresh	O
water	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
fossile	O
vid	O
.	O
antea	O
.	O
177	O
1373	O
.	O
Vesicaria	O
marina	O
of	O
a	O
lesser	O
sort	O
from	O
Bermu	B-place
das	I-place
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	I-pers
207	O
a	O
177	O
✓	O
-1374	O
.	O
Fucus	O
phasganoides	O
,	O
corallines	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
Dover	B-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stack	I-pers
.	O
208	O
1375.	O
red	O
corall	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
dolphin	O
.	O
189	O
1376	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
superfici	O
e	O
cavi	O
a	O
ten	O
tibus	O
20	O
tundis	O
obsita	O
.	O
frar	O
this	O
has	O
grown	O
on	O
a	O
pritty	O
large	O
pedestall	O
of	O
white	O
coraline	O
matter	O
wt	O
some	O
few	O
small	O
red	O
flatt	O
spotts	O
round	O
spotts	O
&	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
found	O
upon	O
sevll	O
.	O
Coralls	O
&	O
shells	O
in	O
the	O
hott	O
pts	O
of	O
the	O
W.	O
Indies	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
ben	O
cool	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
206	O
1377	O
.	O
Astroit	O
es	O
in	O
flint	O
wt	O
a	O
few	O
/small	O
stars	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
sea	O
coast	O
near	O
Talacra	B-place
Flintshire	B-place
43	O
1378	O
.	O
Fungus	O
sylvaticus	O
petrefactus	O
vel	O
.	O
surculus	O
lapideus	O
,	O
Adarce	O
Tartaro	O
crustatus	O
Scheuch	O
Sp	O
.	O
tit	O
f.	O
g.	O
27	O
Sent	O
me	O
from	O
Joh	B-pers
:	I-pers
Petrus	I-pers
Ischudius	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Canton	B-place
of	I-place
Glaris	I-place
in	O
Swisser=	B-place
land	I-place
43	O
10	O
-126	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-127	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
?	O
growing	O
upon	O
an	O
oyster	O
shell	O
.	O
200	O
.	O
-128	O
.	O
Corallina	O
opuntiodes	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
190	O
201	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
A	O
segment	O
or	O
portion	O
of	O
lapis	O
astro=	O
=ites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
200	O
130	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
Starry	O
points	O
an	O
corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
muricatum	O
?	O
203	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
corallium	O
porosum	O
latssim=	O
=um	O
foliatum	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
✓	O
132	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
130	O
?	O
206	O
.	O
✓	O
-133	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
squared	O
.	O
189	O
134	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
strange	O
piece	O
of	O
astroites	O
,	O
wt	O
.	O
irregular	O
striæ	O
on	O
it	O
hollow	O
within	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
Astroites	O
stone	O
.	O
Fossil	O
?	O
wt	O
.	O
some	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
189	O
136	O
.	O
Corallium	O
Stellatum	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Walraven	I-pers
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
Astroitidis	O
Species	O
?	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
202	O
15	O
q	O
-137	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
with	O
fine	O
Striæ	O
.	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
.	I-pers
190	O
-138	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
of	O
a	O
blewish	O
colour	O
?	O
189	O
-139	O
.	O
Severall	O
pieces	O
of	O
corall	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
large	O
pieces	O
&	O
c.	O
/	O
white	O
pun	O
ded	O
corall	O
-	O
200	O
10a	O
1379	O
.	O
Coralline	O
muscus	O
sell	O
muscus	O
marinus	O
tenui	O
capplle	O
spermos	O
phoras	O
.	O
Pluck	O
Alan	O
Tab	O
168	O
f	O
3	O
Muscus	O
Coralliodes	O
pumilus	O
ramosus	O
.	O
Dood	O
.	O
App	O
nenlosess	O
ines	O
polys	O
pienaers	O
Resyn	O
.	O
g.	O
Cis	O
Bob	O
.	O
Ll	O
it	O
Tab	O
g.	O
b	O
.	O
Is	O
.	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
Fucus	O
Phasganoides	O
from	O
the	O
Orkney	B-place
Islands	I-place
✓	O
207	O
R.	O
S.	O
330	O
.	O
1380	O
.	O
A	O
Common	O
glasse	O
quart	O
Bottle	O
cover	O
'd	O
wt	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adul=	O
terimim	O
,	O
J.B.	O
Shells	O
&	O
Vermicula	O
Marina	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
✓	O
207	O
1381	O
.	O
Epicoralline	O
A	O
n	O
galense	O
venicosum	O
&	O
rutide	O
purpurea	O
a	O
D.	O
Will	O
Brown	O
Clus	O
.	O
H.	O
2	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
1382	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
971.	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
0	O
1383	O
.	O
Five	O
pieces	O
of	O
Eight	O
cemented	O
together	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
water	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
antea	O
189	O
.	O
1384.	O
an	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
Vid	O
antea	O
.	O
mark	O
'd	O
No	O
.	O
187	O
.	O
1385	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
Astroites	O
white	O
&	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
starry	O
tubuli	O
joined	O
together	O
arison	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
center	O
very	O
rare	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
antea	O
193	O
11	O
140	O
.	O
One	O
small	O
Corall	O
mushrom	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
Stone	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
141	O
.	O
Corallina	O
nervo	O
tenviori	O
,	O
fragiliorique	O
internodia	O
longiora	O
nectente	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p	O
4.	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Corallina	O
minima	O
Capillacea	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
stone	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
Coralline	O
,	O
Algæ	O
,	O
pieces	O
of	O
shells	O
&	O
c	O
all	O
wrought	O
together	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
-	O
Shore	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
?	O
204	O
143	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
hist	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
204	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
Jointed	O
red	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
Cape	B-place
of	I-place
good	I-place
hope	I-place
.	O
190	O
145	O
.	O
Some	O
tubularia	O
of	O
white	O
colour	O
?	O
an	O
fossil	O
?	O
189	O
146	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
ex	O
scotia	O
E	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
200	O
147	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
from	O
Jersey	B-place
vid	O
6d	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
200	O
200	O
148	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
&	O
dura	O
.	O
200	O
149	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
tennis	O
.	O
200	O
150	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
minor	O
ramosa	O
.	O
200	O
✓	O
151	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
cornucervi	O
divisuris	O
.	O
208	O
11a	O
#	O
A	O
marine	O
body	O
called	O
here	O
commonly	O
coutiage	O
from	O
its	O
having	O
(	O
when	O
burned	O
powdered	O
)	O
the	O
tormenting	O
stinging	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
East	O
India	O
Coutiage	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
by	O
Batanists	O
.	O
Alcyonium	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catesby	I-pers
207	O
12	O
152	O
.	O
Androsace	O
chamæ	O
conchæ	O
innascens	O
.	O
andro	O
sace	O
sue	O
Cotyledon	O
Marinus	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
230	O
.	O
189	O
153	O
.	O
Corallina	O
minima	O
Capillacea	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4	O
.	O
190	O
201	O
154	O
.	O
Tethitis	O
e	O
Virginia	O
#	O
>	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
190	O
155	O
.	O
Irange	O
du	O
mer	O
.	O
Monsp	O
?	O
190	O
156	O
.	O
Seta	O
marina	O
?	O
201	O
157	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
201	O
158	O
.	O
Alga	O
angustifolia	O
vitrariorum	O
wt	O
.	O
its	O
root	O
.	O
75	O
159	O
.	O
Lapis	O
Spongiæ	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
altissima	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7	O
?	O
201	O
161	O
.	O
Quercus	O
marina	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
coralline	O
growing	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
leaved	O
fucus	O
from	O
Jersey	B-place
growing	O
on	O
a	O
pebble	O
3d	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
Silken	O
wrack	O
wt	O
.	O
hairy	O
edges	O
?	O
from	O
Dover	B-place
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
148	O
.	O
201	O
12a	O
1386	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
branched	O
large	O
containing	O
within	O
it	O
Pholades	O
,	O
Vermiculi	O
taken	O
somewhere	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
and	O
Not	O
fossil	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Antea	O
.	O
Mark	O
'd	O
formely	O
905	O
.	O
200	O
1387	O
.	O
Lapis	O
Astroites	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
S	O
paw	O
Flint	O
or	O
Chrystal.Vid	O
.	O
antea	O
Marked	O
.	O
109	O
.	O
L.	O
202	O
1387	O
Madrepora	O
?	O
&	O
c	O
Mark	O
'd	O
formerly	O
321	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1388	O
.	O
A	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
tree	O
oysters	O
&	O
Tubuli	O
vermium	O
very	O
intire	O
growing	O
upon	O
it.Vid	O
.	O
antea	O
.	O
Mark	O
'd	O
formerly	O
49	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Fossils	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Ravensdale	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Westmoreland	I-place
.	O
&	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Brownrigg	I-pers
1389	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Corallium	O
implexum	O
,	O
tubulis	O
intus	O
&	O
extremitatibus	O
stellatis	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Antea	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
666.	O
et	O
1009	O
.	O
15	O
q	O
201	O
.	O
1390	O
.	O
N.	O
2	O
.	O
Idem	O
sed	O
major	O
201	O
.	O
1391	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Fossil	O
Coral	O
vid	O
No	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1392	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
No	O
.	O
579	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1393	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
13	O
165	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
with	O
the	O
root	O
.	O
189	O
166	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
branched	O
&	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
branches	O
anastomos	O
'd	O
or	O
sticking	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
189	O
167	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
slender	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
made	O
into	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
crooked	O
needle	O
189	O
168	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
very	O
deep	O
coloured	O
red	O
corall	O
.	O
189	O
169	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
very	O
deep	O
coloure	O
'd	O
red	O
corall	O
join	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
Starr	O
pointed	O
corall	O
.	O
189	O
170	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
growing	O
on	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
?	O
189	O
171	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
growing	O
upon	O
the	O
convex	O
side	O
of	O
0	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
0.	O
one	O
valve	O
of	O
a	O
bivalve	O
.	O
2sh	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
189	O
172	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
concave	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
bivalve	O
with	O
white	O
corall	O
-	O
sprouting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
edges	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
189	O
173	O
.	O
Red	O
corall	O
&	O
common	O
sponge	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
buccinum	O
.	O
189	O
174	O
.	O
A	O
thick	O
piece	O
of	O
corall	O
being	O
white	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
&	O
red	O
without	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
center	O
.	O
189	O
175	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
or	O
brown	O
corall	O
surround	O
=ed	O
wt	O
.	O
red	O
striated	O
.	O
Coralium	O
rubrum	O
cum	O
antipathe	O
Aldrov	O
.	O
Mus	O
:	O
Metall	O
:	O
p.	O
290	O
189	O
176	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
flesh	O
colour	O
'd	O
corall	O
.	O
189	O
13a	O
1393	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
385	O
.	O
611	O
1088.	O
wt	O
.	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
foregoing	O
adhereing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1394	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Idem	O
varietas	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
15	O
P	O
1395	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1396	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
1397	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
A	O
sparry	O
nodule	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
curious	O
Ætites	O
it	O
structure	O
will	O
appear	O
from	O
comparing	O
it	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
following	O
201	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
1398	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
Another	O
sparry	O
nodul	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
16	O
J	O
1399	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
Idem	O
varietas	O
201	O
.	O
1400	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
Idem	O
201	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
1401	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
whole	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
Spongia	O
spuria	O
ra	O
mosa	O
foraminulis	O
pertusa	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
207	O
.	O
1402	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
whole	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
cardicans	O
adulterinum	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
the	O
branches	O
intire	O
&	O
interwoven	O
one	O
wt	O
.	O
another	O
.	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
at	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
a	O
Fisherman	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
1403	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
1190.	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
Striæ	O
plan	O
nn	O
er	O
.	O
Id	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
1404	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
1227	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
1405	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
1231.	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Collume	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
14	O
177	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
redish	O
coloured	O
white	O
Corall	O
.	O
189	O
178	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
Corall	O
.	O
Corallo	O
biunco	O
Imperati	O
Edit	O
.	O
Napt	O
.	O
1590.	O
p.	O
714	O
.	O
Edit	O
Venet	O
.	O
1672.	O
p.	O
623	O
.	O
Edit	O
Latin	O
.	O
p.	O
809	O
/	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
et	O
Observations	O
eurieuses	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
/	O
Adrovand	O
.	O
Mus	O
.	O
Metall	O
.	O
189	O
179	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
brownish	O
black	O
corall	O
.	O
189	O
180	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
black	O
Corall	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
root	O
&	O
over	O
red	O
corall	O
Vid	O
.	O
Imperat	O
.	O
Edit	O
.	O
prime	O
.	O
Nap	O
.	O
1590	O
.	O
714	O
.	O
Vanet	O
1672.	O
p.	O
623	O
.	O
Edit	O
Latin	O
.	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
Observ	O
.	O
Curieuses	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
p.	O
809	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
189	O
181	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
hippuris	O
Coralloides	O
large	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
182	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
189	O
183	O
.	O
A	O
saffron	O
colour	O
'd	O
jointed	O
Corall	O
.	O
189	O
184	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
185	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
hollow	O
&	O
pointed	O
wt	O
.	O
holes	O
,	O
or	O
starry	O
points	O
.	O
189	O
186	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
wt	O
red	O
corall	O
on	O
the	O
center	O
of	O
some	O
pieces	O
208	O
187	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
Corall	O
wt	O
.	O
Starry	O
radiated	O
points	O
.	O
189	O
188	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
in	O
wch	O
is	O
a	O
pebble	O
207	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
radiated	O
starrs	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
is	O
not	O
branched	O
.	O
189	O
190	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
I.B	O
.	O
on	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
corallina	O
.	O
Aldrovand	O
.	O
Mus	O
.	O
Metall	O
:	O
p.	O
283	O
.	O
189	O
14a	O
1406	O
.	O
A	O
variety	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
1242.	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
208	O
1407	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
239	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
1408	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
133.	O
blanch	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
water	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
1409	O
.	O
Many	O
Primordia	O
of	O
the	O
Lapis	O
Astroites	O
indulatus	O
some	O
where	O
of	O
have	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
a	O
pedicle	O
but	O
most	O
growing	O
on	O
worm	O
shells	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1410	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
turn	O
'd	O
stony	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1411	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
very	O
white	O
&	O
trasparent	O
in	O
a	O
confused	O
manner	O
resembling	O
sparr	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
1412	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
103.	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
pedicle	O
more	O
distinct	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
204	O
1413	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
90.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
shell	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
204	O
1414	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
136.	O
only	O
smaller	O
pipes	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
202	O
1415	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
or	O
stone	O
.	O
Id	O
207	O
1416	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
large	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
inward	O
starry	O
Substance	O
consumed	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
15	O
191	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
with	O
very	O
large	O
starry	O
points	O
or	O
pores	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
192	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
i	O
.	O
189	O
193	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
194	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
195	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
hand	O
?	O
189	O
196	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
latissimum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
.	O
189	O
197	O
.	O
White	O
solid	O
corall	O
with	O
pores	O
on	O
its	O
Surface	O
?	O
an	O
white	O
corall	O
?	O
vid	O
.	O
antea	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
polish	O
.	O
Vid	O
No	O
.	O
590	O
.	O
This	O
has	O
been	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
Corall	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
scarse	O
&	O
rare	O
189	O
198	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
smaller	O
pieces	O
.	O
189	O
199	O
.	O
The	O
sea	O
rose	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
Catalog	O
.	O
Lapidis	O
astroitidis	O
sive	O
stellaris	O
secund	O
.	O
genus	O
.	O
Boet	O
.	O
de	O
-	O
Boodt	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
.	O
199	O
b	O
200	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
differing	O
.	O
201	O
201	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
differing	O
.	O
201	O
202	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
a	O
variety	O
.	O
190	O
15a	O
207	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
,	O
nascimento	O
folto	O
di	O
pori	O
intagliati	O
in	O
modo	O
di	O
stella	O
,	O
con	O
stremita	O
piana	O
:	O
han	O
alcuni	O
nestigü	O
di	O
menbrane	O
in	O
detta	O
stremita	O
,	O
e	O
nelle	O
cavita	O
che	O
in	O
essa	O
peruingono	O
.	O
Mellapor	O
.	O
Vid	O
Imperati	O
.	O
Edit	O
.	O
Napol	O
.	O
1590.	O
p	O
720	O
.	O
Venet	O
.	O
1672	O
pag	O
,	O
629	O
Milleporus	O
Latinæ	O
pag	O
.	O
818	O
.	O
Porus	O
martronalis	O
,	O
fatus	O
poris	O
incisis	O
instar	O
stella	O
refartus	O
extremitate	O
plana	O
,	O
cum	O
vestigus	O
quibusdam	O
membrane	O
indictu	O
extremitate	O
,	O
ingne	O
cavitate	O
,	O
quæ	O
in	O
illo	O
conspicisur	O
.	O
16	O
203	O
.	O
A	O
variety	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
190	O
204	O
.	O
A	O
variety	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adult=	O
=erinum	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
growing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
189	O
205	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
litle	O
.	O
189	O
206	O
.	O
Four	O
large	O
starry	O
points	O
united	O
at	O
bottom	O
&	O
separated	O
at	O
tops	O
.	O
190	O
207	O
.	O
Severall	O
starry	O
radiated	O
points	O
rising	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
bottom	O
.	O
189	O
208	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
Brain	O
stones	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
striæ	O
finer	O
.	O
190	O
210	O
.	O
A	O
section	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
190	O
211	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
striæ	O
irregular	O
.	O
190	O
212	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
striæ	O
very	O
large	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
190	O
213	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
.	O
starr	O
stones	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
very	O
large	O
starrs	O
,	O
&	O
porous	O
.	O
190	O
189	O
214	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
&	O
porous	O
.	O
6d	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
-	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
189	O
16a	O
1417	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maxim	O
.	O
muricatum	O
?	O
where	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
Soft	O
the	O
starr	O
have	O
taken	O
different	O
figures	O
.	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
207	O
1418	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
fossil	O
Madrepora	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
15	O
P.	O
1419	O
.	O
A	O
masse	O
of	O
purple	O
&	O
white	O
Worm	O
Shells	O
upon	O
a	O
White	O
freestone	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
lyes	O
a	O
Pholos	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
1420	O
A	O
congeries	O
of	O
smaller	O
Worms	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
Balanus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
207	O
1421	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
&	O
725	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Pebble	O
on	O
the	O
branches	O
on	O
the	O
are	O
two	O
Concha	O
Margaritifera	O
of	O
the	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
17	O
215	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
more	O
solid	O
with	O
distinct	O
large	O
Starry	O
pores	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
216	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
217	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
218	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
190	O
219	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
irregularly	O
shap	O
'd	O
starrs	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
189	O
220	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
roundish	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
189	O
221	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
distinct	O
-	O
Starry	O
h	O
p	O
oles	O
.	O
15	O
P	O
189	O
202	O
.	O
222	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
irregularly	O
figured	O
radiated	O
pores	O
.	O
189	O
223	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
Starry	O
pores	O
.	O
189	O
224	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
flatt	O
with	O
blak	O
small	O
white	O
Starry	O
pores	O
.	O
In	O
Sloane	O
Coll	O
.	O
July	O
10	O
1889	O
189	O
225	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
roundish	O
.	O
201	O
226	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
solid	O
.	O
189	O
227	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
round	O
wt	O
.	O
irregularly	O
figured	O
radiated	O
pores	O
.	O
43	O
189	O
228	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
190	O
100	O
17a	O
18	O
229	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
very	O
large	O
rad=	O
=iated	O
pores	O
,	O
very	O
porous	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
189	O
230	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
porous	O
wt	O
.	O
lesser	O
holes	O
.	O
189	O
231	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
large	O
radiated	O
pores	O
.	O
an	O
fossil	O
?	O
189	O
232	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
solid	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
growing	O
on	O
one	O
shell	O
of	O
a	O
bivalve	O
.	O
an	O
on	O
auris	O
marina	O
?	O
189	O
233	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
larger	O
pores	O
.	O
an	O
on	O
an	O
auris	O
marina	O
?	O
189	O
234	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterin=	O
=um	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
growing	O
with	O
its	O
root	O
?	O
189	O
235	O
.	O
The	O
root	O
&	O
young	O
sprouts	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
236	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
minus	O
muri=	O
=catum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
?	O
206	O
237	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nortras	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
189	O
238	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
corall	O
.	O
189	O
239	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
18a	O
19	O
240	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
somewhat	O
longer	O
&	O
slender	O
etc	O
.	O
15	O
P	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
281	O
241	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
flatt	O
points	O
.	O
after	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
opimtie	O
hard	O
&	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
from	O
Antigua	B-place
208	O
190	O
208	O
.	O
✓	O
242	O
.	O
Corallina	O
offic	O
.	O
199	O
201	O
.	O
243	O
.	O
Fungus	O
saxeus	O
major	O
.	O
199	O
189	O
244	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
a	O
peduncle	O
.	O
100	O
190	O
245	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
very	O
white	O
with	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
leaves	O
.	O
or	O
Lamella	O
An	O
escharæ	O
Marinæ	O
species	O
?	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
190	O
246	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
eschara	O
marina	O
.	O
190	O
247	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulteri=	O
=num	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
just	O
sprouting	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
✓	O
248	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
long	O
with	O
starry	O
radiated	O
pores	O
branched	O
&	O
hollow	O
with	O
starrs	O
in	O
its	O
center	O
?	O
an	O
fossil	O
List	O
.	O
189	O
201	O
202	O
194	O
249	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
round	O
.	O
189	O
250	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
given	O
by	O
the	O
Indians	O
for	O
the	O
biting	O
of	O
snakes	O
?	O
-	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0.	O
an	O
fossil	O
?	O
190	O
251	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
CIII	O
.	O
252	O
.	O
Corallina	O
nervo	O
tenuiori	O
fragilioriqz	O
internodia	O
longiora	O
nectente	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
the	O
larger	O
sort	O
189	O
19a	O
20	O
253	O
.	O
A	O
Sprigg	O
of	O
the	O
more	O
solid	O
white	O
porous	O
corall	O
broad	O
.	O
From	O
Pulo-Condore	B-place
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
.	O
206	O
254	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
177	O
255	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
189	O
256	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
rounder	O
.	O
177	O
257	O
.	O
A	O
sprigg	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
smaller	O
&	O
rounder	O
.	O
206	O
258	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
177	O
259	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
260	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
207	O
206	O
261	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
majus	O
-	O
muricatum	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
✓	O
207	O
206	O
.	O
262	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
207	O
263	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
mines	O
muricat	O
.	O
=um	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
p.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
✓	O
206	O
.	O
264	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
265	O
.	O
Fungus	O
saxeus	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
266	O
.	O
Astroites	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
106	O
75	O
20a	O
21	O
-267	O
.	O
Porous	O
red	O
corall	O
from	O
Pulo	B-place
Condore	I-place
189	O
.	O
-268	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
-269	O
.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
millepora	O
from	O
Pulo	B-place
Condore	I-place
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
growing	O
to	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
189	O
✓	O
200	O
-270	O
.	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
stellated	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
.	O
200	O
15	O
P	O
271	O
.	O
Porus	O
minimus	O
fossilis	O
furcatus	O
.	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-272	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
millepora	O
from	O
China	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
✓	O
-273	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Hipppuris	O
saxea	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Theobalds	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	I-pers
.	I-pers
younger	I-pers
.	I-pers
200	O
-274	O
.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
rough	O
solid	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
189	O
-275	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
undulated	O
&	O
stellated	O
corall	O
.	O
177	O
-276	O
.	O
A	O
stellated	O
white	O
corall	O
with	O
a	O
tubulus	O
vermis	O
growing	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
-277	O
.	O
A	O
millepora	O
petrified	O
?	O
or	O
basaltes	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	I-pers
202	O
75	O
-278	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
202	O
-279	O
.	O
Small	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
202	O
21a	O
22	O
-280	O
.	O
A	O
Fruticulus	O
marinus	O
on	O
a	O
Corallin	O
rock	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
XCIIII	O
.	O
-281	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
from	O
the	O
Orkneyes	B-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
201	O
.	O
-282	O
.	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
or	O
brain	O
stone	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	O
201	O
-283	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
201	O
-284	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
starr	O
stone	O
or	O
featherd	O
flint	O
polished	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
?	O
-285	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
-	O
black	O
&	O
white	O
marble	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
?	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
Sall	O
seller	O
189	O
.	O
15	O
P	O
-286	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adult=	O
=erinum	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
189	O
-287	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricat	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
15	O
P	O
-288	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
stellatum	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
15	O
P	O
189	O
-289	O
.	O
An	O
Astroites	O
or	O
starr	O
stone	O
wt	O
.	O
white	O
sparr	O
&	O
free	O
stone	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
&	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
shining	O
sparry	O
substance	O
.	O
189	O
204	O
-290	O
.	O
An	O
incrustation	O
or	O
Corallin	O
substance	O
?	O
22a	O
298	O
.	O
Keratophyton	O
flabelli	O
forme	O
,	O
cortice	O
verucoso	O
obductum	O
Coralloides	O
granulosa	O
alba	O
I.B	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
flabelliformis	O
cortice	O
verucosa	O
obductus	O
.	O
Doody	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
Seqnop	O
.	O
Edit	O
.	O
Ba	O
.	O
p.	O
32	O
.	O
It	O
grows	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
foot	O
high	O
and	O
abounds	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Soundings	O
near	O
the	O
lands	O
end	O
whence	O
King	O
Charles	O
2d	O
.	O
had	O
one	O
abt	O
.	O
four	O
foot	O
high	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
over	O
the	O
in	O
his	O
Closet	O
to	O
his	O
dying	O
day	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
rarity	O
.	O
23	O
-291	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
flint	O
-	O
from	O
Wiltshire	B-place
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
202	O
-292	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
202	O
-293	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Spurr	O
or	O
Chrys	O
tall	O
In	O
Sloane	O
Coll	O
.	O
July	O
10	O
1889	O
col.	O
3	O
202	O
.	O
74	O
.	O
-294	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
fossil	O
corall	O
from	O
Mendip	B-place
.	O
/	O
Sprouts	O
of	O
mineral	O
corall	O
growing	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
together	O
from	O
Mendip	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	I-pers
phil	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
150.	O
p.	O
180.	O
fig	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-295	O
.	O
A	O
Sort	O
of	O
Small	O
fossil	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
201-	O
201	O
-296	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
201	O
-297	O
.	O
Millepora	O
.	O
Imperat	O
.	O
p.	O
720	O
.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
235	O
.	O
207	O
-298	O
.	O
A	O
coralline	O
shrub	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
a.	O
white	O
crust	O
from	O
lands	O
end	O
.	O
Erica	O
marina	O
alba	O
frutescens	O
.	O
M.	O
Pet	O
.	O
50	O
Mus	O
Petiver	O
207	O
299	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
minus	O
nostras	O
Park	O
?	O
/	O
A	O
greener	O
sort	O
from	O
Magellan	B-place
streights	I-place
201	O
.	O
-300	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
white	O
punctated	O
corall	O
from	O
Holland	B-place
.	O
/	O
One	O
is	O
larger	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
200	O
-301.	O
small	O
fossil	O
corall	O
from	O
Mendip	B-place
?	O
201	O
-302	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
its	O
matrix	O
or	O
stone	O
?	O
from	O
Pendryn	B-place
.	O
203	O
201	O
23a	O
24	O
-303	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
album	O
muricatum	O
foliatum	O
Cat	O
.	O
-	O
Jam	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
-304	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
minus	O
album	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
✓	O
200	O
-305	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adult=	O
=erinum	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
on	O
a	O
stick	O
-306	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
Ger	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
an	O
astroites	O
growing	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
189	O
-307	O
.	O
Astroites	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
2	O
starrs	O
are	O
confounded	O
sometimes	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-308	O
.	O
Astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
least	O
starrs	O
.	O
201	O
-309	O
.	O
A	O
stone	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
starrs	O
?	O
from	O
Althorpe	B-place
.	O
15	O
P	O
190	O
201	O
.	O
-310	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
190	O
-311	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Fossil	O
?	O
very	O
small	O
189	O
-312	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
15	O
P	O
190	O
24a	O
25	O
313	O
.	O
Lapides	O
spongiæ	O
?	O
202	O
15	O
P.	O
-314	O
.	O
Astroites	O
petrified	O
&	O
Sparry	O
.	O
202	O
-315	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
|	O
Astroites	O
major	O
D.	O
Plott	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
hist	O
.	O
Oxford	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
|	O
gray	O
&	O
more	O
solid	O
.	O
from	O
cowly	B-place
common	I-place
.	O
202	O
-316	O
.	O
Small	O
corall	O
in	O
a	O
gray	O
stone	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
-317	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
lying	O
in	O
clay	O
.	O
an	O
-	O
Hippuris	O
saxea	O
?	O
204	O
-318	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Astroites	O
found	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	I-pers
15	O
q	O
204	O
-319	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
larger	O
found	O
at	O
Althorpe	B-place
?	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
15	O
P.	O
204	O
-320	O
.	O
Coralline	O
from	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
Fife	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
-321	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
&	O
c	O
?	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
-322	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
lesser	O
.	O
-323	O
.	O
321	O
clear	O
'd	O
of	O
its	O
muricies	O
?	O
25a	O
26	O
-324	O
.	O
The	O
sea	O
rose	O
?	O
205	O
-325	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
latissimum	O
muricatum	O
foliatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
murices	O
rub	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
e.	O
-326	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
latum	O
punctatum	O
?	O
208	O
✓	O
327	O
.	O
Eschara	O
&	O
c.	O
206	O
.	O
✓	O
328	O
.	O
Lapis	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
75	O
201	O
.	O
-329	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
|	O
From	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
205	O
330	O
.	O
Astroites	O
stone	O
with	O
small	O
starrs	O
?	O
an	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
a	O
cockle	O
?	O
207	O
331	O
.	O
Stony	O
or	O
sparry	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
189	O
332	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
larger	O
.	O
202	O
333	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
flinty	O
with	O
teeth	O
in	O
it	O
from	O
Darbyshire	B-place
204	O
334	O
.	O
Small	O
corall	O
in	O
a	O
Stone	O
.	O
from	O
Darby	B-place
shire	I-place
15	O
P	O
203	O
335	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
from	O
Darbyshire	B-place
15	O
P	O
204	O
26a	O
27	O
336	O
.	O
Corallina	O
ramulis	O
planis	O
purpureis	O
&	O
c.	O
207	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208	O
c.	O
337	O
.	O
Corallina	O
rumulis	O
quaquaversum	O
diffusis	O
ret	O
.	O
marin	O
.	O
species	O
?	O
on	O
a	O
bass	O
of	O
tubuli	O
&	O
spandish	O
.	O
CXIX	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
338	O
.	O
Spongia	O
alta	O
gracilis	O
&	O
c.	O
200	O
✓	O
339	O
.	O
Astroites	O
fossil	O
for	O
Farrington	B-place
in	O
Barkshire	B-place
199	O
e	O
208	O
.	O
C	O
189	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
Astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
Large	O
Starrs	O
.	O
|	O
From	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
203	O
.	O
341	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
latum	O
punctatum	O
?	O
177	O
-342	O
.	O
Astroites	O
with	O
Small	O
starrs	O
cutt	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
.	O
189	O
.	O
343	O
.	O
A	O
coralline	O
shrub	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
incrustation	O
from	O
Tangier	B-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
.	O
With	O
a	O
Barnicle	O
shell	O
growing	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Vid	O
No	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
208	O
344	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
208	O
345	O
.	O
Astroites	O
.	O
|	O
with	O
small	O
starrs	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
203	O
.	O
-346	O
.	O
Eschara	O
.	O
|	O
From	O
Gibraltar	B-place
or	O
Tangier	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
27a	O
28	O
-347	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
?	O
from	O
Monmouth	B-place
shire	I-place
?	O
201	O
.	O
-348	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
latum	O
stellatum	O
?	O
fossil	O
?	O
-349	O
.	O
Hippuris	O
saxea	O
coralloides	O
.	O
Clus	O
.	O
from	O
Java	B-place
P	I-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
One	O
single	O
large	O
astroites	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
202	O
351	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
round	O
ovall	O
lamps	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
201	O
352	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
with	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
202	O
.	O
-353	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
-354	O
.	O
Astroites	O
minoribus	O
Stellulis	O
e	O
fluvio	O
Birsa	O
dicto	O
territorÿ	O
Basileensis	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
Scheuchzer	O
.	O
lithog	O
.	O
Helvet	O
.	O
cur	O
.	O
p.	O
39.	O
fig	O
.	O
52.	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lavater	I-pers
.	O
202	O
355	O
.	O
Astroites	O
fossil	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
?	O
201	O
.	O
28a	O
29	O
356	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
smaller	O
starrs	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
P.	O
357	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
75	O
202	O
358	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
flatt	O
corall	O
with	O
Starrs	O
fossil	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
201	O
359	O
.	O
360	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
I.B	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
an	O
astroites	O
Sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
360	O
.	O
Fungus	O
saxeus	O
wt	O
.	O
an	O
astroites	O
Sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
Spongia	O
medullæ	O
panis	O
similis	O
?	O
200	O
362	O
.	O
Hippuris	O
saxea	O
?	O
Lodged	O
in	O
a	O
stone	O
taken	O
up	O
near	O
Althorpe	B-place
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
.	O
202	O
363	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
202	O
15	O
q	O
364	O
.	O
Spongia	O
fistulosa	O
apicibus	O
extantbus	O
donata	O
from	O
the	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
200	O
29a	O
30	O
365	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
&	O
solid	O
spongia	O
ramosa	O
from	O
the	O
Orkney	B-place
Islands	I-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
200	O
366	O
.	O
Astroites	O
,	O
from	O
Barbados	B-place
.	O
189	O
368	O
.	O
367	O
The	O
primordia	O
of	O
the	O
astroites	O
.	O
367	O
.	O
368	O
Astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
201	O
369	O
.	O
Astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
smaller	O
starrs	O
.	O
189	O
189	O
370	O
.	O
Corallina	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Wight	I-place
.	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
190	O
201	O
371	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
201	O
372	O
.	O
The	O
under	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
majus	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
373	O
.	O
Corallina	O
apuntioides	O
folio	O
corrug-	O
=ato	O
vid	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
growing	O
upon	O
Corall	O
207	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
374	O
.	O
A	O
flatt	O
coralline	O
shrub	O
.	O
Coralloides	O
Fruticosa	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
&	O
c	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
14.	O
et	O
Amsterdam	O
Edit	O
.	O
p.	O
8	O
.	O
Coralline	O
Fruticosa	O
.	O
208	O
-375	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
corall	O
broad	O
foliated	O
&	O
stellated	O
from	O
Batavia	B-place
given	O
me	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
it	O
being	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
bason	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
China	O
fish	O
.	O
upon	O
200	O
CXXI	O
.	O
30a	O
31	O
-376.	O
yellow	O
Coralline	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Wight	I-place
.	O
189	O
-377	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
with	O
large	O
starrs	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	O
201	O
.	O
-378	O
.	O
Astroites	O
undulatus	O
of	O
one	O
starr	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
190	O
379	O
.	O
A	O
Co	O
ye	O
rallina	O
fruticosa	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
yellow	O
crust	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
207	O
?	O
et	O
Observat	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
fig	O
.	O
34	O
:	O
208	O
.	O
-380	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
small	O
starrs	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	O
189	O
-381	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
189	O
-382	O
.	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
exalbidum	O
pennam	O
gallinaceam	O
crassum	O
ramulis	O
alias	O
binis	O
alias	O
plurib	O
us	O
sæpius	O
amputatis	O
.	O
Dni	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lluid	I-pers
.	O
from	O
Witney	B-place
in	O
Oxfordshire	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
-383	O
.	O
Porus	O
minimus	O
reticulatus	O
coloris	O
sæpe	O
albidi	O
nonnunquam	O
rubiginosi	O
.	O
Dni	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lluid	I-pers
from	O
Faringdon	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
202	O
-384	O
.	O
385	O
Astroites	O
4us	O
.	O
Plotÿ	O
.	O
H.	O
Oxon	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
7.	O
from	O
Bullington	B-place
Green	I-place
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lluid	I-pers
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
31a	O
32	O
-385	O
.	O
Fungites	O
coralloides	O
,	O
seu	O
potius	O
corallium	O
majus	O
fungosum	O
altius=	O
=cule	O
striatum	O
.	O
Dni	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lluid	I-pers
from	O
Steeple	B-place
Barton	I-place
in	O
Wiltshire	B-place
.	O
0.0.6	O
.	O
Porpites	O
undulatus	O
littoralis	O
,	O
seu	O
porpitæ	O
congener	O
fungites	O
cinereus	O
Hambirianus	O
gyratium	O
subtus	O
undulatus	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
9	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
204	O
-386	O
.	O
Columellus	O
vulgaris	O
Dni	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lluid	I-pers
.	O
from	O
Chauley	B-place
in	O
Berkshire	B-place
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
204	O
-387	O
.	O
Pila	O
marina	O
subrotunda	O
compressa	O
mollis	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
Aldrovand	O
Mus	O
.	O
Metal	O
.	O
p.	O
280	O
.	O
208.	O
c	O
199	O
e	O
-388	O
.	O
Spongia	O
globosa	O
di	O
Imperat	O
.	O
c	O
p	O
at.-	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
199.	O
e	O
-389	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
major	O
alba	O
fistulosa	O
fibris	O
crassioribus	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
-390	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
altissima	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
Corallium	O
album	O
porosum	O
minus	O
muricatum	O
208.	O
c.	O
199.	O
e	O
-391	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
,	O
superficie	O
apicibus	O
acutis	O
extantibus	O
aspera	O
intus	O
cavernosa	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199.	O
e	O
32a	O
33	O
-392	O
.	O
Spongia	O
minor	O
&	O
mollior	O
,	O
medullæ	O
panis	O
similis	O
fibris	O
tenuissimis	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
207	O
199	O
e	O
-393	O
.	O
Spongia	O
dura	O
seu	O
spuria	O
maxima	O
ramosa	O
fistulosa	O
?	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199.	O
e	O
-394	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulteri=	O
=num	O
.	O
I.B	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1.	O
from	O
Jam=	B-place
=aica	I-place
.	O
207	O
199	O
e	O
-395	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nortras	O
.	O
R	O
B	O
oaÿ	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
streights	B-place
of	I-place
Magellan	I-place
&	O
amp	O
;	O
falmouth	B-place
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
206	O
-396	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
maximum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
T	O
f	O
he	O
under	O
parts	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
199.	O
e	O
-397	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
minus	O
murica=	O
=tum	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
varietie	O
doubted	O
to	O
be	O
Corall	O
.	O
stell	O
.	O
alb	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
33a	O
34	O
-398	O
.	O
Corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
latissimum	O
muricatum	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
199.	O
e	O
-399	O
.	O
Corallium	O
minimum	O
capillaceum	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
199.	O
e	O
-400	O
.	O
Braine	O
stones	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
199.	O
c	O
-401	O
.	O
Fungus	O
lapideus	O
major	O
undulatus	O
?	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
-402	O
.	O
Fungus	O
lapideus	O
minor	O
?	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-403	O
.	O
Starr	O
stones	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
2.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-404	O
.	O
Thsame	O
fossill	O
?	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-405	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
a	O
flint	O
from	O
Wiltshire	B-place
.	O
75	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
34a	O
35	O
-406	O
.	O
Eschara	O
Marina	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
Retepora	O
?	O
Vid	O
.	O
1048	O
.	O
208	O
199.	O
e	O
?	O
-407	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Alcyonium	O
or	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
-408	O
.	O
Frutex	O
marinus	O
elegantissimus	O
.	O
Clus	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
3.	O
growin	O
on	O
a	O
shell	O
.	O
From	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
208	O
-409	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
growing	O
on	O
another	O
shell	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208	O
-410	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
cleared	O
of	O
its	O
crust	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
CXXI	O
.	O
-411	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
humilior	O
&	O
crassior	O
ramis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
,	O
super=	O
ficie	O
tuberculata	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
3	O
.	O
-	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
-412	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
more	O
slender	O
twiggs	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
or	O
Cadiz	B-place
?	O
207	O
35a	O
36	O
-413	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
ramulis	O
&	O
cauliculis	O
compressis	O
quaquavers	O
=um	O
expansis	O
purpureis	O
elegant=	O
issimis	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
207	O
.	O
199.	O
e	O
-414	O
.	O
Corallina	O
opuntioides	O
,	O
ramulis	O
densionlus	O
&	O
folÿs	O
magis	O
sinuatis	O
atqz	O
corru=	O
=gatis	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
208	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
-415	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
of	O
a	O
yellow	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
a	O
dirty	O
colour	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-416	O
.	O
Corallina	O
major	O
nervo	O
crassiori	O
fuciformi	O
internodia	O
breviora	O
nectente	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c.	O
-417	O
.	O
Corallina	O
nervo	O
tenuiori	O
fragilioriq	O
internodia	O
longiora	O
nectente	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-418	O
.	O
Corallina	O
minima	O
capillacea	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
36a	O
37	O
-419	O
.	O
Fucus	O
marinus	O
vesiculas	O
habens	O
membranis	O
extantibus	O
alatas	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
242	O
c	O
-420	O
.	O
Lenticula	O
marina	O
serratis	O
folÿs	O
,	O
Lob	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
4.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
208.	O
c	O
242.	O
c	O
-421	O
.	O
Lenticula	O
marina	O
folÿs	O
latis	O
brevibus	O
serratis	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
242.	O
c.	O
422	O
.	O
Lenticula	O
marina	O
folÿs	O
latis	O
breviss=	O
=imisqz	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208.	O
c	O
199.	O
e	O
-423	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
fucus	O
maritimus	O
gallo	O
pavonis	O
pennas	O
referens	O
.	O
C.B	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
growing	O
together	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
corall	O
.	O
242.	O
c	O
-424	O
.	O
Fucus	O
fæniculaceus	O
seu	O
coralloides	O
-	O
lenta	O
fæniculacea	O
cauliculis	O
longiori=	O
=bus	O
gracilioribus	O
&	O
demaioribus	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
some	O
growing	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
242.	O
c	O
37a	O
38	O
-425	O
.	O
Fucus	O
feniculaceus	O
seu	O
coralloides	O
lenta	O
fæniculacea	O
minor	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Sticking	O
to	O
pebbles	O
shells	O
&	O
c.	O
208.	O
c.	O
199	O
e	O
-426	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
-427	O
.	O
Fucus	O
marinus	O
denticulatus	O
triangul=	O
=aris	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
Jama=	B-place
=ica	I-place
.	O
207	O
-428	O
.	O
Fucus	O
marinus	O
coralloides	O
fungosus	O
albidus	O
teres	O
segmentis	O
in	O
sum=	O
=mitate	O
planis	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
|	O
The	O
large	O
piece	O
.	O
P.	O
201	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-429	O
.	O
Alga	O
angustifolia	O
vitrariorum	O
.	O
C.B	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
The	O
Leaves	O
&	O
roots	O
.	O
242.	O
c	O
-430	O
.	O
Alga	O
marina	O
graminea	O
angustissimo	O
folio	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
242.	O
b	O
38a	O
39	O
-431	O
.	O
Fucus	O
maritimus	O
gallo	O
pavonis-	O
pennas	O
referens	O
.	O
C.B	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
5.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
growing	O
on	O
coralls	O
.	O
242.	O
b	O
.	O
-432	O
.	O
Muscus	O
marinus	O
plumiformis	O
ramulis	O
&	O
folÿs	O
densissimis	O
capillaceis	O
.	O
-	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
Island	B-place
Madera	I-place
.	O
242.	O
b	O
c	O
242.	O
c	O
-433	O
.	O
Pila	O
marina	O
velut	O
ex	O
ampullis	O
constans	O
ad	O
spumæ	O
similitudinem	O
.	O
C.B	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
smaller	O
vosicæ	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
207	O
.	O
-434	O
.	O
Vesicaria	O
marina	O
non	O
ramosa	O
,	O
ex	O
ampullis	O
majoribus	O
paucioribus	O
sinuatis	O
auriculæ	O
instar	O
constans	O
,	O
cujus	O
superficies	O
favi	O
instar	O
not=	O
=antur	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
242.	O
b	O
.	O
-435	O
.	O
Vesicaria	O
marina	O
non	O
ramosa	O
e	O
vesiculis	O
infundibuli	O
forma	O
mem=	O
=brana	O
undulata	O
extante	O
coronatis	O
constans	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
39a	O
40	O
-436	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Abies	O
marina	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
-437	O
.	O
Muscus	O
corallinus	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Crocodile	B-place
Islands	I-place
near	O
China	B-place
gathered	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
1700	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
&	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-438	O
.	O
Fucus	O
coralloides	O
?	O
Sent	O
from	O
China	B-place
by	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-439	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
sett	O
upon	O
a	O
brasse	O
silver	O
guilt	O
pedestall	O
sett	O
wt	O
.	O
Turtoises	O
2	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
206	O
-440	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
a	O
litle	O
broken	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
206	O
-441	O
.	O
A	O
sprigg	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
smaller	O
0	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
6.	O
and	O
belonging	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
ones	O
✓	O
206	O
-442	O
.	O
Corallina	O
off	O
.	O
181	O
x	O
-443	O
.	O
Corallum	O
album	O
off	O
.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
232	O
.	O
182	O
x	O
181	O
-444	O
.	O
Corallum	O
rubrum	O
off	O
.	O
Worm	O
p.	O
231	O
.	O
181	O
x	O
-445	O
.	O
Spongia	O
off	O
.	O
181	O
x	O
40a	O
41	O
-446	O
.	O
An	O
astroites	O
with	O
sparr	O
gathered	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
earth	O
?	O
-447	O
.	O
Corallium	O
striatum	O
&	O
stellatum	O
from	O
the	O
Canaries	B-place
.	O
208	O
-448	O
.	O
Corallium	O
stellatum	O
sticking	O
in	O
its	O
bed	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
.	O
/	O
Columellus	O
turbinatus	O
albus	O
Cretaceorum	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
8	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
204	O
-449	O
.	O
Alcyonÿ	O
fragmentum	O
perforatum	O
P.	O
Astroites	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
-450	O
.	O
Sponge	O
&	O
corall	O
small	O
&	O
white	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
?	O
201	O
.	O
-451	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
growing	O
to	O
the	O
rocks	O
i	O
a	O
n	O
the	O
shores	O
in	O
Cornwall	I-place
.	O
201	O
-452	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
white	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
P.	O
189	O
-453	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
.	O
200	O
-454	O
.	O
Small	O
white	O
solid	O
muricated	O
corall	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
?	O
/	O
From	O
E.	O
Indies	O
.	O
206	O
-455	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
41a	O
42	O
-456	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
larger	O
trunc	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Boccone	O
Recherch	O
obs	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
Amsterdam	O
.	O
1674.	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
142	O
.	O
205	O
-457	O
.	O
An	O
oblong	O
piece	O
of	O
astroites	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-458	O
.	O
A	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
.	O
very	O
large	O
201	O
.	O
-459	O
.	O
A	O
coralline	O
?	O
incrustation	O
from	O
the	O
wrecked	O
Spanish	O
Spainish	O
ship	O
near	O
Hispaniola	B-place
upon	O
iron	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
-460	O
.	O
Spongia	O
ramosa	O
.	O
200	O
-461	O
.	O
Corallina	O
off	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-462	O
.	O
Corallina	O
&	O
c.	O
segmentis	O
in	O
summitate	O
planis	O
?	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-463	O
.	O
Corallium	O
pumilum	O
album	O
nostras	O
from	O
the	O
Magellanic	B-place
streights	I-place
?	O
201	O
.	O
-464	O
.	O
Tethya	O
?	O
fimus	O
equinus	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
-465	O
.	O
Lapides	O
Spongiæ	O
.	O
246.	O
n	O
-466	O
.	O
Young	O
corall	O
sprouting	O
?	O
Alcyonium	O
?	O
15	O
P	O
32	O
42a	O
43	O
-467	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
stellatum	O
&	O
punctatum	O
?	O
or	O
rather	O
Astroites	O
branched	O
fossil	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
-468	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Coralline	O
branch	O
from	O
the	O
Leeward	B-place
Islands	I-place
with	O
Starr	O
fishes	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Codrington	I-pers
to	O
her	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
the	I-pers
Dutchesse	I-pers
of	I-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
who	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
that	O
growing	O
in	O
the	O
Soundings	O
No	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
-469	O
.	O
Some	O
tubuli	O
of	O
the	O
astroites	O
?	O
or	O
Canary	O
corall	O
?	O
in	O
a	O
soft	O
bed	O
from	O
-	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
in	O
a	O
Limestone	O
bed	O
.	O
204	O
-470	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
from	O
Nova	B-place
Zembla	I-place
by	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
/	O
Streights	B-place
of	I-place
Magellan	I-place
201	O
.	O
-471	O
.	O
A	O
Species	O
of	O
Sea	O
rose	O
or	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
-undulatus	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
205	O
-472	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Coralline	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Staggs	O
horn	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
200	O
-473	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
sea	O
Sponge	O
from	O
Portsmouth	B-place
.	O
-474	O
.	O
Lapis	O
spongiæ	O
off	O
.	O
181.	O
x	O
43a	O
44	O
-475	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
lapidea	O
a	O
Sneeberg	O
Saxoniæ	O
M.	O
Schonberg	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
204	O
-476	O
.	O
Porus	O
coralloides	O
ex	O
monte	O
juxta	O
Messanam	O
Siciliæ	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
-477	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
common	O
roundish	O
sponge	O
.	O
00	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
00	O
.	O
200	O
-478	O
.	O
The	O
sea	O
fann	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
208	O
-479	O
.	O
An	O
Eschara	O
marina	O
latifolia	O
|	O
Cock	O
spurrs	O
from	O
-	O
00	O
.	O
05	O
.	O
00.	O
Broughton	B-place
in	O
Craven	B-place
.	O
L.	O
|	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
A	O
broad	O
or	O
&	O
narrower	O
sort	O
.	O
an	O
extrochos	O
knocked	O
off	O
.	O
List	O
.	O
phil	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
100.	O
p.	O
6190.	O
fig	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
/	O
Glossopetræ	O
ceratites	O
.	O
belemnites	O
sive	O
conoides	O
exturbinis	O
figura	O
nominati	O
-	O
striati	O
.	O
L.	O
L.	O
A	O
cockspur	O
found	O
at	O
Broughton	O
&	O
Coushe	O
/	O
L.	O
Cockspurrs	O
found	O
at	O
Broughton	O
Sparr	O
plentifully	O
lapides	O
conoides	O
ex	O
turbinis	O
figura	O
nominati	O
.	O
L.	O
|	O
A	O
cocks	O
spurr	O
found	O
at	O
Stow	O
market	O
at	O
the	O
one	O
end	O
is	O
its	O
flower	O
.	O
L.	O
Columellus	O
turbinatus	O
albidus	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
8.	O
fig	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
✓	O
15	O
q	O
207	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
200	O
200	O
-480	O
.	O
White	O
solid	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
This	O
polished	O
makes	O
the	O
white	O
corall	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
-481	O
.	O
Corallium	O
.	O
album	O
porsoum	O
muricatum	O
minus	O
.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
107	O
CIV	O
II	O
.	O
44a	O
45	O
-482	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
white	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
480	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
-483	O
.	O
A	O
fossil	O
coralloid	O
body	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
starr	O
.	O
dugg	O
up	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
?	O
202	O
.	O
75	O
-484	O
.	O
The	O
pietra	O
stellaria	O
or	O
lapis	O
stellaris	O
with	O
small	O
starrs	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	I-pers
15	O
P.	O
189	O
202	O
-485	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
larger	O
starrs	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
189	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
-486	O
.	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
202	O
-487	O
.	O
Corallium	O
asperum	O
candicans	O
adulterinum	O
SB	B-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
same	O
207	O
.	O
-488	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
Park	O
.	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
45a	O
46	O
-489	O
.	O
The	O
corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
Sticking	O
to	O
the	O
roots	O
of	O
fucus	O
phasga=	O
=noides	O
.	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Sam	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
201	O
.	O
-490	O
.	O
A	O
box	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Urry	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
281	O
-491	O
.	O
The	O
common	O
coralline	O
of	O
the	O
shops	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
fine	O
fucus	O
fæniculaceus	O
from	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
201	O
-492	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
white	O
corall	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
?	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Cheyne	I-pers
.	O
201	O
75	O
-493	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
or	O
branch	O
of	O
red	O
corall	O
as	O
it	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
not	O
polished	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
-494	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
redish	O
Eschara	O
marina	O
from	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
the	O
Cape	B-place
of	I-place
good	I-place
hope	I-place
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
169	O
2/3	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Sam	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
189	O
46a	O
47	O
-495	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
corall	O
on	O
the	O
trunc	O
of	O
which	O
growes	O
white	O
corall	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
Een	O
corall	O
boom	O
met	O
wit	O
en	O
swart	O
door	O
een	O
ander	O
gemengelt	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
51	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
455	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
XCVI	O
.	O
-496	O
.	O
Black	O
corall	O
growing	O
wreathed	O
like	O
an	O
unicorns	O
horn	O
.	O
Een	O
swart	O
corall	O
boom	O
gewassen	O
op	O
de	O
maniese	O
als	O
de	O
horn	O
van	O
een	O
Eenhorn	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
456	O
.	O
208	O
-497	O
.	O
Astroites	O
turned	O
into	O
a	O
ponderous	O
gray	O
stone	O
from	O
Althrop	B-place
.	O
15	O
P.	O
202	O
.	O
-498	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
eschara	O
marina	O
from	O
a	O
clay	O
pitt	O
of	O
a	O
blewish	O
colour	O
?	O
202	O
.	O
-499	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
stellatum	O
minus	O
found	O
fossil	O
in	O
France	B-place
near	O
Paris	B-place
sent	O
me	O
by	O
Monsr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Geoffroy	I-pers
.	I-pers
200	O
-500	O
.	O
Artificiall	O
red	O
corall	O
made	O
for	O
rockwork	O
.	O
of	O
soft	O
wax	O
&	O
c.	O
200	O
47a	O
48	O
-501	O
.	O
Coralline	O
bodies	O
immersd	O
in	O
a	O
pebble	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
shore	O
near	O
Wainfleet	B-place
in	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
15	O
.	O
P.	O
202	O
-502	O
.	O
Coralline	O
bodies	O
inclos	O
'd	O
in	O
stone	O
from	O
the	O
lead	O
mines	O
in	O
Haddon	I-place
parish	I-place
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
.	O
Id	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
202	O
-503	O
.	O
Fungus	O
saxeus	O
petrified	O
?	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lavater	I-pers
.	O
204	O
504	O
.	O
The	O
smallest	O
por	O
'd	O
Astroites	O
with	O
a	O
cavity	O
in	O
it	O
wherein	O
was	O
a	O
crab	O
?	O
C.	O
-505	O
.	O
Fungi	O
saxei	O
flatt	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
190	O
199	O
-506	O
.	O
One	O
Sprout	O
of	O
the	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
206	O
✓	O
-507	O
.	O
A	O
Tethya	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
chama	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
48a	O
49	O
-508	O
.	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
fossil	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
?	O
200	O
-509	O
.	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
coralline	O
body	O
like	O
a	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
.	O
fossil	O
?	O
It	O
hath	O
a	O
pedicle	O
&	O
round	O
head	O
striated	O
within	O
200	O
-510	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
coralline	O
body	O
wch	O
.	O
hath	O
a	O
tapering	O
head	O
,	O
flatted	O
wt	O
.	O
striæ	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
circumference	O
to	O
the	O
center	O
as	O
sevll	O
.	O
coralline	O
bodies	O
have	O
.	O
Fossil	O
from	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
Paris	B-place
from	O
Monsr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Geoffroy	I-pers
.	O
511	O
.	O
That	O
sort	O
of	O
coralline	O
body	O
or	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
called	O
a	O
sea	O
rose	O
.	O
The	O
strie	O
are	O
dentaded	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
-512	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
porous	O
white	O
corall	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
anastomos	O
'd	O
&	O
c.	O
206	O
-513	O
.	O
The	O
more	O
solid	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
corallium	O
porosum	O
album	O
muricatum	O
&	O
c.	O
Cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
✓	O
206	O
49a	O
517	O
.	O
Corallio	O
congener	O
ceratium	O
fossile	O
;	O
sen	O
pseudo-	O
corallium	O
pumilum	O
cornucervi	O
divisura	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
from	O
Witney	B-place
.	O
Porus	O
minimus	O
furcatus	O
fossilis	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
an	O
specie	O
distinguendus	O
a	O
ceratio	O
fossili	O
nobis	O
dicto	O
incertus	O
from	O
Id	O
.	O
50	O
-514	O
.	O
A	O
spongia	O
spuria	O
ramosa	O
apicibus	O
extantibus	O
exasperata	O
.	O
Cuaps	O
Sprinkhorn	O
.	O
From	O
Holland	B-place
.	O
200	O
-515	O
.	O
A	O
frutex	O
marinus	O
of	O
an	O
horny	O
substance	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208	O
-516	O
.	O
Another	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
yellow	O
incrustation	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
-517	O
.	O
Fossil	O
corall	O
on	O
a	O
gray	O
stone	O
.	O
|	O
From	O
Althorp	B-place
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
.	O
|	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
exalbidum	O
pennam	O
gall	O
inaceam	O
crassum	O
ramulis	O
alias	O
pluribus	O
sepius	O
binis	O
alias	O
amputatis	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
6	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
94	O
.	O
&	O
92.	O
larger	O
&	O
smaller	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
minimum	O
nostras	O
?	O
159	O
32	O
?	O
201	O
.	O
-518	O
.	O
A	O
rete	O
marinum	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
yellow	O
incrust=	O
=ation	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
From	O
Holland	B-place
.	O
208	O
-519	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
solid	O
foliated	O
muricated	O
corall	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
colour	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
by	O
a	O
fishermans	O
net	O
in	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
.	O
the	O
solid	O
white	O
part	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
duskish	O
colour	O
likely	O
from	O
the	O
Thames	O
bottom	O
soil	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
sea	O
.	O
206	O
-520	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
redish	O
coralline	O
substance	O
not	O
branched	O
sticking	O
to	O
the	O
rocks	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
sea	O
abt	O
.	O
Jamaica	B-place
200	O
50a	O
51	O
-521	O
A	O
small	O
branched	O
corall	O
or	O
lachryma	O
Elephanti	O
?	O
200	O
-522	O
.	O
Corall	O
from	O
the	O
Canaries	B-place
with	O
shells	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
208	O
-523	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
flatt	O
piece	O
of	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
undulatus	O
.	O
202	O
-524.	O
corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
.	O
From	O
Barcelona	B-place
.	O
251	O
.	O
201	O
525	O
.	O
Corallina	O
fruticosa	O
humilior	O
&	O
crassior	O
ramis	O
quaquaversum	O
expansis	O
super=	O
=ficie	O
tuberculata	O
.	O
cat	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
3	O
.	O
|	O
smaller	O
crust	O
from	O
the	O
streights	B-place
?	O
208	O
208	O
526	O
.	O
Corallium	O
album	O
pumilum	O
nostras	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
streights	B-place
of	I-place
Magellan	I-place
.	O
201	O
51a	O
52	O
527	O
.	O
Black	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
shell	O
growing	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
0.5.0	O
.	O
2sh	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
189	O
528	O
.	O
Red	O
corall	O
,	O
.	O
&	O
fungi	O
lapidei	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
single	O
staras	O
the	O
plectroiutes	O
&	O
wt	O
.	O
long	O
foot	O
stalks	O
,	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
bivalve	O
shell	O
.	O
an	O
of	O
crowstones	O
206	O
529	O
.	O
Corallium	O
griseum	O
growing	O
on	O
a	O
pebble	O
.	O
an	O
corallium	O
album	O
minus	O
nostras	O
a	O
litle	O
more	O
then	O
ordinarily	O
branched	O
?	O
177	O
.	O
530	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
pedicle	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
|	O
wt	O
.	O
indented	O
striæ	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
531	O
.	O
A	O
smll	O
fungus	O
saxeus	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
short	O
footstalk	O
grow	O
in	O
on	O
a	O
tree	O
oyster	O
wt	O
.	O
tubuli	O
vermium	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
190	O
-532	O
.	O
A	O
lump	O
of	O
grey	O
corall	O
very	O
short	O
&	O
resembling	O
the	O
lapis	O
astroites	O
928	O
undulatus	O
but	O
more	O
solid	O
then	O
that	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
streights	B-place
of	I-place
Magellan	I-place
?	O
200	O
52a	O
53	O
533	O
.	O
The	O
rudiments	O
or	O
originall	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Dover	B-place
by	O
the	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	I-pers
Millepora	O
arpenosa	O
anglica	O
found	O
at	O
Deal	B-place
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
.	I-pers
Pet	O
.	O
M.	O
27	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
brought	O
by	O
some	O
ship	O
from	O
another	O
Place	O
an	O
accidentaly	O
covered	O
wt	O
.	O
sand	O
.	O
189	O
201	O
.	O
534	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
redish	O
fucus	O
?	O
-535	O
.	O
Branchiali	O
congener	O
columellus	O
striatus	O
sive	O
bryonie	O
radix	O
lapidea	O
Plot	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
7	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
120.	O
from	O
mendip	B-place
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
|	O
various	O
bignesses	O
.	O
L.	O
15	O
P.	O
200	O
-536	O
.	O
Fungus	O
Saxeus	O
minor	O
arcuatus	O
.	O
Certain	O
stones	O
like	O
the	O
broken	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
claws	O
of	O
crabs	O
,	O
or	O
lobsters	O
.	O
L.	O
Columelli	O
Llind	O
.	O
Species	O
.	O
200	O
-537	O
.	O
Fungus	O
Sexeus	O
minor	O
ramosus	O
.	O
From	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
from	O
mendip	B-place
hills	I-place
.	O
201	O
.	O
15	O
L	O
-538	O
.	O
Redish	O
Lapis	O
astroites	O
found	O
in	O
mendip	B-place
?	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
202	O
53a	O
542	O
.	O
Madrepora	O
ramosa	O
con	O
le	O
stremita	O
terminate	O
in	O
piano	O
,	O
nel	O
modo	O
dell	O
'	O
altra	O
detta	O
:	O
si	O
vede	O
nelle	O
parti	O
de	O
suoi	O
tronchi	O
molta	O
differenza	O
,	O
percioctie	O
le	O
parti	O
che	O
sono	O
in	O
luoco	O
de	O
tronchi	O
primi	O
,	O
sone	O
sense	O
,	O
e	O
bianche	O
in	O
modo	O
de	O
Coralli	O
,	O
le	O
seguenti	O
ectre	O
sono	O
quasi	O
annue	O
aggiunte	O
,	O
sono	O
rave	O
,	O
e	O
deboli	O
edi	O
color	O
orcuro	O
,	O
e	O
purpureo	O
,	O
e	O
contenenti	O
alquanto	O
di	O
sustanza	O
simile	O
à	O
membrana	O
,	O
onde	O
puote	O
argomentarsi	O
esiore	O
in	O
essa	O
participazion	O
di	O
vita	O
sensitiva	O
,	O
nel	O
modo	O
che	O
e	O
selle	O
sole	O
marine	O
,	O
e	O
melle	O
spongie	O
.	O
Imperali	O
.	O
Edit	O
.	O
Nap	O
.	O
1590.	O
pag	O
.	O
721	O
.	O
Vene	O
&	O
1672	O
p.	O
629	O
Porus	O
matronalis	O
ramosus	O
,	O
extremitatibus	O
in	O
planum	O
desinantibus	O
,	O
digiti	O
indicis	O
instar	O
.	O
in	O
cujus	O
ramorum	O
partibus	O
magna	O
spectatur	O
differentia	O
,	O
illis	O
qui	O
primorum	O
loco	O
sunt	O
trunctrum	O
denvis	O
existentilus	O
.	O
atys	O
.	O
instar	O
Corallis	O
albicantibus	O
,	O
sequentibus	O
,	O
quæ	O
annuæ	O
velut	O
accessiones	O
sunt	O
,	O
rani	O
,	O
ac	O
debilibus	O
,	O
colore	O
obscuro	O
&	O
purpureo	O
,	O
nonnitil	O
substantiæ	O
membranaceæ	O
continuntibus	O
vide	O
conjuare	O
treat	O
,	O
illos	O
vitæ	O
sensitivæ	O
particepes	O
osse	O
,	O
parinde	O
ac	O
in	O
vela	O
marino	O
et	O
spongüs	O
.	O
Latin	O
.	O
819	O
.	O
54	O
-539	O
.	O
Corallium	O
minimum	O
calcarÿs	O
rupibus	O
adnascens	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
Synops	O
.	O
sti	O
o	O
p.	O
Brit	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
.	O
L.	O
201	O
.	O
-540	O
.	O
Astroites	O
.	O
fossil	O
?	O
L.	O
202	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
-541	O
.	O
A	O
whitish	O
small	O
coralloides	O
growing	O
upon	O
a	O
gray	O
lapis	O
fissilis	O
.	O
O.	O
vide	O
.	O
208	O
-542	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
corall	O
with	O
very	O
large	O
starrs	O
at	O
the	O
joints	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
217.	O
upon	O
206	O
CXXIII	O
-543	O
.	O
Severall	O
pieces	O
of	O
Severall	O
sorts	O
of	O
coralls	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-544	O
.	O
A	O
porous	O
white	O
corall	O
wt	O
.	O
very	O
many	O
starrs	O
.	O
P.	O
202	O
.	O
-545	O
.	O
An	O
corallÿs	O
annumer	O
and	O
?	O
from	O
a	O
cave	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
near	O
Amlock	B-place
in	O
Anglesey	B-place
.	O
L.	O
P.	O
vid	O
.	O
539	O
.	O
201	O
54a	O
55	O
-546	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
coralloid	O
body	O
found	O
in	O
Sommersetshire	B-place
in	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
From	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
15	O
P.	O
201	O
200	O
-547	O
.	O
Columellus	O
turbinatus	O
albidus	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
8	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
181.	O
sevll	O
.	O
sorts	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
200	O
-548	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
?	O
ib	O
.	O
one	O
a	O
marcasite	O
?	O
M.	O
15	O
P.	O
204	O
-549	O
.	O
A	O
coralloid	O
substance	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Mourille	O
.	O
M.	O
202	O
.	O
-550	O
.	O
Porpites	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
182.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
M.	O
an	O
echinites	O
?	O
157	O
.	O
-551	O
.	O
A	O
porpites	O
wt	O
.	O
striæ	O
from	O
the	O
circum	O
ference	O
to	O
the	O
center	O
representing	O
continued	O
lines	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
182.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
M.	O
204	O
.	O
-552	O
.	O
A	O
porpites	O
wt	O
.	O
striæ	O
from	O
the	O
circum	O
ference	O
to	O
the	O
center	O
representing	O
prick	O
'd	O
lines	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
tab	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
&	O
7	O
.	O
M.	O
204	O
.	O
55a	O
56	O
-553	O
.	O
A	O
porpites	O
of	O
a	O
more	O
elevated	O
surface	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
182	O
.	O
15	O
q	O
204	O
-554	O
.	O
Branchiale	O
ferruginosum	O
,	O
fungis	O
Lapideis	O
forsan	O
annumerandum	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
fig	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
182.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
M.	O
204	O
75	O
-555	O
.	O
Astroites	O
wt	O
.	O
concave	O
starrs	O
intermixd	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
limelike	O
matter	O
&	O
sparr	O
from	O
new	O
inn	O
stone	O
pilt	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
183	O
.	O
Rance	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
-556	O
.	O
Impressions	O
of	O
the	O
astroites	O
on	O
limestone	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
-557	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
555	O
.	O
A	O
Sparry	O
concave	O
nodule	O
adorned	O
wt	O
.	O
asteriscs	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
174	O
.	O
75	O
202	O
-558	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
of	O
coarser	O
matter	O
the	O
striæ	O
continud	O
tending	O
to	O
a	O
primineat	O
center	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
56a	O
57	O
-559	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
striæ	O
resembling	O
prick	O
'd	O
lines	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
from	O
Culworth	B-place
Stone	O
pitts	O
.	O
202	O
75	O
-560	O
.	O
Astroites	O
chrystallinus	O
sive	O
fluor	O
pellucidus	O
Artleburiensis	O
,	O
stellata	O
superficie	O
insignis	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
9	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p	O
183	O
.	O
75	O
202	O
.	O
-561	O
.	O
An	O
Astorites	O
wt	O
.	O
round	O
radiated	O
holes	O
exactly	O
like	O
corall	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
183.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
15	O
P.	O
202	O
.	O
-562	O
.	O
A	O
coralloid	O
body	O
of	O
simple	O
coralloid	O
stems	O
,	O
immersd	O
in	O
a	O
limestone	O
nodule	O
.	O
from	O
Culworth	B-place
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
184	O
.	O
-563.	O
the	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
Stems	O
thinner	O
Sett	O
more	O
obscurely	O
radiated	O
.	O
from	O
Cosgrave	B-place
stone	O
pitts	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
15	O
q	O
203	O
199	O
e	O
207	O
-564	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
.	O
variety	O
of	O
coralloid	O
bodies	O
branched	O
&	O
accreted	O
to	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
limeston	O
&	O
sparr	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
p.	O
184	O
.	O
&	O
185	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
199	O
e	O
208.	O
c	O
57a	O
58	O
-565	O
.	O
Simple	O
coralloid	O
bodies	O
of	O
the	O
lime=	O
Stone	O
kind	O
un	O
branched	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
185	O
?	O
M.	O
201	O
-566	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
563.	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
colour	O
from	O
Cosgrave	O
.	O
M.	O
204	O
15	O
q	O
-567	O
.	O
Coralloid	O
bodies	O
of	O
the	O
limestone	O
kind	O
branched	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
185.	O
tab	O
.	O
2.	O
fig	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Corallium	O
fossile	O
exalbidum	O
mini	O
=mum	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
p.	O
6	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
98	O
.	O
201	O
-568	O
.	O
558	O
Porus	O
minimus	O
reticulatus	O
sive	O
alcyonium	O
accreted	O
to	O
pebles	O
.	O
Mort	O
.	O
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
585	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
-569	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
smaller	O
.	O
from	O
New	B-place
inn	I-place
Limestone	O
pitt	O
.	O
M.	O
15	O
q	O
202	O
-570	O
.	O
Simple	O
Stems	O
of	O
a	O
coralloid	O
bodies	O
immersd	O
in	O
limestone	O
&	O
Sparr	O
?	O
from	O
Culworth	B-place
.	O
M.	O
an	O
.	O
lap	O
.	O
Ind	O
?	O
202	O
-571	O
.	O
Small	O
round	O
&	O
ovall	O
pebbles	O
like	O
cherries	O
&	O
c	O
?	O
M.	O
58a	O
59	O
-572	O
.	O
Coralloidis	O
ramusculi	O
from	O
swisser	B-place
land	I-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	O
201	O
-573	O
.	O
Ramus	O
cujusdam	O
arboris	O
marinæ	O
ex	O
Norwegiæ	O
fundo	O
maris	O
erutæ	O
&	O
si	O
verum	O
sit	O
quod	O
mihi	O
dixerint	O
latores	O
,	O
profunditas	O
maris	O
eo	O
loci	O
erat	O
centum	O
ulnarum	O
,	O
sit	O
centum	O
pedum	O
,	O
profunditas	O
revera	O
satis	O
considerablis	O
.	O
Arbor	O
hommis	O
proceritatem	O
superat	O
crassities	O
brachium	O
humanum	O
superat	O
s	O
p	O
ubstantia	O
fungosa	O
praesertum	O
circa	O
ramos	O
,	O
&	O
satis	O
quoqz	O
dura	O
circa	O
truncum	O
jam	O
vero	O
ramos	O
reperi	O
friabiles	O
ut	O
percipies	O
ex	O
altera	O
parte	O
hic	O
addita	O
.	O
Rapis	O
frusto	O
im=	O
posui	O
uti	O
soleo	O
cæteris	O
rebus	O
meis	O
.	O
Ruysch	O
.	O
Epist	O
.	O
1714	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
200	O
-574	O
.	O
Pars	O
arboris	O
supercus	O
descriptæ	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
200	O
-575	O
.	O
Lithophytum	O
purpureum	O
Africanum	O
Ruysch	B-pers
.	O
206	O
.	O
-576	O
.	O
Lithophytum	O
Africanum	O
amulans	O
sauharum	O
cinamomisatum	O
(	O
si	O
ita	O
loqui	O
liceat	O
)	O
belgice	O
dic	O
t	O
itur	O
caneel	O
succhre	O
.	O
Ruysch	B-pers
.	O
206	O
59a	O
60	O
-577	O
.	O
Lithophytum	O
Africanum	O
ex	O
luteo	O
purpureum	O
.	O
Ruysch	B-pers
.	O
206	O
-578	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
wt	O
.	O
576.	O
wt	O
out	O
its	O
crust	O
-	O
Kerato	O
lithophytum	O
&	O
c.	O
Ruysch	B-pers
.	O
206	O
208	O
-579	O
.	O
An	O
Alcyonÿs	O
accedens	O
fasciculus	O
:	O
seu	O
geniculatus	O
lapis	O
fasciatim	O
manipuli	O
frumentarÿ	O
ritu	O
coalitus	O
cuter	O
entrochos	O
&	O
alcyonia	O
ambigens	O
.	O
Lluid	O
.	O
lith	O
.	O
p.	O
7	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
Virgaltum	O
corallinum	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
act	O
.	O
phil	O
.	O
Lond	O
.	O
150.	O
fig	O
.	O
26	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
observed	O
in	O
the	O
perpendicular	O
fissures	O
of	O
a	O
limestone	O
quarry	O
near	O
fryar	O
end	O
in	O
Craven	O
large	O
pieces	O
of	O
this	O
fossil	O
filling	O
up	O
the	O
vacancies	O
&	O
sticking	O
close	O
to	O
both	O
sides	O
of	O
the	O
rock	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
stone	O
quarry	O
at	O
Mickal	O
sse	O
high	O
Bradford	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
markd	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Succus	O
concretus	O
marinus	O
scalecias	O
.	O
Aldrovand	O
.	O
Mus	O
:	O
Metall	O
:	O
p.	O
281	O
.	O
✓	O
201	O
.	O
-580	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
beautifull	O
piece	O
of	O
marble	O
blackish	O
wt	O
.	O
pentagons	O
like	O
the	O
cells	O
of	O
a	O
hony	O
comb	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
above	O
Ingleton	B-place
in	O
-	O
Craven	B-place
.	O
Id	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
581	O
.	O
Two	O
fungi	O
Saxei	O
growing	O
together	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
corrugated	O
&	O
c	O
sticking	O
together	O
as	O
though	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
liquid	O
190	O
60a	O
590	O
Spezie	O
di	O
Corallo	O
di	O
color	O
piu	O
'	O
blanco	O
punticchiato	O
nella	O
sua	O
superficie	O
;	O
tuberculoso	O
di	O
tronchi	O
