TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
26th	O
and	O
27th	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
and	O
27th	O
days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1685.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenew	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bullivant	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hamman	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Helder	I-pers
John	B-pers
Eston	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Comport	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Seymore	I-pers
William	B-pers
Revet	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Kettilby	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Franckly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
July	O
the	O
15th	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
Sedition	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Speeches	O
and	O
Words	O
to	O
render	O
her	O
most	O
gracious	O
Majesty	O
,	O
our	O
present	O
Queen	O
,	O
odious	O
in	O
the	O
Opinions	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
liege	O
Subjects	O
,	O
saying	O
as	O
follows	O
;	O
The	O
Queen	O
is	O
the	O
Pope	O
's	O
Bastard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Treason	O
to	O
speak	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
Crown	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
caused	O
the	O
D.	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
forthwith	O
to	O
be	O
pared	O
to	O
death	O
with	O
a	O
Razor	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Privy	O
Counsellor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Queen	O
had	O
often	O
petitioned	O
the	O
King	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
D.	O
of	O
M.	O
speaking	O
divers	O
other	O
very	O
scurrilous	O
words	O
against	O
Authority	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
neither	O
in	O
Confutation	O
of	O
the	O
Crimes	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
always	O
bore	O
very	O
loyal	O
thoughts	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
but	O
produced	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Voller	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
Church	I-pers
:	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
Church	O
's	O
House	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
busie	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
when	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Dolbin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
coyned	O
Gold	O
from	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
other	O
Gold	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
:	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Plantiff	O
it	O
only	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
her	O
self	O
unconcern	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harbert	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
cheat	O
Hue	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
of	O
six	O
pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
grounded	O
upon	O
a	O
Mistake	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
18th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Poliday	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
lest	O
his	O
Friend	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
follows	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
January	O
17th	O
.	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anthony	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
wounding	O
him	O
therewith	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
the	O
said	O
Loe	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arising	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Loe	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
about	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Davis	O
strook	O
Loe	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
challenging	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
fighting	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Loe	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
wounded	O
,	O
Davis	O
and	O
Buckmaster	O
being	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Davis	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
fought	O
Loe	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Coward	O
.	O
The	O
Physician	O
,	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
Loe	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
of	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
two	O
Fevers	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Fever	O
the	O
said	O
Loe	O
died	O
:	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
likewise	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
healed	O
,	O
and	O
perfectly	O
cured	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Body	O
was	O
corrupted	O
by	O
other	O
Distempers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
25th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
27	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Frolick	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
three	O
Stuff	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
little	O
defence	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
20th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
one	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Bib	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
drop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
July	O
27th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
away	O
a	O
Chamblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hulston	I-pers
:	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hacker	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hulston	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
returning	O
speedily	O
again	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
searching	O
for	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
carried	O
a	O
Cloak	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dennis	B-pers
Dally	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
seditiously	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
in	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
Rebels	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
late	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
had	O
better	O
Title	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
than	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
Rebellion	O
:	O
all	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Lieutenant	O
and	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
true	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
for	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Flatman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
21.	O
for	O
Breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
7	O
Napkins	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Linnen	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Tomson	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
Flatman	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
Tomson	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
and	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
Flatman	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Charly	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
November	O
20th	O
.	O
1684	O
for	O
Breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Spanish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Cloth	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
122	O
l.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Charly	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
thereto	O
belonging	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Lewis	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
many	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
in	O
several	O
Shops	O
:	O
Lewis	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sims	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
Charly	O
was	O
Burnt	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
Charly	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Huget	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
for	O
Breaking	O
up	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
proved	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Roberts	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hanah	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Baucer	I-pers
and	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Widdows	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Marman	I-pers
:	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Scot	O
,	O
Baucer	O
,	O
and	O
Widdows	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Watkins	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
whence	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Baucer	O
and	O
Widdows	O
say	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Scot	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
Baucer	O
appeared	O
to	O
beold	O
Offenders	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
Baucer	O
,	O
Scot	O
,	O
and	O
Widdows	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Watkins	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gorden	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hayles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Presnol	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
Gorden	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Hayles	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
Draper	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Arrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Critor	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
leaving	O
,	O
August	O
10th	O
,	O
three	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
to	O
be	O
maintained	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
great	O
Damage	O
and	O
Oppression	O
thereto	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
made	O
it	O
apparent	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
their	O
business	O
and	O
trade	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
nature	O
to	O
leave	O
young	O
Infants	O
(	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
gotten	O
under	O
the	O
species	O
of	O
Nurses	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
and	O
Commiseration	O
of	O
a	O
Parish	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
of	O
their	O
natural	O
Parents	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
engratiate	O
themselves	O
with	O
the	O
Overseers	O
or	O
Church-wardens	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Nursing	O
might	O
once	O
more	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
their	O
Charges	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
would	O
engross	O
to	O
themselves	O
a	O
double	O
Pension	O
,	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
Parent	O
,	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
Parish	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
make	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
defence	O
that	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
pertinent	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Confutation	O
of	O
one	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
so	O
in	O
two	O
Children	O
that	O
were	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
being	O
Twins	O
basely	O
born	O
,	O
he	O
agreeing	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoners	O
five	O
pounds	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
which	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
Children	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Custodies	O
,	O
they	O
agreeing	O
together	O
,	O
carried	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
Bishopsgate	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
them	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
which	O
with	O
all	O
their	O
other	O
Evasions	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
fostered	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Urin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
18	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
from	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Castre	O
Sugar	O
Cup	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
one	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
purple	O
Breeches	O
with	O
the	O
Moneys	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
laying	O
little	O
stress	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bucknell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
with	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Monevs	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Common	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Bucknell	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
proving	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Common	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
upon	O
;	O
proving	O
further	O
his	O
Credit	O
by	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Lawrence	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
106	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burbidg	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Lee	O
's	O
Custody	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
Missing	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
pertinent	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
July	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Darcy	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
running	O
the	O
said	O
Rapier	O
into	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Phillip	O
Darcy	O
Languishing	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
and	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
meeting	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
Accusing	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
for	O
Riding	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
satisfied	O
him	O
thereof	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
told	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
Indebted	O
to	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
denying	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Lye	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Words	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
Drawing	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
mutual	O
Passes	O
and	O
Tilts	O
they	O
were	O
interchangably	O
Wounded	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
very	O
Discongruous	O
in	O
their	O
Relations	O
:	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Fight	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
first	O
stroke	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
Drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
provoking	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
to	O
Draw	O
likewise	O
,	O
which	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Side	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Hand	O
before	O
he	O
Drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
had	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
spoke	O
very	O
honourably	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
brought	O
at	O
least	O
five	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Provocation	O
,	O
striking	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Drawing	O
and	O
Stabbing	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
side	O
before	O
he	O
Drew	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Debate	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
F	O
-	O
Fell	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Darcy	O
was	O
carryed	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
some	O
small	O
Consult	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Detraby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
August	O
,	O
twenty	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Pullyon	I-pers
:	O
Pullyon	O
(	O
being	O
himself	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Detraby	O
take	O
one	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
telling	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sum	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
Detraby	O
,	O
who	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elioner	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
sugar	O
Castre	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pound	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
pound	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
one	O
silver	O
Chavendish	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Elioner	O
Steel	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
;	O
who	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Urin	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
but	O
Urin	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
denyed	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
August	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
one	O
gray	O
Nag	O
with	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Daniel	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Nottingham	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
:	O
he	O
pleaded	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
,	O
on	O
July	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Earl	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Orchard	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pledwell	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Champian	I-pers
accessary	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Haynsword	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
aforenamed	O
Champian	O
engratiating	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Haynsword	O
,	O
seduc	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
Parents	O
,	O
taking	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
pretended	O
Lodging	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Pledwell	O
,	O
where	O
Champian	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
stay	O
with	O
Pledwell	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
Champian	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
Pledwell	O
shuts	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
compelled	O
her	O
to	O
undress	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
stopping	O
her	O
mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Will	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
stab	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
if	O
she	O
refused	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Rape	O
was	O
committed	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Pledwell	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
altogether	O
impertinent	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
a	O
common	O
Bawdy-house	O
.	O
A	O
Butchers	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Haynsword	I-pers
was	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
Woman	O
both	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Champian	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
Haynsword	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
Parents	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
Pledwell	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Champian	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Vincent	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
July	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Pounds	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
of	O
Moneys	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hortshorn	I-pers
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
very	O
little	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bide	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
for	O
Stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth-Serge	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Bide	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forthwith	O
apprehended	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloth	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
fall	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Esther	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
:	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Burstall	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Wright	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
a	O
Decoy	O
contriving	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
16	O
s.	O
of	O
Burstalls	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
return	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
Railing	O
against	O
Burstall	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
one	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
Bolster	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
Three	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Garden	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	O
Six	O
Persons	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Dennis	O
Dally	O
and	O
William	O
Bras	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
Ricard	O
Bide	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Detraby	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Nine	O
recieved	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Charly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Scop	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bancer	I-pers
,	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Widdows	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glunister	I-pers
,	O
Eleaner	O
Steel	O
.	O
Thirty	O
old	O
Offenders	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Kings	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
