TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
and	O
16	O
,	O
days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Merlin	B-pers
Burly	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Burly	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Gible	I-pers
John	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
George	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Filer	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Howler	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vigers	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fits	I-pers
Garred	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Brumfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Frances	B-pers
Turconel	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Cloth	O
thence	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Cloth	O
into	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
appeared	O
very	O
Impudent	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
very	O
Immaterial	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Heat	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Interloping	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Geese	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Geese	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pretended	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Geese	O
Pinioned	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Pump	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Pump	O
Handle	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Aldredge	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
That	O
Lacy	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
importuning	O
the	O
Plantiff	O
Aldridge	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Importunities	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
four	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
drink	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assaulted	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Aldridge	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
beating	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
abusing	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
Bruises	O
his	O
Daughter	O
attested	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
deposing	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
seeing	O
his	O
Wounds	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Abuses	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Aldridge	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
robbing	O
him	O
likewise	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
Aldridge	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
door	O
and	O
there	O
bruised	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
testified	O
by	O
divers	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
forthwith	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
September	O
10	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
Pot-lids	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
lids	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cole	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
,	O
whip	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
.	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
for	O
Stealing	O
15	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Moneys	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
wanting	O
some	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ironmonger-Lane	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Plow	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Pursue	O
and	O
Taken	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
Agony	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
nothing	O
therefore	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
September	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Wounding	O
him	O
therewith	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Harding	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
Drawing	O
upon	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
Harding	O
appearing	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Abused	O
party	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
Stab	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
Died	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
arresting	O
the	O
Wound	O
occasioned	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
D	O
-	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
divers	O
Blows	O
with	O
other	O
Provocations	O
;	O
called	O
Papist	O
Rogue	O
,	O
one	O
putting	O
the	O
other	O
forward	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
Knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
(	O
they	O
pressing	O
two	O
hard	O
upon	O
him	O
)	O
obliged	O
to	O
Draw	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
be	O
cautious	O
;	O
which	O
Harding	O
not	O
regarding	O
,	O
pressed	O
himself	O
on	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Drop	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
some	O
40	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
first	O
hapned	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Maynards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
September	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Brass	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Edgworth	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
he	O
won	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
the	O
6th	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Rowland	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
.	O
Squire	O
Little	O
losing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Gardner	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Sword	O
lying	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Coy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Cammell	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Pocher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hellingdon	B-place
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Pocher	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
eight	O
Souldiers	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Drank	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
upon	O
his	O
demand	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
Souldiers	O
Drew	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Killed	O
one	O
Pocher	O
:	O
The	O
Souldiers	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Assaulted	O
,	O
and	O
Turner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
had	O
his	O
Scabbard	O
struck	O
from	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
prick	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Coy	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Turner	O
,	O
Cammel	O
and	O
Robinson	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Oucher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
September	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Anslow	I-pers
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
proffer	O
'd	O
for	O
Sale	O
to	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hawly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Swords	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridgdan	I-pers
:	O
It	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Presby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1019	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
Prosecuted	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Undone	O
:	O
It	O
farther	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
Branded	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
English	I-pers
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
Presby	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
stealing	O
1019	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
harboured	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
had	O
been	O
scandalous	O
for	O
giving	O
Entertainment	O
for	O
Thieves	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
proved	O
but	O
by	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bred	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
September	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Beron	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
152	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Linsy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhollows	I-place
.	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
deserting	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
recieved	O
Pay	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
wore	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
received	O
Pay	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
ran	O
from	O
his	O
Captain	O
and	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fell	O
Sick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Westcock	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
confessed	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
four	O
serge	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
two	O
Draper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Hancocks	O
House	O
,	O
lay	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
mising	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
mistrusting	O
their	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
making	O
enquiry	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Hancock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
Fisher	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Account	O
,	O
Apprehending	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
they	O
Impeached	O
each	O
other	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hopeful	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Mary	I-place
Wood	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
for	O
Trayterously	O
and	O
Feloniously	O
Clipping	O
a	O
1000	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
piece	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
as	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Six	O
pieces	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
Hore	O
had	O
delivered	O
out	O
many	O
sums	O
of	O
Moneys	O
,	O
allowing	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
every	O
Pound	O
for	O
putting	O
it	O
Off	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Moneys	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
newly	O
Clip	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
divers	O
Neighbours	O
of	O
very	O
considerable	O
Credit	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Honesty	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
August	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
and	O
Stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
silk	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
was	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
brought	O
the	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Ring	O
of	O
one	O
Judith	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
Golder	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
forth	O
with	O
brought	O
in	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
from	O
Cha	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
no	O
Defence	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-	I-place
le-bone	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
two	O
Black	O
Cows	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
with	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Gilman	B-pers
:	O
The	O
Cows	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
and	O
giving	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Indicted	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
for	O
Stealing	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
with	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
confessed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
directed	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
to	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Broker	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Goods	O
being	O
delivered	O
by	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
Peace	O
,	O
Confessed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
Moneys	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
from	O
Arnold	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
came	O
in	O
against	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
he	O
that	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
said	O
Brite	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twitnam	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
Octob	O
.	O
4	O
for	O
that	O
being	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
carrying	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
to	O
a	O
Brook	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
therein	O
,	O
choaking	O
and	O
drowning	O
it	O
with	O
Water	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
hers	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
thereof	O
in	O
a	O
Meadow	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
credited	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Alberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
Septemb	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamman	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Skull	O
of	O
a	O
Boat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
striking	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Hamman	O
died	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
Hamman	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
come	O
a	O
shore	O
,	O
Alberry	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
making	O
room	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
required	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Hamman	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
with	O
many	O
Blows	O
Alberry	O
at	O
length	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Blow	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Haslewood	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Suckden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Vauhun	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
Sept.	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
assaulted	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mackmeth	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
pushing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Mackmeth	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arising	O
betwixt	O
Haslewood	O
and	O
Mackmeth	O
,	O
going	O
both	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
fighting	O
,	O
having	O
before	O
exchang	O
'd	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mackmeth	O
receiving	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
that	O
Mackmeth	O
was	O
very	O
importunate	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
Mackmeth	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
wounded	O
.	O
Haslewood	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Collwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Agnes	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
share	O
thereof	O
to	O
one	O
Downen	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vevion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
assaulted	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Scimiter	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
running	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Hip	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Hickes	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
at	O
first	O
was	O
occasioned	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Cook	O
,	O
which	O
Cook	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
upon	O
,	O
making	O
at	O
him	O
divers	O
Blows	O
,	O
Cook	O
returning	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
.	O
Hickes	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
,	O
enquiring	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alighting	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
Hickes	O
into	O
the	O
Hip	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
made	O
many	O
Blows	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
returned	O
any	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
drew	O
his	O
Scimiter	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
knock	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
Horse	O
?	O
When	O
presently	O
divers	O
coming	O
in	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
Hickes	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
Two	O
Chirurgeons	O
probing	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
gave	O
their	O
Judgments	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Scimiter	O
,	O
being	O
exactly	O
of	O
the	O
Dimention	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Scimiter	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
third	O
Chirurgeon	O
likewise	O
probing	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
Judgment	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
triangular	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Rapier	O
bloody	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Wounded	O
Hickes	O
;	O
which	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
as	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
Impression	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
Breeches	O
which	O
the	O
wounded	O
Hickes	O
then	O
wore	O
;	O
but	O
an	O
honourable	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
(	O
who	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
had	O
took	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
who	O
gave	O
his	O
Judgment	O
,	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Rapier	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Chirurgeon	O
before	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Scimiter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
divers	O
to	O
attest	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
civil	O
Demeanour	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18th	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
taking	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Closet-door	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
another	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
design	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ell	B-pers
.	I-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Callmady	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
holland	O
Smocks	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Night-Rails	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
thereof	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
returning	O
missed	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
mistrusting	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
she	O
apprehended	O
them	O
Susan	B-pers
Callmady	I-pers
proved	O
her	O
Reputation	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
assaulted	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
one	O
s.	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Ford	O
since	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
;	O
whom	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
offered	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Incivility	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
fourth	O
person	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Companions	O
,	O
staying	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
a	O
noise	O
being	O
heard	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
returning	O
back	O
found	O
Ford	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hacking	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Ford	O
having	O
a	O
staff	O
like	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
person	O
over	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
offered	O
him	O
very	O
many	O
Abuses	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
very	O
foul	O
Language	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
four	O
aforementioned	O
Persons	O
first	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
he	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
,	O
and	O
forbear	O
such	O
Abuses	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
thereupon	O
fell	O
foul	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
great	O
sticks	O
,	O
he	O
defending	O
himself	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
ran	O
away	O
to	O
call	O
help	O
,	O
whereupon	O
two	O
Men	O
immediately	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
persons	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
he	O
lying	O
under	O
them	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
farther	O
produced	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
who	O
spake	O
very	O
highly	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
civil	O
Demeanour	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hayl	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Staines	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
August	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
300	O
Nails	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
1000	O
other	O
Nails	O
,	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Nails	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Shelswel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Hand	O
spike	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
beating	O
,	O
striking	O
and	O
kicking	O
him	O
so	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
26.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
,	O
all	O
attested	O
as	O
Cooper	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Shelswel	O
had	O
abused	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
occasion	O
for	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
which	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forth	O
with	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
August	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
Herberts	O
History	O
of	O
Henry	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Greek	O
Testaments	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
another	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Southward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Books	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
make	O
little	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
a	O
Country	O
Woman	O
;	O
which	O
bearing	O
little	O
Credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ruller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
Aug.	O
30	O
.	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Herring	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
Man	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
more	O
Souldier	O
s	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
rescue	O
the	O
Man	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
Herring	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
making	O
resistance	O
,	O
Herring	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
received	O
a	O
Cut	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Nichols	O
pretended	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
drawhis	O
Sword	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
was	O
drew	O
from	O
his	O
Sword	O
by	O
another	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Nichols	O
and	O
Crompton	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
Ruller	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
August	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Hoods	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hiring	O
Goffe	O
for	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Putney	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Cloths	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
pretending	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
orders	O
her	O
Maid	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
taking	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
Cheat	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hue	B-pers
Branford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
September	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Hue	B-pers
Branford	I-pers
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
all	O
which	O
being	O
testified	O
by	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
very	O
little	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
circumstantially	O
defending	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
with	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
with	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	O
,	O
Son	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
within	I-place
the	I-place
Liberties	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
one	O
l.	O
one	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twenty	O
one	O
l.	O
ten	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	O
le	O
Fever	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Witness	O
that	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
very	O
slender	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
patched	O
up	O
only	O
with	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
they	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Reputations	O
,	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
Conversations	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hously	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Hously	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
Sept.	O
28	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
value	O
fifteen	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
:	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Langstaff	I-pers
:	O
likewise	O
upon	O
a	O
third	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tryals	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
were	O
severally	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Will	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Hously	I-pers
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
it	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
and	O
through	O
their	O
means	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
to	O
gracious	O
as	O
to	O
defer	O
the	O
residue	O
of	O
the	O
Tryals	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
will	O
be	O
produced	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbered	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Liver	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
forthwith	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
Septem	O
.	O
4th	O
.	O
as	O
accessary	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Collwood	I-pers
in	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
ten	O
s.	O
with	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Agnes	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
major	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
grounded	O
upon	O
supposition	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
which	O
account	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
impertinent	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Eleven	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Maynards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
D	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Alberry	I-pers
,	O
Henry	O
Haslewood	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	O
Green	O
.	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hawly	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Coy	I-pers
.	O
Seven	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Heat	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
,	O
Walter	O
Hunt	O
,	O
Hue	B-pers
Branford	I-pers
.	O
One	O
to	O
be	O
Impillored	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
Peveril	O
.	O
Thirteen	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Presby	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Linsy	O
,	O
H	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Crompton	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Brown	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Collwood	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
of	O
which	O
Women	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	O
Davis	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
being	O
panneled	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Truth	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdicts	O
that	O
all	O
three	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
Goal	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
