TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
9th	O
.	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Fryday	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
11th	O
days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Gefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Aley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cannum	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Redish	I-pers
George	B-pers
Lilburn	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Fouls	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Floyer	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Meredale	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hempstead	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
For	O
Conspiring	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
thinking	O
fit	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
any	O
further	O
delay	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Challenge	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Kings	O
Council	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Keeling	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
the	O
Plot	O
or	O
Conspiracy	O
in	O
General	O
,	O
how	O
designed	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
and	O
methods	O
carried	O
on	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sundry	O
times	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Goodenough	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
discoursed	O
about	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
Trayterous	O
design	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bateman	O
approved	O
and	O
promised	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
contented	O
to	O
manage	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Twenty	O
Parts	O
into	O
which	O
the	O
City	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
an	O
Insurrection	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
agreed	O
that	O
500	O
men	O
should	O
be	O
raised	O
in	O
each	O
part	O
,	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
City	O
,	O
Savoy	O
,	O
Whitehall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Persons	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
:	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
Interest	O
.	O
Further	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
D.	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
having	O
discoursed	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Dukes	O
Servants	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Bateman	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Lee	O
that	O
the	O
late	O
Duke	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
ingage	O
in	O
the	O
Design	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
several	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
that	O
intent	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goodenough	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
approve	O
of	O
the	O
design	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
City	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
force	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
seize	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
remembrance	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
Head	O
in	O
Swithins	O
Alley	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
insisted	O
in	O
defence	O
,	O
how	O
improbable	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
discourse	O
so	O
with	O
Lee	O
or	O
Goodenough	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
were	O
a	O
Mad	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
for	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Baker	O
,	O
a	O
Broken	O
person	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
heard	O
after	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
was	O
over	O
and	O
Lee	O
was	O
gone	O
who	O
testified	O
against	O
Lee	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Plot	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
engaged	O
to	O
have	O
talked	O
of	O
State	O
affairs	O
to	O
Bateman	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
joyn	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
man	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
favourable	O
hearing	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
offer	O
materially	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Treason	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
withdrawn	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Banwell	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Daniel	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
fallen	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
party	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
,	O
pushed	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
demanded	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
Boxed	O
,	O
which	O
occasioning	O
other	O
words	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
fetched	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
assaulted	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
much	O
scuffling	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
Dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
assault	O
being	O
given	O
by	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
altogether	O
unarmed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Vice-Countess	B-pers
Chamly	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
Receiver	O
in	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
Scituate	O
in	O
Broad-street	B-place
London	O
,	O
52	O
Guineas	O
and	O
46	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
told	O
out	O
700	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Kings	O
use	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
Message	O
from	O
a	O
Woman	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
departure	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
conceived	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
some	O
persons	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
Lived	O
to	O
testifie	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Walkinton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
November	O
22d	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
along	O
Column	O
street	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
jostled	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
whereupon	O
many	O
unseemly	O
words	O
passed	O
in	O
heat	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
further	O
dispute	O
,	O
a	O
Skirmish	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
Blows	O
were	O
struck	O
on	O
either	O
part	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gervas	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
seized	O
Walkinton	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
till	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
yet	O
Jones	O
and	O
the	O
party	O
Deceased	O
continued	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
closed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
undermost	O
,	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
andgave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
Dyed	O
.	O
Jones	O
pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
no	O
Weapon	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
Walkington	O
was	O
secured	O
and	O
submitted	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
consequence	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
possibility	O
of	O
abetting	O
Jones	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
Killed	O
Smith	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
George	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
day	O
being	O
the	O
Kings	O
Birth	O
day	O
,	O
divers	O
Youths	O
making	O
Bonefires	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
upon	O
attempting	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Wood	O
one	O
Company	O
had	O
gotten	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
many	O
were	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
attack	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Blow	O
upon	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
which	O
broke	O
his	O
Skull	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
verily	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
struck	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Innocence	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
abused	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
occasioned	O
his	O
being	O
Blooded	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
he	O
produced	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
ingaged	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
fatal	O
blow	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Spurgeon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Spurgeon	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
began	O
with	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
struck	O
each	O
other	O
divers	O
blows	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
did	O
the	O
like	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
when	O
Joan	B-pers
Spurgeon	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
Aires	O
had	O
grapled	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
pummel	O
of	O
Aires	O
his	O
Sword	O
broke	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
divers	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
thrust	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
being	O
advised	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
wash	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
pump	O
that	O
stood	O
hard	O
by	O
:	O
upon	O
some	O
provoking	O
words	O
,	O
Spurgeons	O
Wife	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
after	O
many	O
blows	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
sword	O
pierced	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
made	O
the	O
first	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereupon	O
Spurgeon	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Griffen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
&	O
another	O
party	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
calling	O
for	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
blow	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Taster	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
man	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
denyed	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gucherfield	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
Apron	O
,	O
six	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
about	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
:	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Candle	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
though	O
his	O
Companion	O
escaped	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
his	O
plea	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
party	O
who	O
pursued	O
him	O
falling	O
down	O
for	O
hast	O
,	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Paragon	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
34	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Damask	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Beeling	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Convent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
Upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
often	O
imployed	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
aforementioned	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sending	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
rate	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
producing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
expressing	O
much	O
sorrow	O
for	O
his	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
This	O
being	O
supposed	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
he	O
ever	O
committed	O
of	O
that	O
nature	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Cuckin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
Gold-Rings	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
to	O
offer	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Ring	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
refusing	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
or	O
buy	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Brooks	O
held	O
her	O
in	O
discourse	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
stole	O
the	O
Rings	O
:	O
upon	O
possitive	O
Proof	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
They	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Notorious	O
Thieves	O
,	O
their	O
plea	O
of	O
Innocence	O
availed	O
them	O
nothing	O
.	O
[	O
Brooks	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Cuckin	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bovington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhollows	I-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
,	O
Two	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Evidence	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Law-Suit	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
Defamation	O
,	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
out-weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
as	O
Salts	O
,	O
Plates	O
,	O
Spoons	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hulls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
to	O
divers	O
people	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
ptewerer	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Labourer	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
opportunity	O
to	O
purloine	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
seized	O
where	O
he	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
,	O
declared	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hansworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
in	O
Cornhill	I-place
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
19.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
when	O
applying	O
himself	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
Majorr	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Men	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
drunk	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Big	O
with	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
improbable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Bettony	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Eleven	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Four	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
proposed	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
employed	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
Charles	B-pers
Gum	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridgets	I-place
alias	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
she	O
accosted	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
unseemly	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
rudeness	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
and	O
4	O
Shillings	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-Gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
over	O
a	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
following	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
sharing	O
the	O
mony	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
only	O
the	O
luck	O
to	O
take	O
Hancock	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
escaping	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
mony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
a	O
Ninepence	O
of	O
that	O
mony	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pilferer	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
And	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
valued	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
entertained	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Week	O
(	O
she	O
had	O
payed	O
for	O
)	O
was	O
expired	O
,	O
absented	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
pulling	O
her	O
Hood	O
over	O
her	O
eyes	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
:	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
marryed	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
Anno	O
1672	O
.	O
At	O
St.	O
James	O
Dukes-place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
1684.	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Godfry	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Chappel	O
in	O
Kentish	I-place
Town	I-place
,	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
marriage	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
other	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
his	O
cohabiting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coroborating	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Pancras	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indictedfor	O
Robing	O
one	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
valued	O
8	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
four	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Boxes	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
,	O
two	O
Ivory	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
concerned	O
therein	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
Committed	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
no	O
noise	O
made	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
a	O
receptacle	O
of	O
such	O
idle	O
Fellows	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
as	O
accessary	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pullet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarken-well	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Grocers	B-place
Hall	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Butler	O
missing	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
issued	O
out	O
to	O
apprehend	O
divers	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
into	O
whose	O
hands	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
;	O
going	O
into	O
Berry-street	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
such	O
suspected	O
persons	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
Lodge	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
opposition	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
search	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
under	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
a	O
Stocking	O
,	O
which	O
Bag	O
and	O
Stocking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
likewise	O
did	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
149	O
Knots	O
of	O
Glaziers	O
Lead	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
24	O
s.	O
;	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
some	O
parcels	O
of	O
Window	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
one	O
piece	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
affirmed	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
of	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
without	O
,	O
and	O
cohse-quently	O
it	O
being	O
no	O
Felony	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
,	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
valued	O
an	O
56	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Cruse	I-pers
;	O
in	O
Court	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
and	O
cloathing	O
her	O
,	O
lent	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
Cakes	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
bad	O
returns	O
of	O
that	O
kindness	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
absent	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Cup	O
in	O
Lumbard-street	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
compassionated	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Mitigation	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
finding	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
penalty	O
of	O
Petti-lurceny	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pots	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Standish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
:	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
drink	O
,	O
watched	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Pots	O
that	O
stood	O
upon	O
a	O
side	O
Dresser	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
e	O
'	O
r	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
stowed	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
redeem	O
his	O
Pledge	O
,	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
he	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
and	O
two	O
odd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Blanshaw	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
divers	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
upon	O
notice	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
gotten	O
some	O
odd	O
ones	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
own	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
alledged	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
pavement	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
expose	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
as	O
so	O
his	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Leonard	B-pers
Bate	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
Dorothy	B-pers
England	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
party	O
Jury	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
half	O
Natives	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Aliens	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Meridale	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Morisco	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boliby	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Romain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lassoon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Legoss	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Monau	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	O
Le-count	O
,	O
Upon	O
this	O
Jury	O
,	O
having	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
England	I-pers
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
house	O
,	O
had	O
before	O
the	O
grand	O
assault	O
and	O
violence	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
Indicted	O
)	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
roughly	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Being	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seemingly	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
likewise	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
came	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
much	O
strugling	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
,	O
he	O
over	O
powered	O
and	O
penetrated	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Two	O
Midwives	O
were	O
likewise	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
affirmed	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Virginity	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
bad	O
usage	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
long	O
sickness	O
or	O
indisposition	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
bruises	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
Testimony	O
to	O
ballance	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
by	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
committed	O
that	O
violence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
mony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
discovered	O
it	O
in	O
almost	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
which	O
objection	O
being	O
answered	O
and	O
further	O
testimony	O
of	O
his	O
rudeness	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Charge	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
withdrawing	O
returned	O
within	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Felony	O
as	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ironmonger-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
and	O
places	O
,	O
did	O
Conspire	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
promising	O
to	O
be	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Assisting	O
in	O
raising	O
men	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valued	O
at	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
confessed	O
he	O
Sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dry	O
a	O
Lottery	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
four	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
of	O
which	O
Money	O
he	O
played	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
indeavoured	O
to	O
evade	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
Lent	O
Money	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
appear	O
,	O
he	O
proceeded	O
to	O
alledge	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
being	O
rendered	O
invaild	O
by	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
:	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
indictments	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herd	I-pers
alias	O
Racket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
uttering	O
divers	O
Irreverent	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
His	O
most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
reflecting	O
on	O
the	O
Established	O
Government	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
not	O
fitting	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
to	O
be	O
inserted	O
)	O
which	O
words	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Prostitute	O
,	O
her	O
denial	O
weighed	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jeffers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
Irreverent	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
words	O
against	O
His	O
most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Steward	O
of	O
Westminster	O
for	O
Picking	O
a	O
Pocket	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
company	O
she	O
,	O
spoke	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
little	O
defence	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Meggs	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Knots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Diodate	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
Cabinet	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
Conscious	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
then	O
Locked	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
proper	O
Goods	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
,	O
prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
about	O
30	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tunck	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
time	O
surprized	O
,	O
attemptingto	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
conjectured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
charged	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
after	O
much	O
shifting	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
evasions	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
she	O
supposed	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Trunck	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
3	O
Rings	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
those	O
Rings	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
and	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
whereupon	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stapely	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hoggs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Page	I-pers
:	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
them	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Felonys	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Blisset	O
of	O
Islington	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
Stapely	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
imployed	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
though	O
favoured	O
with	O
the	O
penalty	O
of	O
Perry	O
Larceny	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Stapely	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Taylor	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Savory	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hasleburg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Drawers	O
and	O
2	O
Woolen	O
Wastcoats	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
appearing	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
rather	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
a	O
Line	O
in	O
the	O
Gallery	O
or	O
Balcony	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
Drink	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Tallow-Chandlers	O
Shop	O
,	O
whilst	O
She	O
was	O
buying	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Compter	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
set	O
on	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
the	O
Boy	O
Mony	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
better	O
incouragement	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
four	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Pullets	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Johncock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Buff	O
Coat	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Carbine	O
Belt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
;	O
On	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Pied	O
Bull	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	O
,	O
where	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
yet	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Doors	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
were	O
Locked	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Fringe	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sucklin	I-pers
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
valued	O
2	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
be	O
below	O
,	O
were	O
shewed	O
up	O
staires	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
continued	O
till	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
but	O
the	O
Fringe	O
that	O
incompassed	O
the	O
Valans	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
testimony	O
of	O
their	O
honest	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
a	O
gainst	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
Buy	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
laid	O
the	O
Hood	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
going	O
away	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
neither	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Though	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
,	O
nor	O
appearing	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Goreing	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
two	O
prostitutes	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
one	O
Morgans	O
in	O
White-Fryers	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
played	O
upon	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
making	O
him	O
Drunk	O
,	O
they	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
slipped	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
confessing	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
therein	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Hadis	B-pers
Legreen	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstans	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
some	O
words	O
a	O
Scufle	O
happened	O
in	O
Flowerdelis	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
Fleet-street	I-place
between	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Sword	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonington	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
charged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
An	O
Indictment	O
being	O
preferred	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
violence	O
and	O
falsly	O
imprisoning	O
William	B-pers
Chanay	I-pers
Mercer	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Lane	I-place
London	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Davis	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
;	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Hays	O
and	O
Holland	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
where	O
Hays	O
in	O
a	O
seeming	O
consternation	O
,	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
repeated	O
some	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
accused	O
for	O
them	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
discover	O
his	O
Author	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
himself	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Holland	O
entering	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Arrested	O
and	O
Hurried	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
where	O
Hays	O
pressed	O
him	O
seeing	O
the	O
matter	O
might	O
be	O
still	O
hush	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
pacifie	O
Holland	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
pretended	O
himself	O
a	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Guard	O
)	O
with	O
mony	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
they	O
hurried	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
White-Hall	O
,	O
pretendingly	O
to	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
many	O
intreaties	O
of	O
Hays	O
and	O
threats	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
,	O
where	O
meeting	O
with	O
Davis	O
and	O
Price	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
himself	O
a	O
Barrister	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
up	O
a	O
Scrivener	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
extorted	O
a	O
Bond	O
and	O
judgment	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Penalty	O
400	O
l.	O
to	O
pay	O
100	O
l.	O
Which	O
were	O
likewise	O
signed	O
by	O
Hays	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Cheat	O
being	O
discovered	O
upon	O
Hollands	O
sending	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
Silks	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
proof	O
(	O
though	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
)	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Agnes	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Robery	O
Committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Leonel	B-pers
Gatford	I-pers
in	O
Lime	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
stealing	O
Rings	O
,	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
300	O
l.	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
appeared	O
that	O
two	O
person	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gatfords	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
Wearing	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
pretending	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Gatford	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
scrupling	O
to	O
admit	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Davis	O
,	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
seizing	O
her	O
with	O
violence	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
her	O
Coat	O
over	O
her	O
head	O
and	O
then	O
calling	O
his	O
Companion	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jack	O
:	O
they	O
riffled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seized	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
Mistress	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
bound	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
departed	O
with	O
many	O
threats	O
if	O
they	O
stir	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
being	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
:	O
The	O
Thieves	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
Davis	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Walton	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
with	O
the	O
posie	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Margeret	O
Harris	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Walton	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
by	O
one	O
Mr	O
Hamlin	O
,	O
whom	O
Agnes	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
taking	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
for	O
Davis	O
unawares	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
secure	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
shared	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Holland	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
demanding	O
how	O
he	O
durst	O
appear	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
least	O
he	O
ruin	O
both	O
himself	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
by	O
this	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
material	O
matters	O
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Davis	O
and	O
Holland	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
and	O
Agnes	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
their	O
Confederate	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
presented	O
his	O
humble	O
Petition	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
allowed	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Pen	O
Ink	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
request	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
a	O
Keeper	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Brampston	I-pers
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
Auruiels	O
Peircy	O
Wiseman	O
,	O
pleaded	O
this	O
Sessions	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
Papers	O
of	O
Gloves	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
cases	O
.	O
These	O
being	O
the	O
Summ	O
of	O
the	O
Tryals	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Ten	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cuckley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spurgeon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Tranporsted	O
Four	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
desiring	O
the	O
same	O
viz	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Staply	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Nine	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hainsworth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Agnes	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Banwell	I-pers
,	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Bate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
;	O
the	O
latter	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
Perilarcenaries	O
,	O
Eleven	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
from	O
Ludgate	O
to	O
Charig-Cross	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
James	O
Griffin	O
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Timotby	O
Scarborugh	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Savory	I-pers
.	O
For	O
speaking	O
Scandalous	O
Words	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jeffers	I-pers
Fined	I-pers
10	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Session	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herd	I-pers
Fined	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
upon	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
.	O
