TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
of	O
peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Fryday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
1684	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smyth	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Honylove	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Bernard	B-pers
Minn	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
Kenlem	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ginne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Levis	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sherbrook	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
For	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Bridal	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Rainsford	B-pers
Waterhouse	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltsby	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
William	B-pers
Shirly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
proceedings	O
a	O
nst	O
the	O
prisoners	O
&	O
c.	O
ae	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wickham	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
beakers	O
Value	O
10l	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
Value	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Trencher	O
Plate	O
,	O
Value	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Porrenger	O
Value	O
40s	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wye	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wye	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
plate	O
before	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
left	O
her	O
service	O
,	O
selling	O
the	O
Trencher	O
plate	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Arlington	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
for	O
38s	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
Rings	O
Valued	O
at	O
32s	O
.	O
but	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Porringer	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
questioned	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
lad	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lead	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
after	O
some	O
examination	O
did	O
likewise	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Hoods	O
,	O
Scarves	O
,	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Golves	O
,	O
Forehead	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
hankering	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
pretending	O
a	O
frivolous	O
excuse	O
of	O
bespeaking	O
full-yards	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Hopkins	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Hill	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
as	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspition	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
being	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
possession	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bramstone	I-pers
Indicted	O
at	O
Common-Law	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquistion	O
for	O
Killing	O
Aurelius	B-pers
Perte	I-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lyon	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Fetter	I-place
Lane	I-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
general	O
exception	O
in	O
case	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
jurors	O
should	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
allowed	O
and	O
twelve	O
new	O
Sworn	O
,	O
Mr.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ton	O
Councelor	O
at	O
Law	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictments	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
Richard	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Tavern	O
before	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
was	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
together	O
in	O
loving	O
and	O
friendly	O
manner	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
divers	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
a	O
Club	O
being	O
usually	O
held	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
several	O
Bottles	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
leaving	O
them	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
at	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
drinking	O
of	O
another	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
coming	O
up	O
found	O
them	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Mony	O
that	O
was	O
dropped	O
,	O
who	O
bidding	O
him	O
begon	O
,	O
he	O
withdrew	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Bell	O
ringing	O
he	O
soon	O
and	O
observing	O
them	O
standing	O
,	O
and	O
facing	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
intrusting	O
some	O
Ruff	O
words	O
might	O
have	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
him	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
to	O
retire	O
he	O
This	O
being	O
deposed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smart	O
was	O
Sworn	O
in	O
to	O
gave	O
evidence	O
that	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
upon	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
he	O
rose	O
and	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
had	O
let	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
above	O
a	O
another	O
Chirurgeon	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
give	O
assistance	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Wound	O
declared	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
burning	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
soon	O
perceived	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
the	O
Wound	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
a	O
considerable	O
depth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
conjectures	O
failed	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
of	O
that	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
his	O
intimate	O
friend	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
intirely	O
loved	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Play-house	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
company	O
leaving	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
even	O
and	O
odd	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
lost	O
,	O
whereat	O
he	O
seemed	O
displeased	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
yeild	O
it	O
but	O
gave	O
him	O
many	O
rough	O
words	O
whereat	O
to	O
avoid	O
further	O
dispute	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Drawer	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
departed	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
came	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
still	O
pressing	O
forward	O
rushed	O
on	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
when	O
finding	O
himself	O
Wounded	O
he	O
cryed	O
,	O
Jack	O
you	O
have	O
touched	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
Push	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
himself	O
faint	O
,	O
he	O
retreated	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
death	O
Wound	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
replyed	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
Perrey	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
opening	O
his	O
Bosom	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Sword	O
had	O
entered	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
Bleeding	O
inwards	O
,	O
he	O
sucked	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
that	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
with	O
all	O
speed	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
none	O
came	O
went	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
voluntarily	O
returned	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
was	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
expressing	O
great	O
sorrow	O
for	O
the	O
misfortune	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
means	O
might	O
be	O
used	O
for	O
saving	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
his	O
friend	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
gave	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
he	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
upon	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
much	O
friendship	O
appeared	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
participate	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stiles	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
them	O
at	O
Garraways	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
appeared	O
the	O
greatest	O
friendship	O
imaginable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Perto	O
's	O
in	O
Abb-Church-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
dined	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
till	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
friendly	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
declared	O
as	O
much	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
he	O
having	O
met	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Derbyshire	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
good	O
friends	O
,	O
they	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
play	O
together	O
,	O
C	O
Turner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bostock	O
gave	O
testimony	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
being	O
thus	O
for	O
examined	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bramstone	O
called	O
Sir	O
Edward	O
Turner	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
D	O
,	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Brown	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
,	O
C	O
Turner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sparrow	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lacy	O
to	O
who	O
unanimously	O
declared	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
mild	O
temper	O
and	O
courteous	O
behaviour	O
,	O
being	O
always	O
inclinable	O
rather	O
to	O
prevent	O
than	O
to	O
provoke	O
quarrels	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
observed	O
much	O
love	O
and	O
friendship	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
summed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
former	O
malice	O
,	O
appearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
only	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Langworth	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
was	O
delivered	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
strangled	O
her	O
Child	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
String	O
,	O
putting	O
it	O
so	O
Murthered	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
discovery	O
of	O
her	O
delivery	O
,	O
she	O
owning	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
confessing	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
stop	O
its	O
Crying	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
in	O
court	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
indevoured	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
read	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
death	O
to	O
any	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
delivered	O
of	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Issue	O
dead	O
and	O
conceal	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
upon	O
a	O
Childs	O
being	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Garret	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
;	O
that	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
lately	O
delivered	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
Child-bed	O
Woman	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
dis	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
dead	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Infant	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
apparently	O
been	O
delivered	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
her	O
condition	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
adjacent	O
habitation	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berril	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Dec	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
and	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
rising	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
yet	O
would	O
they	O
not	O
give	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
it	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
Berril	O
being	O
brusied	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
death	O
that	O
Day	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
end	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
strangers	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
no	O
former	O
grudge	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
what	O
happened	O
was	O
occasion	O
'd	O
through	O
sudden	O
heat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Phileman	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bullocks	O
Valued	O
at	O
17s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Jan	O
one	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Farrier	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
his	O
arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
alias	O
Irish	B-pers
Kate	I-pers
alias	O
Catherine	B-pers
Irise	I-pers
alias	O
Twford	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Guinneys	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Dec	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
fellow	O
servant	O
s	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Essex	O
Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
fore-mentioned	O
parcel	O
of	O
Guinneys	O
into	O
her	O
Role	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
convey	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
she	O
watched	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Role	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
ask	O
what	O
hour	O
it	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
after	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
yet	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
abrupt	O
leaving	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
some	O
words	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
her	O
speak	O
in	O
her	O
dispraise	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
light	O
fame	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merreday	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Indian	O
silk	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
silks	O
,	O
having	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
piece	O
valued	O
at	O
4l	O
.	O
in	O
liew	O
of	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
up	O
her	O
bundle	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
being	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
bargained	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
finding	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
she	O
did	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
alledging	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
unknowingly	O
amongst	O
her	O
other	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
bundle	O
,	O
restoring	O
it	O
assoon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
,	O
producing	O
divers	O
to	O
give	O
testimony	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
,	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
designed	O
theft	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
conversant	O
in	O
Halls	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
People	O
busie	O
,	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
possess	O
himself	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
sending	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
upon	O
suspition	O
,	O
which	O
obliged	O
his	O
Comerade	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
safety	O
to	O
discover	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
resolutely	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
assoon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
missed	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
other	O
reason	O
to	O
absent	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
challenged	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
pregnant	O
reasons	O
to	O
believe	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
searge	O
coat	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
arraignment	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
one	O
Nurse	O
Joans	O
,	O
watched	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
nail	O
whereon	O
it	O
hung	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
escape	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
perceived	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
although	O
he	O
used	O
many	O
excuses	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Court	O
pl	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Young	O
Offender	O
,	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
within	O
the	O
statute	O
of	O
Pettelarcinary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Jan	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
suits	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
a	O
Person	O
Condemned	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
Executed	O
,	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
time	O
discovered	O
,	O
that	O
Biggs	O
Robbed	O
the	O
house	O
giving	O
directions	O
how	O
and	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
those	O
directions	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
and	O
a	O
wastcoat	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
compound	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
raise	O
money	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denyed	O
all	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Hounds-ditch	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
accidentally	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
calling	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
frequent	O
inhabiter	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
artifice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Caborn	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
diminishing	O
,	O
with	O
sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
,	O
the	O
lawful	O
and	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
some	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
worked	O
privately	O
,	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
to	O
melt	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
after	O
,	O
much	O
difficulty	O
getting	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheers	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Money	O
newly	O
Clipped	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
90l	O
.	O
with	O
melting	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
suitable	O
to	O
that	O
unlawful	O
practice	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
Clippings	O
there	O
found	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
90	O
Ounces	O
,	O
which	O
plainness	O
of	O
fact	O
caused	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignments	O
to	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
instance	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
of	O
one	O
Elinor	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
kept	O
him	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Indicted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
retract	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
himself	O
again	O
confessing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
declaring	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
into	O
that	O
snare	O
by	O
evil	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
too	O
much	O
hearkned	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
in	O
Alderman-bury	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
swop't	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Cutlers	O
near	O
Charing-cross	O
for	O
another	O
Sword	O
and	O
a	O
Guinney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
and	O
not	O
sensible	O
,	O
but	O
waiting	O
on	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
him	O
in	O
hast	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
ashamed	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
trivial	O
excuse	O
availed	O
him	O
little	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
jury	O
upon	O
return	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Clouts	O
,	O
8	O
Bibs	O
,	O
8	O
Forehead	O
Cloths	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
and	O
three	O
Laced	O
Head-dressings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
As	O
likewise	O
28s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Lace	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
its	O
being	O
challenged	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Barber	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
party	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Heath	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
supposed	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
bought	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Monys	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
left	O
her	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jebb	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ed	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
as	O
knowing	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
lay	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
missed	O
and	O
search	O
for	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
upon	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
part	O
she	O
had	O
house	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Party	O
Robbed	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
recovering	O
11	O
l.	O
to	O
that	O
charge	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
felony	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
but	O
surrended	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
pretence	O
and	O
weighing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harrock	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinney	O
and	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Tho	O
M	O
del	O
at	O
the	O
Ax	B-place
in	O
Alderman-bury	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
helper	O
to	O
the	O
Ostler	O
,	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
the	O
Key	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
specified	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
taxed	O
and	O
carryed	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
Guinney	O
and	O
a	O
Crown-piece	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Guinney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Crown-piece	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emm	B-pers
Sanby	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Sanby	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
25s	O
.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
sometime	O
after	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
owning	O
so	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gander	O
and	O
a	O
Geese	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
yard	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lyley	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Proprietor	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
party	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Basons	O
,	O
6	O
Raysors	O
,	O
30	O
Porringers	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
trimming	O
Towel	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
of	O
Jan.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
entred	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
youth	O
,	O
and	O
tracked	O
in	O
the	O
Snow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
having	O
dropped	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
almost	O
all	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
restored	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
mercy	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
Verdict	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
fleece	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Dozen	O
of	O
plate	O
Buttons	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Magenis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
loosing	O
the	O
things	O
absented	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
seal	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Witness	O
conjectured	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
but	O
he	O
alledging	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
seal	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Taylors	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
25s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Glasspool	I-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Glasspool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
to	O
eat	O
Roast-beef	O
,	O
she	O
snacht	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
purse	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
dropped	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
latter	O
as	O
accessory	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Golden	O
cross	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Meddal	O
,	O
inlayed	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
Justin	B-pers
MacCartis	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
Murphy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stollen	O
the	O
goods	O
specified	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Doyle	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
expose	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
only	O
alledging	O
that	O
his	O
Companion	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Murphy	O
only	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
7	O
pence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
later	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
after	O
many	O
excuses	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
acknowledged	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
three	O
Childrens	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Pin-cushions	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
two	O
shillings	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Dec	O
taking	O
her	O
opportunity	O
when	O
Charles	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
entered	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
nor	O
any	O
Testimony	O
of	O
her	O
honest	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
though	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Fulham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Panmer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
;	O
after	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
desired	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Lad	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
their	O
departure	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
upon	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
absented	O
his	O
Masters	O
Service	O
for	O
many	O
day	O
his	O
single	O
testimony	O
weighed	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
so	O
the	O
Conviction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
no	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cart	O
Wheel	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
5s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
grounds	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
of	O
South	B-place
Mimms	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
tha	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Tire	O
Irons	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
on	O
Michael	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
sandy	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
owner	O
had	O
knowledge	O
of	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
dispose	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Salt	O
and	O
chid	O
him	O
for	O
making	O
it	O
know	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Evidence	O
,	O
although	O
they	O
used	O
many	O
endeavours	O
to	O
excuse	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pettelarcinary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
panel	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Larente	I-pers
of	O
Hanworth	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Pannel	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gander	O
hanging	O
at	O
his	O
girdle	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Pannel	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Spaniel	O
Bitch	O
killed	O
the	O
Gander	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Spanniel	O
had	O
been	O
shot	O
upon	O
which	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
circumstances	O
that	O
offered	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fincham	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
valued	O
at	O
18l	O
.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Wool-church	I-place
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
1681	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
action	O
of	O
Trover	O
being	O
brought	O
,	O
Unkle	O
had	O
payed	O
16l	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
composition	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
satisfying	O
Richardson	O
,	O
he	O
now	O
made	O
his	O
prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
severely	O
repremanded	O
for	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
stifle	O
a	O
Fellony	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Laurence-lane	I-place
,	O
valued	O
at	O
6l	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
further	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
reputation	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Weaver	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harland	I-pers
near	O
Pauls-wharf	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
observing	O
it	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
espied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Celler	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
a	O
Brass-Cock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
thence	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Williams	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
cock	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Craford	I-pers
a	O
scotch	O
schismatick	O
,	O
having	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
rendered	O
him	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
obstinately	O
refusing	O
it	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
tender	O
perversely	O
pretending	O
a	O
scruple	O
of	O
conscience	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
statute	O
of	O
Premunire	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
when	O
as	O
Fraisier	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
refused	O
so	O
lawful	O
and	O
reasonable	O
a	O
complyance	O
with	O
the	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
duty	O
to	O
his	O
Prince	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
evil	O
consequences	O
,	O
attending	O
his	O
obstinacy	O
,	O
was	O
contented	O
to	O
wave	O
his	O
scrupilosities	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Oath	O
before-mentioned	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bags	O
of	O
Nailes	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
5l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
8d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Kings	O
stores	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Partridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Nailes	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Broad-Arrow	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
moulded	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
signature	O
,	O
which	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Kings	O
Nailes	O
have	O
impressed	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
up	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
WAR	O
called	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
near	O
Chaham	O
,	O
bringing	O
divers	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
bought	O
the	O
Iron-work	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
unless	O
the	O
Marks	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
stealing	O
a	O
S	O
valued	O
25s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
P	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
13	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
finding	O
the	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cross	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
which	O
Head	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
they	O
apparently	O
had	O
killed	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pettelarcinary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Toulson	I-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Toulson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bedding	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	O
berry	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
sale	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
alledged	O
that	O
her	O
Land	O
ladies	O
daughter	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
sufficient	O
excuse	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
yards	O
of	O
Sale-cloath	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Cloath	O
being	O
missed	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
,	O
one	O
Bolt	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Hoggs	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Cole	O
threw	O
down	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Evidence	O
although	O
they	O
alledged	O
,	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
for	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pettelarcinary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Oates	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
excuse	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
person	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
Committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chard	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
give	O
his	O
Horse	O
Hay	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
unwillingly	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
obliged	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Hayloft	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
,	O
stopping	O
her	O
mouth	O
when	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
no	O
timely	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
declaring	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
owning	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
instance	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
living	O
at	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
having	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
that	O
point	O
by	O
giving	O
a	O
large	O
Testimony	O
of	O
his	O
civil	O
behaviour	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Johns	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
in	O
stay	O
of	O
Execution	O
upon	O
their	O
late	O
sentence	O
,	O
produced	O
severally	O
His	O
Majesties	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
allowed	O
,	O
they	O
Pleaded	O
then	O
upon	O
their	O
knees	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
admonished	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
of	O
such	O
rashness	O
as	O
had	O
caused	O
them	O
much	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
above	O
all	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
the	O
future	O
business	O
of	O
their	O
lives	O
,	O
to	O
express	O
their	O
gratitude	O
and	O
extraordinary	O
acknowledgement	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Grace	O
and	O
Princely	O
compassion	O
,	O
in	O
behaving	O
themselves	O
respectfully	O
,	O
shewing	O
their	O
Duty	O
and	O
Loyalty	O
on	O
all	O
occasions	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Lordship	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Collonel	O
Webb	O
had	O
signalized	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
turbulent	O
and	O
staggering	O
times	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Papers	O
of	O
Gloves	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Officers	O
immediately	O
attending	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
is	O
usual	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mongomery	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
having	O
obtained	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
offered	O
it	O
the	O
17th	O
instant	O
in	O
barr	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
allowed	O
,	O
pleading	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
reminded	O
of	O
the	O
heinousness	O
of	O
his	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
admonished	O
to	O
behave	O
himself	O
circumspectly	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
vindicating	O
a	O
mistaken	O
honour	O
to	O
involve	O
himself	O
in	O
quarrels	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
occasion	O
the	O
shedding	O
of	O
innocent	O
Blood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
he	O
gave	O
Gloves	O
,	O
as	O
Esq	O
;	O
St.	O
Johns	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
A	O
complaint	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
an	O
Indictment	O
was	O
grounded	O
,	O
being	O
exhibited	O
against	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
Steward	O
of	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
a	O
further	O
time	O
to	O
try	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
giving	O
security	O
,	O
was	O
allowed	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Sir	O
James	O
Hacket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
,	O
prayed	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
answered	O
that	O
an	O
Appeal	O
being	O
already	O
brought	O
and	O
allowed	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
granted	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
prayer	O
Recorded	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
practicable	O
in	O
such	O
cases	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
admitted	O
to	O
bail	O
himself	O
,	O
entring	O
into	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
his	O
sureties	O
500	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
by	O
his	O
Council	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
Bar	O
the	O
succeeding	O
Term	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bramstone	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
convicted	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
prayed	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
allowed	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
Kings	O
Warrant	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
His	O
Majesty	O
signified	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
penalty	O
should	O
be	O
suspended	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
further	O
pleasure	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
bailed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
having	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
rendered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
refusing	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
refusal	O
was	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Recorded	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
remanded	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Tryal	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
His	O
plea	O
in	O
a	O
canting	O
Tone	O
,	O
being	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
promissory	O
Oath	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
the	O
5	O
persons	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
were	O
John	O
Wickham	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hoskins	O
,	O
John	O
Clark	O
,	O
Emm	O
Sanbie	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Toulson	O
.	O
The	O
5	O
persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
were	O
John	O
Harrock	O
,	O
William	O
Finchman	O
,	O
Richard	O
Scot	O
,	O
Frances	O
Abraham	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Scarlet	O
.	O
The	O
9	O
Persons	O
that	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
Abraham	O
Biggs	O
,	O
Richard	O
Caborn	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Redman	O
,	O
Phileman	O
Adams	O
,	O
Dorcas	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Waller	O
,	O
Jane	O
Langworth	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Stoakes	O
,	O
and	O
Katherine	O
Cotterel	O
.	O
The	O
11	O
Persons	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
Richard	O
Williams	O
,	O
David	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Murphey	O
,	O
George	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Jacob	O
Clark	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Shipley	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
George	O
Laurence	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Dun	O
,	O
Ambros	O
Hog	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Cole	O
.	O
Andrew	O
Craford	O
being	O
convicted	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
confinement	O
in	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
KING	O
'S	O
pleasure	O
.	O
