TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
The	O
14th	O
.	O
and	O
15th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
April	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
and	O
15th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rool	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Crisdell	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sheepheard	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hudgbout	I-pers
James	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
James	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dunton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
,	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
1	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
April	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
Widdow	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
drawing	O
the	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Masters	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
giving	O
very	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Antholins	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
March	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Paragon	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Summers	B-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
marching	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
soon	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
mean	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Everidge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Thomas	I-place
the	I-place
Apostles	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
about	O
Six	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
(	O
March	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Leeson	O
dyed	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Carmen	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
,	O
were	O
driving	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
turning	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
(	O
unseen	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
was	O
accidently	O
catch	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
grinding	O
its	O
Face	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Carmen	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
March	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Mallinton	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
the	O
said	O
Mallinton	O
dyed	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mallinton	O
being	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
his	O
Masters	O
Shop	O
,	O
was	O
Assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Mallinton	O
declared	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
made	O
manifest	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
unhappily	O
given	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
George	B-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Grandison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
from	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
Four	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
their	O
respective	O
Masters	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbord	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Blackston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
his	O
Right-Pap	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Blackston	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
wounded	O
,	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
dress	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Fighting	O
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
when	O
and	O
where	O
Black-stone	O
was	O
Killed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Letter	O
likewise	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
understanding	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Blackston	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
innocent	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
alone	O
had	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
only	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
occasioned	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
enforcing	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
alias	O
Wright	B-pers
,	O
o	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Benedick	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
April	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Earle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Earle	O
apprehending	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
run	O
many	O
spaces	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
an	O
old	O
Offendor	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Petty-coat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Pooler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
whilst	O
one	O
was	O
prizing	O
a	O
Childs	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
sliped	O
away	O
the	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
and	O
forthwith	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pooler	O
perceiving	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
them	O
,	O
seizes	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
deny	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Guinua	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
March	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
riding	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
beating	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
bruise	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
he	O
dyed	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Powel	O
walking	O
in	O
a	O
Footpath	O
,	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
at	O
a	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
beat	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
by	O
the	O
hinder	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
horse	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
spake	O
word	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Chirurgeons	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
wounds	O
he	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
occasioned	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
objecting	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
road	O
which	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
aggravation	O
to	O
his	O
crime	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
pretended	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
over	O
ruled	O
by	O
his	O
horse	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
head-strong	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Point	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Point-Lace	O
.	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Simon	B-pers
Luttrill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Family	O
going	O
all	O
abroad	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Servant	O
only	O
excepted	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
abroad	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
aggravation	O
of	O
their	O
Suspition	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
some	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
demanded	O
therefor	O
,	O
had	O
often	O
denyed	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
being	O
grounded	O
on	O
suspition	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Portinger	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
that	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
going	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
locking	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Alarum	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
before	O
reb	O
ted	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
invited	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Thieves	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
called	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
and	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matjellons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
search	O
for	O
her	O
money	O
missed	O
the	O
Sum	O
cisied	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Drawer	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
making	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Steers	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Rose	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Higgison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
White	B-place
Chappell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Rackit	I-pers
,	O
an	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
Five	O
Bags	O
of	O
Salt-Teter	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
confes	O
'd	O
they	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
aforesaid	O
Bags	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
themeans	O
had	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
only	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Majesties	O
pay	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
his	O
Captain	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
pay	O
diserted	O
his	O
Majestics	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
some	O
Twenty	O
Miles	O
from	O
his	O
Quarters	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Toy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
,	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Robing	O
him	O
of	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Saywell	O
the	O
person	O
Robed	O
,	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Toy	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
first	O
Kicking	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
afterwards	O
Robed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
aforesaid	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Design	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
over-much	O
Drinking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles's-Cripple-gate	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
Eighteen	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Nineteen	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
Locking	O
his	O
Doors	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
rose	O
at	O
Five	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
his	O
Doors	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pewterer	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
proffered	O
them	O
,	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Pewter	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pewterer	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
usual	O
Evasion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Morgan	B-pers
Pully	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
:	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
escape	O
them	O
leap	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Window	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
(	O
and	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Pharoh	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
on	O
his	O
Right-Side	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Pharoh	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
:	O
The	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Pharoh	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
did	O
causually	O
affront	O
Jone	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
complaining	O
of	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
Jones	O
presently	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Passion	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
biding	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Pharoh	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
first	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
passing	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Rapier	O
,	O
instantly	O
wounded	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
Pharoh	O
forthwith	O
dyed	O
;	O
but	O
little	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Butler	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
which	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
Jones	O
had	O
Killed	O
Pharoh	O
,	O
Butler	O
should	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
Butler	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
excusing	O
himself	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
hundred	O
Yardsoff	O
when	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
;	O
producing	O
likewise	O
Evidence	O
for	O
restification	O
of	O
his	O
civil	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Demeanour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Allamod	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
formerly	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bogling	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Cupbord-cloath	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Fleming	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
were	O
conveyed	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
further	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
produced	O
many	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
repute	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
honestly	O
with	O
all	O
People	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
dealing	O
with	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
desisted	O
her	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
absenting	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
declared	O
to	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
for	O
bringing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Flemming	O
indisgrace	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
small	O
piece	O
about	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
two	O
fingers	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
giving	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
litigious	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
forthwith	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stoke-Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Periwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
only	O
bound	O
over	O
upon	O
suspition	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
repute	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
further	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Condrel	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Godfry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
going	O
abroad	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Watches	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
missed	O
his	O
Watches	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
after	O
strict	O
enquiry	O
made	O
therefor	O
,	O
he	O
understood	O
that	O
Condrel	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Watch	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
forth	O
with	O
procured	O
his	O
apprehension	O
:	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
appearing	O
likewise	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
attesting	O
that	O
Condrel	O
did	O
bring	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Arnold	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
present	O
as	O
a	O
Companion	O
to	O
Condrel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Condrel	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offendor	O
and	O
branded	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
refuting	O
his	O
charge	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Arnold	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
forthwith	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Condrel	I-pers
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Higison	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Seven	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbord	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Hall	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Hill	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Goodwin	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Charick	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Hundred	O
Forty	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Eight	O
Pound	O
.	O
Divers	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
His	O
Majestys	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
with	O
out	O
having	O
their	O
Tryals	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
laid	O
claim	O
thereto	O
after	O
Conviction	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Condril	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Stam	O
ford	O
was	O
likewise	O
discharged	O
by	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Five	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Toy	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Church-hill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Crofis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
,	O
Rebeckab	O
Rose	O
.	O
But	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebeckah	O
Rose	O
pleading	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Empaneled	O
to	O
make	O
search	O
thereof	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
their	O
Virdict	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
affirmative	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
the	O
were	O
delivered	O
.	O
The	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Wall	O
for	O
runing	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
was	O
defered	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
