TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
24th	O
.	O
25th	O
.	O
and	O
26th	O
,	O
days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
25th	O
.	O
and	O
26th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lambard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bon	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Corneck	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Prattle	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
Lancelot	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Gidly	B-pers
Cranwell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Row	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Cades	I-pers
Fisher	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Crawly	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Min	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Tanner	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
H.	B-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
(	O
February	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
R.	B-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
valued	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
M	O
-	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
space	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
Dispute	O
arising	O
betwixt	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
and	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Gaming	O
together	O
,	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
giving	O
the	O
other	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
foul	O
,	O
and	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
baring	O
with	O
great	O
Patience	O
,	O
returning	O
him	O
very	O
good	O
words	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
satisfied	O
therewith	O
pressing	O
on	O
to	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
;	O
the	O
Coroner	O
likewise	O
attesting	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
produced	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
and	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
Gameing	O
together	O
,	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
having	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
grew	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
obliged	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
to	O
have	O
played	O
longer	O
;	O
swearing	O
at	O
a	O
prodigious	O
rate	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
giving	O
him	O
very	O
kind	O
words	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
forbear	O
his	O
rallery	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
satisfied	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
regain	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
part	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
modestly	O
refusing	O
to	O
play	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
throws	O
down	O
his	O
share	O
together	O
with	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
further	O
Dispute	O
,	O
begins	O
to	O
retire	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
strikes	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
two	O
blows	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
seeing	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
remedy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
returns	O
his	O
blows	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
stroke	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
some	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
being	O
pressed	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
retire	O
himself	O
being	O
drove	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
draws	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
coming	O
on	O
too	O
hard	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
presently	O
fell	O
and	O
dyed	O
,	O
it	O
further	O
being	O
made	O
very	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
or	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
of	O
his	O
power	O
,	O
had	O
always	O
endeavoured	O
for	O
the	O
advancement	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
spoke	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
in	O
order	O
thereunto	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
attested	O
by	O
a	O
Noble	O
Pear	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Applications	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
the	O
Verdict	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Banbry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
valued	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
valued	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
valued	O
9	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Banbry	I-pers
indicted	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
day	O
one	O
Silver	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Barkly	B-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
likewise	O
confessed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
February	O
the	O
22	O
four	O
Sheep	O
value	O
90	O
s.	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
sheep	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
who	O
to	O
excuse	O
himself	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
party	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
(	O
December	O
the	O
21th	O
)	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Codner	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stone	O
Buttons	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
apparent	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
distributed	O
amongst	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
which	O
Buttons	O
,	O
being	O
apprehended	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buttons	O
,	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
pretending	O
the	O
buttons	O
were	O
gave	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Peter	O
Lad	O
y	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
February	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
)	O
two	O
Shirts	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Mantu	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
was	O
Apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shirt	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
likewise	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
who	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
Andrew	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
Mary	O
,	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
his	O
Examination	O
clearing	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
in	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
one	O
John	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
31th	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Indicted	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
one	O
Black	O
Nag	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Serjeant	B-pers
Indicted	O
likewise	O
on	O
a	O
third	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
(	O
January	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
)	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Serjeant	O
three	O
and	O
twenty	O
Sheep	O
skins	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
confessed	O
in	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridgets	I-place
alias	O
Brides	B-place
,	O
indicted	O
as	O
common	O
Thieves	O
keeping	O
false	O
keys	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
Houses	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
with	O
Bullets	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
very	O
little	O
excuse	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Seyton	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
by	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
to	O
bring	O
our	O
present	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
into	O
hatred	O
with	O
his	O
Subjects	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Second	O
was	O
a	O
Cheat	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
word	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
possitively	O
thereto	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
invallidate	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
preffered	O
20	O
s.	O
10	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
declared	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
,	O
(	O
January	O
the	O
23th	O
.	O
)	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Lace-Pinner	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pinner	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Defendent	O
not	O
denying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
Medals	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hoversham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
Feb.	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankerd	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Caryck	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
October	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
)	O
one	O
Hundred	O
Forty	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
before	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ken	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
(	O
February	O
the	O
12th	O
)	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Manteau	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
one	O
to	O
run	O
with	O
more	O
speed	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
being	O
dropt	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
making	O
a	O
Defence	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stoke	I-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Masters	B-pers
;	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Indicted	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
Sacks	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Sack	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Cooper	B-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
denying	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
Feb.	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value4	O
d.	O
It	O
was	O
manifest	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
,	O
but	O
pretending	O
with	O
a	O
frevilous	O
excuse	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carpender	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Glasborrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Marys	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
January	O
the	O
23th	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
mony	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Carpenders	O
hands	O
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Glasborrow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Allhallows	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Dowgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
Barrs	O
of	O
Iron	O
on	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
when	O
demanded	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Edith	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
seller	O
valued	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Wine	O
,	O
whilst	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Pain	O
were	O
busie	O
in	O
drinking	O
,	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
makes	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
opportunity	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
silver	O
Salt-seller	O
,	O
marchs	O
off	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Companions	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
Temple	O
missing	O
his	O
Salt	O
seller	O
,	O
apprehends	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Pain	O
,	O
as	O
Accessary	O
in	O
the	O
Theft	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
being	O
carryed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
by	O
him	O
bound	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
penalty	O
of	O
the	O
theft	O
themselves	O
;	O
whereupon	O
making	O
diligent	O
inquiry	O
at	O
length	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
,	O
whom	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Theft	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Salt-seller	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Pain	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
and	O
honest	O
Conversations	O
,	O
producing	O
one	O
who	O
arrested	O
that	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
served	O
many	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
forthwith	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
indicted	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
walking	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wigg	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
Mr	O
Roe	O
,	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
his	O
flight	O
droped	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wigg	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
closely	O
followed	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
very	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Marfellon	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Porrenger	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
suspected	O
as	O
ill	O
persons	O
,	O
were	O
seized	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
Keys	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Plates	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
bring	O
in	O
the	O
Plates	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
giving	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
and	O
Thacker	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Thacker	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Drury	O
and	O
Clarke	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb	O
one	O
silver	O
Tanckerd	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
Three	O
Manteaus	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
five	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Musling	O
Neckcloath	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Thieves	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
protesting	O
innocence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	O
Fitz-zachary	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
two	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleves	O
and	O
six	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Neckcloath	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Robinson	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
satisfaction	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
more	O
words	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cole	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
make	O
Merchandise	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
Robinson	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
Cole	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
has	O
Life	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Verdict	O
Robinson	O
Guilty	O
Cole	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Holy	I-place
Trinity	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
a	O
live	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
of	O
both	O
which	O
Marriages	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
by	O
him	O
made	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
one	O
Arthur	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Tobacco-Pipe	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Goff	O
languishing	O
till	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Dyed	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
Goff	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asking	O
for	O
Victuals	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
took	O
Goff	O
to	O
the	O
Cupbord	O
,	O
biding	O
him	O
Fat	O
and	O
welcome	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
allowing	O
of	O
,	O
comes	O
to	O
Goff	O
and	O
Kicking	O
him	O
,	O
tells	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
Kicking	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
being	O
somewhat	O
satisfied	O
,	O
siting	O
down	O
almost	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
rising	O
up	O
re-assaults	O
Goff	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
Tobacco	O
Pipe	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
third	O
thrust	O
pushes	O
Goff	O
into	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
breaking	O
the	O
Pipe	O
in	O
several	O
pieces	O
;	O
another	O
deposed	O
that	O
Goff	O
at	O
his	O
death	O
charged	O
Jones	O
as	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
commanding	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
arrest	O
that	O
Goff	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
after	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
dyed	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Goff	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
had	O
declared	O
himself	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Chrurgeon	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
Wound	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
really	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
Goffs	O
death	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
choaking	O
and	O
strangling	O
him	O
by	O
lying	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pressing	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
forth	O
with	O
dyed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
sometime	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
was	O
sent	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
Parker	O
;	O
where	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
in	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Parents	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
enquiring	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
Childs	O
death	O
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
told	O
one	O
it	O
dyed	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
disagreement	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
being	O
objected	O
against	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
being	O
before	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
and	O
farther	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
over	O
layed	O
,	O
not	O
supposed	O
designedly	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Verdict	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
misfortune	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Morrice	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennedict	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
confessed	O
that	O
Morrice	O
Archer	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
Archer	O
impeach	O
'd	O
Smith	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
excused	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
Archer	O
acknowledging	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Smith	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Archer	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warfar	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
Stamping	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
Tin	O
with	O
other	O
mix	O
Mettals	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Halfpennys	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
prejudice	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
Counterfeit	O
the	O
Kings	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
in	O
question	O
therefore	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Controllors	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Lord	O
Treasurer	O
;	O
another	O
witnessgave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
show	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Rarity	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
secret	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
Counterfeit	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Inscription	O
contrary	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
allowed	O
by	O
Pattent	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Florent	O
Rex	O
Regina	O
prolifics	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
defence	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
he	O
did	O
order	O
the	O
Coin	O
Specified	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
but	O
never	O
made	O
,	O
or	O
designed	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
advantage	O
thereof	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Pattent	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
endeavour	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
procure	O
;	O
humbly	O
presuming	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
after	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
the	O
Effigies	O
and	O
Motto	O
of	O
his	O
Invention	O
would	O
no	O
ways	O
deny	O
his	O
request	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
,	O
five	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloath	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
them	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad-Cloath	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
:	O
At	O
the	O
Tryal	O
nothing	O
being	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
some	O
small	O
Suspicions	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forthwith	O
discharged	O
.	O
Ewen	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Stamping	O
false	O
Coin	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
Name	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
12.	O
pieces	O
of	O
Tin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
as	O
Farthings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Stamping	O
.	O
The	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
left	O
three	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Farthings	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Coin	O
and	O
Stamp	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
attested	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ewen	O
Hill	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryon	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Trunk	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
18	O
Napkins	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
Feb.	O
2	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
French-man	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Trunck	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dun	O
excused	O
Ryon	O
and	O
Knight	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Trunck	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
which	O
excuse	O
being	O
unallowed	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Dun	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
January	O
the	O
25	O
3	O
Table	O
Cloathes	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Parker	B-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
proving	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broadstock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
January	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
one	O
Bible	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
his	O
Bible	O
another	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
her	O
Thimble	O
,	O
at	O
both	O
which	O
times	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
depos	O
'd	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
than	O
verity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forthwith	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
defrauding	O
one	O
Brewer	B-pers
of	O
a	O
Basket	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Apples	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Cliff	O
coming	O
to	O
one	O
Lovejoys	O
house	O
,	O
demanded	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
delivered	O
him	O
he	O
carryed	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
Cheat	O
being	O
at	O
length	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Millener	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Cup	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cover	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
d.	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Williams	O
,	O
under	O
colour	O
of	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
taking	O
her	O
opportunity	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Wakelyn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Norgrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Embroider	O
'd	O
Sumpter	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Felson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
Cloath	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
party	O
no	O
whom	O
they	O
offered	O
it	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
their	O
Tryal	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Morfee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Barthelomew	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Tankerd	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Spurrier	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Spurrier	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Tanckard	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
whilst	O
Morfee	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
Spurrier	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Tanckerd	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
Spurrier	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
Morfee	O
,	O
suspecting	O
him	O
as	O
accessary	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
escap	O
'd	O
;	O
Morfee	O
seeing	O
himself	O
suspected	O
,	O
swearing	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
,	O
tells	O
Spurrier	O
he	O
had	O
dispoiled	O
his	O
Lechery	O
,	O
but	O
Spurrier	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
who	O
forthwith	O
committed	O
him	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
Russel	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Morfee	O
's	O
means	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
Spurrier	O
to	O
his	O
Tanckard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
an	O
unsatisfactory	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
Morfee	O
produced	O
some	O
;	O
who	O
spoke	O
of	O
his	O
reputation	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Company	O
he	O
kept	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Dimothy	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
Apron	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Young	I-pers
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
formerly	O
Branded	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
giving	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hallous	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shooes	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shirts	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
value	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Habern	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
pounds	O
of	O
Beef	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
Grace	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
denying	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
pretending	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
pretended	O
to	O
give	O
,	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
Six	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Caryck	I-pers
Marrice	I-pers
Archer	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Heversham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Thirteen	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carpender	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
,	O
Fredrick	O
Hape	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Morfee	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Banbry	I-pers
.	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
in	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
one	O
days	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Seyton	I-pers
for	O
speaking	O
seditious	O
words	O
,	O
Fined	O
five	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
sureties	O
for	O
one	O
year	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
pillory	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
Newgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
on	O
his	O
Forehead	O
.	O
Eleven	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Levis	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
Millenor	O
Tomson	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Wakelyn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norgrave	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Of	O
which	O
,	O
Millenor	O
,	O
Tomson	O
,	O
and	O
Ellenor	O
Davis	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
women	O
was	O
pannel	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
returned	O
the	O
Verdict	O
in	O
the	O
Affirimative	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
delivered	O
.	O
