TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
14th	O
.	O
and	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Woods	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lowfield	I-pers
Bernard	B-pers
Minn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jenne	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
Kenlem	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Mathew	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Medcalf	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bugins	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Trego	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Minchin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sanyer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Donne	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Wansal	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-Gate	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
a	O
Victualig-House	O
,	O
intruded	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
thither	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
words	O
arising	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
thrust	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
somewhat	O
troublesome	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
push	O
him	O
behind	O
a	O
Table	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
to	O
remove	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Tobacco-Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
unfortunately	O
struck	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Nostril	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
which	O
breaking	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
Two	O
Inches	O
bearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
Wound	O
he	O
Dyed	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
kindness	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
Agressor	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
valued	O
at	O
24	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Bow	I-place
from	O
John	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
Hobs	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Bosom-Inn	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
who	O
slipping	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
missed	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
doubtful	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
giving	O
something	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Consorts	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Ring	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pleading	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Convers	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
and	O
on	O
an	O
Indictment	O
at	O
Common-Law	O
for	O
Killing	O
Major	B-pers
Wadden	I-pers
;	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
some	O
hot	O
words	O
passed	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
discourse	O
that	O
happened	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
Wagers	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
whereupon	O
and	O
through	O
some	O
other	O
provocation	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
e	O
'	O
r	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
prevented	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wadden	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
another	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
4	O
Inches	O
deep	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
2	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pressing	O
to	O
close	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
run	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
And	O
it	O
not	O
appearingthey	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
each	O
other	O
before	O
that	O
unhappy	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mischief	O
happened	O
through	O
a	O
suddain	O
heat	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ames	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Trunk	O
where	O
with	O
9	O
more	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
possessed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
belief	O
that	O
his	O
Maid	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
carrying	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
satisfie	O
a	O
Man	O
into	O
whose	O
debt	O
she	O
had	O
run	O
during	O
her	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
her	O
Masters	O
leaving	O
his	O
Keys	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
Trunk	O
stood	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Confession	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
Fear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collard	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perrewig	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Mony-box	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
upon	O
their	O
discovery	O
and	O
slight	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Theif	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
scuffling	O
with	O
them	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
business	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
particular	O
seeming	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Sedon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Jane	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
three	O
inches	O
;	O
Upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
a	O
Victualling-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
by	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Guest	O
called	O
her	O
Shameless	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
incensed	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sought	O
for	O
stones	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
none	O
she	O
could	O
readily	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
to	O
pacifie	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
Dirt	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
Cravat	O
,	O
when	O
to	O
get	O
loose	O
,	O
pushing	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
several	O
Cuts	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
through	O
loss	O
of	O
Blood	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
good	O
looking	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
Antient	O
,	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
that	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Violence	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
offered	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Obryan	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
handle	O
Sword	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Levit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
the	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
within	O
the	O
penalty	O
of	O
Petty-larcerary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tohmas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Keys	O
valued	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Barry	O
said	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Buildings	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
divers	O
Workmen	O
had	O
left	O
Keys	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
heat	O
had	O
passed	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
frivelous	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meechin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wether	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Wether	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
found	O
(	O
upon	O
search	O
)	O
his	O
Skin	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Barham	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Meechin	O
had	O
killed	O
the	O
said	O
Wether	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
inquiry	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Flesh	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Powdering-Tub	O
,	O
which	O
making	O
the	O
Felony	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
former	O
confessions	O
proved	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
they	O
endeavored	O
to	O
shufle	O
it	O
off	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
Barham	O
altogether	O
alledging	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Meechin	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilburn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ewe	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hyat	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
five	O
persons	O
laying	O
claim	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
proprietors	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
one	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ewe	O
being	O
restored	O
,	O
through	O
that	O
defect	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Hayns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
34	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Travell	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
that	O
coming	O
thither	O
to	O
Lodge	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
under	O
some	O
indisposition	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
recovered	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
express	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
sence	O
of	O
sorrow	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
compassionated	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
degree	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
guilty	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Burning	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Reyon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Coife	O
,	O
Pinner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Standish	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
counterfeited	O
himself	O
a	O
Country	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
pretending	O
much	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
third	O
Night	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
he	O
had	O
friends	O
to	O
visit	O
him	O
)	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
rifling	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
:	O
In	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
being	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Fellonies	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarfe	O
valued	O
at	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Serge	O
Mantle	O
valued	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
borrow	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Coats	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
whilst	O
she	O
mended	O
her	O
own	O
Cloathes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lent	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
using	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
proposed	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
above-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
cast	O
her	O
self	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
consideration	O
the	O
things	O
stolen	O
were	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
value	O
mentioned	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
receiving	O
their	O
Directions	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
Catherine	B-pers
Phrasier	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
under	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
entred	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
and	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
alluring	O
to	O
his	O
wicked	O
purposes	O
and	O
frighting	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
into	O
a	O
concealment	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
her	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
if	O
she	O
discovered	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
disorder	O
occasioning	O
extream	O
soreness	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complaining	O
,	O
her	O
Parents	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
having	O
formerly	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
seeming	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23.	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tumbler	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
his	O
Lawndress	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
when	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
Tumbler	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
nor	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Tumbler	O
other	O
ways	O
than	O
in	O
jest	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Lawndress	O
more	O
careful	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
intimated	O
as	O
much	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
brought	O
it	O
again	O
without	O
being	O
taxed	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
her	O
Reputation	O
appearing	O
very	O
candid	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Case	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Towel	O
and	O
12	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
the	O
Locks	O
were	O
found	O
picked	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
notice	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
fled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
till	O
they	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
for	O
another	O
Robery	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Towel	O
and	O
Napkins	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Walker	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
known	O
a	O
notorious	O
Theif	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
shift	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
discovery	O
,	O
nor	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taxed	O
with	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
alledging	O
the	O
Towel	O
and	O
Napkins	O
were	O
lent	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
necessary	O
uses	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Worrell	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
with	O
106	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
a	O
Caster	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gartrix	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
on	O
the	O
18.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
cast	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
part	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
but	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
confederacy	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
hankring	O
thereabout	O
,	O
which	O
considered	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
19	O
l.	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
and	O
pass	O
over	O
to	O
Calais	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
proof	O
of	O
which	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
again	O
confessed	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Neats	O
Leather	O
Shoos	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ketle	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
seized	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Felonies	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Handkercheifs	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Upchurch	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
appearing	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
leave	O
than	O
stole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Inn	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
notice	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
by	O
the	O
Ostler	O
of	O
that	O
Inn	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
Hay	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
thither	O
by	O
that	O
direction	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Gelding	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
proof	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Limbrey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
Fresh	O
Wharf	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hansly	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
the	O
Coats	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
being	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Party	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
near	O
the	O
Shop	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denying	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
deminishing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
for	O
suspicious	O
persons	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Witness	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
stooped	O
to	O
the	O
Grates	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
3	O
melting	O
Pots	O
and	O
a	O
Ladle	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
pleading	O
Innocence	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
like	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
deminishing	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
40	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
,	O
40	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Clippings	O
being	O
found	O
by	O
one	O
Abigal	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
his	O
Cousin	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
stopping	O
her	O
,	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
hadthem	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
more	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
a	O
melting	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
to	O
testifie	O
for	O
his	O
Honesty	O
in	O
his	O
calling	O
,	O
bring	O
a	O
Cabinet-Maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
finding	O
some	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
weighed	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Chequer	O
'd	O
Silk	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Isaac	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
cheapning	O
Silk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
perceived	O
to	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
shuffled	O
under	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
their	O
departure	O
,	O
the	O
Silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
producing	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lunday	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
white	O
Felt	O
Hats	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
against	O
him	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
the	O
Hats	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
St.	O
Georges	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
whereupon	O
sight	O
of	O
12	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
making	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
Anne	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caurless	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hanah	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstantial	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
the	O
parties	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
concealing	O
and	O
confederating	O
with	O
one	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mack	I-pers
Donniel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
defrauded	O
the	O
Honorable	O
Bernard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Esq	O
:	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
on	O
two	O
Notes	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
furnished	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
other	O
riding	O
materials	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
declaring	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
undone	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
Treason	O
or	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
the	O
Roads	O
to	O
Yarmouth	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Transporting	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
concealed	O
him	O
till	O
5	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
having	O
ordered	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
His	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
detained	O
him	O
in	O
hopes	O
he	O
was	O
Colonel	O
Douglas	O
his	O
Man	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
many	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
his	O
behavior	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
post	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Conivance	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
for	O
concealing	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
deteriment	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
and	O
Diminution	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
And	O
against	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
searched	O
upon	O
suspition	O
,	O
the	O
Parcel	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Gaston	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
party	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
intrusted	O
him	O
upon	O
liking	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
some	O
Mony	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
if	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
agreement	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Hewes	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gattway	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Tryals	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pardo	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Chapelo	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Enson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
Eatables	O
,	O
as	O
Beef	O
,	O
Pork	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
How	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
boiling	O
Pots	O
,	O
Pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
Plates	O
,	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
36	O
pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
material	O
Evidence	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
affirmed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
both	O
those	O
Roberies	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
producing	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ursula	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
three	O
Hoods	O
and	O
a	O
Coif	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brandy	O
Cups	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
evident	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
norwithstanding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alledged	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
a	O
Barrock	O
,	O
or	O
Bed-Room	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Garrison	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hazler	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Barrock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
,	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Rings	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Pearice	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
Cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
Rings	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
laying	O
claim	O
but	O
to	O
one	O
Ring	O
amongst	O
many	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
defaced	O
by	O
the	O
Stones	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
her	O
Son	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mack	I-pers
Danniel	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
before-mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
s	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trig	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Trigs	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Lace	O
in	O
her	O
Stocking	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
hoods	O
Scarves	O
plain	O
and	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Rumbold	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstancial	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
were	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Convers	I-pers
,	O
Roger	O
Seldon	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mack-Donniel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lundy	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Hayns	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Reyon	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
that	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dyks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
alias	O
Worrel	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barkam	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meechin	I-pers
,	O
Margard	O
Wright	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Fined	O
,	O
were	O
William	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
Fined	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
