TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
20th	O
.	O
21st	O
.	O
and	O
22d	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
21st	O
.	O
and	O
22	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chowne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
Edmond	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Bartholomew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
John	B-pers
Overran	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Siredock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Steere	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
George	B-pers
Clisby	I-pers
Edmond	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Curtiss	I-pers
Ephriam	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Reding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
about	O
Seventy	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
meeting	O
at	O
Habberdashers	O
Hall	O
Door	O
;	O
(	O
they	O
receiving	O
Alms	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
)	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Pension	O
yet	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Drunken	O
Sot	O
,	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
(	O
after	O
their	O
return	O
home	O
)	O
there	O
rise	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
Water	O
and	O
threw	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Engaged	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
at	O
him	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
Sword	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
dyed	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
produce	O
any	O
Evidence	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Verdict	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Loathbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Preswick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rod	O
of	O
Birch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
she	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Girls	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Age	O
,	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
several	O
Faults	O
,	O
as	O
Lying	O
,	O
and	O
Slurishness	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
but	O
moderate	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
sickly	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
consumption	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
Wound	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
Ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hare	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
one	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Drawer	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
30	O
l.	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
it	O
so	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lye	O
sleeping	O
at	O
a	O
Wharfe	O
by	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
a	O
Carman	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
Boy	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
upwards	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
whose	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Fathers	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
threatening	O
him	O
with	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
Confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
Boy	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
hid	O
themselves	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
had	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
brought	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
two	O
Brass	O
Shillings	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
not	O
denying	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
Ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lemon-Colour	O
'd	O
Satin	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
about	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Hatband	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
down	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
her	O
Mistress	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Rumford	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivilous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hellier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridgets	I-place
alias	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chaffin	I-pers
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Chaffin	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Water-side	O
at	O
Dorset	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
King	O
take	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
amongst	O
the	O
Croud	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
suddenly	O
snatched	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
next	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
droped	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Simon	B-pers
Suchin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
Two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
Two	O
Quoifs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Suchin	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Employed	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
only	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Two	O
Shirts	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
Spoon	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ninteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Doudel	I-pers
Cheesemonger	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Doudel	O
and	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
usually	O
did	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
Butter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
missed	O
some	O
quantity	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
comeing	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
whilst	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
the	O
said	O
Cheese	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
some	O
few	O
paces	O
from	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cheese	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Doudle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Wesminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Austin	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	B-place
in	O
the	O
Pall	I-place
Mall	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
if	O
his	O
Boots	O
were	O
cleaned	O
(	O
he	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
was	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
Boots	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
Company	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
understanding	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Clamour	O
about	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
grew	O
to	O
very	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
forth	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
the	O
Fire-fork	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stirring	O
up	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
other	O
aggravating	O
words	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
so	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
by	O
a	O
Thrust	O
in	O
his	O
Navel	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languishing	O
,	O
died	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
before	O
the	O
stroke	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
designed	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
were	O
always	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
provocation	O
was	O
given	O
first	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
Fork	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
not	O
countervailing	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tanckard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fausiter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Tanckard	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
droped	O
the	O
Tanckard	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Raper	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
both	O
Porter	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
plying	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
Stairs	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
occasion	O
to	O
quarrel	O
about	O
a	O
Burthen	O
that	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
another	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
fetched	O
each	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
happening	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Thrust	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
died	O
as	O
afore-said	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
proving	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Challenged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
premediated	O
Malice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gouge	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Quarrel	O
about	O
their	O
own	O
Child	O
;	O
she	O
urging	O
him	O
into	O
extream	O
passion	O
,	O
he	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
certain	O
instrument	O
called	O
a	O
Gouge	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Carpenters	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
stuck	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
Handle	O
off	O
in	O
getting	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
her	O
Four	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Wound	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
very	O
fully	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
making	O
any	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
Kill	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Enamel	O
'd	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
Enamel	O
'd	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10.	O
l.	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
Fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sanctlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Madam	O
Amphrilis	B-pers
Chiffinch	I-pers
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
thither	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Celler	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Board	O
and	O
conveyed	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Celler	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
slip	O
'd	O
back	O
the	O
Bolt	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
Ladys	O
Chamber	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
afore	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
some	O
enquiry	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
with	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Rersby	I-pers
.	O
Kt	O
.	O
One	O
silver	O
Stand	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
One	O
silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
Five	O
silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
One	O
silver	O
Gilt	O
Cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
One	O
silver	O
Pepper-Box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Rersby	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
himself	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
having	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
he	O
entertained	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
maintenance	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
place	O
vacant	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
wrote	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
for	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
satisfied	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
some	O
dishonest	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Servant	O
fit	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Plate	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Suspition	O
grounded	O
upon	O
this	O
person	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Corroberating	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
pawning	O
the	O
gilt	O
Cup	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
some	O
small	O
Evasion	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Groves	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Person	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Young	B-pers
Woman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
heard	O
at	O
large	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
:	O
The	O
former	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
Nine	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lushington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Pattison	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Lushington	O
left	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Simons	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Pitcher	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Stockings	O
of	O
Simons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
part	O
payment	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
:	O
And	O
Simons	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Barret	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Pitcher	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Snape	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Three	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
Three	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
his	O
m	O
,	O
an	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
pursuing	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
droped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
slightly	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thoms	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Childs	O
Correl	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Pye	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Hide	O
and	O
Wilks	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
peep	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Hide	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Apprentice	O
perceiving	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
said	O
Hide	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wilks	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
a	O
Wall	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
Apprehended	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Correl	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
into	O
another	O
Box	O
,	O
or	O
Trunck	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
Keys	O
found	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Defence	O
for	O
themselves	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
one	O
Lodged	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
mistook	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Edward	O
Hide	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Wilks	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
forasmuch	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
althou	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40.	O
s.	O
One	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Grew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Henry	O
Grew	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Grinder	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
that	O
was	O
Grind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
immediately	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
untill	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
Ten	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
imagine	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
conveyed	O
them	O
thither	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
Numbee	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
repute	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
:	O
and	O
several	O
persons	O
offered	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
but	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Pilferer	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Millikin	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Millikin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Millikin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Fileing	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
Ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
piece	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
;	O
and	O
Ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
piece	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
diminishing	O
from	O
each	O
Shilling	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	O
Millikin	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
Millikin	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
seen	O
through	O
a	O
Window	O
(	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
their	O
Chamber	O
)	O
to	O
Clip	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
information	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
it	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Alice	O
Millikin	O
the	O
Mother	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
half	O
clip	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
David	O
receiving	O
the	O
Clippings	O
as	O
she	O
Cut	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	O
Morgan	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspition	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Alice	O
Millikin	O
Confessed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Chaston	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
innocent	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
actually	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
they	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
wicked	O
Act	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Berkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Tower	O
with	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
jostle	O
the	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
Sentinel	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
falling	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
shot	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sea	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmunton	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
his	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
whip	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
striking	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Work-Room	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Silk	O
Stoking	O
Weaver	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Boy	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
cleaned	O
his	O
Frame	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
answered	O
at	O
Easter	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
as	O
afore-said	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Chirugeons	O
which	O
viewed	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
attested	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
violent	O
Fit	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
almost	O
Twenty	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
attest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
given	O
to	O
passion	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
beat	O
any	O
servant	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
John	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
alias	O
Mombay	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Richard	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th.of	O
March	O
last	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
there	O
happened	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
giving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Lye	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
other	O
aggravating	O
words	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
scuffle	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
pot	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
but	O
a	O
Chirugeon	O
,	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attesting	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
perfectly	O
cured	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Paskah	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20s	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Apparel	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
droped	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
Rose	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
and	O
J	O
--	O
M	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
John	O
Spencer	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wild	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
having	O
some	O
intelligence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
H	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
search	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
but	O
no	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wild	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Ryman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Trunck	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
not	O
to	O
keep	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wally	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wally	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fifty	O
Minion-shot	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ship	O
,	O
after	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Turnbal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Turnbal	O
going	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Friends	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
some	O
discourse	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
Ring	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
alias	O
Arnold	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
(	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Accomplices	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
,	O
Two	O
silver	O
Tasters	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Fifty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
Celler-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hid	O
between	O
two	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sugar	O
lying	O
not	O
far	O
a	O
distant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
plea	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stroud	B-place
Green	I-place
in	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
three	O
Chests	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Campaign	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
and	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mons	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leave	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
Barn	O
some	O
two	O
Nights	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
understanding	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
opening	O
the	O
last	O
Chest	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
perceived	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
Moon-shine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
agreeing	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	O
Warner	O
,	O
who	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
up	O
late	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
mony	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
excuse	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
mony	O
droped	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Rings	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Jane	O
S	O
pin	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Chirugeons	O
Instruments	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Hillery	I-pers
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Case	O
of	O
Instruments	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Zachary	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Beever	O
Hatt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Conyers	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
souldier	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
some	O
occasion	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strook	O
the	O
said	O
Conyers	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
strook	O
of	O
his	O
Hatt	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Conyers	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
Flambeaux	O
that	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
taken	O
upon	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
charged	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mancroft	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
One	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
an	O
amethist	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
One	O
Gold	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
Twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Duckets	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
;	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
into	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
lost	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
Mary	O
Lushes	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Mancroft	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
Harbour	O
Pick-pockets	O
and	O
idle	O
Persons	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
about	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
John	O
Mancroft	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Lush	O
as	O
Accessary	O
thereon	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Venetian	O
Neck	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
One	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
One	O
piece	O
Galloon	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Saraw	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Hawkes	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Hiring	O
the	O
said	O
Rogers	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
her	O
Mistris	O
going	O
abroad	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
missing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
made	O
diligent	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
Howard	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
seizing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neck-lace	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
not	O
denying	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hawkes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
Howard	O
making	O
a	O
plausible	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Westcot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Plates	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Crips	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Whistle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
One	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
One	O
Dram-cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
One	O
Neck-lace	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Childs	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Saleswoman	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Childrens	O
Coats	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Childs	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
taxed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
by	O
good	O
witness	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Littleboy	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Littleboy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoives	O
,	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
Badcock	O
Deposing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
being	O
fast	O
Locked	O
.	O
And	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Cole	O
and	O
Littleboy	O
were	O
Accessaries	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Hyde	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cordyner	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Haughton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Corbison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
Richard	O
Thomas	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
Cordyner	O
,	O
Haughton	O
,	O
Williams	O
and	O
Boyce	O
as	O
Abettors	O
thereunto	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
paying	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
by	O
some	O
Labouring	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
Worked	O
near	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
to	O
Apprehend	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
stood	O
upon	O
their	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
every	O
Man	O
of	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
continued	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Combat	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
drawing	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
killed	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Corbison	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
the	O
Swords	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
clear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Cordyner	O
,	O
Haughton	O
,	O
Williams	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Boyce	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Seven	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Henry	O
Dixon	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Griffin	O
,	O
Griffen	O
Irons	O
,	O
Edward	O
Carter	O
,	O
William	O
Cole	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Spencer	O
,	O
Susanna	O
Morice	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
8	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Colwell	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Jones	O
,	O
Alice	O
Clark	O
,	O
John	O
Snape	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wild	O
,	O
John	O
Holms	O
,	O
John	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Ann	O
Lee	O
,	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hide	O
,	O
Alice	O
Millikin	O
,	O
David	O
Millikin	O
,	O
John	O
Hellier	O
,	O
William	O
Doudle	O
,	O
Jonathan	O
Bridgman	O
,	O
Pascha	O
Rose	O
,	O
Edward	O
Smith	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Baxter	O
,	O
Richard	O
Thomas	O
,	O
James	O
Cordiner	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Haughton	O
,	O
Richard	O
Williams	O
,	O
John	O
Mancliff	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lush	O
,	O
Ellenor	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Alice	O
Millikin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lush	O
,	O
and	O
Ellenor	O
Rogers	O
pleading	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
impannelled	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
verdict	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
.	O
The	O
Judgment	O
of	O
John	O
Boyce	O
was	O
deferred	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
3.	O
viz	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Francis	O
Simons	O
,	O
Mary	O
Gale	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
WHereas	O
in	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
published	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
Incerted	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Stamford	O
was	O
likewise	O
discharged	O
by	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Now	O
these	O
are	O
to	O
certifie	O
the	O
Reader	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Lordship	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Sessions	O
upon	O
no	O
other	O
account	O
than	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
one	O
Jacob	O
Joyner	O
,	O
son	O
of	O
that	O
Joyner	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Chairing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
commonly	O
called	O
and	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Cobb	O
Joyner	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
Joyner	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
Westminster	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Lordship	O
of	O
a	O
Jewel	O
worth	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
800	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
which	O
Witnesses	O
attended	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
(	O
taking	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
was	O
Pardoned	O
by	O
His	O
Majesties	O
late	O
Gracious	O
and	O
General	O
Pardon	O
)	O
did	O
thereupon	O
discharge	O
Joyner	O
of	O
that	O
Felony	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
dismiss	O
'd	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
from	O
further	O
Attendance	O
on	O
that	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
Joyner	O
is	O
continued	O
in	O
Custody	O
upon	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
Trover	O
brought	O
for	O
recovering	O
the	O
said	O
Jewel	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
Scandalum	O
Magnatum	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Damages	O
are	O
laid	O
10000	O
l	O
.	O
