TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
8th	O
.	O
and	O
9th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Tear	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
8th	O
.	O
and	O
9th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1687.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Standon	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Millward	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Waples	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Acroy	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lad	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butters	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
;	O
he	O
taking	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Boat	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
:	O
He	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Emertons	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
biding	O
them	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
their	O
Tankerd	O
for	O
which	O
Exchange	O
(	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Proverb	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
L	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
twenty	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
mix	O
'd	O
Drugget	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Panford	I-pers
:	O
who	O
proving	O
the	O
Stuff	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Easy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goomer	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seaburne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Silk	O
Lurestring	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
shew	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
contradicting	O
stories	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	O
Papworth	O
alias	O
,	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
eight	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
three	O
twenty	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Linen	O
Bagg	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Ellis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
keeping	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Entertainment	O
,	O
Lodged	O
the	O
said	O
Papworth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Things	O
,	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
enquiring	O
after	O
,	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
slight	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Three	O
Gentlemen	B-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
above	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Floyd	O
Died	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
Persons	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Floyd	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Paringshovel	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Croud	O
raised	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
much	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
also	O
bringing	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
to	O
testifie	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
rather	O
willing	O
to	O
Reconcile	O
,	O
than	O
breed	O
Quarrels	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Company	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richaed	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Would	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
above	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Gaming	O
at	O
Bannister	O
's	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
borrowed	O
five	O
shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
present	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
struck	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kirby	O
taking	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
Crofts	O
mising	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
Kirby	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Room	O
,	O
Crofts	O
Drew	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
Kirby	O
Retreating	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
Kirby	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	I-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
proving	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bownes	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
Swithin's-Alley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Aleworth	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Thorois	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Man	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
more	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
and	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Ruckle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Carter	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
was	O
Proved	O
by	O
Record	O
to	O
be	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
near	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Crevat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
Rob	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
also	O
declaring	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
recovering	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obstinate	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
prescribed	O
him	O
;	O
saying	O
He	O
would	O
Die	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Buckle	O
may	O
be	O
Hanged	O
;	O
for	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
Hang	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
whole	O
Court	O
almost	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
alias	O
Green	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
several	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
Cawsey	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
for	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Giles	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Another	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winckfeild	I-pers
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
Indictment	O
,	O
one	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Beaver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
corroborate	O
the	O
same	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Croydon	O
with	O
one	O
Meacon	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Robbed	O
and	O
Bound	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Strip	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
.	O
Also	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Mackhorne	I-pers
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
English	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
of	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
English	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Smith	O
they	O
were	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
behind	O
a	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Flaxen	O
Table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
twenty	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
,	O
eight	O
Hollan	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
twenty	O
Bisket	O
Cakes	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Squire	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
string	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
fastned	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Box	O
when	O
the	O
Coachman	O
's	O
Man	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Charity	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
five	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Meddal	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Company-keeper	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
presumed	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Calico	O
Quilts	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
:	O
They	O
persuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hagget	I-pers
but	O
Marshall	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
proving	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
Stole	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Fringe	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Linck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Hollan	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Brass-Kentle	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawksworth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
adjacent	O
House	O
not	O
Inhabited	O
up	O
a	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pocket	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
forementioned	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slight	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
Isaac	B-pers
Orbell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
nigh	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
broad	O
and	O
6	O
inches	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
.	O
Another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tryal	O
held	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Orbel	O
sitting	O
one	O
against	O
another	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Alban-street	I-place
,	O
in	O
two	O
Chairs	O
as	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
some	O
words	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Lye	O
and	O
other	O
opprobious	O
Language	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
a	O
Pipe	O
was	O
thrown	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
presently	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Orbell	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Drew	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
Orbell	O
being	O
a	O
strong	O
Man	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Weapon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
Draw	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
off	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
upon	O
his	O
Weapon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
And	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
an	O
Appeal	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Widdow	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Agnes	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Agnes	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
had	O
;	O
Indictments	O
brought	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
One	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
another	O
cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
another	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
spoke	O
little	O
material	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Callico-Pillowbeers	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Pillow-beers	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
s	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
burnt	O
on	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
afterward	O
in	O
Ratclife-High-way	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
running	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Collar-bone	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Davison	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
very	O
Drunk	O
calling	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
taking	O
her	O
part	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
up	O
his	O
Guts	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
nothing	O
to	O
Kill	O
six	O
such	O
Men	O
as	O
he	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
words	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
Blows	O
struck	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
Davison	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
known	O
further	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sackvill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
Elenor	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
a	O
Fire-shovel	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
Murdered	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Murdered	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Murder	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
last	O
words	O
were	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
hath	O
Murdered	O
me	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoones	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
100	O
of	O
Canes	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
conveyed	O
away	O
some	O
Canes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
Captain	O
Pooles	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
Sir	O
Henrys	O
house	O
,	O
Sir	O
Henry	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Trunck	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
reaching	O
to	O
Burglary	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Loyn	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
of	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Loyn	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Cottrell	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
59	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sallis	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Gorden	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
Cornelius	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Gorden	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Audrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
another	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
Cornets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
)	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Chirurgeon	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
look	O
d	O
after	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
girle	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Examination	O
that	O
the	O
Parents	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Complaint	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
made	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Iron	O
Jack	O
and	O
Eleven	O
Pound	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Waters	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Marshall	O
(	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
)	O
left	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
upon	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
lay	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
bound	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
testification	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
French	O
Pistols	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
Loncolns-Inn	B-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
strong	O
against	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bible	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Hollan	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
this	O
Floyds	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Suspition	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
possitively	O
charging	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
proving	O
they	O
took	O
pains	O
for	O
a	O
livelyhood	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
deserting	O
their	O
Colours	O
without	O
orders	O
from	O
hisMajesty	O
or	O
their	O
Lieutenant	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pendulum	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
five	O
Guinea	O
's	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Markes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
H	O
ford	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Breeches	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
row	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ladyman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Chain	O
and	O
Scissers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Willet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Hopper	O
all	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Bran	O
,	O
having	O
crept	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
whether	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
or	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
broken	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arnor	O
due	O
Poors	O
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
that	O
stopped	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
said	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
speaking	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
Scarf	O
Ala	O
node	O
,	O
one	O
Crop	O
Cornet	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Guise	I-pers
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
charging	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
her	O
but	O
a	O
Pillowbeer	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
for	O
her	O
Honesty	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Glasses	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
.	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
made	O
way	O
under	O
the	O
Coach	O
house	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mansion	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Grevil	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edmund	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
point	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
point	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
one	O
point	O
Pinner	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
point	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
green	O
Velvet	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Bed	O
lined	O
with	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloath	O
Vallens	O
with	O
Silk	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
l.	O
23	O
Silver	O
and	O
Silk	O
Cushions	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
Grevil	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
and	O
conveying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Grevil	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Smith	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
forty	O
one	O
yards	O
of	O
Plush	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Dimity	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Bradley	O
's	O
Wife	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Drawers	O
for	O
Kindness	O
received	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
Highway	O
of	O
a	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruge	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Crevat	O
and	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Sworn	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wigg	O
,	O
and	O
Crevat	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
delivering	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Meggs	I-pers
,	O
one	O
crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Meggs	O
by	O
her	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
very	O
inconsiderable	O
circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
hair	O
Plush	O
,	O
value	O
53	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
at	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Serge	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
failing	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wetherhill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
,	O
thence	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloath	O
Coat	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Snipe	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
three	O
Shillings	O
from	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
in	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
strong	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
a	O
high	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
unbared	O
the	O
doors	O
:	O
And	O
some	O
Writings	O
belonging	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Pockets	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bergen	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fernly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mawrice	B-pers
Cotter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Meddals	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Drunken	O
concern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Meddals	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloath	O
Coat	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Jervas	I-pers
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kites	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Fustian	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hatly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
Silver	O
Seals	O
,	O
two	O
Peticoates	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
;	O
But	O
It	O
appearing	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neeve	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
Cantharides	O
in	O
Drink	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
which	O
had	O
much	O
impaired	O
her	O
Health	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
A	O
Presentment	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
increase	O
of	O
Clippers	O
and	O
Coyners	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Laws	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
received	O
incouragement	O
from	O
petty	O
Tradesmen	O
,	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
requesting	O
that	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Wards	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
care	O
to	O
refuse	O
Counterfet	O
Clipt	O
Coyne	O
,	O
especially	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
final	O
sums	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
bring	O
the	O
suspected	O
persons	O
before	O
the	O
next	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Recommending	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
their	O
Successors	O
,	O
the	O
Grand	O
Juries	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
approved	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Tryales	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
9	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harbert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pricbard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Green	B-pers
,	O
G	B-pers
-	O
W	O
-	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sackvill	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grevil	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Snipe	I-pers
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
were	O
sworn	O
and	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
12	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
L	O
-	O
Elizabeth	O
Goomer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bownes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ladiman	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
4	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Papworth	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
,	O
Arnor	O
due	O
Poore	O
.	O
13	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Alesworth	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Audry	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cowly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Butters	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
from	O
Tower	O
Warfe	O
to	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
