TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
12th	O
.	O
and	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
and	O
13th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Choan	I-pers
Edmond	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chace	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hestcot	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Stanclif	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peppeot	I-pers
Bartholomew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Rooks	I-pers
Gervas	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Addams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Owedel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceeding	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
but	O
at	O
twice	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
First	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
assistant	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Abortive	O
Birth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Infant	O
was	O
altogether	O
imperfect	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
not	O
alive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
First	O
for	O
Firing	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Former	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
kindle	O
a	O
Fire	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
dress	O
her	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
combustible	O
Materials	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Oyl	O
shop	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
certain	O
Pitch	O
Barrels	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
timely	O
discovered	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
took	O
Effect	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Smoke	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
deny	O
in	O
Court	O
she	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
yet	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
for	O
so	O
wicked	O
an	O
undertaking	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
counselled	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
one	O
Evans	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
since	O
fled	O
into	O
Ireland	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
latter	O
it	O
as	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
making	O
her	O
escape	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
self	O
prevented	O
in	O
what	O
was	O
mainly	O
intended	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
s.	O
which	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4000	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
by	O
Crooked	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
were	O
Philips	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
of	O
Glover	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
sundry	O
parcels	O
of	O
Sheet-Lead	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
conjectured	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Plumary	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbouring	O
Church	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
covering	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
deposited	O
,	O
but	O
Glover	O
pleading	O
the	O
Lead	O
so	O
challenged	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
by	O
Mathews	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
Mathews	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
alledging	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
Glover	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Mathews	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
together	O
with	O
Philip	B-pers
Stains	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Rings	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
Jewels	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
l	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Araignment	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Stains	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
admitted	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
staying	O
for	O
more	O
Company	O
,	O
with	O
false	O
Keys	O
opened	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Locks	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
and	O
Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Coin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
departed	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Door	O
Lock	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
soon	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
persons	O
having	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
unless	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
inquiry	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
Committed	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
himself	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
making	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mohair	O
and	O
Bengaul	O
Silks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trimer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Edmunds	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Longhorne	I-place
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
agalnst	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
into	O
Fanchurch-street	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
stay	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
yet	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denyed	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
being	O
possitive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dyed	O
Linnen	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Beaker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Old	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
Beaker	O
's	O
Yard	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Callender	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cloath	O
and	O
departed	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Apprentices	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
unto	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
detain	O
it	O
no	O
longer	O
that	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
surrender	O
it	O
without	O
any	O
hesitation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
appearing	O
by	O
possitive	O
Testimony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
alias	O
Parkham	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
Chamberpot	O
,	O
Candle-stick	O
,	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
agreeing	O
for	O
a	O
furnished	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
up	O
about	O
Business	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
without	O
returning	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
she	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
such	O
Lodging	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
ever	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
offering	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
differing	O
in	O
their	O
Account	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
divers	O
Counterfeit	O
Pieces	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Groats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Paylor	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
had	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
Coined	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
imitation	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Stamp	O
made	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
was	O
assisting	O
to	O
him	O
therein	O
,	O
especially	O
in	O
washing	O
or	O
silvering	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
in	O
puting	O
them	O
away	O
as	O
Currant	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
Apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
much	O
Counterfeit	O
Moneys	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Stamp	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Buttler	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Treason	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
in	O
no	O
wise	O
possitive	O
against	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Hair	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
like	O
Indictment	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
amounting	O
to	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
away	O
Counterfeit	O
pieces	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
New	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
suspition	O
of	O
their	O
Coining	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
arising	O
from	O
the	O
Latter	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
a	O
Coining	O
Stamp	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
known	O
actually	O
to	O
Coin	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
like	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
pieces	O
,	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
New	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
stress	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
only	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
puting	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
his	O
Coining	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
inquisition	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
Killing	O
Jone	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
Silk-twister	O
s	O
,	O
worked	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
difference	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Formers	O
giving	O
the	O
Latter	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Neck	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
it	O
so	O
far	O
increased	O
by	O
the	O
throwing	O
of	O
Bobings	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
and	O
provoking	O
Words	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
forcibly	O
,	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
causing	O
thereby	O
a	O
Blackness	O
on	O
her	O
Eye	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Kick	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Hips	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
fell	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
Dyed	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Chirurgeons	O
who	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
ill-usage	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
from	O
the	O
Effects	O
of	O
a	O
Feaver	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Mallice	O
fore-thought	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Dyed	O
of	O
a	O
Natural	O
Death	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Catharine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
alias	O
Kelley	B-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lecount	I-pers
,	O
and	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
43	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Hall	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Testimony	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
had	O
picked	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carryed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor-Tavern	B-place
near	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
mentioned	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
leaving	O
the	O
house	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Lecount	O
,	O
had	O
bid	O
the	O
Drawer	O
conceal	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
procured	O
the	O
Robery	O
to	O
be	O
Compounded	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
only	O
that	O
her	O
Companion	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Night-walker	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Candle-stick	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
snuffing	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuffick	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Propriety	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
being	O
only	O
in	O
her	O
Trust	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
defect	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
yet	O
a	O
further	O
Prosecution	O
ordered	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
a	O
true	O
owner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Fortier	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
George	B-pers
Calow	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
near	O
Kensington	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Crevat	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Principal	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Calow	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
one	O
Davis	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Kensington	O
between	O
10.	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
met	O
six	O
Men	O
who	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
strip	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
bound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Wigg	O
and	O
Voice	O
,	O
it	O
then	O
being	O
a	O
Moon-shiney	O
Night	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whom	O
afterward	O
he	O
had	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
himself	O
had	O
a	O
Chamber	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Davis	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Calow	O
were	O
Robbed	O
at	O
the	O
day	O
and	O
time	O
specified	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
his	O
Breeches	O
a	O
Key	O
and	O
a	O
Tobaco	O
Box	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
possitive	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
laboured	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Calow	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
and	O
Entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Meggs	I-pers
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
Brainford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lying	O
Drunk	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the-Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
after	O
ward	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Walks	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Garden	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Minchin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wanham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
five	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
took	O
opportunity	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
and	O
Closet-door	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Trunk	O
where	O
the	O
Apparrel	O
was	O
;	O
yet	O
not	O
so	O
silently	O
but	O
the	O
Noise	O
discovered	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Minchin	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Companion	O
escaped	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
Court	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
alledged	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
an	O
Iron	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
himtending	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Rhenish-Wine	O
,	O
five	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Clarret	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
sixty	O
Glass-Bottles	O
,	O
from	O
Annis	B-pers
Kinsmal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Charwoman	O
,	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
purloin	O
the	O
Liquors	O
and	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
twenty	O
five	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
though	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
took	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
not	O
attempting	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
she	O
intended	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Lye	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Born	O
Dead	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
receiving	O
Clipings	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
for	O
hiding	O
and	O
concealing	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Melting	O
Instruments	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
Materials	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
having	O
been	O
Acquitted	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
buying	O
and	O
disposing	O
of	O
Clippings	O
to	O
his	O
profit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plainly	O
made	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Barronet	O
,	O
Scituate	O
in	O
Bromley	B-place
by	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
ten	O
Peuter-Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Peuter	O
Cestern	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
resolving	O
to	O
watch	O
who	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
thence	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
they	O
started	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
hid	O
up-upon	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
whom	O
as	O
they	O
suppose	O
by	O
their	O
Actions	O
and	O
discourse	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
the	O
Peuter	O
and	O
Brass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
geting	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pleading	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
buying	O
Clippings	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
two	O
Bars	O
of	O
Standard	O
silver	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Clippings	O
melted	O
down	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
with	O
other	O
suspitious	O
Marks	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Coifs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Callow	B-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
groundless	O
,	O
&	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Scarse	O
,	O
a	O
Night-fall	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Court	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
relating	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Broad-Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
sometimes	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
no	O
wise	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
otherwise	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
falsely	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
proper	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
Calico	O
Curtains	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
her	O
unlawful	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
altogether	O
capable	O
of	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
consideration	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Kings	O
highway	O
,	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
much	O
disguised	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
&	O
getting	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
was	O
driven	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
him	O
directions	O
whither	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
.	O
so	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
received	O
,	O
he	O
carryed	O
him	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
whose	O
Coach	O
he	O
drove	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
advice	O
Mr	O
,	O
Fletcher	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
challenged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
many	O
eminent	O
testimonys	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
apparant	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
3	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cows	O
,	O
viz	O
one	O
from	O
Esther	B-pers
Wellefar	I-pers
,	O
another	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Allan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
17	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictments	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lorina	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Embroidered	O
Staies	O
,	O
a	O
Petty-coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
in	O
Court	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
excuse	O
or	O
deny	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Haire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Haire	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
uttering	O
false	O
Monys	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
on	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
power	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Commands	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
l.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Ferman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
no	O
Witness	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
stole	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Account	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Durone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
but	O
being	O
over	O
taken	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
pleaded	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
wrong	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivelous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Cathrines	I-place
by	O
the	B-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
a	O
Sail	O
maker	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
Mary	B-pers
Sidercomb	I-pers
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
not	O
exceeding	O
eight	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
undertook	O
the	O
Wardship	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
Mother	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
obliged	O
herto	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Girl	O
testified	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Violence	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
occasioned	O
much	O
bloud	O
and	O
corruption	O
to	O
issue	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
forced	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
of	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
under	O
those	O
circumstances	O
the	O
Law	O
requires	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gervas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Modena	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
by	O
entering	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Fring	O
'd	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
a	O
Laced	O
Coif	O
,	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
discovered	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offering	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Morrice	B-pers
Duaun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cable	O
Rope	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Foreland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
made	O
Forelands	O
Servant	O
drunk	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
cut	O
the	O
Cable	O
mentioned	O
from	O
a	O
longer	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Boat	O
conveyed	O
it	O
on	O
Shoar	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pinner	O
Caps	O
Laced	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Muzling	O
Apron	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cap	O
or	O
Pinner	O
and	O
Muzling	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
landlords	O
Daughter	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
Harding	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pleading	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Casar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
uknown	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalaine	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Gunning	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
confessing	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
finding	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
entered	O
whilest	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Nnowland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Candle-stick	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Luttrel	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
free	O
Access	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Luttrels	O
house	O
,	O
had	O
watched	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confesed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elenor	B-pers
Rooks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
a	O
Whistle	O
of	O
silver	O
with	O
Bells	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Whistle	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
though	O
without	O
the	O
Bells	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Defence	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
consideration	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
of	O
small	O
concern	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute-string	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Silks	O
,	O
but	O
seeming	O
to	O
like	O
none	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
shuffle	O
the	O
parcel	O
mentioned	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
to	O
depart	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
only	O
alledging	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Hide	O
a	O
great	O
Shop-lift	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Borrough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Casement	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hair	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
uttering	O
false	O
Moneys	O
knowingly	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Latter	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
another	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Name	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
likewise	O
confessing	O
the	O
like	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
alledging	O
only	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leanord	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Crape	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
with	O
Brass	O
Clasps	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
proffering	O
the	O
Bible	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
name	O
being	O
written	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Apprehended	O
whereupon	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Worsted	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
greatly	O
denying	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barow	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Leviston	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
Richard	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
confederates	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
who	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
shared	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
passed	O
upon	O
9	O
Persons	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
,	O
Hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Quarter	O
'd	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortier	I-pers
,	O
Laurana	O
Carey	B-pers
,	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gervas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barowalias	I-pers
Leviston	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
only	O
.	O
Persons	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
9.	O
viz	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Duron	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Minchal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Raply	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
3.	O
viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	O
Winson	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Holles	I-pers
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Ellenor	O
Rooks	O
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Morrice	B-pers
Duaun	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Sentenced	O
for	O
Trespasses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
4	O
viz	O
.	O
J.	O
M.	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
till	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
each	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
T.	O
M.	O
and	O
Michael	O
Haire	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
20	O
a	O
Marks	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Weeks	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
