TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
and	O
1st	O
.	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1687	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Camport	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
Roger	O
Ark	O
ist	O
Henry	B-pers
Mortlack	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hatly	I-pers
Thomas	O
Car	O
y	O
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Janes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	B-pers
Jury	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrundel	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
John	B-pers
Francnling	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Treyford	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
John	B-pers
Turney	I-pers
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Skiping	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
alias	O
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Johanes	O
In	O
Nubibus	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
person	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
or	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stockall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Dyed	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before-mentioned	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
divers	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Men	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
washing	O
themselves	O
in	O
a	O
Pond	O
Scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
one	O
Bob	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
seized	O
on	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Lad	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
wash	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
and	O
a	O
Dog	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Dog	O
upon	O
the	O
Naked	O
Boy	O
,	O
which	O
yet	O
did	O
no	O
other	O
harm	O
than	O
take	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
passing	O
on	O
towards	O
Lambs	O
Conduit	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
just	O
gotten	O
his	O
Shirt	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
again	O
set	O
the	O
Dog	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
served	O
him	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
after	O
him	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
near	O
to	O
Griffiths	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Rumour	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
Rable	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
about	O
Griffith	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
Boys	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
refused	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Griffith	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Neighbouring	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
their	O
help	O
seized	O
upon	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
assailants	O
,	O
and	O
forcing	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
kept	O
them	O
there	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Rable	O
increasing	O
every	O
Moment	O
and	O
assaulting	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
greater	O
violence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
remaining	O
obstinate	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
setting	O
at	O
liberty	O
those	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
unless	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
their	O
Masters	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
insisting	O
much	O
upon	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Damage	O
sustained	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Houghton	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
fetch	O
'd	O
about	O
five	O
files	O
of	O
Granadiers	O
when	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
leaving	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
guard	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
marched	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
to	O
oppos	O
the	O
Rable	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Numerous	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
so	O
ho	O
dy-charged	O
from	O
the	O
Banks	O
and	O
advantageous	O
places	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Souldiers	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
bruised	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
they	O
Fired	O
three	O
Pieces	O
but	O
only	O
with	O
Powder	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Storm	O
increasing	O
,	O
Griffith	O
bad	O
them	O
charge	O
with	O
Ball	O
and	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
Sworn	O
viz	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
be	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
Fi	O
e	O
and	O
Kill	O
the	O
Dogs	O
,	O
or	O
they't	O
kill	O
us	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Johane	O
In	O
.	O
Nubibus	O
gave	O
Fire	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Shot	O
Stockall	O
was	O
Killed	O
.	O
Griffith	O
coming	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
declared	O
what	O
Damage	O
he	O
sustained	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Cattle	O
refusing	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
frequently	O
washing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
persons	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
that	O
killed	O
Stockdale	O
but	O
being	O
Bruised	O
and	O
Wounded	O
,	O
he	O
retired	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Roxfords	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
sent	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
Grannadiers	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
news	O
brought	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
King	O
being	O
possitive	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
give	O
order	O
Charge	O
and	O
Fire	O
with	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
attesting	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Stock	O
all	O
was	O
Killed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Houghton	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Granadiers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Obedia	B-pers
Bows	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Baston	I-pers
,	O
are	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
Riotously	O
and	O
Tumulteously	O
assembling	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
active	O
themselves	O
in	O
opposing	O
the	O
Authority	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
suppress	O
the	O
Tumult	O
and	O
,	O
order	O
;	O
but	O
also	O
industrious	O
in	O
Encouraging	O
others	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
throwing	O
of	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
Stones	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Guards	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
against	O
Baston	O
itwas	O
more	O
particularly	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
having	O
wrested	O
a	O
Musquet	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
then	O
in	O
Arms	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
forcible	O
blow	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
wounded	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
denying	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
unhappy	O
disturbance	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ryot	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elias	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Springham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Lemar	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Giles	O
Tro	O
der	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
Riotously	O
and	O
Tumultuously	O
Assembling	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
they	O
Beat	O
and	O
much	O
Bruised	O
one	O
Rust	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
Aided	O
the	O
Constables	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
only	O
against	O
Jones	O
,	O
Kendrick	O
,	O
and	O
Springham	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Ryot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
against	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
possitive	O
Proof	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
ways	O
Aiding	O
or	O
Abeting	O
,	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
like	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
Riotously	O
and	O
Tumultuoutly	O
Assembled	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
500	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
forcibly	O
entered	O
and	O
pulled	O
down	O
the	O
Shead	O
or	O
Musique	O
Booth	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
breaking	O
and	O
destroying	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
actually	O
instrumental	O
therein	O
the	O
Jury	O
round	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Ryot	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Ogleby	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Golden	O
Seal	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapple	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chapple	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
they	O
over	O
power	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
.	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Yard	O
,	O
yet	O
upon	O
his	O
crying	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
after	O
some	O
resistance	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
rather	O
excusing	O
It	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Powr	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Engls	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Confessed	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
all	O
others	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parsons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Monys	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
justly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
Youth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
questioned	O
but	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Waggon	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
Sum	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Coat	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
given	O
how	O
it	O
as	O
placed	O
or	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
supposing	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
fall	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Read	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
al	O
98	O
l.	O
in	O
Monys	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Frim	I-pers
of	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
on	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
confessed	O
to	O
Indictment	O
,	O
pleading	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olives	I-place
Silverstreet	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
for	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nevit	I-pers
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
packing	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
secured	O
e	O
're	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
pursuing	O
or	O
following	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
,	O
he	O
accidentally	O
blundered	O
up	O
the	O
wrong	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Musling	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
she	O
prosecutors	O
to	O
bargain	O
for	O
Musling	O
;	O
the	O
Parcel	O
specified	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
departure	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confessed	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
pleading	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
Monys	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Customer	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
some	O
standing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
that	O
might	O
probably	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Mony	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Stains	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Goud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
six	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Whistle	O
,	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
King	O
,	O
lately	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
being	O
shewed	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
another	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
paying	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
departed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
instantly	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Notice	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sometime	O
after	O
found	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
stood	O
Committed	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
three	O
possitive	O
Oaths	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
party	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
other	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
could	O
commit	O
it	O
although	O
he	O
pleaded	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Fireing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
above	O
named	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Facts	O
committed	O
,	O
another	O
Maid	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
succeed	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
;	O
She	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
perswaded	O
the	O
other	O
Maid	O
to	O
betake	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
for	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
she	O
filled	O
a	O
large	O
Iron	O
Chafing-Dish	O
with	O
live	O
Wood	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
part	O
of	O
Faggot	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
set	O
the	O
Chafing	O
Dish	O
in	O
the	O
Pantry	O
or	O
Closet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
upermost	O
Shelf	O
next	O
the	O
Cealing	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
leaving	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
departed	O
with	O
a	O
structure	O
set	O
in	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chasing-Dish	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
with	O
ther	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
Locking	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
taking	O
they	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
missing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wondering	O
at	O
her	O
stay	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
espying	O
the	O
Fire	O
had	O
the	O
Courage	O
and	O
good	O
Luck	O
to	O
quench	O
it	O
e	O
're	O
it	O
did	O
any	O
other	O
harm	O
than	O
burn	O
through	O
the	O
Ceeling	O
and	O
Boards	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
Flore	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
returned	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Firing	O
the	O
house	O
she	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Maid	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Harwood	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
Lady	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
attended	O
the	O
wicked	O
Enterprise	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
far	O
otherwise	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flowerd	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Philip	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lumbard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
her	O
departure	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
discovered	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
where	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
whichshe	O
had	O
owned	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
these	O
and	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Cower	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Rescued	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
since	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
confessed	O
the	O
stealing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
perceived	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
hid	O
,	O
he	O
forced	O
his	O
way	O
down	O
and	O
leaped	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Shead	O
that	O
was	O
backward	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
only	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
a	O
Man	O
dropped	O
them	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
within	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Pettelarcenary	O
;	O
no	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
St.	I-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bever-Hat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
Fleet-Bridge	B-place
he	O
met	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Swearing	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Friend	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
Tom	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
assaulted	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
carried	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
abused	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
other	O
Affairs	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
that	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Consternation	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
and	O
darkness	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kidwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Musique	B-place
Booth	I-place
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Grays-Inn	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Booth	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Quarreling	O
with	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
within	O
two	O
hours	O
he	O
Dyed	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
had	O
likewise	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
Swearing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Kill	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
pursued	O
his	O
Companion	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
making	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sexton	I-pers
of	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
French	O
Pistols	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Friday-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
Sexton	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
two	O
Woman	O
picking	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
making	O
pursute	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pleading	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mount	I-pers
Joy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
putting	O
away	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Mony	O
for	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
,	O
for	O
Lucre	O
and	O
Gain	O
Sake	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
more	O
appearing	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
away	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Monys	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
Guineas	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
by	O
the	O
discharge	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaden	O
with	O
Bullet	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Grey	O
,	O
being	O
late	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
that	O
were	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Scuffles	O
Grey	O
was	O
Knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Head	O
Broke	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
Stafford	O
that	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
having	O
fetch	O
'd	O
his	O
Pistols	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
Pistol	O
Cock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
Threats	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
that	O
was	O
procured	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
being	O
then	O
busie	O
in	O
dressing	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
intreated	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
and	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
accordingly	O
Grey	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
Stafford	O
upon	O
pushing	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
being	O
struck	O
at	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
whose	O
Staff	O
fell	O
short	O
,	O
fired	O
his	O
Pistols	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Bullet	O
passing	O
through	O
Norman	O
's	O
,	O
Thigh	O
,	O
entred	O
Greys	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
within	O
six	O
days	O
they	O
Dyed	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
excuse	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
divers	O
Chirurgeons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
Eminent	O
Quality	O
,	O
to	O
attest	O
that	O
having	O
formerly	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
his	O
Scul	O
was	O
Tree	O
pan	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
since	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
part	O
been	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Distracted	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Sheepside	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
so	O
much	O
Monys	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
for	O
otherwise	O
her	O
Friends	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
possitive	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littleford	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cornwhite	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edmund	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Cony-Court	B-place
in	O
Grays	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Point	O
Cravat	O
;	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
a	O
wrought	O
Bed	O
Silver	O
wrought	O
Cushions	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Chamber	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
and	O
in	O
many	O
Locks	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Cornwhite	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
Littleford	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Monys	O
&	O
offering	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breaking	O
,	O
and	O
Cornwhite	O
pleading	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
under	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
being	O
an	O
Upholsterers	O
Good	O
that	O
had	O
failed	O
in	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
profit	O
thereby	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murther	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabing	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
happend	O
that	O
day	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Daugbters	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
beat	O
and	O
misused	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
retired	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
sullen	O
Mood	O
shut	O
himself	O
up	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
Notice	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
erpose	O
and	O
reconcile	O
the	O
Difference	O
;	O
when	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
with	O
her	O
Daughter	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
retired	O
to	O
his	O
Closet	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
at	O
their	O
Perril	O
,	O
but	O
sore	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
daring	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
threw	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
furious	O
manner	O
Rushing	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
dawn	O
Sword	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
her	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Dyed	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
they	O
had	O
teased	O
him	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
Mad	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
breaking	O
in	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pressed	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	O
Barnet	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
from	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Tunstall	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
being	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
Grass	O
to	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Dyer	O
a	O
Coach	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Mistress	O
to	O
Ride	O
a	O
Journey	O
and	O
Sold	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Necessity	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pay	O
'd	O
back	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Minchal	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Embroidered	O
Housing	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holster	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Bevil	B-pers
Greenvil	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Sir	O
Bevil	O
's	O
Stable	O
in	O
the	O
Camp	O
time	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
being	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
thence	O
,	O
Stockwell	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
in	O
Kings-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
as	O
a	O
Suspitious	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Embroidered	O
Housing	O
and	O
Holster-Caps	O
to	O
a	O
Taylor	O
in	O
Truck	O
for	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
two	O
Souldiers	O
they	O
met	O
coming	O
from	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Minchal	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Stockwell	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Beaker	O
.	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Ratclif	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
watching	O
his	O
opportunity	O
he	O
stole	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Beaker	O
fled	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
running	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Horse	O
that	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Travel	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
six	O
Hogs-Heads	O
of	O
Sweet	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
six	O
Bags	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
and	O
a	O
Wine-Press	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bargain	O
of	O
Partenership	O
between	O
Travel	O
,	O
who	O
set	O
the	O
rest	O
on	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
in	O
Carts	O
at	O
Noon	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
adjudged	O
it	O
no	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gourdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
Filing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Curant	O
Monys	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
as	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
last	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
Hampton	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Sansbury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Cows	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cows	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
only	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
own	O
which	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
over	O
Night	O
receive	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
distinguish	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gravel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
or	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ladle	O
and	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Longfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
opportunity	O
to	O
con	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pleading	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
sometimes	O
used	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
towards	O
house-keeping	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
some	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mlicent	B-pers
Blackley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
Sleveless	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
seen	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
upon	O
her	O
departure	O
missed	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Locton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fullham	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Garden	O
gathering	O
Herbs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
upon	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
awar	O
and	O
Kick	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
stooping	O
,	O
then	O
stopped	O
her	O
Mouth	O
full	O
of	O
Stones	O
and	O
Gravel	O
,	O
and	O
striped	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
Gag	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
coming	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
fled	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
her	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
some	O
distance	O
thence	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
comeing	O
from	O
Oxford	O
and	O
lay	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
at	O
Stains	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
being	O
positive	O
in	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Hammers	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
Horse-Nails	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hidden	O
and	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
meer	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Josias	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fortenham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
for	O
their	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Noise	O
they	O
made	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
they	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
;	O
yet	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
nothing	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass-Pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Twist	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hankering	O
about	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
before	O
lost	O
divers	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Eye	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
suffering	O
her	O
to	O
enter	O
his	O
out-house	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
scarcely	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
before	O
he	O
seized	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
within	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Pettelarcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Spencer	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entered	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Hat	O
to	O
dress	O
,	O
yet	O
pretending	O
haste	O
departed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Melting	O
down	O
Clippings	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
and	O
Defacers	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
quantitie	O
of	O
12	O
Ounce	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
Working	O
Silver-Smith	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
got	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
burn	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
)	O
some	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
in	O
the	O
Forge	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Cole-Fire	O
,	O
when	O
sending	O
for	O
Charcole	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
he	O
deposed	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
departure	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
where	O
found	O
there	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Melting-Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Hoop	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
saying	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
made	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
order	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Ink-Case	O
mended	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clippings	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstancially	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkwell	I-place
wasTryed	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
uttering	O
divers	O
false	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
pieces	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
in	O
imitation	O
and	O
likeness	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
only	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
away	O
bad	O
Monys	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
rubed	O
a	O
Brass	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
pass	O
Currant	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Coining	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Susanah	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
and	O
Susanah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Peuter	O
Dish	O
,	O
five	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
by	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
Susanah	O
Morrice	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
saw	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Peuter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Susanah	O
Lewis	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
her	O
late	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
concluded	O
this	O
insufficent	O
and	O
Acquited	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Evil	O
Gold	O
,	O
40	O
s	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cousin	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
they	O
both	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
they	O
did	O
by	O
breaking	O
up	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Thacker	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
keeping	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
Clipping	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
like	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
having	O
likewise	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
File	O
dust	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
formerly	O
lodged	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
upon	O
taking	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Buff	O
Leather	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
glass	O
the	O
Landlord	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
black	O
marks	O
,	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Leather	O
that	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Monys	O
was	O
usually	O
rubb	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
proceeded	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
File	O
dust	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
made	O
at	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Boran	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
,	O
entred	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Almond	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
1ast	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
50	O
s.	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Utting	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monys	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
80	O
l	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dunch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Felonies	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomazan	B-pers
Tully	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Staies	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cravat	O
,	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
and	O
twelve	O
Forehead	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Manzer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Facts	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
and	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
wife	O
upon	O
a	O
Sleveless	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
being	O
all	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hats	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Worsly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
30	O
s.	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
late	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
named	O
King	O
,	O
intruded	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
had	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
bit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
King	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
snack	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
termed	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
certainly	O
when	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
what	O
place	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
Committed	O
were	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pinners	O
,	O
twenty	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Musling	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Point	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Henrieta	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
suspected	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
Point	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
be	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
defective	O
against	O
Evans	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Boroughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Counterpain	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
as	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
two	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
Committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
pleading	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Islington	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
owner	O
appear-in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Charles	B-pers
Lanfield	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dyed	O
;	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Decreased	O
being	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
the	O
Latter	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
many	O
Menaces	O
bid	O
the	O
former	O
draw	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
pacifie	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pressing	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
Retreated	O
,	O
forced	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
whereof	O
he	O
Dyed	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
along	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Maxfield	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sedgley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Allhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Taster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
,	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
frivelous	O
or	O
rather	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
grounded	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
troubled	O
one	O
Captain	O
Graunt	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Kidnaping	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Sattain	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
Shifts	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
eight	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
a	O
Trunk	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
they	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
viz	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
S	O
-	O
r	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Stochwell	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
1	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uting	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
that	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
13	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ogleby	I-pers
,	O
J	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kidwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
alias	O
Knowles	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littleford	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Minchal	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
M	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
who	O
had	O
incur	O
'd	O
the	O
like	O
Penalty	O
,	O
was	O
repreived	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
as	O
Pettilarcenary	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Berns	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Lacton	O
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Women	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Enquiry	O
of	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
Impannel	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
only	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Sentenced	O
as	O
Ryoters	O
,	O
were	O
8	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Baston	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Obadia	O
Bows	O
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Springham	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
These	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Ryot	O
,	O
where	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
from	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
to	O
Griffith	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
first	O
Committed	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
five	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
during	O
the	O
Twelve-Month	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
suspend	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
the	O
Sentence	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Kings	O
pleasure	O
was	O
known	O
in	O
relation	O
thereto	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
being	O
refused	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
already	O
incur	O
'd	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
Pardon	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
by	O
Counsel	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
allowed	O
in	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
great	O
Moment	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
suspended	O
his	O
Sentence	O
and	O
consult	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
