TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
14th	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
14th	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Kenelme	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Kenton	I-pers
Stephan	B-pers
Humphryes	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Sinah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eighteenth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
by	O
stopping	O
its	O
Breath	O
with	O
a	O
Cloath	O
put	O
in	O
its	O
Mouth	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
,	O
the	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
all	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
denying	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
all	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
Dead	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloath	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rag	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
something	O
Warm	O
,	O
they	O
tried	O
all	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
recover	O
Life	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
little	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Cloath	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
her	O
Senses	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
Light-headed	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
wherein	O
,	O
If	O
the	O
Child	O
be	O
found	O
Dead	O
and	O
,	O
Concealed	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
were	O
so	O
Born	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
Concealing	O
it	O
,	O
shall	O
suffer	O
Death	O
as	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
except	O
she	O
can	O
prove	O
by	O
one	O
Witness	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
so	O
Concealed	O
was	O
Born	O
Dead	O
.	O
Upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Claudius	B-pers
Bertin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
one	O
Pendulum	O
Gold	O
Clock	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
plain	O
Gold	O
Clock	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Barrow	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
Mr.	O
Barrow	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Write	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
Writing	O
,	O
he	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
spoke	O
by	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Italian	O
Coffee-house	O
:	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Vindication	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rabbet	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
from	O
Uriah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
his	O
Master	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
Milliner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
took	O
the	O
Hood	O
off	O
the	O
Stall	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woollnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
changing	O
of	O
Clipt	O
mony	O
,	O
for	O
broad	O
mony	O
and	O
allowing	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
proffit	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
often	O
to	O
a	O
Vintners	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
several	O
persons	O
who	O
brought	O
large	O
mony	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
Clipt	O
mony	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
thereof	O
;	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
denying	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
English	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crayford	I-pers
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
idle	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Basil	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Basil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Beating	O
their	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
Starving	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
any	O
Blows	O
or	O
Bruises	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
two	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
49	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
hawled	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
there	O
Rifled	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wholly	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
Binding	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Gutton	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Veasy	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
two	O
Rabbets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pullet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
main	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Smith	O
's	O
Boy	O
that	O
had	O
Run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
to	O
Ingratiate	O
himself	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
had	O
Impeach	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Alice	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
Eighteen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mumford	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Ashpoole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chattris	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
Edward	B-pers
Wybourne	I-pers
,	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
dangerous	O
Wounds	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
endangered	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Porringer	O
to	O
drink	O
Punch	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
carryed	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Porringer	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Porringer	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gallamore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Little	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
proffered	O
to	O
Sell	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Justice	O
Harriot	O
of	O
Islington	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Norton-Folgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Pattens	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
taking	O
Avery	O
with	O
the	O
Cloak	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Mills	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tinny	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
mortally	O
Wounding	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
three	O
being	O
Common	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
had	O
fallen	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
declared	O
,	O
his	O
Brain	O
was	O
shatter	O
'd	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
Barbarously	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
held	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
Wade	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Womans	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
before	O
Sr.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shores	I-pers
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Practitioner	O
at	O
that	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burgarly	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
News	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Serge	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
8	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
her	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
Brokers	O
hands	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
Pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
Pawned	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Familiar	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Irish-man	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Tipler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
Tipler	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterward	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Claudius	B-pers
Bertin	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Box	O
guilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Prince	O
's	O
Metal	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
guilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Steel	O
Tooth-pick	O
Case	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
saying	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
A	O
Third	O
Indictment	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Prince	O
's	O
Metal	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
by	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
desiring	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
wearing	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
restored	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
thetime	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
not	O
bringing	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
5	O
l.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Forwood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Olmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbered	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
She	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
missed	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
private	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
surprized	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
15	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carwood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Taffety	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heskins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Demorrey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
8	O
silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bothvies	I-pers
Widdow	O
:	O
He	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Pippins	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
and	O
stole	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Keys	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
valued	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
thing	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Old	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
upon	O
him	O
neither	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Ann	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
two	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Pitch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Susanna	O
Long-fellow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Witton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
Pinner	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
but	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Territ	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Distracted	O
Person	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Prison	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
back	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Discharged	O
as	O
a	O
Lunatick	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Soucks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Abrah	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
Tooth-pick	O
Case	O
garnished	O
with	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Prince	O
's	O
Mettle	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
another	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stole	O
by	O
Claudius	B-pers
Bertin	I-pers
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
such	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
affirmed	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Tooth-pick	O
Case	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Posession	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
his	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hayhurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Killing	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twitnam	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Soldier	O
s	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
about	O
feeding	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Tent	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Wounds	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
also	O
affirmed	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
of	O
Dowse	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
one	O
Inch	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Quarrelling	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threatned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Shoot	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Fight	O
him	O
,	O
giving	O
great	O
provocations	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retired	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dungan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Cloak	O
Lac	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Hair	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Ward	B-pers
Deakes	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
putting	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
concerning	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
play	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
A	O
Third	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
of	O
Ward	B-pers
Deakes	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Arms	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
endangered	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ward	B-pers
Deakes	I-pers
going	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Cloak	O
afore-mentioned	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Price	O
,	O
in	O
Milford	O
Lane	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
those	O
Words	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Upon	O
the	O
Complaint	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Price	O
,	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
Bound	O
over	O
to	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
Bound	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
.	O
Joice	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
alias	O
Sutton	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
thirty	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
sixty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
64	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Barber	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Holton	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
Guinea	O
's	O
;	O
The	O
stockings	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Gilmore	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
ThievingLane	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Gilmore	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Flasket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevats	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
five	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
Butter	O
in	O
the	O
Mornings	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Flasket	O
Empty	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
also	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
she	O
passed	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Flasket	O
Empty	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Collington	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Cooks	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
sent	O
out	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
gave	O
White	O
Mercury	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
being	O
great	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
Poyson	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
Born	O
Alive	O
,	O
continued	O
Languishing	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Died	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Poyson	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Midwife	O
or	O
Chirurgeon	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Kennersly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Dram	O
Cups	O
:	O
The	O
Watchman	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
Composition	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
and	O
Oliver	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Flowred	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sattin	O
Stayes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
North	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpworth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
also	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessorys	O
.	O
Barlow	O
and	O
Morris	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Sentence	O
for	O
standing	O
Mute	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
that	O
stands	O
Mute	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
Plead	O
upon	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
laid	O
Naked	O
upon	O
the	O
bare	O
Earth	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
something	O
to	O
cover	O
his	O
Privy	O
Parts	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Feet	O
uncovered	O
,	O
one	O
Arm	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
to	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Arm	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
shall	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
upon	O
his	O
Body	O
Iron	O
and	O
Stone	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
bear	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
drink	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
next	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
except	O
Running	O
Water	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
morsels	O
of	O
Barley	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
shall	O
be	O
his	O
Diet	O
till	O
he	O
Die	O
Yet	O
they	O
persisted	O
Obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Accessorys	O
were	O
Discharged	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sentence	O
was	O
again	O
read	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
shewn	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Priests	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
Absolution	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
;	O
yet	O
they	O
remained	O
Obstinate	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
Sentence	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
returned	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
out	O
of	O
favour	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Adjourned	O
till	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
Barlow	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
another	O
Jury	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Richard	O
Bromfield	O
Roberts	O
Minns	O
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hatway	I-pers
George	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Barlow	O
had	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
Appleby	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
the	O
goods	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Morris	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Door	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Broken	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Afterward	O
Oliver	O
Morris	O
being	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
remained	O
Willful	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
five	O
Half	O
hundred	O
Weights	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
Plead	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
Record	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Barlow	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Morris	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
continued	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
4	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
Oliver	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Sinah	O
Jones	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
were	O
sworn	O
and	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
11	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Claudius	B-pers
Berton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dalamore	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Cary	O
John	B-pers
Avory	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Demorry	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cornel	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hayhurst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dungan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
8	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooly	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Forwood	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Kennersly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Dungan	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Maypole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
thro	O
'	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
Water-Lane	O
Ann	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
sureties	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
