TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
5th	O
.	O
and	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Session	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
and	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
1688	O
:	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stanners	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Purefoy	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lamas	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lucar	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Glinn	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Peddon	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Boate	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kensie	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holison	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Sitsick	I-pers
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
a	O
Bayliff	O
's	O
Follower	O
.	O
Upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bailing	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
under	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
the	O
Bail-Bond	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
due	O
Regard	O
,	O
was	O
signed	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
.	O
Of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Writ	O
taken	O
out	O
to	O
Arrest	O
him	O
,	O
procured	O
a	O
Supersedias	O
by	O
putting	O
in	O
Bail	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Marshals	O
Court	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Head-Bayliff	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
unbecoming	O
Oath	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
attempting	O
with	O
a	O
reviewed	O
Writ	O
to	O
attack	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
and	O
his	O
Followers	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mischievous	O
things	O
,	O
whereby	O
his	O
Life	O
was	O
endangered	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
when	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pressing	O
on	O
,	O
received	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Arm	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
When	O
upon	O
weighing	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Witherly	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Roger	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
or	O
Bell	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Contest	O
with	O
a	O
Party	O
in	O
whose	O
Company	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
whil'st	O
they	O
were	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strugling	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
received	O
a	O
Bruise	O
in	O
his	O
Members	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Bruises	O
occasioned	O
by	O
that	O
Encounter	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
Urine	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Swelling	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Languishment	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
only	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
late	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
no	O
Demand	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
some	O
days	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
elsewhere	O
dropt	O
,	O
Glover	O
having	O
likewise	O
inferred	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
as	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
stole	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
promise	O
of	O
a	O
Reward	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
found	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
and	O
moreover	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
candid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cropley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Perry	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
.	O
When	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Lane	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
had	O
her	O
Pocket	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
applying	O
herself	O
for	O
the	O
Recovery	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
some	O
persons	O
about	O
Newgate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
coming	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
upon	O
stricter	O
Examination	O
,	O
but	O
weakly	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Guinea	O
's	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
104	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Writings	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
committing	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
Ward	I-place
about	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
therein	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Oliver	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
,	O
which	O
hapned	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
space	O
,	O
not	O
exceeding	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
it	O
proving	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
means	O
where	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
by	O
urging	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
deposit	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
true	O
Owner	O
might	O
be	O
inquired	O
out	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Discourse	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
consideration	O
no	O
proof	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
or	O
purloining	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Southby	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
six	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
suspected	O
and	O
taxed	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
finding	O
10	O
s.	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
within	O
the	O
last	O
Year	O
he	O
had	O
defrauded	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
In	O
Objection	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
Confession	O
so	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
was	O
through	O
Fear	O
and	O
Constraint	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
roughly	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
extort	O
an	O
Acknowledgment	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
frankly	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
compulsion	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
further	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
have	O
gotten	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Monies	O
,	O
and	O
facilitate	O
the	O
Enterprize	O
without	O
Suspition	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Charles	B-pers
D'Laune	I-pers
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
at	O
somewhat	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
or	O
Cellar	O
Apartment	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
there	O
,	O
growing	O
incredulous	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
to	O
be	O
further	O
satisfied	O
.	O
And	O
thereupon	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
only	O
Two	O
Women	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
?	O
And	O
thereupon	O
some	O
other	O
words	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
challeng-him	O
at	O
first	O
to	O
Box	O
;	O
but	O
whil'st	O
he	O
was	O
laying	O
down	O
a	O
small	O
Stick	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
conjectured	O
,	O
the	O
Expectation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mathews	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
forcible	O
a	O
blow	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
or	O
Cane	O
,	O
that	O
stunning	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
languished	O
sensless	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
In	O
excuse	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
altogether	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Malice	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
,	O
what	O
in	O
him	O
lay	O
,	O
to	O
support	O
,	O
succor	O
,	O
and	O
contribute	O
to	O
his	O
Recovery	O
,	O
not	O
attempting	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Provocation	O
begun	O
and	O
continued	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hussy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Henric	I-pers
,	O
as	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hacket	O
,	O
in	O
compassing	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henric	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Ale	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
denied	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
proceeded	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
Swords	O
being	O
drawn	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Skirmish	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
pricked	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Henric	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
somewhat	O
before	O
,	O
died	O
Hacket	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
Henric	O
.	O
In	O
Extenuation	O
of	O
this	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
Henric	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
Sword	O
before	O
any	O
Wounds	O
were	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
render	O
'd	O
him	O
altogether	O
incapable	O
of	O
contributing	O
to	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
sum	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
approved	O
to	O
extend	O
to	O
Aiders	O
and	O
Abetters	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Party	O
immediately	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Hussy	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Morgan	B-pers
Donow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Taff	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
in	O
a	O
Rope-yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
like	O
number	O
,	O
being	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
occasioning	O
a	O
considerable	O
Disorder	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
gathering	O
a	O
concourse	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
his	O
Death	O
by	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
under	O
the	O
Left-arm	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
concourse	O
of	O
People	O
the	O
Commotion	O
occasioned	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
for	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
distinguish	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
utterly	O
protesting	O
himself	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
at	O
least	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
active	O
in	O
promoting	O
the	O
Disorder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Assault	O
was	O
given	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
directions	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
for	O
one	O
Margaret	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
pretending	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Kinswoman	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
he	O
departed	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Notice	O
'	O
,	O
when	O
immediately	O
upon	O
the	O
Boys	O
return	O
the	O
Tankardwas	O
missing	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
blundered	O
away	O
inconsiderately	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
And	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Overture	O
of	O
payment	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
till	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
computed	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
making	O
out	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
Trust	O
,	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
very	O
industrious	O
in	O
Painting	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
Journey-work	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
earned	O
18	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
in	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
missing	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
inquiry	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Southern	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
together	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Justification	O
,	O
insisting	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
Horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
though	O
without	O
Tolling	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Southwark	O
who	O
keeps	O
Livery	O
Stables	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
far	O
insinnated	O
into	O
the	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
though	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
;	O
That	O
it	O
created	O
in	O
them	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
belief	O
of	O
his	O
Innocence	O
as	O
to	O
Acquit	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
an	O
Irish-man	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
the	O
Terror	O
and	O
Disturbance	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Liege	O
Subjects	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Threatning	O
the	O
Subversion	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Against	O
whom	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Six-Bells	B-place
,	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
Discourse	O
that	O
arose	O
touching	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
present	O
Juncture	O
of	O
Affairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeming	O
inraged	O
that	O
the	O
Pope	O
and	O
his	O
Priests	O
were	O
disparaged	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Audible	O
Voice	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
Communion	O
with	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
were	O
Hereticks	O
;	O
and	O
deserved	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
Bellies	O
ripped	O
up	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
shortly	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
Bellies	O
ripped	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
reproved	O
for	O
these	O
uncharitable	O
Expressions	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Rage	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
he	O
obstinately	O
persevered	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
urging	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bred	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
We	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Protestants	O
,	O
were	O
Heretick	O
Dogs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
To	O
his	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
utterly	O
denying	O
to	O
have	O
spoken	O
the	O
words	O
;	O
but	O
confessing	O
he	O
was	O
warmed	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Pope	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
vilified	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
score	O
he	O
might	O
speak	O
unadvisedly	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
no	O
harm	O
to	O
the	O
Protestants	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
doing	O
Business	O
for	O
several	O
Eminent	O
of	O
that	O
Persuasion	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
highly	O
resenting	O
the	O
Expression	O
,	O
and	O
representing	O
the	O
anger	O
of	O
such	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Speech	O
against	O
an	O
Established	O
Religion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
misdisdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomazine	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Prentice	O
Boy	O
was	O
busie	O
in	O
looking	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
conveyed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pair	O
into	O
her	O
Bundle	O
or	O
otherways	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
'em	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
an	O
immediate	O
Discovery	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Lad	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
less	O
than	O
Seven	O
Groats	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
,	O
were	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
her	O
Reputation	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
ways	O
candid	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Eight	O
Lockets	O
,	O
composing	O
a	O
Bracelet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
18	O
l.	O
against	O
whom	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
to	O
speak	O
three	O
words	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
possess	O
himself	O
of	O
the	O
Lockets	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
Arm	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
like	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
haing	O
Things	O
common	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
Lockets	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
year	O
since	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
desirous	O
to	O
shake	O
off	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
finding	O
the	O
prosecution	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
little	O
weight	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
might	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
800	O
l.	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
engaged	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
,	O
or	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
return	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Turner	O
,	O
Robbed	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
and	O
pleading	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busie	O
about	O
his	O
Occasions	O
,	O
his	O
Till	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
having	O
Notice	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Parties	O
were	O
hankering	O
about	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
seize	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
confident	O
enough	O
altogether	O
,	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
Companion	O
,	O
disowned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
their	O
confederate	O
,	O
give	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
weighing	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Confession	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
Fear	O
,	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
of	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
perceiving	O
something	O
busle	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
turning	O
suddenly	O
;	O
had	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
a	O
hand	O
drawing	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Croud	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
perfectly	O
discern	O
the	O
person	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Outcry	O
he	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
in	O
his	O
Challenge	O
of	O
either	O
the	O
Man	O
or	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dubass	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Parish-Church	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Bassaw	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
Child	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
:	O
And	O
she	O
only	O
alledging	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
proof	O
of	O
its	O
so	O
being	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
calling	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
The	O
party	O
Jury	O
of	O
Natives	O
and	O
Alienes	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tipet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Linen	O
Silks	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
Robinson	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
contributed	O
towards	O
the	O
Discovery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Patience	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Paul	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Shirt	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
affirming	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Husbands	O
Shirts	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Church	I-pers
of	O
27	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
one	O
that	O
practised	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Night	O
walking	O
,	O
she	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
But	O
they	O
had	O
scarcely	O
begun	O
to	O
grow	O
familiar	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
dived	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
his	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
slip	O
,	O
hastening	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
concealing	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
escaped	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
he	O
Made	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
Overtures	O
of	O
Composition	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
utterly	O
denied	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
Tavern	O
;	O
alledging	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Common	O
Women	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
that	O
Night	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
whole	O
Cluster	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
and	O
might	O
more	O
probably	O
defraud	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
being	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
over	O
familiar	O
with	O
her	O
whil'st	O
they	O
were	O
toying	O
,	O
she	O
forgot	O
not	O
her	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
eased	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
,	O
upon	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
positive	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
pursuing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Copping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cutting	O
Sheers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clipping	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
evident	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
had	O
Clipped	O
Monies	O
,	O
and	O
brag	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
quantities	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
furthermore	O
a	O
Shilling	O
new	O
Clipped	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
alledged	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Employ	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
Loads	O
as	O
a	O
Basket	O
Woman	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
Character	O
given	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
Sessions	O
a	O
Presentment	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Representing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
Ill	O
Conveniences	O
of	O
Soldiers	O
Quartering	O
within	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Terror	O
and	O
Danger	O
occasioned	O
by	O
their	O
insolencies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Which	O
the	O
Court	O
promised	O
to	O
take	O
into	O
Consideration	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
Four	O
Person	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
bland	O
,	O
viz	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	O
Witherly	O
and	O
Peter	O
Maxfield	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Robinson	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Seven	O
Persons	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
Morgan	O
Donow	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Dubas	O
Elizabeth	O
Cropley	O
alias	O
Perry	O
and	O
Jan	O
King	O
Edmund	O
Mathews	O
Repreived	O
before	O
Judgement	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Benjamine	O
Hall	O
and	O
Thomazin	O
Strong	O
.	O
Fined	O
Two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
500	O
Mark	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Copping	I-pers
5	O
Marks	O
.	O
