TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Baggs	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Jerman	I-pers
,	O
Timo	B-pers
,	I-pers
Waldoe	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
William	B-pers
Villers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Obadiah	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Hodsden	I-pers
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kerton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chooter	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylour	I-pers
William	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Side	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sherbone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Bengal	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
forty	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
277	O
yards	O
of	O
Narrow	O
Silk	O
Ribboning	O
.	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
thirty	O
five	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
Silk	O
Galloon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Purple	O
Morning-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Sherbone	O
,	O
who	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Early	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
stirring	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Break	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
whereby	O
to	O
clear	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Synnock	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
they	O
three	O
did	O
Feloniously	O
Enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
thence	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
Drink	O
,	O
they	O
slipt	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Pursued	O
,	O
they	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
one	O
Ashes	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
between	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Martin	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
withal	O
,	O
cleared	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
being	O
any	O
ways	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
alias	O
Mills	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
Feloniously	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Persons	O
and	O
Houses	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborne	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
.	O
From	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
taking	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Coif	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
smaller	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ashborne	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
these	O
Pranks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stiffly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
Robbing	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Cary	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
desired	O
Lodging	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
time	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Service	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
,	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	B-place
;	O
Having	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
espied	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
about	O
30	O
l.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
strived	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
so	O
concurred	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Coral	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
thence	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
single	O
Boot	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Padlock	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bush	O
's	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pepper	I-pers
alias	O
Pebworth	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Isabella	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Poynt	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Table-cloath	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Diaber	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
when	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Family	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Key	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
from	O
Church	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Johnson	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
Sick	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Pepper	O
Robbed	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Johnson	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
:	O
And	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Pepper	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
his	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Buises	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Breast	O
and	O
Belly	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
Battery	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Allen	O
,	O
lay	O
Languishing	O
from	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bruises	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Allen	O
received	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
or	O
set	O
forth	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
Die	O
by	O
some	O
Distemper	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
Rooted	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Eminent	O
Doctors	O
and	O
Chirurgeons	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
positively	O
determine	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Bruises	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
very	O
Sufficient	O
Persons	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
Mild	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
Quiet	O
Conversation	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
meeting	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
Late	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Affronts	O
before	O
he	O
Resisted	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Night-walker	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Hilkiah	B-pers
Osmonton	I-pers
of	O
70	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Coyned	O
Gold	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
some	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Osmonton	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
Enticed	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
happening	O
to	O
fall	O
Asleep	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
Person	O
to	O
vindicate	O
her	O
Credit	O
;	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
positively	O
Swearing	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
so	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Physiognomy	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
alias	O
Shakemable	B-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Eagleston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
Defraud	O
our	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
Subjects	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
evil	O
Example	O
to	O
others	O
;	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Victualler	O
or	O
Cook	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
Carter-lane	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Eagleston	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
offering	O
a	O
Brass	O
Six	O
pence	O
to	O
Exchange	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
immediately	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
hid	O
several	O
pieces	O
more	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
holes	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
sate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
nothing	O
worthy	O
of	O
Notice	O
to	O
offer	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
changing	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
for	O
Clip	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
receiving	O
for	O
his	O
Encouragement	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
every	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
now	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Changed	O
several	O
Sums	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Baley	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
all	O
above	O
50	O
l.	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
which	O
Evidence	O
was	O
well	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Commended	O
for	O
their	O
so	O
Ingenuously	O
confessing	O
their	O
Faults	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
;	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Beale	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Holbourn	B-place
Bridge	I-place
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Moneys	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
Defence	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Night-walkers	O
and	O
Debauched	O
Livers	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Smith	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Batters	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Henson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
and	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Servitor	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
House-wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robinson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bason	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Ewer	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
one	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
four	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Potts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
two	O
Cupps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Sugar	O
Caster	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Mustard-box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Delaforth	I-pers
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Delaforth	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hereofore	O
confessed	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
:	O
And	O
making	O
no	O
great	O
shew	O
of	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Middlesex	O
Side	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Runing	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
entertained	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Dartmouth	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Regiment	O
he	O
continued	O
for	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
upward	O
,	O
and	O
Received	O
the	O
Kingspay	O
;	O
But	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
sented	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Money	O
oweing	O
him	O
f	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Suttler	O
,	O
or	O
Seller	O
of	O
drink	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
Received	O
the	O
Kings	O
pay	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
positive	O
of	O
his	O
Receiving	O
the	O
Press	O
Money	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twittenham	I-place
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Running	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
Captain	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Kings	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
in	O
short	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Received	O
the	O
Press	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
Received	O
the	O
Kings	O
pay	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
a	O
making	O
of	O
Pipes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
not	O
away	O
with	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
that	O
he	O
Borrowed	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
to	O
Ride	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
his	O
friend	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
his	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
Drinking	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Wounded	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
fasten	O
the	O
perpetration	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
themselves	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstantial	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lingford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Sommerset	I-place
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Smith	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Quarreled	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Blows	O
struck	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
receiving	O
no	O
Hurt	O
by	O
the	O
Blows	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
being	O
judged	O
to	O
die	O
a	O
Natural	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Changing	O
of	O
False	O
Guinea	O
's	O
for	O
new	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
New	O
False	O
Five	O
shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
Half	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
there	O
changed	O
False	O
Guinea	O
's	O
for	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Searched	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Crucibles	O
and	O
other	O
Shears	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
Coyned	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
severe	O
Reprehension	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
once	O
Indicted	O
formerly	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fault	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mogg	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gardyner	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jewel	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Pynkard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Noat	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
ten	O
Indicted	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
never	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
Serve	O
a	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
a	O
Mop-stick	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Weapon	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Right	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
Strenuous	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Coyner	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Valentine	B-pers
Couswell	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
false	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
and	O
other	O
false	O
Metals	O
.	O
The	O
Chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Kinsmen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
and	O
Committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
make	O
and	O
Coyn	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
one	O
Bucklands	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lyon	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
the	O
two	O
Bayleys	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Cogswell	O
was	O
a	O
comrade	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Art	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
two	O
Bayley	O
's	O
themselves	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Evidence	O
against	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
Coyning	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
several	O
Instruments	O
were	O
producted	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
Coyned	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
custody	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
material	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
being	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
hearing	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
high	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Lamborne	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Clipper	O
and	O
Coyner	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
and	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Kings	O
lawfull	O
and	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
the	O
Bayleys	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
demonstrations	O
much	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
before	O
in	O
Collet	O
's	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Work	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
Baldwins	B-place
Gardens	I-place
and	O
in	O
the	B-place
Mint	I-place
in	I-place
Southwark	I-place
&	O
c.	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
urge	O
for	O
himself	O
that	O
could	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
high	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
Fil	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
Clipt	O
it	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
one	O
Williamson	B-pers
Emets	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
helpt	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Work	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
Coins	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Evice	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	O
Mack-donnald	O
Girle	O
about	O
Sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
an	O
Evi	O
or	O
House	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
Repute	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
made	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
fully	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
Forced	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Arrabella	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Leaden	O
Six	O
pences	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
also	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
uttering	O
of	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
and	O
False	O
Coyns	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
uttered	O
about	O
Sixty	O
or	O
Seventy	O
Pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Shillings	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
weighed	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Neck-cloath	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Gaberry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aldred	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Sadler	O
.	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
Pick	O
'd	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Mountebanks	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
not	O
Swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ayres	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
in	O
White-chappel	B-place
on	O
the	O
16.	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Confessed	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
Rode	O
to	O
Wallworth	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
up	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
notwithstanding	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Douglace	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thereout	O
five	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
Swearing	O
positively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Charges	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Alice	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Concealing	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
a	O
Malicious	O
intent	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
calling	O
several	O
good	O
House-keepers	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
honest	O
Conversation	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Footman	O
at	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Miles	B-pers
Inhall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Discharged	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
when	O
probably	O
the	O
Deceased	O
might	O
be	O
going	O
or	O
Riding	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Pistol	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
orders	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Cleaned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
Charged	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Chance-medley	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beacon	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Fire-Fork	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
met	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
the	O
Wall	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
like	O
trivial	O
thing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
said	O
Beacon	O
received	O
his	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
a	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
certain	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
Diligence	O
,	O
Riding	O
at	O
Anchor	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
1688.	O
taking	O
therefrom	O
Ninety	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
Two	O
hundred	O
thousand	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Ship	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
some	O
Ropes	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Pymm	I-pers
Baronet	O
;	O
Deering	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
were	O
together	O
with	O
him	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessories	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murther	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Pymm	I-pers
,	O
received	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Waters	O
desired	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
might	O
be	O
Tryed	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
put	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
one	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
lasted	O
long	O
)	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
His	O
Tryal	O
at	O
large	O
the	O
Reader	O
may	O
expect	O
within	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
10	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trodd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lamborne	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
W	O
-	O
P	O
-	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Reprieved	O
immediately	O
after	O
Judgment	O
was	O
past	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
pleading	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
8	O
Persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
Rowland	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Howeland	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
3	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Paint	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
good	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
1	O
Person	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
6	O
Persons	O
were	O
fined	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
alias	O
Shakemaple	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Eaglestone	I-pers
the	O
same	O
,	O
Arrabella	O
Reeves	O
,	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
One	O
Fisher	O
a	O
High-way	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
down	O
to	O
Essex	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Tryal	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Judgment	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
deferred	O
till	O
farther	O
Orders	O
.	O
