TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
and	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
and	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aynger	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
Abrab	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hemingway	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
Zachariah	B-pers
Burrowes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
William	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gosner	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Savadge	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Combe	I-pers
Williams	B-pers
Cotterhill	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fynch	I-pers
James	B-pers
Goulton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Side	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
five	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Story	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
's	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
,	O
stole	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
utterly	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Peatley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
1688.	O
one	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Mo-hair	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
;	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Peatley	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
But	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
Whitsontide	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
;	O
and	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Blankets	O
and	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
Brass	O
Kettles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Sold	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Broaker	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
Wright	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
but	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Middlesex	O
Side	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Short-ribbs	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
thus	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
Prize	O
being	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Kensington	O
on	O
Whitson	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
happen	O
'd	O
among	O
the	O
Rabble	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
amongst	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Man	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
Walker	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
wipe	O
his	O
Sword	O
through	O
his	O
Coat	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Crowd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
Kill	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
Kill	O
one	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
ten	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
single	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
swearing	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Killed	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Scuffle	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Salter	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gamell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jury	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Best	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
summ	O
of	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Throng	O
)	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Mony	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
only	O
Borrowed	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
ancient	O
Offenders	O
,	O
especially	O
Rudd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
eminent	O
Pick-pocket	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Latish	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Blackfryers	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
a	O
Water-man	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Water-man	O
Deceased	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
another	O
Boat	O
which	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Water-man	O
his	O
Fare	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
struck	O
the	O
Water-man	O
several	O
Blows	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
an	O
Oar	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
Blows	O
caused	O
the	O
said	O
Parker	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Drowned	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
alledged	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Tryal	O
was	O
over	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
and	O
urged	O
that	O
some	O
further	O
Evidence	O
might	O
be	O
heard	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
insinuated	O
that	O
the	O
Water-man	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
times	O
before	O
they	O
medled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
gave	O
a	O
severe	O
Reprimand	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
near	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Natural	O
Brother	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
which	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right-side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
under	O
the	O
Short-ribbs	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Philip	O
Constantine	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Garlick	O
Hithe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Numerous	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Brothers	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
a	O
whole	O
Afternoon	O
together	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
a	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
Charges	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
slight	O
thing	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
James	O
Tavern	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Friends	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
heard	O
;	O
and	O
Company	O
gathering	O
together	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Wounded	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mortal	O
by	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
Dress	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Drink	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drank	O
running	O
through	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
told	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
the	O
Case	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
a	O
meer	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
accordingly	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jone	I-pers
alias	O
Coleson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
Huckle	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
affirmed	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
Common	O
Shop-lifters	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Grew	I-pers
of	O
one	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
fifteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
63	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
unto	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Ubanck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
Numerous	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Midwives	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Childs	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
Body	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Farthings	O
to	O
entice	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
also	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Childs	O
Mouth	O
.	O
The	O
Midwives	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Skill	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Chyrurgeon	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Search	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
strange	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
differed	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
their	O
Opinions	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
by	O
any	O
force	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
a	O
large	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guil	O
-	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lothland	B-pers
Mackingtash	I-pers
a	O
Scotch	O
Man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Thistleworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
his	O
Left	O
Pap	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Frazier	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Companies	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Tent	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
wholly	O
bent	O
to	O
Kill	O
some	O
one	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
interposing	O
to	O
qualifie	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
doing	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
:	O
Another	O
Person	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Serjeants	O
Assistance	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
familiar	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Malice	O
propense	O
being	O
proved	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Dinn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
frequently	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
to	O
Borrow	O
somewhat	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
may	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
out	O
the	O
Porringer	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
House-of	O
Office	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
an	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Springfield	I-pers
.	O
More	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Table-cloath	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Clifton	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
renewed	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
about	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
do	O
by	O
an	O
Old	O
Man	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Clifton	O
,	O
at	O
Holloway	B-place
,	O
near	O
Highgate	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
offering	O
her	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Shrewsbury	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Perrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ragoose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ragoose	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cool-Tankard	O
,	O
with	O
Water	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Vintner	O
's	O
back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
having	O
none	O
else	O
up	O
besides	O
himself	O
)	O
they	O
espy	O
'd	O
their	O
opportunity	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Spoon	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
them	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
themselves	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
One	O
Silk-Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
in	O
White-chappel	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Young	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Minn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
Twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
drive	O
his	O
Cart	O
to	O
Acton	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
But	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
Westwood	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
new	O
Master	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
his	O
Money	O
shak	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
fled	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Two	O
Wives	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
he	O
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Trinity	O
Minories	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Gresham	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
married	O
at	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
;	O
both	O
which	O
Marriages	O
were	O
fully	O
and	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
very	O
material	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Wife	O
was	O
yet	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
her	O
Certificate	O
for	O
her	O
Marriage	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phinehas	B-pers
Unicome	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Stachouse	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Price	O
10	O
l.	O
Fifteen	O
Hands	O
high	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gibbert	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holly	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Carreer	I-pers
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
takeing	O
away	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag-Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carreer	I-pers
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
or	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Wake	O
,	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
driving	O
his	O
Cartwheel	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Meroy	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Riding	O
along	O
Brick-lane	B-place
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
being	O
Unruly	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fore	O
Horse	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
run	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
thing	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
Accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
his	O
great	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gleeve	I-pers
,	O
Adrian	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
Gent	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Earning	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gleeve	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
being	O
Accessories	O
&	O
c.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Short-ribbs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
Quarrelled	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Quarrel	O
the	O
said	O
Earning	O
lost	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
stifly	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
they	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
all	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Beaver-Hat	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mr	O
Leader	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
very	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Hat	O
upon	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Wapping	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Clothes	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Littlemore	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
wheedled	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
healing	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Mo-hair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
contradict	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
fixed	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Valentine	B-pers
Cogswell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Making	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Coining	O
forty	O
pieces	O
of	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
compounded	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
and	O
other	O
Mettals	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
better	O
advising	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
prayed	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Plea	O
withdrawn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bckwell	O
,	O
in	O
Red-Lion-Fields	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
the	O
two	O
Bayleys	O
had	O
Coined	O
their	O
Money	O
and	O
Clipt	O
;	O
who	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
seen	O
him	O
help	O
at	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
Art	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Baileys	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
only	O
to	O
save	O
themselves	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
Pardoned	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
a	O
notorious	O
Shop-lifter	O
and	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Beaver-hat	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
had	O
newly	O
bought	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
about	O
the	O
May-pole	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
a	O
Hand	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
conveyed	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
,	O
it	O
though	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Musket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
shooting	O
his	O
Piece	O
level	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Musket	O
was	O
loaden	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
said	O
Riley	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
behind	O
an	O
House-of-office	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
or	O
Garden	O
at	O
Labouring	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Casualty	O
,	O
yet	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fyander	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Muslin	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Conley	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Coral	O
with	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
Coral	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
viz	O
.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Lace	O
,	O
from	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Carron	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
His	B-pers
Majestie	I-pers
s	O
Deer	O
out	O
of	O
Hide-Park	B-place
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immedately	O
Discharged	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
seventeen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Long	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
converted	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
Dismembring	O
one	O
William	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John-Child	I-pers
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
biting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
his	O
Tongue	O
off	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
John-Child	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Fled	O
)	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
it	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
got	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Tongue	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
it	O
off	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
one	O
Swearing	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
6	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
A	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
,	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Poarter	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	O
Cogswel	O
,	O
and	O
Nick	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
for	O
Coining	O
.	O
16	O
Persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Latish	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
Cbarles	O
Constantine	O
,	O
The	O
Rogers	O
,	O
Nich	O
.	O
Mason	O
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Lathland	O
Macking	O
.	O
tash	O
,	O
T	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
Daniel	B-pers
Perros	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Woodbam	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Wil	O
.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Conly	I-pers
.	O
11	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Ferdinando	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibbers	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holly	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Littlmore	I-pers
,	O
Dor	O
.	O
Fyander	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gamel	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Tabitha	O
Poarter	O
Pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Empanelled	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
Not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
