TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tuley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
King	I-pers
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Kittelbey	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Trodd	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harisonr	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Snabling	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Howlet	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
Bennet	B-pers
Child	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hartfoot	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Kendon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Margett	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Benderidge	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knowless	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Underhill	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
one	O
Man	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
Beakers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
Tasters	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Yates	O
.	O
Being	O
Apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Beakers	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
being	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
twenty	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
a	O
Dyer	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
sculk	O
about	O
the	O
Dye-house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
watched	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Stuff	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bonny	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Coast	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
forty	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
Six	O
pence	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bandon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
all	O
five	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Snape	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Snape	O
within	O
three	O
days	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
Drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
in	O
Hackney	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Press-shilling	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
without	O
telling	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
further	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
so	O
high	O
a	O
degree	O
that	O
Snape	O
lost	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
would	O
have	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Town	O
made	O
a	O
Rising	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
they	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
strong	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
equally	O
concerned	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursivall	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
:	O
The	O
Indictment	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
in	O
Divinity	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
one	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
one	O
Coif	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Bridle	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
all	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignments	O
all	O
three	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Short-ribs	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Languished	O
and	O
Died	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Mile-end	O
Town	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
Lewd	O
Life	O
;	O
after	O
whom	O
the	O
Boys	O
ran	O
and	O
Reflected	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
much	O
disturbed	O
,	O
and	O
vowed	O
Revenge	O
upon	O
the	O
next	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
which	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
he	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
Sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Argued	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
deposited	O
:	O
After	O
a	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Welding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
hapned	O
Thus	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Souldiers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
hapned	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
about	O
Love	O
to	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
taking	O
Carrington	O
's	O
part	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
Cary	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
abovesaid	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
found	O
against	O
Carrington	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Cary	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Folwer	I-pers
Wid	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
(	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Duncan	O
Mack	O
laughan	O
a	O
Scotch	O
Man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Alexander	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
since	O
in	O
Paddington	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
with	O
several	O
Wounds	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
)	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
but	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
altho	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
pleaded	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
Cornhil	B-place
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
other	O
Faults	O
heretofore	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
pleading	O
nothing	O
effectual	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Peruge	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
Razors	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
one	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Hone	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Perukque	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Reynold	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
a	O
convenient	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
conclusion	O
Franklin	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Reynolds	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Needle-work	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alley	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Alley	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Averye	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Beaver	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Demy	O
Castor	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Hats	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Diggs	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therefrom	O
6	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
:	O
So	O
in	O
fine	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Weekes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Coney-hatch	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
therefrom	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shagg	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Gray	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Poynt-lace	O
Corners	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Black	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Poynt-lace	O
Coifs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Quilted	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
old	O
Holland	O
Pillow-beer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Prince	O
's	O
Metal	O
handled	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
another	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	O
Weekes	O
;	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
were	O
very	O
many	O
,	O
chiefly	O
Weekes	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Worthy	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Mordent	I-pers
,	O
who	O
hapned	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Weekes	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
amongst	O
the	O
Family	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
espied	O
them	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Birding-piece	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
against	O
the	O
Thieves	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
Kill	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
to	O
London	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
overcome	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
Disguised	O
in	O
their	O
habit	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Evidence	O
knew	O
Obrian	O
and	O
Goddard	O
the	O
Elder	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
to	O
contradict	O
,	O
especially	O
Obrian	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offerfor	O
himself	O
that	O
could	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
his	O
Innocency	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
so	O
likewise	O
was	O
Goddard	O
the	O
Younger	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Goddard	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Prassley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
Souldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Souldiers	O
also	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
a	O
Victualler	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Page	O
,	O
Widdow	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
of	O
Yarrow	O
and	O
Dawson	O
,	O
and	O
espoused	O
their	O
Quarrel	O
so	O
far	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Thrust	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Page	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
fair	O
Hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
Eleven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
Martha	B-pers
Fryday	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Cheek	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Fryday	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
where	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Pistols	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Maid	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
Shoot	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
laid	O
Six	O
pence	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Shoot	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
Shot	O
her	O
Dead	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Chance-medly	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
not	O
Taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
charged	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
to	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Barber	O
's	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
twice	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
matter	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
said	O
Stephens	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
Swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Caudley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gomers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
Unlawfully	O
procuring	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
into	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
that	O
she	O
Clipped	O
;	O
yet	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Biting	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Tongue	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
hapned	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
fell	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
held	O
him	O
whil'st	O
her	O
Husband	O
bit	O
off	O
his	O
Tongue	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
any	O
one	O
saw	O
him	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Flanders-lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hixon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
crept	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
insinuated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
notorious	O
House-breaker	O
and	O
Shoplifter	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
)	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sellway	I-pers
in	O
Grays-Inn-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Saws	O
and	O
Plains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
Breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
fully	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
good	O
Credit	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Extenuation	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
offering	O
the	O
Tools	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
heretofore	O
Sollway	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
weighed	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
frivolous	O
and	O
long	O
Defence	O
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pinder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Under-shaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Josias	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
the	O
Spoons	O
in	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Vauson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ratteray	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
all	O
three	O
Servant	O
s	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
twelve	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Beck	O
and	O
Ratteray	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
and	O
Vauson	O
as	O
the	O
Principal	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
charged	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
as	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Bishops	O
were	O
Cleared	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Bonfires	O
made	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
near	O
the	O
Lord	O
Salisbury	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Beadles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
commanded	O
to	O
Suppress	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
others	O
quarreling	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
Reconcile	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
were	O
repulsed	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
came	O
on	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
defiance	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Inferior	O
Officers	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
further	O
Disturbance	O
arose	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Rencounters	O
followed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
first	O
denying	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
their	O
Hats	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
wish	O
the	O
Bishops	O
much	O
Joy	O
of	O
their	O
deliverance	O
,	O
which	O
indeed	O
was	O
the	O
Original	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
of	O
them	O
followed	O
the	O
Servants	O
into	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Butler	O
;	O
and	O
thrust	O
too	O
far	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
;	O
in	O
fine	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pistol	O
discharged	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Shots	O
Kill	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Matson	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snetton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
cloath	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Tenter-hooks	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pearfall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Elling	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clackstone	I-pers
.	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Crime	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
in	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lehay	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Maneer	I-pers
,	O
two	O
French	O
Men	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
27	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Taffity	O
Lutestring	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
thirty	O
two	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
Cross-stript	O
Lutestring	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
fully	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
favourably	O
dealt	O
with	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Maneer	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
and	O
Lehay	O
as	O
Principal	O
.	O
[	O
Lehay	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Elinor	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
other	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
Stuff	O
Childrens	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Bengall	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
goods	O
all	O
goods	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
Lodged	O
in	O
Wood	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
much	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
be-ing	O
known	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
Evil	O
Life	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bare	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Hollistone	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
flatly	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
and	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
67	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
picked	O
the	O
Locks	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
:	O
But	O
Richard	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
desired	O
his	O
Wife	O
might	O
be	O
excused	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Acquitted	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Pidgley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Speare	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Bristol	O
offering	O
the	O
Geldings	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
Pidgley	O
Sold	O
them	O
and	O
Gerrard	O
was	O
the	O
Voucher	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Speare	O
Swore	O
plainly	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
;	O
but	O
Gerrard	O
having	O
not	O
so	O
strong	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Cleared	O
,	O
but	O
Pidgley	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
some	O
Scarfs	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
Stockings	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Charge	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
five	O
Tun	O
of	O
Red	O
Saunders	O
Wood	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
105	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
Maddox	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
Broke	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
against	O
Young	O
:	O
Maddox	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Young	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Silk	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Blamtin	B-pers
;	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
Confessed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
Enticed	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
Money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
William	I-pers
James	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Accessory	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Nacket	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
are	O
fled	O
since	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Endrick	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Dyed	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Instant	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Persons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Endricks	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
having	O
a	O
Woman	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
Mr.	O
Endrick	O
lost	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Positive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
Killed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
rather	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pedder	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Spanish-wool	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Wool	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Seaman	O
:	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Credit	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Wool	O
at	O
Underrates	O
;	O
so	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
9	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prosley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursival	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pidgley	I-pers
.	O
17	O
Persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pinder	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Diggs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Snetton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lehay	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Merryk	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
.	O
9	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Judeth	O
Howard	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bare	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
.	O
And	O
Sarah	B-pers
Caudley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
through	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
3	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Averye	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Richard	O
Vauson	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ratteray	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Bayled	O
by	O
two	O
Free-holders	O
of	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
in	O
200	O
l.	O
each	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
500	O
l.	O
a	O
peice	O
for	O
their	O
appearance	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
next	O
Ensuing	O
Sessions	O
.	O
