TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
26th	O
.	O
and	O
27th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
26th	O
.	O
and	O
27th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Bithoul	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Pead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rowle	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hutchibout	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sanders	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Okey	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
Jonas	B-pers
Morly	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hunsdon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cromwel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
James	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Side	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
or	O
Cann	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
Victualler	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
Poole	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Dutton	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
both	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Exchange	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Tinn	O
Cana	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
marcht	O
off	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Cann	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Poole	O
;	O
but	O
both	O
being	O
concerned	O
,	O
Dutton	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Mayfield	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tumbler	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Baines	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Anderson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
under	O
the	O
Maids	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
only	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Desborrow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
AlderMary	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Grace	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
Eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Black	O
Shamma	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
Eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shamma	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Balduck	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
in	O
her	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Guttridge	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Velvet	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
where	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
their	O
Stuffs	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ninth	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
in	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Markes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
And	O
nothing	O
being	O
positive	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Reeves	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Westly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Vallens	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
Furnished	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
a	O
rate	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
therefore	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Emmanuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
among	O
some	O
Women	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealingon	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Mayfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
Carter	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
Carter	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Parnell	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
slit	O
in	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
thin	O
Stick	O
and	O
Bird-lime	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trumper	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Organs	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lingar	I-pers
,	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Trencher-plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
Trumper	O
's	O
Pocket	O
:	O
And	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebeka	B-pers
Hollingshead	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloaths	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Pillow-beers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Coral	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Camlet	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
Wash	O
Linnen	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Nicholas	I-place
Cole-Abby	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Heeling	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Lacet	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boram	I-pers
alias	O
Kent	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wily	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
Buttons	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Pendulum	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Wily	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
Baggs	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
leather	O
Bagg	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
with	O
600	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wily	I-pers
;	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
hearing	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
several	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
forementioned	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
buttons	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Charter-House	O
Lane	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilies	O
Name	O
being	O
engraven	O
underneath	O
the	O
Buttons	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Confederate	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
also	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
in	O
several	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
also	O
pleading	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Buttons	O
at	O
Creed-Eane	O
end	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Linning	O
lay	O
foul	O
in	O
a	O
lower	O
Parlor	O
,	O
in	O
Baldwins	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
espying	O
his	O
shadow	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
dropt	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Crooke	I-pers
alias	O
Hide	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
alias	O
Lush	B-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hollyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Nicholas	I-place
Acres	I-place
,	O
at	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
one	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloath	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
They	O
being	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Nicholas	I-place
Cole-Abby	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Heeling	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
jumping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Almond	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
one	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
living	O
in	O
Leicester-shire	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
London	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Employed	O
the	O
Carrier	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
Town	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Gentlemans	O
Hat	O
in	O
Norfolk-street	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
Seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Muslebrooke	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Muslebrooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hewes	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
Numbred	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
There	O
could	O
be	O
little	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
Brick-maker	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
that	O
Work	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
which	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Young	O
Man	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
speaking	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Crosland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Killing	O
David	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Souldier	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
some	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reproving	O
him	O
for	O
abusing	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Drew	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
careless	O
of	O
himself	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Drinking	O
very	O
hard	O
and	O
going	O
abroad	O
;	O
also	O
his	O
Colonel	O
and	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bisby	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
his	O
wife	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
Lettuce	B-pers
Fynch	I-pers
,	O
e	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Jenkenson	I-pers
,	O
canvas	O
Bag	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbred	O
;	O
but	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
taking	O
y	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
upon	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
on-	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
a	O
Souldier	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gillyes	I-pers
a	O
Scotch	O
pedlar	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
Camerick	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
32	O
'	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
The	O
Scotchman	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
with	O
his	O
Pack	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Croud	O
gathered	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
setting	O
down	O
his	O
Pack	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
be	O
charged	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Conclough	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Church	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
missing	O
her	O
Watch	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
Seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
next	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
presently	O
Search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
dropp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atchison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
above	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
of	O
the	O
Servant	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afterward	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
carryed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
outright	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
gave	O
orders	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
Broker	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Standley	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Mare	O
and	O
one	O
Guiney	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
one	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
being	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Hill	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Robbed	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
positive	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Linsy	B-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Philips	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Brereton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
killed	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Muddiman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lodging	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
run	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Person	O
abstracted	O
and	O
much	O
discomposed	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
verily	O
believed	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
ill	O
success	O
in	O
Love	O
;	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
upon	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Minister	O
and	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
whose	O
whole	O
business	O
lies	O
among	O
Persons	O
Distracted	O
,	O
they	O
related	O
several	O
Stories	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
might	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
subject	O
to	O
Frensies	O
and	O
Deliriums	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
held	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
all-into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Brackly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
She	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
goods	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
gave	O
Directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Miles	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
some	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
which	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
positive	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boys	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Parishes	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews-Holborn	O
and	O
Clarkenwel	O
,	O
meeting	O
upon	O
the	O
bounds	O
of	O
the	O
Parishes	O
,	O
and	O
opposing	O
one	O
another	O
as	O
they	O
use	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
those	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews-Holborn	O
goon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cockt	O
his	O
Piece	O
and	O
fired	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Level	O
,	O
killing	O
the	O
2	O
Persons	O
Deceased	O
with	O
one	O
Bullet	O
,	O
shooting	O
one	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Brest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Navel	O
standing	O
behind	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
and	O
murthering	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
some	O
Seamen	O
and	O
others	O
quarrelling	O
at	O
a	O
Musick	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	B-place
,	O
having	O
no	O
Swords	O
or	O
sticks	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rusht	O
in	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
hearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
abusing	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
slaughter	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
deceased	O
his	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fellis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
high	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Drover	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
Leicester-Shire	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Boarded	O
House	O
beyond	O
Islington	O
about	O
break	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
other	O
circumstances	O
occurring	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Persons	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bringing	O
some	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
also	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chip	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
of	O
Branford	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Porrenger	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tasters	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
Jacobus	O
pieces	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
open	O
the	O
Windows	O
whereby	O
other	O
Thieves	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
circumstances	O
concurring	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
mony	O
numbred	O
:	O
The	O
only	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
missing	O
his	O
Mony	O
in	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
saying	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
proofe	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
and	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-White-chappel	I-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
others	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
and	O
Elisha	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elisha	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Diaper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sprosley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Poors	O
Box	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Gent	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hatt	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Stockhurst	I-pers
,	O
and	O
snatching	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
Summerset	B-place
house	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Hatt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Pettycoat	O
February	O
the	O
11th	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Cup	O
with	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Garret	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
some	O
Tubb-men	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Latimer	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holborn	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Killing	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
pleaded	O
hard	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
going	O
home	O
through	O
Chancery-lane	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
meeting	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
Justled	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
Blows	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
never	O
Drawn	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterward	O
carried	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
Died	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Gentleman	O
should	O
say	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
,	O
that	O
Ridley	O
Killed	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Sword	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
should	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
fault	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
silver	O
Sale	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
mony	O
numbred	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
Wood	B-place
Green	I-place
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
upon	O
Thompson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Dowlas	O
smock	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Copestaff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
false	O
Guineys	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Shilling	O
guilt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scepters	O
in	O
graven	O
on	O
;	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
's	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Horn	O
,	O
from	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Atterton	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Vary	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
linnen	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Atterton	I-pers
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Attaway	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
Plates	O
of	O
horn	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hethrington	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
mony	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
alias	O
Davis	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
linnen	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Mastlin	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
3	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
only	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
10	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Crooke	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Wyot	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Parsons	O
put	O
by	O
.	O
16	O
Persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Desborrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Guttridge	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crosland	I-pers
,	O
Thomasin	O
Burton	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Brackly	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Atterton	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Sanders	O
.	O
3	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sprosley	I-pers
.	O
14	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tramper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Brackley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Muslebrooke	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Muslebrooke	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Mastlin	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Copestaffe	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Bars	O
at	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
end	O
,	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d	O
.	O
