TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
&	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
At	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
5th	O
days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
4th	O
.	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Hagar	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
Jeffery	B-pers
Woolstone	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurss	I-pers
John	B-pers
Downton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Leesey	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Babbs	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Karrington	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bethlem	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ticknall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Walter	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
with	O
a	O
Cutlace	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Murray	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
prest	O
him	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Press-master	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
giving	O
Preston	O
ill	O
words	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
(	O
Ned	O
)	O
a	O
Nickname	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Preston	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
wound	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
fully	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Side	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
Murray	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
:	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
price	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brasbridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
an	O
Horse	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fitz-Gerald	I-pers
value	O
8	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
persued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Lute-string	O
Silk	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
lac't	O
Tippet	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Predey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
it	O
fully	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Frize	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Walley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
wander	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
whil'st	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
opening	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Frize	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
branded	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheares	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
most	O
scandalous	O
and	O
pernicious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
being	O
in	O
some	O
Company	O
on	O
Shipboard	O
,	O
a	O
Discourse	O
arose	O
concerning	O
the	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
the	O
Prosperity	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
contradicted	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
spake	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
Jefferies	O
did	O
Nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
always	O
Just	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
that	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
is	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
be	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Justice	O
done	O
by	O
King	O
James	O
already	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
done	O
very	O
suddenly	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
those	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
spoke	O
such	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stoake-Newington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Herbert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
another	O
Ring	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Ring	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
A	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
Sword	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Swore	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
Sworn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Parish	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Pyn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Fork	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
Which	O
Pyn	O
's	O
Wife	O
Swore	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Fork	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Lodged	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
only	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
impudently	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Macksfield	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wethered	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
4	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Wethered	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
glasses	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
glasses	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dudlison	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
Anthony	O
Morris	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
journeymen	O
taylors	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
cutting	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
more	O
plenty	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
and	O
a	O
taster	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
clearly	O
proved	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Whiteway	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
three	O
several	O
indictments	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bigway	I-pers
and	O
others	O
unto	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
murthering	O
her	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Market	I-place
:	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
midwives	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
-	O
So	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hinton	I-pers
his	O
wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Adam	B-pers
Oatly	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thereout	O
one	O
silk	O
mantua	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
another	O
mantua	O
with	O
gold	O
fringe	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
green	O
stip	O
'd	O
lute	O
string	O
coat	O
,	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
wastecoat	O
,	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
300	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
for	O
the	O
king	O
and	O
queen	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
brokers	O
,	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
the	O
wife	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Thomas	O
Hinton	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Twopots	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
upon	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
Harrison	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
on	O
horseback	O
between	O
Hampsted	B-place
and	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
more	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
flatly	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
old	O
Newgate	O
story	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
So	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
St.Martins	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
widow	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Ellin	B-pers
Fitz-Patrick	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
7	O
other	O
yards	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
ground	O
lace	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
pearl	O
lace	O
15	O
s	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
was	O
stole	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
yet	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Hesey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Love	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
120	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
silk	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
encompassed	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
evidence	O
swore	O
only	O
to	O
Parrey	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
So	O
Parrey	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kyrten	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Methwin	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
bearing	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
one	O
blunderbus	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pistol	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	O
Methwin	O
Esq	O
;	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
countrey	O
,	O
leaving	O
only	O
a	O
servant	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
near	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
evidence	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
plausible	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
evidenced	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
branded	O
before	O
,	O
also	O
going	O
by	O
two	O
names	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Pollentine	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
silver	O
porringers	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
tankards	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
cup	O
55	O
s.	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
coral	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
silk	O
gowns	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
satin	O
peticoat	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
crape	O
gown	O
23	O
s.	O
3	O
other	O
peticoats	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
mantuas	O
17	O
l.	O
and	O
250	O
l.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
peticoat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Mary	O
Grovers	O
back	O
at	O
a	O
musick-house	O
in	O
Dog	O
fields	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
peticoat	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
evidence	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
fully	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Mr	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holbert	I-pers
in	O
the	O
highway	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
J	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
T	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
W	B-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
--	I-pers
-	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
together	O
with	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
Gent	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
bruises	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
shoulder	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
breast	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
lived	O
languishing	O
until	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
A	O
--	O
-E	O
--	O
-	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
being	O
accessaries	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Marshall	O
deceased	O
in	O
Mr.	O
T	O
--	O
-	O
shop	O
a	O
pewterer	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
shop	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
how	O
pewter	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
depart	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
small	O
resistance	O
against	O
Mr.	O
E	O
--	O
-	O
the	O
first	O
prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
bruises	O
abovesaid	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
medled	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
E	O
--	O
-	O
several	O
blows	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Which	O
Mr.	O
E	O
--	O
-	O
declared	O
in	O
court	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bit	O
his	O
fingers	O
end	O
off	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
.	O
)	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
further	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
well	O
recovered	O
of	O
the	O
hurt	O
received	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
to	O
declare	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
after	O
the	O
fray	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
abundance	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
physicians	O
said	O
might	O
occasion	O
him	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
a	O
malignant	O
fever	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cowel	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Flanders	O
lac	O
'd	O
cornet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
golden	O
pendants	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
taster	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
12	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
family	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Morwood	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
breeches	O
,	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
flatly	O
sworn	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
town	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
good	O
repute	O
heretofore	O
in	O
Ireland	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Lord	O
's	O
service	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
avail	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowers	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Hurlock	I-pers
between	O
Kinsington	B-place
and	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
holding	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
demanding	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
watch	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
execute	O
his	O
office	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
assisting	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
behavour	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Savory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
accessories	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
and	O
executed	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
committed	O
upon	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sapsford	B-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Saysford	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Baker	O
brought	O
his	O
goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Steers	O
produced	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Mary	O
Savory	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
knew	O
of	O
Sibley	O
's	O
committing	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
left	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
distrain	O
'd	O
:	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Battin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Eveson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
case	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Cozens	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Wildon	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
hay	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
orchard	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
evidence	O
swore	O
they	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
Franklin	O
's	O
Hay	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
perceived	O
by	O
the	O
tracing	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
from	O
Franklin	O
's	O
Hay-close	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
orchard	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
composition	O
made	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
coach	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
:	O
It	O
ap-	O
peared	O
that	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
upon	O
the	O
highway	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
any	O
person	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
trespass	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Sterten	I-pers
of	O
a	O
sword	O
and	O
48	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sterton	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
stand	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
Scot	O
did	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
farther	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
him	O
hold	O
his	O
horse	O
whilst	O
he	O
dived	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
Scot	O
and	O
Stiles	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
clear	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
:	O
So	O
Scot	O
and	O
Stiles	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
but	O
Jones	O
and	O
Stafford	O
were	O
freed	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
with	O
some	O
plate	O
buttons	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
knew	O
Jones	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hollister	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
gelding	O
6	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
none	O
but	O
Stiles	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
Scot	O
,	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Stafford	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
A	O
fifth	O
time	O
they	O
stood	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Calcot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
Dutch	O
money	O
and	O
Duccatoons	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Stafford	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
Scot	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
notorious	O
rogues	O
and	O
eminent	O
highway-men	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
,	O
Scot	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
ring	O
leader	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Jones	O
,	O
Stafford	O
,	O
and	O
Stiles	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Northern	B-place
Foregat	I-place
were	O
tryed	O
,	O
Lee	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hawking	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
silver	O
cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
porringer	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
spoon	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Jones	O
said	O
that	O
Lee	O
brought	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
produced	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
45	O
s.	O
And	O
no	O
evidence	O
being	O
given	O
that	O
affected	O
Jones	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Lee	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
his	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
treason	O
,	O
in	O
clipping	O
the	O
current	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
having	O
certain	O
sheers	O
and	O
other	O
instruments	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
subjects	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
clip	O
money	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
asserted	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stifly	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
but	O
slender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Lucretia	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Maxfeild	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gutteridge	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
40	O
cloth	O
coats	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
30	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
40	O
l.	O
5	O
silk	O
hoods	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Lymehouse	B-place
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Ball	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Gutteridge	O
owned	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Lucretia	O
Stephenson	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
corroborating	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
William	O
Ball	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
laborer	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
several	O
indictments	O
:	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
lost	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
Stand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
money	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
who	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
flatly	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
evidence	O
being	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Vandrew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Levandrew	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Dutch	O
men	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Waterworth	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Clerkenwel	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
belly	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
Henry	O
Vandrew	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
.	O
Vandrew	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
drummer	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
quarrel	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	B-place
Garden	I-place
near	O
Hockley	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Hole	I-place
,	O
about	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
sport	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
thrust	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
immediately	O
drew	O
their	O
swords	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
scuffle	O
the	O
said	O
Waterworth	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
some	O
evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Vandrews	O
nose	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
colour	O
for	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
Vandrew	O
was	O
found	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
,	O
and	O
Levandrew	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Edith	B-pers
Shank	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Shank	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
her	O
navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
Edith	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
fatal	O
thrust	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
her	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
beaver	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
hatband	O
,	O
6s	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Edlin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
hat	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
,	O
two	O
looking	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
glasses	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
boy	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Elderkin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Archbishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Canterbury	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
mortars	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
9s	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mortars	O
and	O
dishes	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
dishes	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
pewterers	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
cast	O
some	O
aspersions	O
upon	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
further	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
9	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
dishes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
dishes	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
4	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Lyonel	B-pers
Hurlock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
coats	O
,	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
wastcoats	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
80	O
l.	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Emmerson	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
of	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Tonstall	I-pers
Esq	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
several	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Tonstall	O
and	O
others	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
chamber	O
in	O
Essex-Court	B-place
,	O
having	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
goods	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
only	O
removed	O
in	O
order	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
broke	O
any	O
lock	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
innocency	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
jury	O
were	O
not	O
induced	O
to	O
believe	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
intending	O
thereby	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
subjects	O
of	O
their	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
,	O
which	O
keys	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
divers	O
times	O
lurking	O
to	O
seek	O
their	O
prey	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
evidenced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
several	O
worthy	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
who	O
helpt	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
finding	O
several	O
keys	O
in	O
their	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
pick-locks	O
besides	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
pick-locks	O
:	O
But	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
demonstrate	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
might	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
jury	O
to	O
believe	O
them	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
fully	O
appeared	O
they	O
were	O
equally	O
concern	O
'd	O
being	O
most	O
emment	O
pickpockets	O
,	O
and	O
notorious	O
villains	O
,	O
one	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
trespass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
trespass	O
in	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Custos	O
Brevium	O
office	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stair-case	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
peep	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
dispersed	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
met	O
again	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
being	O
all	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denying	O
the	O
fact	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
;	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
stories	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
very	O
odious	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
..	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salesbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
weather	O
sheep	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
lambs	O
12	O
s	O
.	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fieters	I-pers
:	O
The	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ratten	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
two	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
bason	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
evidence	O
affecting	O
Ball	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Harper	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gutteridg	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
bearing	O
away	O
30	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
30	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Mayor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Branford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
parish	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
tipper	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
Bennet	O
swore	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
Lambs	B-place
Conduit	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
wounding	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Carole	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
-	O
Carole	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Imbezling	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Gourdon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
Silk	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Mantua	O
's	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
Three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
Several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Night	O
Raile	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
400	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Gourdon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witness	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Gourdon	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
with	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
considerable	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Imbezlement	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
abetting	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
comforting	O
Edward	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Boswel	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
10	O
Coronets	O
,	O
4	O
Night	O
Rayls	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Laced	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
9	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ludd	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Point	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
Church	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Morss	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlace	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Shirt	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Irish	O
Papist	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
by	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
containing	O
what	O
follows	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
known	O
and	O
open	O
Papist	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
Write	O
,	O
Compose	O
and	O
Publish	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
Written	O
,	O
Composed	O
and	O
Published	O
a	O
most	O
False	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Pernicious	O
Libel	O
against	O
the	O
People	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Christen	O
'd	O
Convention	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
scandalous	O
Reflections	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
our	O
Eyes	O
are	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
opened	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
we	O
see	O
those	O
Men	O
that	O
pretend	O
to	O
do	O
our	O
Religion	O
Right	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
securing	O
our	O
Liberties	O
,	O
do	O
bring	O
us	O
into	O
Slavery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
Matter	O
and	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stood	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Writing	O
,	O
Composing	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
of	O
the	O
Libel	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
should	O
be	O
implied	O
,	O
more	O
particularly	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Publication	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
hoped	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
find	O
him	O
Guilty	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
but	O
a	O
Papist	O
would	O
have	O
spoke	O
such	O
Words	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
called	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Libel	O
to	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Persons	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
commend	O
it	O
very	O
highly	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
This	O
happened	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Proclamation	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lent	O
the	O
Libel	O
to	O
the	O
Priest	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
whereby	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
Pendergrass	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
And	O
further	O
,	O
The	O
Libel	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
as	O
above	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
writ	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
Publish	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Cou-	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
[	O
any	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
remember	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
read	O
any	O
such	O
Paper	O
to	O
any	O
Gentlemen	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
Papers	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prefe	O
'd	O
so	O
hard	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Controversies	O
past	O
between	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
behaved	O
himself	O
like	O
a	O
person	O
Inspired	O
with	O
the	O
true	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Popery	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
most	O
seasonable	O
Reprimands	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
And	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
proceeded	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
Exquisitely	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
was	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
Publish	O
the	O
Libel	O
,	O
yes	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
2	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
maliciously	O
to	O
do	O
mischief	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
induced	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
high	O
Estimation	O
he	O
set	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
withal	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Crime	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
deep	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
how	O
many	O
such	O
kind	O
of	O
pernicious	O
Libels	O
had	O
been	O
(	O
of	O
late	O
)	O
thrown	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
Putting	O
them	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
what	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
the	O
promoting	O
of	O
such	O
Principles	O
might	O
prove	O
to	O
the	O
Liberties	O
and	O
Properties	O
of	O
all	O
True	O
Englishmen	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
endeavour	O
to	O
suppress	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
at	O
their	O
doors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
a	O
little	O
space	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
After	O
the	O
Tryals	O
were	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
5	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Sambrook	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Hynton	I-pers
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Elderkin	O
Will	O
.	O
Whiteway	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
3.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gardner	I-pers
William	I-pers
Battin	I-pers
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
2	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
From	O
Newgate	O
to	O
London-stone	O
.	O
Izabella	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheares	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pay	O
20	O
Nobles	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Inscription	O
be	O
set	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
declaring	O
his	O
Crime	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Mark	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
until	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Fined	O
20	O
l.	O
apiece	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviours	O
for	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
Imprisonment	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
was	O
Respited	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Vandrew	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
course	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Waterworth	O
.	O
One	O
Joah	O
Land	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Clip	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behavior	O
.	O
Likewise	O
one	O
Roper	O
convicted	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
continue	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Correction	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Palace-Yard	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
To	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
's	O
Majesties	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
Kath	O
.	O
Williams	O
John	B-pers
Twopots	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
George	B-pers
Maxfeild	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Elizab	O
.	O
Moulton	O
John	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atherton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
the	O
Labourer	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
being	O
July	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
First	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
cures	O
any	O
Canker	O
,	O
Ulcer	O
,	O
or	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
fastning	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
black	O
ones	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
1689	O
.	O
