TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Baggs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Compeer	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Pynder	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
Everard	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Ayleworth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hollyday	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hayton	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
William	B-pers
Farnborrow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
William	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Redhill	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Malefactor	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
One	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
held	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
Other	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Turn-Key	O
s	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ster	O
of	O
the	O
Prison	O
Major	O
Richardson	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Malefactors	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
Kelsey	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Thieves	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
executed	O
lately	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Mutiny	O
in	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
hang	O
out	O
a	O
Bloody	O
Flag	O
of	O
Defiance	O
against	O
Major	O
Richardson	O
and	O
his	O
Servants	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Goodman	O
interposing	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Kelsey	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodhead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
12	O
d	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
Soldier	O
s	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Lord	O
Sidney	O
's	O
first	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
and	O
going	O
together	O
to	O
receive	O
their	O
Pay	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
arose	O
he	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
some	O
slight	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
blow	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
said	O
Woodhead	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
proved	O
any	O
Malice	O
premeditated	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
since	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
General	O
Pardon	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Risbey	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
immediately	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
20	O
s.	O
10	O
pair	O
more	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Padlock	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
about	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Taking	O
hold	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hartslop	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Long	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Quarter-Staff	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
rude	O
Fellows	O
viz	O
White	O
Fryers	O
Men	O
,	O
were	O
striving	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
some	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Tenant	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
deceitfully	O
into	O
the	O
Mint	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Landlord	O
interposing	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Mutiny	O
,	O
and	O
Riotous	O
Tumult	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
any	O
who	O
should	O
oppose	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Quarter-staves	O
,	O
and	O
short	O
wooden	O
pocket	O
pistols	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
term	O
them	O
)	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
Chambers	O
,	O
or	O
narrow	O
places	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Instruments	O
of	O
Cruelty	O
.	O
Goodson	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
an	O
Ashen	O
Quarter	O
staff	O
about	O
five	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Hart-slope	O
struck	O
any	O
Blow	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Bruise	O
.	O
Goodson	O
offer	O
'd	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Conversation	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
swore	O
positively	O
Goodson	O
struck	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
a	O
Debate	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Result	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
matter	O
should	O
at	O
present	O
be	O
found	O
Special	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Christian	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
Hendrick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
quarrelled	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
about	O
parting	O
Two	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
great	O
provocation	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Malice	O
propense	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rhoades	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
alone	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
laid	O
across	O
the	O
Chamber-pot	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
great	O
matter	O
of	O
harm	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Child	O
died	O
about	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
to	O
express	O
herself	O
very	O
affectionately	O
towards	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
somewhat	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
her	O
Innocency	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
Outlawed	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
now	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
18	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fled	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
might	O
be	O
lookt	O
after	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Stepney	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
feared	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
condition	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
was	O
found	O
alive	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
near	O
Stepney	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
groaned	O
much	O
,	O
wishing	O
that	O
he	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
was	O
bloody	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Stepney	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
was	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Friends	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Officer	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
civilly	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
his	O
Command	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Leager	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1689.	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Lute	O
string	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
another	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
with	O
four	O
Gold	O
Galooms	O
5	O
l.	O
an	O
Indian	O
peticoat	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
crimson	O
peticoat	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Lute-string	O
Gown	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
peticoat	O
lac't	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
abundance	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
a	O
Gown	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Whitwood	O
's	O
Daughters	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
Swore	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
Whitwood	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pantalina	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
a	O
Thief	O
said	O
was	O
St.	O
Leager	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
or	O
whatever	O
else	O
was	O
charged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
St.	O
Leager	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitwood	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
old	O
things	O
of	O
Sir	O
Adam	B-pers
Oatley	I-pers
's	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
St.	O
Leager	O
stifly	O
denying	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
of	O
33	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
Pratt	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
did	O
entice	O
Pratt	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
purloin	O
Lace	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
Pratt	O
confest	O
that	O
Jones	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
away	O
Lace	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Stephens	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
.	O
Jones	O
pretended	O
to	O
justifie	O
her	O
innocency	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
somewhat	O
circumstantial	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Pratt	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
a	O
Welshman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Hughes	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
met	O
Seymour	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Eling	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
white	O
coloured	O
Mare	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
a	O
pannel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Sum	O
of	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Seymour	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
Seymours	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
violently	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
hereupon	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
persued	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
well	O
weighing	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
a	O
Pipe-maker	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
an	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
by	O
Hangmans	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Parker	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Iron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lame	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
such	O
a	O
Weight	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
mature	O
consideration	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Effold	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vallens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
upon	O
Hamsted-Heath	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
)	O
several	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
Bone	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Ann	O
King	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
thatthey	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
rude	O
manner	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
being	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Durrant	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
year	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
discharged	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Free	O
pardon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mallard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
90	O
s.	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Coats	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
personally	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gagg	O
'd	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
afterwards	O
ransacking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
betwixt	O
Bednal-Green	B-place
and	O
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
their	O
advantage	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
six	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
Green	I-place
with	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
those	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
tryed	O
two	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Four	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
lace	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
lace	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Free	O
pardon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
Likewise	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
was	O
accused	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
Margaret	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Buffet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Deverell	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felonies	O
committed	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Napkin	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
a	O
Chamber-Window	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
Napkin	O
from	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
three	O
persons	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
Burglary	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
pardon	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
CRONE	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
Committed	O
against	O
our	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
having	O
and	O
holding	O
Correspondence	O
with	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
thereby	O
to	O
Depose	O
our	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
of	O
their	O
Royal	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Raise	O
War	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
this	O
our	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Miserable	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
amongst	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
pass	O
and	O
procure	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
his	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
was	O
long	O
in	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Indulgence	O
was	O
extended	O
towards	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
shewed	O
to	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Circumstance	O
at	O
that	O
Bar	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
clear	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
every	O
point	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
used	O
several	O
Evasions	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
Inforced	O
,	O
)	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Extenuations	O
,	O
several	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
to	O
perswade	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
Ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
several	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
their	O
Keeper	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
upon	O
a	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
wait	O
patiently	O
upon	O
them	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Mind	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Court	O
Ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Sustenance	O
,	O
or	O
Candle-Light	O
,	O
allowing	O
them	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
somewhat	O
to	O
Lie	O
upon	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
the	O
Court	O
met	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
Agree	O
,	O
One	O
or	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
making	O
some	O
particular	O
Scruples	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Resolved	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
Twelve	O
or	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
United	O
to	O
Return	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Crone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Prayed	O
for	O
an	O
Arrest	O
of	O
Judgment	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Exceptions	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
Councel	O
might	O
be	O
Assigned	O
him	O
to	O
Argue	O
to	O
his	O
Exceptions	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
in	O
Case	O
any	O
Point	O
arose	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
Prayed	O
that	O
Five	O
Councel	O
might	O
be	O
Assigned	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
their	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
Ordered	O
that	O
a	O
Court	O
should	O
be	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Scruples	O
,	O
)	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
Twelth	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
Seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
full	O
Tryal	O
will	O
be	O
Printed	O
at	O
Likewise	O
Anthony	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Leager	I-pers
had	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Three	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Risbey	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
One	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn-Bars	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Nine	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Effoll	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Vallens	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Macqueer	I-pers
the	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Reprieved	O
the	O
last	O
Execution-day	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
with	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rothery	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
suspicion	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
Bail	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Judge	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
.	O
Also	O
Matthew	O
Soot	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
Bail	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
likewise	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
having	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Doudall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Labourn	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Bishop	O
Labourn	O
,	O
belonging	O
formerly	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
was	O
remanded	O
.	O
One	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
suspected	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
for	O
divers	O
Offences	O
and	O
Misdemeanors	O
,	O
were	O
Released	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Elsingstone	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
the	O
former	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
for	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
about	O
the	O
QueensPlate	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mawn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
discharged	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Anthony	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Leager	I-pers
had	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
pardon	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
the	O
persons	O
concerned	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
very	O
seasonable	O
and	O
Christian-like	O
Advice	O
,	O
to	O
persuade	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
abuse	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Clemency	O
extended	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
issuing	O
out	O
His	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Act	O
of	O
Indempnity	O
and	O
Free	O
Pardon	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
furthermore	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
ever	O
they	O
committed	O
the	O
like	O
Crimes	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
would	O
stand	O
in	O
full	O
Force	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
severely	O
executed	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
newly	O
publisht	O
a	O
Play	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Bloody	O
Duke	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Adventures	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
Tragy	O
Comedy	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
lately	O
Acted	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
Alba	O
Regalis	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
This	O
Play	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
those	O
two	O
new	O
Ones	O
lately	O
publisht	O
;	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Abdicated	O
Prince	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Revolution	O
.	O
Containing	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
private	O
Entrigues	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
most	O
memorable	O
Transactions	O
that	O
have	O
hapned	O
since	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
An	O
Antidote	O
against	O
Lust	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Uncleanness	O
:	O
Shewing	O
its	O
various	O
Kinds	O
,	O
great	O
Evis	O
,	O
the	O
Temptations	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
effectual	O
Cure	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Care	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Casuistical	O
Morning	O
Exercises	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
Volume	O
,	O
lately	O
preached	O
by	O
several	O
Ministers	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Dunton	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
bath	O
occasion	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
Library	O
,	O
or	O
parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
cuber	O
in	O
large	O
or	O
small	O
Quantities	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
receive	O
ready	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
View	O
thereof	O
,	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
both	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
.	O
1690	O
.	O
