TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
Follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Helder	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Killbey	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Elkin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Becus	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Moreword	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
Gillborn	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Kettlebey	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ranew	I-pers
James	B-pers
Croyle	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milgate	I-pers
Randale	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gowers	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
Leonard	B-pers
Crossbey	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Clever	I-pers
The	O
Proceeding	O
's	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yarrold	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aspin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
offering	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Boy	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
slipping	O
among	O
the	O
Crowd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Crape	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chitvel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Crape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
dropt	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
altogether	O
ignorant	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
Spight	O
agaist	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
could	O
induce	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
believe	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Highway	O
men	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Turvil	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
of	O
Fulham	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
;	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Nag	O
,	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
,	O
price	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pannel	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
young	O
Turvill	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
Men	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
Swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Smith	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Mask	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
:	O
But	O
another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
W	O
-	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
robbed	O
a	O
Coach	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
buy	O
Horses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Carriages	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
several	O
insinuating	O
Evasions	O
and	O
frivelous	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
call	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
,	O
nor	O
prove	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
alledged	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
singly	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ball	O
'd	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gibborn	I-pers
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
sadle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gibborn	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Gelding	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
near	O
Tyburn	B-place
all	O
which	O
he	O
stifly	O
denyed	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
produce	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
any	O
way	O
advantageous	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Nook	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
forth	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
it	O
privately	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taxed	O
about	O
it	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
made	O
several	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Settle-bed	O
;	O
in	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Midwives	O
and	O
others	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
stilborn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
Shame	O
.	O
The	O
Statute	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
among	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
beset	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
jumping	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Entry	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
manifest	O
Proof	O
of	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Banghey	I-pers
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
presently	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Cane	O
before	O
upon	O
a	O
Dung	O
hill	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
being	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
young	O
Boy	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
De-Pree	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mark	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Blackman	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
only	O
circumstantially	O
;	O
How	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
possitively	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
favour	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
Malice	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Killbey	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
:	O
Who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Wills	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Killbey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
of	O
ready	O
Mony	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
great	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Killbey	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
Proof	O
against	O
,	O
Killbey	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Wills	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tyrrell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
from	O
Rachel	B-pers
Sturdy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sallowes	I-pers
(	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
steal	O
away	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Mony	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
evinced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
Sallowes	O
set	O
her	O
a	O
work	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Homer	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
were	O
all	O
3	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Homer	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Abbington	I-pers
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Poynt	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Principle	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
180	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Crowder	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Shed	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
lay	O
the	O
Crape	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directed	O
them	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
prevail	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
Silk	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
laced	O
Necloth	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
from	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Ward	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
short	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
main	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
farthing	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Glove	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocquet	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
very	O
weak	O
Arguments	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
.	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hamborrough-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
arraignment	O
she	O
desired	O
a	O
Party	O
Jury	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
William	B-pers
Carboneel	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Killbey	I-pers
Claudius	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Elkin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Pegott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mertin	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Morewood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Laughene	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gibborne	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Vausyer	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Streeton	I-pers
After	O
which	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
gave	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
fled	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Ruth	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drove	O
his	O
Cart	O
near	O
to	O
a	O
Poast	O
,	O
and	O
pressed	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
between	O
the	O
Cart	O
Wheele	O
and	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Head	O
was	O
not	O
broken	O
,	O
only	O
bruised	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
surgeon	O
declared	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
living	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Carrs	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
besides	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
where	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
two	O
Porringers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
:	O
Who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
since	O
fled	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
charged	O
against	O
her	O
but	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Maid	O
;	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
this	O
Maid	O
was	O
drawing	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
knocking	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
honest	O
Reputation	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
favourable	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
civily	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
(	O
likewise	O
)	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
slipt	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
material	O
Defence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Moseles	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
2	O
King	O
Jame	O
's	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
besides	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
24	O
l.	O
which	O
Eaton	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
Arden	O
;	O
Which	O
Gold	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
buried	O
under	O
an	O
Elder-Tree	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Eaton	O
,	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Withers	O
but	O
Arden	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
Mony	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
buried	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
Arden	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
entice	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
Rob	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Spynke	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Symon	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lazenberry	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
two	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
the	O
Daughters	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lazenberry	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
want	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Piece	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
freely	O
confess	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
Z	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
a	O
German	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
Party	O
Jury	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Standish	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Oselstone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
are	O
these	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
Lewis	B-pers
Hackall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Valatt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Wagoner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millgate	I-pers
James	B-pers
Marteen	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
John	B-pers
Provoe	I-pers
Randale	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ronetry	I-pers
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Oselstone	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Standish	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
through	O
Poverty	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
an	O
High	O
wayman	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
Benbridge-Hill	B-place
;	O
about	O
8	O
Miles	O
off	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Rapier	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
3	O
Men	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
Benbridge	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
stript	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Mony	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rid	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
crept	O
into	O
a	O
Hedge	O
near	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
passed	O
out	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
4	O
half	O
Crowns	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Hedg	O
,	O
being	O
affrighted	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
him	O
Leave	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
behaviour	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Millicent	B-pers
Humberstone	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Lutestring	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
another	O
Hood	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
16	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
aged	O
11	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Anterine	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Jevon	I-pers
:	O
It	O
seems	O
the	O
Girl	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Jevon	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
samething	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Pierces	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Girl	O
lay	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
it	O
:	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pilfering	O
idle	O
Wench	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Ursula	B-pers
Meritt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Meritt	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ward	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
Deliberation	O
begged	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
appointed	O
her	O
the	O
Portion	O
of	O
a	O
Petty-Lacenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pluckwell	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pluckwell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Roasting-Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
each	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefforye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fullam	B-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Pigs	O
out	O
of	O
Jefforye	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
urged	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Jefforyes	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Neighbors	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
his	O
Men	O
were	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
perfectly	O
.	O
But	O
Mrs.	O
Jefforyes	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
that	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
suspect	O
others	O
to	O
be	O
Confederates	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
elsewhere	O
when	O
the	O
Pigs	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
vexatious	O
and	O
lertgious	O
Woman	O
in	O
her	O
Neighbourhood	O
:	O
Which	O
did	O
so	O
well	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hurle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mugg	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
They	O
both	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
,	O
Clark	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mugg	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
near	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
Smith	O
,	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Mugg	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
both	O
did	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
Court	O
believe	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Smith	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joshua	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
the	O
20	O
l.	O
abundance	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
besides	O
160	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
suspect	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
close	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Daynter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
great	O
Robbery	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Nutmeg	O
grater	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
1	O
Picture	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
very	O
Rich	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
inveigled	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
perswade	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
Oppertunity	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
Which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
Door	O
ashoar	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
dressing	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slipt	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Trunk	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
found	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
one	O
Judith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
So	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
great	O
Villany	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
using	O
several	O
Evasions	O
,	O
particularly	O
desiring	O
Counsel	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
of	O
Law	O
arose	O
:	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Cox	O
and	O
another	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
upon	O
Hownslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Brown	O
Mare	O
price	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
Boucher	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
Cox	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
ceased	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
Pierce	O
's	O
Stable	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Cox	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
an	O
arrest	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
effect	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Taster	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
September	O
,	O
from	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
time	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
by	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
Q	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
Trimmer	B-pers
Salesbury	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Q	O
-	O
had	O
the	O
Tankards	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
Q	O
-	O
would	O
have	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
peremptorily	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Salisbury	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Q	O
-	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Tankards	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Hathaway	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
side	O
with	O
a	O
Bagonet	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
them	O
to	O
Hathaway	O
;	O
so	O
M	O
-	O
Q	O
-	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Salisbury	O
as	O
Accessary	O
afterwards	O
.	O
[	O
Q	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Salesbury	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
said	O
;	O
That	O
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
had	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Mother	O
confirmed	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
deposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
so	O
Yates	O
and	O
Jones	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Smith	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
:	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Warham	I-pers
value	O
5	O
l.	O
Unto	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Lamb	B-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Taffety	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Lambubert	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
unto	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
1689	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarfe	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver-Fringed	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
Silk	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
with	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kern	I-pers
:	O
But	O
she	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beckham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
shooting	O
Peter	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
into	O
the	O
Groyne	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
meer	O
Accident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	O
Varlen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
;	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peckering	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
5	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Some	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
accused	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
of	O
8	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
a	O
while	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
mist	O
his	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
Girdle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Honesty	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
20	O
s.	O
nine	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Pillowberes	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
Value	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
fully	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Fyrmin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Susan	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
Widow	O
of	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Johnson	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Spoons	O
were	O
lent	O
her	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Bass	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Thief	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hereford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gause-hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Taffary	O
Hood	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Scarfe	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Neck	O
Scarf	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
:	O
And	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
robbed	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
Madam	B-pers
Dines	I-pers
:	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
offer	O
Cherries	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
of	O
Petty-Lacenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
was	O
accused	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Hope	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Kath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Symmons	I-pers
of	O
Totnam	B-place
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Symmons	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
has	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Judgment	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lieutenant	O
James	B-pers
Weames	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
.	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
That	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
French	O
were	O
landed	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
place	O
the	O
Rig	O
hteous	O
King	O
in	O
his	O
Throne	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Land	O
would	O
never	O
be	O
blest	O
till	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Nobility	O
of	O
England	O
were	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Fat	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
for	O
King	O
William	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Religion	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
save	O
their	O
wealth	O
and	O
Honor	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
King	O
William	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
Villain	O
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Dog	O
and	O
an	O
Usurper	O
,	O
in	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Fathers	O
Crown	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
that	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
.	O
To	O
invalidate	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
numerous	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
particular	O
and	O
clear	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
zealous	O
Protestant	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
affected	O
to	O
the	O
Present	O
Government	O
,	O
as	O
might	O
appear	O
divers	O
ways	O
;	O
witness	O
his	O
forward	O
Zeal	O
in	O
New-England	O
(	O
being	O
sent	O
thither	O
under	O
the	O
Command	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
)	O
for	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Alteration	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
stage	O
of	O
Affairs	O
,	O
here	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
caused	O
all	O
the	O
Guns	O
in	O
the	O
Fort	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
number	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
vigorous	O
Defence	O
also	O
against	O
the	O
French	O
and	O
Indians	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Incursion	O
upon	O
the	O
Plantation	O
:	O
Besides	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
true	O
Protestant	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
note	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
meer	O
Revenge	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
appear	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
man	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
in	O
New-England	O
,	O
but	O
behaved	O
himself	O
there	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Master	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
small	O
Correction	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Fellow	O
was	O
heard	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
threaten	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
England	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
But	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
returning	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
frequent	O
communication	O
with	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
kept	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
slight	O
occasion	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
arrested	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Agreement	O
made	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Witness	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
pronounce	O
more	O
Threats	O
against	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
and	O
base	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowthorp	I-pers
,	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
Printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
most	O
pernicious	O
,	O
scandalous	O
,	O
Seditious	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Libel	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
as	O
well	O
before	O
as	O
after	O
)	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
Entituled	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Satum	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Pastoral	O
Letter	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
Treasonable	O
Sentences	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
other	O
very	O
reflecting	O
Sentences	O
said	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
support	O
his	O
Designs	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
purely	O
and	O
indeed	O
to	O
Raise	O
Rebellion	O
and	O
Discord	O
between	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
People	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Nation	O
into	O
a	O
Flame	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cause	O
them	O
to	O
cut	O
each	O
others	O
Throats	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
more	O
fully	O
laid	O
open	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
Court	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Message	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
)	O
was	O
to	O
preach	O
the	O
glad	O
Tidings	O
of	O
Peace	O
and	O
Salvation	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
perswade	O
Men	O
,	O
That	O
unless	O
they	O
repent	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
in	O
King	O
James	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
damned	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Writing	O
,	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
or	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
all	O
contained	O
5	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
about	O
400	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
Now	O
for	O
the	O
Vindication	O
of	O
himself	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
urged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
writ	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	O
,	O
to	O
beg	O
his	O
Advice	O
and	O
fatherly	O
Instruction	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
offended	O
by	O
it	O
and	O
mistook	O
his	O
measures	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
heatrily	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
)	O
:	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
Fair	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
John	O
Lowthers	O
was	O
Fined	O
500	O
Masks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Books	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
by	O
the	O
Common	O
Hangman	O
at	O
the	O
Palace-Yard	O
Westminster	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Temple	O
bar	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
the	O
same	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
And	O
to	O
be	O
Degraded	O
of	O
the	O
Ministering	O
Function	O
.	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Grace	O
Hedges	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
H	O
-	O
Z	O
-	O
,	O
Mary	O
with	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Trimmer	O
Salesbury	B-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
5.	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Alien	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Faton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	O
Tyrrell	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yarrold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Daynter	I-pers
,	O
M	O
-	O
Q	O
-	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
G	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Anne	O
Hereford	O
alias	O
Roberts	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
Q	O
-	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Jean	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Anne	O
Harsford	O
,	O
Pleading	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Marrons	O
were	O
empanelled	O
whose	O
Verdict	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Q	O
-	O
,	O
Brown	O
and	O
Hereford	O
were	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
Yates	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
13.	O
Frances	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Spinke	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Turner	O
,	O
Henry	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
,	O
Millisent	O
Humberston	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Jane	O
Pagert	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Banett	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wode	I-pers
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Notorious	O
Murther	O
that	O
was	O
lately	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Strange	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Thomas	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
suspected	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
Bowman	O
are	O
continued	O
in	O
Newgate	O
to	O
answer	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
John	O
Staples	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Lydia	O
C	O
ny	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
her	O
of	O
three	O
Pound	O
five	O
shilling	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
caution	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
To	O
beware	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
IF	O
any	O
Gentlemen	O
or	O
Ladies	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
spare	O
two	O
Hours	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
truly	O
and	O
properly	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
explain	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
C.	O
Switterda	O
Esq	O
;	O
professes	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
most	O
exact	O
Method	O
to	O
teach	O
them	O
the	O
said	O
Languages	O
in	O
one	O
Year	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
have	O
learned	O
formerly	O
may	O
recover	O
it	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
.	O
He	O
offereth	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
performance	O
thereof	O
.	O
He	O
teacheth	O
also	O
High	O
and	O
Low-Dutch	O
and	O
Italian	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
Time	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
desires	O
Historical	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
succ	O
Grammer	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Grammatical	O
Cards	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
taught	O
Children	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
:	O
They	O
men	O
have	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
2	O
Places	O
where	O
he	O
teacheth	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
S.	O
Clemence-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Canon	O
Street	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
Tuesdays	O
,	O
Thursdays	O
and	O
Saturdays	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
Charles	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
's	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Falkon-Court	O
over-against	O
S.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
A	O
Voyage	O
round	O
the	O
Word	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
pocket	O
Library	O
,	O
divided	O
into	O
several	O
Volumnes	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
Discoveries	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Method	O
never	O
made	O
by	O
Rambler	O
before	O
:	O
The	O
whole	O
Work	O
intermixt	O
with	O
Essaies	O
,	O
Historical	O
,	O
Moral	O
and	O
Divine	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
kinds	O
of	O
Learning	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Lover	O
of	O
Travels	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Wits	O
of	O
both	O
Universities	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
True	O
and	O
Impartial	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
Plot	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Conspirators	O
Names	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
An	O
Antidote	O
against	O
Lust	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Uncleanness	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
All	O
three	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
The	O
Plotting	O
Brothers	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
new	O
player	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Bloody	O
Duke	O
,	O
the	O
Abdicated	O
Prince	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Late	O
Revolutions	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
containing	O
the	O
Secret	O
History	O
of	O
Affairs	O
from	O
the	O
Restoration	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirleus	I-pers
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
Who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
,	O
Cures	O
all	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Stabs	O
Scurfs	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
Kings-Evil	O
,	O
Leprosie	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
be	O
Cures	O
not	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
bath	O
Cured	O
above	O
500	O
persons	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
It	O
quickly	O
and	O
safely	O
Cure	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
Mercury	O
without	O
danger	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
Purges	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
Purges	O
,	O
in	O
cleansing	O
all	O
Crudities	O
and	O
Impurities	O
so	O
prevent	O
and	O
cure	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Stone	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Diseases	O
he	O
gives	O
his	O
opinion	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
