TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	I-pers
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bynks	I-pers
Kenelm	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Dansey	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
David	B-pers
Grile	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cator	I-pers
John	B-pers
Werts	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gerrald	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
John	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bredon	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
William	B-pers
Syncock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Barch	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Anne	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
ell	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
18	O
d	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
;	O
which	O
matter	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
own	O
Throat	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Brigs	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brendon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jean	B-pers
Voudger	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Rance	I-pers
56	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Holland	O
Cornets	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
Quoifs	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Hoods	O
13	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Elinor	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
writing	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
false	O
Letters	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
deni	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Cheat	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Whitwood	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
knowing	O
Joseph	O
Taylor	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
Receive	O
,	O
Comfort	O
,	O
and	O
Maintain	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
with	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Eades	O
in	O
Whitwood	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Whitwood	O
called	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
chid	O
his	O
Man	O
for	O
committing	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
;	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prosecute	O
both	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Eades	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
N	B-pers
-	I-pers
Y	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
sorely	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
further	O
search	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
tell	O
who	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
threatned	O
very	O
often	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sellinger	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
380	O
yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
was	O
Arraign	O
'd	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
poors	O
Box	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Poultrey	B-place
Compter	I-place
,	O
but	O
proceeding	O
somewhat	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
the	O
Glocester	O
Carrier	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
brass	O
Blunderbus	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Gun	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
leathern	O
Purse	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
mone	O
y	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Four	O
Men	O
met	O
the	O
Carrier	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Honslow	B-place
,	O
stopt	O
his	O
Wagon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
Wagon	O
,	O
besides	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Portmantua	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
to	O
open	O
Doors	O
and	O
Locks	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
upon	O
his	O
Commitment	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
he	O
would	O
Fire	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Taylor	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
Eades	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
:	O
Taylor	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
until	O
Eades	O
was	O
cleared	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
respite	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
telling	O
them	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
standing	O
mute	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
immediately	O
Pressed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Whitwood	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Taylor	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Stauton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
upon	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
so	O
also	O
did	O
Eades	O
;	O
but	O
Eades	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Taylor	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Whitwood	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
Taylor	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Eades	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
[	O
Taylor	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Eades	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Southorn	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
produce	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
appearing	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
the	O
Sheep	O
;	O
so	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Denellan	I-pers
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
;	O
Denellan	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
casting	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
bruising	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
.	O
Abundance	O
of	O
Evidence	O
were	O
produced	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Distress	O
upon	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Nusance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jones	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Pots	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
said	O
Denellan	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
Woman	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
confest	O
that	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Distress	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Bruise	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Bruises	O
were	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Denellan	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
Woman	O
a	O
small	O
push	O
,	O
but	O
designed	O
no	O
hurt	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
at	O
her	O
Death	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Jones	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kibworth	I-pers
alias	O
Savidge	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Trunk	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
Rugg	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
hang	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher	O
s	O
Hooks	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
of	O
that	O
Profession	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
wrench	O
'd	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
five	O
Canvas	O
Sheets	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
yet	O
denied	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Togood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Doyley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
pair	O
more	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Dowlace	O
Sheets	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
D	O
-	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
favour	O
'd	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Moutsanta	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Rake	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Looking-Glass	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
they	O
found	O
sold	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
and	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
Watson	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
pawned	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
denied	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
Montsantas	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Watson	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Dowglace	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
35	O
s.	O
seven	O
pieces	O
more	O
8l	O
7	O
s.	O
another	O
35	O
s.	O
nine	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
4	O
l.	O
five	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
25	O
s.	O
three	O
Hoods	O
18	O
s.	O
four	O
Box	O
Combs	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Ivory	O
Combs	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
a	O
Maid	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hunt	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
opportunity	O
to	O
direct	O
some	O
Thieves	O
where	O
the	O
Gold	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
relenting	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Case	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Serge	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Serge	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
;	O
she	O
deni	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Leather	O
Trunk	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
more	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
Petticoats	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
Smocks	O
and	O
some	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Edson	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
her	O
Husband	O
rather	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Hansley	I-pers
alias	O
Hunsley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mabel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
in	O
December	O
last	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
same	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
these	O
Goods	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
2	O
Guinea	O
's	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
readiness	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
Keys	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Hansley	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Knight	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Watchman	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Boards	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
betimes	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
thro	O
'	O
want	O
of	O
Bread	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Togood	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
Evidenc	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Spoon	O
removed	O
that	O
lay	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
an	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferr	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
laid	O
short	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
a	O
Minister	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
false	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
upon	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
for	O
20	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
being	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
flatly	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Gospel	O
Law	O
required	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
Witness	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
followed	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
Forgery	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
Shipton	O
with	O
a	O
Bill	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
received	O
9	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Bill	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
manifested	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
who	O
wrote	O
the	O
Bills	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
saying	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Bitch	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
given	O
to	O
Drinking	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Cabinet	O
Maker	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Court	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Ferrer	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
malicious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
saying	O
,	O
First	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
William	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
his	O
Declaration	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
preserve	O
the	O
Laws	O
:	O
But	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
altered	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
suddenly	O
repent	O
of	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
maintain	O
our	O
Rights	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
James	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Right	O
done	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
fair	O
Proposels	O
made	O
of	O
Casting	O
a	O
Free	O
Parliament	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Terry	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
the	O
Words	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
to	O
testifie	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
Protestant	O
,	O
and	O
relinquisht	O
his	O
Commission	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
Papist	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
well	O
satisfied	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
drawing	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
upon	O
a	O
Bill	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Villers	O
for	O
14	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
at	O
St.	O
Albans	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Young	I-pers
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Serjeant	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Notorious	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
excel	O
Granger	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
and	O
Clansey	O
for	O
Cheating	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Forgery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waltam	I-pers
of	O
Eling	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Mary	B-pers
Waltam	I-pers
his	O
Child	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
against	O
a	O
wooden	O
Post	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Ear	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
under	O
Chains	O
when	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Madman	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
singing	O
to	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
dasht	O
its	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
Post	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Riggs	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
8	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
besides	O
sheets	O
,	O
Table	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
day	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
in	O
number	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
without	O
their	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
whil'st	O
the	O
rest	O
ransackt	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
but	O
obscurely	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
to	O
his	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gullsford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Caleb	B-pers
Price	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
Holland	O
Pillowbares	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Carkass	O
of	O
Mutton	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Borkin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Butcher	O
Borkin	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mutton	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
persued	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
the	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
killed	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
for	O
Execution	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
stay	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Nine	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Judges	O
delivering	O
their	O
Opinions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
on	O
a	O
Sledge	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
Quartered	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Bowels	O
burnt	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
a	O
Presentment	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
First	O
,	O
Against	O
Alehouses	O
for	O
selling	O
Drink	O
on	O
the	O
Sabbath	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Abuse	O
thereof	O
,	O
Indulging	O
the	O
Apprentices	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Tipling	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
their	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Reproach	O
and	O
Dishonour	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
Against	O
the	O
Lotteries	O
and	O
Gaming-houses	O
.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
Against	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
used	O
in	O
publick	O
Houses	O
.	O
And	O
Fourthly	O
,	O
Against	O
that	O
most	O
notorious	O
and	O
common	O
Sin	O
of	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
most	O
honourable	O
Answer	O
,	O
highly	O
commending	O
their	O
great	O
Care	O
promising	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
(	O
with	O
all	O
possible	O
speed	O
)	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Three	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
Convicted	O
two	O
Sessions	O
before	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
N	O
-	O
Y	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Denallan	I-pers
was	O
Respited	O
before	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
bring	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sellinger	I-pers
was	O
Respited	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
intending	O
to	O
consider	O
further	O
of	O
his	O
Cause	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gulliford	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
Six	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
Timothy	O
Carter	O
,	O
Ursula	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Peter	O
Potter	O
,	O
all	O
four	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waltam	I-pers
for	O
killing	O
his	O
Child	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bedlam	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
Sedicious	O
Words	O
.	O
One	O
Peter	B-pers
Romane	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Drinking	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
the	O
Hoppiness	O
and	O
Prosperity	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
An	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
against	O
one	O
Clark	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
from	O
one	O
Carleton	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
rest	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
the	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
killed	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
for	O
Execution	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
stay	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Nine	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Judges	O
delivering	O
their	O
Opinions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
on	O
a	O
Sledge	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
Quartered	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Bowels	O
burnt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Togood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kibworth	I-pers
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Vowger	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Dowglas	O
;	O
Abigail	B-pers
Hansley	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Vowger	I-pers
,	O
Abigail	B-pers
Hansley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
pleading	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Empannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
Vowger	O
and	O
Knight	O
were	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Hansley	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
alias	O
Smith	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
;	O
1st	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
2dly	O
.	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
3dly	O
.	O
at	O
Westminster	O
Hall-Gate	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
next	O
Term	O
;	O
4thly	O
at	O
the	O
New-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
200	O
Marks	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
each	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
20	O
Mark	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
who	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
committed	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Respited	O
till	O
further	O
Orders	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
Several	O
Letters	O
written	O
by	O
some	O
French	O
Protestants	O
now	O
Refug	O
'd	O
in	O
Germany	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Tyrannical	O
Persecution	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Unity	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Protestants	O
of	O
England	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Presbyterians	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Arch-Bishops	O
and	O
Bishops	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
6.	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
and	O
Commons	O
Assembled	O
in	O
Parliament	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Highness	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
,	O
now	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
bishop	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtis	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Tears	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
First	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
water	O
,	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
canseth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
these	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mantioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
serves	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
1690	O
.	O
