TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Ayers	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lycence	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Foxley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Chard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hazlewood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Symson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Axton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Hodgden	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
Randol	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
jun	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Redknapp	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Mawn	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
price	O
20	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
only	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Felonious	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
stranger	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Notion	O
of	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
beyond	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
faultering	O
stories	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
yards	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
striped	O
Velvet	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tully	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
one	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
to	O
offer	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
sale	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
Hayes	O
,	O
Hayes	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Kirk	O
,	O
which	O
Kirk	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
sercht	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
in	O
May	O
pole	O
Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
persons	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
civilly	O
formerly	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
Circumstantial	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Alhallows	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
gold	O
Coral	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Potings	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
12	O
s.	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
an	O
Emerald	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esquire	B-pers
Fangham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chamber	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
altered	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
all	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
her	O
Husbands	O
,	O
one	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Calling	O
for	O
some	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
proved	O
her	O
Marriage	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Holland	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
favouring	O
of	O
her	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Noney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
black	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leading	O
Staff	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Silver	O
Head	O
on	O
it	O
weighing	O
19	O
Ounces	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Company	O
of	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Hall	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Company	O
having	O
the	O
Head	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
25	O
s.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
one	O
Falconer	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
have	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Reeves	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
tempted	O
and	O
constrained	O
by	O
Poverty	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bereman	I-pers
Carman	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Vintrey	I-place
,	O
two	O
Cyder-Presses	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
two	O
Scrues	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Cyder-Mill	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Iron-Bars	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Utensils	O
fitting	O
for	O
Cyder-making	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
did	O
send	O
such	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
in	O
Thames	O
street	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Porters	O
,	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
Seis	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
Rent	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
White	O
had	O
disagreed	O
before	O
in	O
their	O
Accounts	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
Watkins	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
Credible	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
Mr.	O
White	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
called	O
very	O
Credible	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
White	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
Evil	O
Intention	O
,	O
and	O
Bereman	O
being	O
not	O
positively	O
accused	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Babbington	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Uriah	B-pers
Babbington	I-pers
his	O
son	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
Murther	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Cotter	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Raper	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Ten	O
Inches	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Right	O
Pap	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
demonstrated	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Babbington	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
were	O
a	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	B-place
in	O
Panton's-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
Cotter	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
where	O
sat	O
Mr.	O
Babbington	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Cotter	O
making	O
a	O
Complement	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Kiss	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
much	O
offended	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Cotter	O
and	O
young	O
Babbington	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
farther	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
Cotter	O
was	O
Killed	O
and	O
young	O
Babbington	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cotter	O
was	O
Killed	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
only	O
that	O
which	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
most	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
procure	O
his	O
Sons	O
Escape	O
,	O
by	O
disarming	O
of	O
Cotter	O
,	O
and	O
interrupting	O
his	O
being	O
secur	O
'd	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Well	O
weighing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Column	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jakeman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
Jones	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
Nine	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bragget	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Relph	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Kyrbey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
aforesaid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
9	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
10	O
l.	O
another	O
Cup	O
7	O
l.	O
another	O
Salt	O
9	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Poringer	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Bowl	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Ladle	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
gilt	O
3	O
l.	O
another	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Tumblers	O
5	O
l.	O
7	O
Spoons	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Watch	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
gold	O
Twist	O
,	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
13	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
3	O
Silk	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Night-Royle	O
,	O
16	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
2	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Guinea	O
's	O
:	O
Also	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
abovesaid	O
.	O
Two	O
lac	O
'd	O
Bands	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
Purse	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Ring	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
Handkerchief	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
33	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
2	O
Thimbles	O
18	O
d.	O
4	O
lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
Baker	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
Hynds	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
racking	O
up	O
their	O
Horses	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
forcing	O
their	O
way	O
against	O
all	O
the	O
Bolts	O
and	O
Locks	O
,	O
making	O
the	O
very	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
and	O
Wooden	O
Doors	O
to	O
yield	O
to	O
their	O
wicked	O
and	O
bloody	O
Designs	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Baker	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
their	O
Beds	O
,	O
gagging	O
not	O
only	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
whole	O
Family	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
they	O
began	O
their	O
Pranks	O
,	O
Rifling	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
Williams	O
and	O
Column	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
persued	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
People	O
,	O
at	O
Anny-seed	O
cleer	O
in	O
Jakeman	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
Williams	O
,	O
Column	O
,	O
and	O
Chambers	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Ratcliffe	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Four	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
that	O
could	O
positively	O
charge	O
the	O
other	O
Five	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
Notice	O
taken	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
so	O
base	O
and	O
villainous	O
Attempt	O
against	O
so	O
many	O
innocent	O
persons	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Rothery	O
,	O
now	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
witnessed	O
against	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Plot	O
in	O
Intrigue	O
made	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
Rob	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Gang	O
,	O
being	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
since	O
repented	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
declare	O
all	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
thereby	O
to	O
attain	O
Favour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
Snacks	O
at	O
Jakeman	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Anny-seed	O
Cleer	O
,	O
but	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
yet	O
made	O
his	O
Bargain	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
share	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Snack	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
rest	O
compassed	O
their	O
devilish	O
Intentions	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
proof	O
of	O
this	O
(	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
being	O
before	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
beforementioned	O
)	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
up	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
Tryed	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
hereafter	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Emes	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
strip	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
)	O
the	O
Gown	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
an	O
End	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Dan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Diana	B-pers
Dan	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
four	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
sheets	O
40	O
s.	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Pewter-Plates	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
Chamber-Pots	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monies	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
80	O
l.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
whilst	O
Boswell	O
was	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
Dying	O
here	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
after	O
Boswell	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
Buried	O
,	O
pretending	O
a	O
lawful	O
Right	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
because	O
she	O
deceased	O
was	O
their	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
meaning	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
Felony	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
series	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
sales	O
10	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Mullinax	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Witnessed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mullinax	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
pretended	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
while	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
nor	O
took	O
their	O
Lodging	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Robbed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Key	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hankin	I-pers
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
preferred	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
Tryed	O
,	O
as	O
hereafter	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Luadore	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Silver	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guinea	O
in	O
the	O
Roll	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Knee	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
several	O
Extenuations	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
also	O
Pick	O
Locks	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
tended	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
Discredit	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Elinor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Susanna	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dugan	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Flaxen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
Feloniously	O
and	O
Burglarily	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Black	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
some	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Salt	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Black	O
Lead	O
about	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
Mark	O
Casks	O
withal	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
)	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trippet	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Goods	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bags	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
65	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
confest	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
for	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rider	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rider	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Beating	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
Spinster	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Year	O
of	O
our	O
late	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
(	O
of	O
Blessed	O
Memory	O
.	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
and	O
some	O
Blows	O
hapened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Beat	O
Townsend	O
's	O
Head	O
against	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Cistern	O
till	O
the	O
Blood	O
gushed	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
favoured	O
of	O
an	O
express	O
Malice	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Resdale	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
sale	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Huyet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
47	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gavel	I-pers
alias	O
Gardiner	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
in	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Square	I-place
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
Gavel	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
his	O
flight	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
accused	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Barrow	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Maqueer	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Notorious	O
Highway-Men	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Sword	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Rix-Dollar	O
24	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
Coloured	O
Gray	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Maqueer	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hansey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cane	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
Finchley	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
where	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
persons	O
stopt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Witness	O
did	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Highway-man	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Kotbell	I-pers
's	O
Wagon	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
Silk	O
,	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Merchandizing	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
sent	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Henley	O
and	O
Wallingford	O
.	O
The	O
Carrier	O
said	O
that	O
divers	O
persons	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
onethu	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
likewise	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Periwig	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Lynes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Hewets	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
Parish	I-place
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kennedee	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Black	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Hole	I-place
near	O
Hockley	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Hole	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
13	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
9	O
Poringers	O
6	O
s.	O
some	O
Pots	O
and	O
Linens	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
of	O
goods	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
window	O
,	O
swearing	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
should	O
oppose	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
evidence	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
only	O
Bristow	O
had	O
some	O
Linen	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Plates	O
were	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
which	O
Kennedee	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Soldiers	O
reply	O
d	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
People	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
beset	O
,	O
round	O
about	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
ill	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gray	O
Gelding	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Partner	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Mawn	I-pers
in	O
Horse-stealing	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Gamester	O
at	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
Play	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mawn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
silly	O
Countrey	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
easily	O
drawn	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
of	O
,	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Lowder	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burton	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blake	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Blackmoors-street	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hermond	B-pers
Roxall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ruttey	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Dutch	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Kneeves	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Denzick	B-pers
Farbert	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
inches	O
,	O
Upon	O
which	O
Tryal	O
,	O
a	O
Party-Jury	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
was	O
these	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richman	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Bredey	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pedley	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Ernes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Gize	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
Raymond	B-pers
Rayney	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rayne	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gradey	I-pers
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
Roxell	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
Kneeves	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
away	O
Kneeves	O
Shovel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
striving	O
to	O
obtain	O
them	O
they	O
both	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Roxal	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
Kneeves	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
after	O
dropt	O
down	O
head	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
their	O
interpreters	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
Kneeves	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Midleton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Acton	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
family	O
was	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
slipt	O
the	O
Tankard	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Person	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sufficient	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gravestock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
shooting	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Feney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
Bullet	O
upon	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
4	O
inches	O
depth	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
Dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
Charged	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Powder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
intend	O
Mischief	O
against	O
the	O
Girl	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
8	O
Counter	O
Curtains	O
,	O
10	O
Flaxen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloath	O
,	O
one	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
diver	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
alledged	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
Napkin	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
positively	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Napkins	O
among	O
and	O
her	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
good	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fincham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Elinor	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
Sattins	O
,	O
and	O
Linnens	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Mantles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Barnardine	B-pers
Tunstone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
somewhat	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Tunstone	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Fincham	O
Lodged	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
Fincham	O
called	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
to	O
buy	O
14	O
Clouts	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Fox	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Clouts	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Innocency	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Broker	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
being	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Livers	O
.	O
Fincham	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Tunstone	O
's	O
House	O
Rent	O
free	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
no	O
way	O
Charge	O
them	O
positively	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
various	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Elderkin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Foot	B-pers
Onslow	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Velvet	O
,	O
abundance	O
of	O
House	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
;	O
besides	O
they	O
had	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
Elderkin	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
likewise	O
did	O
Wilson	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Pistols	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
Robbed	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Elderkin	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
and	O
Third	O
time	O
singly	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
form	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
Woollen	O
,	O
and	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
and	O
Alamode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
with	O
Pinners	O
,	O
and	O
Coives	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
Countess	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
indictments	O
.	O
One	O
thing	O
there	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Noted	O
,	O
That	O
Elderkin	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
refused	O
to	O
Plead	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
Mute	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forthwith	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
immediately	O
Press	O
'd	O
to	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
humble	O
Petition	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Consideration	O
,	O
the	O
Sentence	O
was	O
revers	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
Three	O
Several	O
Tryals	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictments	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
said	O
false	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Weather-Sheep	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Payar	B-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fessets	O
Grounds	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
Sheep	O
upon	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
persued	O
they	O
dropt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Bentley	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
persuit	O
,	O
but	O
Key	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
further	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
they	O
Seized	O
the	O
Sheep	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
hold	O
them	O
down	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
persued	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bibbey	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Poringer	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastecoat	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
with	O
Napkins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
charged	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Todd	O
,	O
also	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pinner	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeoffery	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Oxen	O
price	O
28	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	O
De-veil	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
and	O
all	O
others	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Clergy	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fully	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kenyon	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Martin	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
James	O
Clerkenwell	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Bar	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
Ives	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Soldier	O
s	O
came	O
on	O
Kenyon	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
Drinking	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
about	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
13	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Threatned	O
to	O
Kill	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
with	O
Bloody	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
That	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
wasdefence	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
were	O
very	O
Rude	O
and	O
Insolent	O
,	O
not	O
withstanding	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
a	O
Plate	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Beef	O
and	O
Pork	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
good	O
Evidencers	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
St.	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evall	I-pers
,	O
all	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swanley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilest	O
Mr.	O
Swanley	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
Williams	O
and	O
Evall	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
against	O
Marshall	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Davis	B-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
at	O
one	O
Bushes	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trippet	I-pers
Yeoman	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elinor	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Bodkin	O
and	O
a	O
Thimble	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Besides	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
Confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Elfingstone	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
36	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Brownlow	I-pers
Baronet	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
concerning	O
Melting	O
down	O
the	O
Queens	O
Plate	O
at	O
White-hall	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jakeman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
Williams	O
and	O
Column	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
at	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
anew	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
abetting	O
,	O
counselling	O
,	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Williams	O
,	O
Column	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
by	O
parting	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
at	O
Jakeman	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Anny-seed-Clare	B-place
,	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
Cox	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
present	O
,	O
yet	O
Williams	O
kept	O
the	O
Snack	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Cox	O
,	O
to	O
invalidate	O
what	O
was	O
urg	O
'd	O
,	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
Civilly	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
punctual	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Dealings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rothery	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
of	O
Baker	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Cox	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
might	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
,	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Witness	O
against	O
Jakeman	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
likewise	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vallen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
seized	O
Taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
punctual	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
Pancras	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
Smocks	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
They	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Searle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
1687	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
General	O
Pardon	O
granted	O
since	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Derby	B-pers
Lyndsey	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
compounded	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Presgrave	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
lookt	O
into	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Bills	O
of	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Ralph	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
for	O
above	O
16	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
imbezled	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
dated	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2d	O
in	O
April	O
following	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
at	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bane	O
;	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Fifteen	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
E	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Hermond	O
Roxall	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ruttey	I-pers
,	O
Dutch-men	O
,	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jeoffery	O
Edwards	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
Thomasin	O
Lowder	O
;	O
alias	O
Burton	O
,	O
alias	O
Blake	O
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Fourteen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mawn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Column	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Maqueer	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Elderkin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hillgrave	I-pers
,	O
who	O
Received	O
Judgment	O
to	O
Dye	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
Five	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gavell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gardner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Trippet	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Seven	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Noney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Black	O
,	O
who	O
Robbed	O
Habberdashers-hall	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
David	O
Key	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bibbey	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Green	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holborn	O
Bars	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Resdale	I-pers
were	O
Repriev	O
'd	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gravestock	I-pers
order	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
course	O
.	O
One	O
Jones	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kennion	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
course	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
Martin	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
20	O
Convicts	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
pleading	O
it	O
upon	O
their	O
Knees	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Crone	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
arraigned	O
this	O
Sessions	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
,	O
his	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
particular	O
Reasons	O
,	O
Adjourned	O
till	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
hath	O
occasion	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
Library	O
,	O
or	O
parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
large	O
or	O
small	O
Quantities	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
receive	O
ready	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
View	O
thereof	O
,	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
A	O
New	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Siege	O
of	O
London-Derry	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
late	O
memorable	O
Transactions	O
of	O
that	O
City	O
faithfully	O
represented	O
,	O
to	O
rectifie	O
the	O
Mistakes	O
,	O
and	O
supply	O
the	O
Omissions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
Account	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
,	O
Chaptain	O
to	O
a	O
Regiment	O
there	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
Sieze	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
Mouth	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
;	O
those	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
