TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Eaveley	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
George	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stancliffe	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Blagrove	I-pers
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Jeremiah	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mirdale	I-pers
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boltbey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gunstone	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Weekes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Remidge	I-pers
Abraham	O
Hedge-about	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Brumfeild	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Philip	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neale	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
in	O
Bartholomew	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
coyned	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
each	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
10	O
s	O
Pieces	O
,	O
22	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
besides	O
60	O
l	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Gold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
neither	O
stayed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
favoured	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
prevent	O
Discovery	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
Ignorant	O
Silly	O
Girle	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eave	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Shoe	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bowle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Coife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Lynen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Eave	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
Lynen	O
about	O
her	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
affirm	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
somewhat	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castlealias	I-pers
Cassey	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
making	O
50	O
Pieces	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
I	O
Shillings	O
,	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
of	O
the	O
false	O
Shillings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Marygold-Alley	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Salt-Box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
for	O
melting	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
Files	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
several	O
Evasions	O
,	O
where	O
by	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Making	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
of	O
20	O
Pieces	O
of	O
K.	O
James	O
L	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
I	O
's	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
same	O
Evidences	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Stamp	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Hammer	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Impression	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
And	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
coyne	O
only	O
struck	O
the	O
Stamp	O
,	O
which	O
another	O
Person	O
might	O
easily	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Vallard	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
also	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyne	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
ketched	O
clipping	O
of	O
Mony	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
clip	O
a	O
Shilling	O
almost	O
round	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Clipings	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Testimony	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
uttering	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
said	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
by	O
one	O
Wright	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
Wright	O
allowed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
29s	O
of	O
clipt	O
Mony	O
for	O
20	O
s	O
of	O
broad	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Penny	O
in	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
putting	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
uttered	O
Mony	O
faslly	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Blenchard	I-pers
,	O
about	O
9	O
o	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
ofSeptember	O
last	O
,	O
2	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evidenced	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
off	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
swear	O
the	O
Burglary	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	O
Fire-bank	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborne	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
8	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Watches	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
some	O
what	O
promiseuous	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Constance	O
Wayne-wright	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Pot	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Paul	B-pers
Hayley	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elmor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
at	O
Graves-end	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
Lynen	O
and	O
Wollen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
one	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Mandrill	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Everal	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cloves	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
seven	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
upon	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
numerous	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
That	O
Jackson	O
being	O
press	O
'd	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
a	O
Fewd	O
arose	O
about	O
pressing	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Occasion	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
thus	O
.	O
Whilst	O
the	O
four	O
latter	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
ashoar	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mandyil	O
's	O
Dye	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
3	O
Cranes	O
,	O
to	O
press	O
his	O
Servants	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
one	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Posture	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
escape	O
:	O
Which	O
Browning	O
seeing	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Stroak	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Cutlace	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
bled	O
violently	O
at	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
conveyed	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
a	O
Fracture	O
in	O
his	O
Skull	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mandrill	I-pers
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Browning	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mandrills	O
,	O
and	O
press	O
'd	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
manner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
only	O
Browning	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
killing	O
the	O
said	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
found	O
Special	O
,	O
until	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Judges	O
shall	O
determine	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
their	O
further	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
alias	O
Juxon	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
was	O
ordered	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Andgrave	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
eat	O
some	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
2	O
Bags	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
marrying	O
2	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
named	O
Elinor	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Edith	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Fisher	O
he	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
32d	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
he	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
II	O
.	O
Upon	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Griscall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Cupboard-Cloath	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bryant	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
9	O
l.	O
with	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
400	O
l.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
one	O
Mich.	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
,	O
as	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
appeared	O
;	O
In	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Rotherick	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
Eye	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
depth	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
Shandois-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
one	O
Pass	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucey	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Megs	I-pers
of	O
Thistle-worth	B-place
of	O
8	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
22	O
s.	O
2	O
Forks	O
13	O
s.	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
bright	O
Bay	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Meggs	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
entrusted	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
proved	O
false	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
2	O
Spoons	O
and	O
2	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
Mrs.	O
Meggs	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
adjoyning	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
:	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Finch	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
lead	O
,	O
he	O
promising	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Boy	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
some	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
reared	O
a	O
Ladder	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
she	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Braseby	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Goodspeed	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ince	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
at	O
West	B-place
Ham	I-place
in	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
Spoons	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
Spoons	O
(	O
Braseby	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
)	O
were	O
melted	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Persons	O
that	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Poppet	O
Shews	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
More	O
fields	O
,	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
old	O
Offenders	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
Boy	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Luke	B-pers
Braseby	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Concealing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
File	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
besides	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Haksworth	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
3	O
Frames	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
wooden	O
Benches	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Felony	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
to	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Chawk	I-pers
of	O
Hillingdon	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
containing	O
several	O
Cloathes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Staynes	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
begging	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
and	O
Lyon	B-pers
Fountaine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Roger	B-pers
Shakesbey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Hat	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruque	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Shakesbey	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
Water	O
at	O
Salesbury	B-place
stairs	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lyon	O
Fountaine	O
set	O
upon	O
Shakesbey	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Peruque	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
another	O
indictment	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
against	O
them	O
forthwith	O
.	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lowbridge	I-pers
alias	O
Spencer	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
coloured	O
grey	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
instant	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Mare	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
Hammond	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
Cooper	O
for	O
44	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Inn	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
was	O
ordered	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
London	O
side	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
tryed	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Batrone	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
;	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
confest	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prefect	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
50	O
yards	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
Irish	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
13	O
s.	O
There	O
came	O
3	O
Women	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Eaton	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Jones	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
.	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Dod	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
never	O
produced	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
some	O
Evidence	O
that	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
1000	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
value	O
1200	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
one	O
Buckle	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
Bird	O
was	O
not	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Christmas	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Carryer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
of	O
84	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
9	O
more	O
met	O
Christmas	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
his	O
Wagon	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
shared	O
the	O
Mony	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Robbery	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Breteridge	I-pers
of	O
Kensington	B-place
:	O
James	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Brock	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
they	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
offered	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Newport-Market	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Dog	O
and	O
Bitch-yard	O
,	O
in	O
Damnation-Ally	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Shovel	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
his	O
Shovel	O
at	O
a	O
Sow	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
chane	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
declared	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
spake	O
well	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Randale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nowell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
without	O
Leave	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
Suffolk	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
aside	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
or	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
instant	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Oliver	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
refusing	O
it	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
might	O
mistake	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
L	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckstone	I-pers
of	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
a	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Buckstone	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
going	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Armorer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
without	O
paying	O
her	O
Fees	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
40	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
Rubbers	O
to	O
rub	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
in	O
Eling	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
near	O
Acton	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Testimony	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
clipt	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
clipt	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
denyed	O
it	O
stiffly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
used	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
they	O
hide	O
them	O
from	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
using	O
several	O
extenuating	O
Arguments	O
to	O
stiffle	O
their	O
horrid	O
Crime	O
;	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
no	O
good	O
Effect	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
singly	O
indicted	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Harbouring	O
of	O
Thieves	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
keeping	O
them	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
as	O
High	O
waymen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Highway-men	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
near	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
distribute	O
themselves	O
abroad	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
once	O
set	O
a	O
Grazier	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
High-way-men	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
notorious	O
base	O
Fellow	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Wagons	O
robbed	O
within	O
this	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
going	O
that	O
Road	O
,	O
through	O
his	O
Instigation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Anne	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
getting	O
Clipings	O
privately	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
concealing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
that	O
Profession	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Filing	O
heard	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Clippings	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
another	O
Young	O
Man	O
lodged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Clippings	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Firmin	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Berestar	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
the	O
Court	O
adjourned	O
till	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
being	O
set	O
,	O
they	O
proceeded	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Juxon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
evidenced	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Russel	O
opposing	O
him	O
he	O
strook	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
invalidate	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
passing	O
off	O
29	O
Pieces	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
change	O
Broad	O
Money	O
for	O
clipt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Innocency	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
changing	O
bad	O
Mony	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Fault	O
,	O
in	O
passing	O
off	O
36	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Mony	O
:	O
Which	O
was	O
fully	O
evidenced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
off	O
three	O
pound	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
availed	O
him	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dant	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Drachm	O
Cups	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Hunt	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Hunt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
above-stairs	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
write	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
presently	O
stopt	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
besides	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
lately	O
Convicted	O
for	O
very	O
Wicked	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Crimes	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
upon	O
their	O
respective	O
Knees	O
,	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
:	O
Whose	O
Names	O
are	O
exactly	O
inserted	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
Christoph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Mackquear	I-pers
George	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
James	B-pers
Gardyner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Vallence	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Quarles	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Joanna	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Anne	B-pers
Hereford	I-pers
James	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
Susannah	B-pers
Tirrel	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Exhortation	O
,	O
To	O
beware	O
how	O
they	O
abused	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mercy	O
,	O
by	O
returning	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
expect	O
no	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
a	O
severe	O
and	O
condign	O
Punishment	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
L	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dant	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Batrone	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
2	O
Henry	B-pers
Chawke	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Brassbey	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
3.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Griscal	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
12	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
Constance	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowbridge	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Jones	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
alias	O
Cassey	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Vallard	I-pers
,	O
Bryant	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Vallard	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
upon	O
a	O
Sledge	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
by	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
cut	O
down	O
alive	O
,	O
their	O
Bowels	O
burnt	O
,	O
their	O
Bodies	O
quartered	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
at	O
their	O
Majesties	O
pleasure	O
.	O
And	O
Anne	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
alive	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Brassbey	I-pers
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
peaceable	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Juxon	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
4	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
he	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
quiet	O
behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
were	O
both	O
finded	O
5	O
Pound	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
having	O
given	O
in	O
Bail	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
what	O
should	O
be	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
now	O
move	O
for	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
pleased	O
to	O
tender	O
him	O
the	O
Oaths	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
comply	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
continue	O
upon	O
Bail	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
Turner	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
A	O
Bargain	O
dear	O
bought	O
,	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Cap	O
.	O
Rider	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
all	O
Recognizances	O
.	O
Lyon	O
Fountaire	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Firmin	I-pers
,	O
notwithstanding	O
their	O
being	O
acquitted	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
they	O
find	O
sufficient	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
better	O
Conversation	O
;	O
Firmin	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
uppear	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
lately	O
fled	O
from	O
Justice	O
.	O
THO	O
.	O
PILKINGTON	O
Mayor	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
confeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
days	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Areana	O
's	O
as	O
occasion	O
serves	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Politicks	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Journal	O
concerning	O
the	O
present	O
Affairs	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
its	O
Two	O
most	O
Active	O
Powers	O
;	O
William	B-pers
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
the	O
Fourteenth	O
.	O
price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Continuation	O
of	O
which	O
Journal	O
will	O
be	O
now	O
published	O
every	O
Saturday	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
sheet	O
,	O
Sold	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfry	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirleus	I-pers
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	B-pers
Physician	I-pers
to	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
Who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
,	O
Cures	O
all	O
Vleers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
in	O
the	O
Faco	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
Kings-Evil	O
,	O
Leprosie	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
he	O
Cures	O
not	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
bath	O
Cured	O
about	O
500	O
persons	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
It	O
quickly	O
and	O
safety	O
Cures	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
Mercury	O
,	O
without	O
danger	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
Purges	O
.	O
They	O
excel	O
all	O
Purges	O
,	O
in	O
cleansing	O
all	O
Crudities	O
and	O
Impurities	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
prevent	O
and	O
Cure	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
she	O
Gent	O
and	O
Stone	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Diseases	O
he	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
