TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
and	O
25th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
and	O
25th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
Tobias	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lupton	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Foxley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bocket	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Medcapp	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Cupper	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnel	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltbey	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hemstead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bowrne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barrow	B-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Acron	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
Indicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
selby	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
H.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saltmarsh	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
six	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
assaulted	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Mony	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
possitively	O
to	O
Riggs	O
and	O
Acron	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
possitive	O
as	O
to	O
Pearson	O
and	O
Harris	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
J	O
-	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
no	O
father	O
than	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Saltmarsh	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	O
Rudd	O
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Pick-Pocket	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
privately	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
So	O
Riggs	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
one	O
Sheet	O
,	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
small	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoates	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Crofts	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Kallowe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Bushes	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
somewhat	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bushes	O
was	O
found	O
empty	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Thomson	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Poynt	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Top-knot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Dowagers	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Elkin	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Samuel	O
Watson	O
,	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Maliciously	O
sworn	O
against	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
Idle	O
Woman	O
,	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
away	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
dark	O
coloured	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
and	O
Partner	O
in	O
Pater	B-place
Noster	I-place
Row	I-place
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Howel	B-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grymes	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
and	O
K	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
all	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Acton	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Allom	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
his	O
Lady	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allom	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Jane	B-pers
Allom	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
fear	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Allom	O
a	O
Gray	O
Gelding	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
fromMrs	O
.	O
Allom	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
Allom	O
.	O
he	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
numerous	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Allom	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Acton	O
towards	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
and	O
Daughter	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Persons	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
knocking	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
having	O
Robbed	O
the	O
Coach	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
ore	O
possitive	O
to	O
Howel	O
and	O
Grimes	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
possitive	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
disguised	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
ad	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
their	O
Periwigs	O
in	O
their	O
Mouths	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Allom	O
new	O
Powel	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
tender	O
upon	O
her	O
Oath	O
.	O
Other	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Powel	O
,	O
it	O
droping	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Madam	O
Allom	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
strengthened	O
the	O
former	O
Depositions	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Kyrbey	O
was	O
one	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Smith	O
Rifled	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Howel	O
first	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
uttering	O
most	O
desperate	O
Oaths	O
,	O
with	O
threats	O
,	O
against	O
Madam	O
Allom	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
fled	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbouring	O
People	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
Smith	O
being	O
shot	O
in	O
making	O
his	O
Escape	O
in	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
Powel	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rideing	O
along	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Grymes	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
and	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
which	O
Horse	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Alloms	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
beset	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Clifton	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
toucht	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
or	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
Hide	O
Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
(	O
after	O
mature	O
Consideration	O
)	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Goudge	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Newberry	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
an	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
of	O
Sunbury	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
another	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
several	O
Poringers	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Cromwell	O
and	O
others	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
beset	O
about	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
by	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
Gagged	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
300	O
l.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
set	O
it	O
home	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Story	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Win	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wyng	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vaughan	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Philips	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
)	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mims	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
)	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
:	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Madam	O
Mary	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistole	O
,	O
a	O
Luadore	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Coyned	O
Gold	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
31	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
Madam	O
Hale	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Win	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
side	O
and	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Mony	O
and	O
Gold	O
.	O
Madam	O
Hale	O
swore	O
possitively	O
against	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
punctually	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Win	O
;	O
besides	O
other	O
confirming	O
Evidence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
Win	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
so	O
heartily	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Defence	O
(	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
)	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
two	O
Robberies	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
Bullet	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
House	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Pistols	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
handling	O
them	O
one	O
accidentally	O
went	O
off	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
disceased	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know-that	O
it	O
was	O
Charged	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
per	O
Misfortunam	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Toplady	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Callcot	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
Gun	B-place
Musick	I-place
House	I-place
in	O
Salisbury	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
they	O
bred	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
Thomas	O
Floyd	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
,	O
only	O
Toplady	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
thrust	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
and	O
Partner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
possitive	O
that	O
Askew	O
dropt	O
she	O
Silk	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Symons	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Stuff	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
in	O
Lumbard-street	B-place
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Stuff	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Alesby	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
East-cheap	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruse	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
March	O
following	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Cook	O
Maid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
lived	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Alderman	O
Rogersons	O
in	O
Clements-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plates	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Affront	O
,	O
by	O
medling	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Plate	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
expressed	O
her	O
sorrow	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
sad	O
Accident	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Cane	O
,	O
alias	O
Crofts	O
,	O
before	O
specified	O
.	O
John	O
Thomson	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Law	O
being	O
tender	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tymothy	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Jane	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Geoge	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Coffe-House	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
body	O
within	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
view	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Friends	O
in	O
Maypole	O
Alley	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
or	O
there	O
about	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
probably	O
be	O
suggested	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Selwood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jenkins	B-pers
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Mackquear	I-pers
alias	O
Bayley	B-pers
alias	O
the	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
Teagae	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Witts	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
Hounslow	B-place
heath	I-place
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mony	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
when	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harmsworth	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex.	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
material	O
,	O
only	O
Read	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
taken	O
accidentally	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
shooting	O
off	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
were	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
Ingle	O
having	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
drew	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
and	O
shot	O
Townsend	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
unwillingly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Charged	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Verdict	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Special	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
it	O
per	O
misfortunam	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
hundred	O
threescore	O
and	O
five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Westmortland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
possitive	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	O
Jones	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Carter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
over	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
very	O
Comical	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
endeavour	O
to	O
hang	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
further	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Define	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Ferrers	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Ferrers	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Oxendon-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
suddenly	O
snatcht	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
being	O
dark	O
:	O
but	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
Confest	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
besides	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
Trant	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Stubbins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dunkin	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Linnen	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Pick-lock	O
keys	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
wise	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Midwife	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
Lye	O
In	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Midwife	O
promised	O
she	O
should	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
promised	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
privately	O
made	O
away	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Puddle	O
of	O
Water	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
She	O
confessing	O
(	O
when	O
taken	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
Gasped	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
;	O
adding	O
that	O
it	O
cryed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
pinched	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
and	O
dispatcht	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
several	O
Women	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Distracted	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
laid	O
any	O
violent	O
Hands	O
upon	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
not	O
pinch	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
to	O
cover	O
her	O
Shame	O
,	O
begging	O
hard	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
pitty	O
her	O
sad	O
Condition	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pikeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
privately	O
a	O
Watch	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Knowles	O
knocking	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
begging	O
in	O
Southhampton	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
her	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
threaten	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Knowles	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
possitive	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
price	O
4	O
l.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
Hampshire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bullmoor	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Ring	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
having	O
several	O
Credible	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Reparation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Selbey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
alias	O
Bartley	B-pers
,	O
by	O
Cutting	O
her	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
Eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
run	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
deceased	O
Bartlett	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
common	O
Baudy	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Selbey	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
first	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
served	O
Bartlett	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
not	O
well	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
)	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Selby	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Fire	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Selbey	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
woman	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
sate	O
till	O
about	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
drinking	O
,	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
3	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
5	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Mum	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Drunk	O
:	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Selbey	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
)	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Old	O
Woman	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Nurse	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
only	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Nurse	O
)	O
might	O
fetch	O
up	O
one	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Womans	O
Throat	O
to	O
the	O
Wind	O
Pipe	O
;	O
and	O
leaving	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Gloves	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Nurse	O
at	O
the	O
Stayrs	O
Foot	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
slight	O
Cuts	O
in	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
strugling	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
prevented	O
his	O
Bloody	O
Design	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Woman	O
bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Murther	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
hearing	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
finding	O
her	O
much	O
Wounded	O
,	O
they	O
presently	O
conveyed	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
searcht	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
deceased	O
Bartlett	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Throat	O
Cut	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
dreadful	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
stopt	O
into	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Wounds	O
to	O
her	O
Forehead	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
Face	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
pursued	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
climbing	O
over	O
some	O
Pales	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cravat	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
bespotted	O
with	O
Blood	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
owned	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Gloves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
over	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Fear	O
;	O
but	O
those	O
were	O
Frivelous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
Nurse	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Person	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
all	O
that	O
Evening	O
:	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Officers	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Officer	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
in	O
Fullers	B-place
Rents	I-place
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
an	O
Execution	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
entred	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
submissive	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Officer	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
immediately	O
he	O
arose	O
and	O
went	O
behind	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
his	O
Gown	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Brase	O
of	O
Pistols	O
and	O
shot	O
one	O
off	O
at	O
Charleton	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
within	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Pistol	O
he	O
presented	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
obstructed	O
his	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Officer	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
door	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
assaulted	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
pass	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
,	O
running	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
Breast	O
and	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
gave	O
the	O
word	O
of	O
Arrest	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
haste	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Mr.	O
F	O
proved	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
very	O
distinctly	O
charged	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
withdrawn	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
clearing	O
them	O
further	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Verdict	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Recorded	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Win	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
Shears	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
that	O
work	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Burry	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
Clipt	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frequently	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Rebekkah	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
lately	O
fled	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
likewise	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
Counterfeit	O
and	O
make	O
several	O
Shillings	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tyon	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
material	O
being	O
produced	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Inkhorn	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
19	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
into	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
Benifit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Sengintin	I-pers
one	O
Yard	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Silver	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
Golden	O
Locket	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Twelve	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
when	O
first	O
taxed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
tender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
D	B-pers
-	I-pers
L	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Staynes	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
Pettycoats	O
,	O
some	O
Hoods	O
,	O
some	O
Laced	O
Muslin	O
Coronets	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Anderson	O
,	O
and	O
Staynes	O
had	O
a	O
Coronet	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
L	O
-	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
Fairbank	O
had	O
one	O
Mantua	O
and	O
two	O
Pettycoats	O
;	O
L	O
-	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
whenthe	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Anderson	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
D	O
L	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Staynes	O
,	O
Fairbank	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Will	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Chambers	O
,	O
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
and	O
receives	O
9	O
l.	O
odd	O
Mony	O
,	O
swearing	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Chambers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
short	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
On	O
Fryday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Rutland	I-pers
Junior	O
,	O
Renatus	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tysoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
it	O
little	O
less	O
than	O
Treason	O
as	O
was	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
thus	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
Evil	O
Minds	O
,	O
Turbulent	O
and	O
Unquiet	O
,	O
little	O
regarding	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
their	O
Allegiance	O
to	O
our	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
but	O
intending	O
to	O
terrifie	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
and	O
procure	O
Sedition	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
and	O
among	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Leige	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Government	O
,	O
Title	O
,	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
now	O
by	O
Law	O
Established	O
,	O
to	O
Scandalize	O
,	O
Vilifie	O
and	O
render	O
doubtful	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
faithful	O
Subjects	O
into	O
Dispair	O
of	O
Their	O
Protection	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
deter	O
and	O
hinder	O
them	O
from	O
Lending	O
,	O
Helping	O
,	O
and	O
Supplying	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
with	O
Mony	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Common	O
and	O
know	O
Enemies	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
to	O
Encourage	O
and	O
Comfort	O
Their	O
said	O
Enemies	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
present	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
declare	O
and	O
publish	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
,	O
That	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
would	O
become	O
Assurer	O
to	O
pay	O
Mony	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Castle	O
of	O
Dublin	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Power	O
or	O
Possession	O
of	O
any	O
King	O
,	O
Prince	O
or	O
Potentate	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Person	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
next	O
,	O
other	O
than	O
in	O
the	O
actual	O
Possession	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
or	O
Their	O
Heirs	O
or	O
Successors	O
,	O
according	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Establishment	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
5	O
l.	O
paid	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
Premium	O
upon	O
the	O
Assurance	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
that	O
rate	O
for	O
every	O
other	O
Summ	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
by	O
any	O
Person	O
assured	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Charge	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
opened	O
at	O
large	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
all	O
the	O
Aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
attended	O
such	O
a	O
Politick	O
Invention	O
;	O
especially	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
tended	O
to	O
weaken	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
to	O
alienate	O
the	O
Hearts	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Raise	O
and	O
to	O
Stir	O
up	O
the	O
Seeds	O
of	O
Sedition	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
the	O
Hearts	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Enemies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
paid	O
25	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Rutland	O
25	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Tysoe	O
5	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gandy	O
9	O
l.	O
This	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Policys	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
farther	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Argued	O
by	O
their	O
Council	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
evil	O
Design	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
customary	O
thing	O
,	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
venture	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Insurance	O
of	O
Ships	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Persons	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
highly	O
resented	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
Ensure	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Their	O
Fines	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rutland	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
200	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
200	O
Marks	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tysoe	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gandy	O
100	O
Marks	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
until	O
Christmas	O
next	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Pigg	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Beed	O
and	O
carryed	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
alias	O
Walker	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
four	O
score	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Stockins	O
and	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Edward	O
Stent	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Knot	O
of	O
Ribbons	O
tyed	O
to	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Sarah	O
Stent	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Ribbons	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Smith	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Sarah	O
Stent	O
's	O
Hands	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Stent	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
chief	O
Actor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
Acquited	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Chamberline	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Luke	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Tippet	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
before	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
about	O
fifty	O
Mile	O
off	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Poulterer	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
three	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
Rabits	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Old	O
Coney	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
three	O
pound	O
of	O
Links	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
Brooks	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pettycoat	O
and	O
two	O
Holland	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Clarks	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stayrs	O
coming	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
gain	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Honour	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Webb	B-pers
in	O
Whitechappel	B-place
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
since	O
fled	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
clapt	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
witness	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
of	O
Essex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
ofMarch	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
4	O
other	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
12	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Doe	O
Skin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spur	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Whipcord	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
returned	O
thither	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Tryal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darlington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
borrow	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ewer	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
confest	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
alias	O
Cook	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Joan	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Lac't	O
Coives	O
,	O
halfe	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
White	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
alias	O
Norris	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
King	B-place
street	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
So	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquited	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Anne	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
and	O
some	O
Sleeves	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
came	O
in	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
Two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Hugh	O
Griffeth	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Griffeth	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Hugh	O
Griffeth	O
Married	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
day	O
Fortnight	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Griffeth	O
Lyes	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
ten	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
from	O
Ursula	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Upstone	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Higginbottom	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9	O
.	O
Robert	O
Toplady	O
John	O
Symons	O
D	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
Dorothy	O
Cooper	O
Elizabeth	O
Hale	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
John	O
Newell	O
Edward	O
Stent	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bizzle	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessons	O
for	O
coyning	O
Mony	O
,	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Excuted	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
shall	O
Suffer	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
Fryday	O
during	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
by	O
Attiring	O
himself	O
in	O
Womens	O
Apparel	O
,	O
geting	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Warwick-lane	O
end	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Terror	O
of	O
Death	O
did	O
affright	O
him	O
;	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
Guilty	O
:	O
For	O
which	O
Impudent	O
Expression	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
severe	O
Repremand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
the	O
Tryals	O
were	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9	O
.	O
Robert	O
Toplady	O
John	O
Symons	O
D	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
Dorothy	O
Cooper	O
Elizabeth	O
Hale	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
John	O
Newell	O
Edward	O
Stent	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bizzle	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
5	O
.	O
John	O
Thomson	O
John	O
Leech	O
John	O
Anderson	O
Nicholas	O
Upstone	O
and	O
John	O
Ran	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
21	O
.	O
William	O
Riggs	O
Anne	O
Harris	O
Elizabeth	O
Wilson	O
Elizabeth	O
Walton	O
Ruth	O
Stanes	O
Elizabeth	O
Fairbank	O
Henry	O
Powell	O
John	O
Grymes	O
Charles	O
Smith	O
K	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
John	O
Story	O
Henry	O
Win	O
George	O
Read	O
William	O
Selwood	O
William	O
Mackquear	O
Peter	O
Desine	O
Elizabeth	O
Deale	O
William	O
Phipps	O
James	O
Selbey	O
Honour	O
Allen	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessons	O
for	O
coyning	O
Mony	O
,	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Excuted	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
shall	O
Suffer	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
Fryday	O
during	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
by	O
Attiring	O
himself	O
in	O
Womens	O
Apparel	O
,	O
geting	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Warwick-lane	O
end	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Terror	O
of	O
Death	O
did	O
affright	O
him	O
;	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
Guilty	O
:	O
For	O
which	O
Impudent	O
Expression	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
severe	O
Repremand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Reprieved	O
after	O
Judgment	O
5	O
.	O
Anne	O
Harris	O
Elizabeth	O
Wilson	O
Ruth	O
Stanes	O
Elizabeth	O
Fairbank	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Walton	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
10	O
.	O
Elinor	O
Clark	O
William	O
Bolton	O
Alice	O
Chamberline	O
John	O
Browne	O
Jane	O
Williams	O
Thomas	O
Darlinton	O
Rebekah	O
Dennis	O
Martha	O
Herbert	O
Anne	O
Stubbins	O
and	O
Chatles	O
Pearson	O
,	O
tryes	O
formerly	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
understand	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
had	O
moved	O
that	O
Execution	O
might	O
be	O
Awarded	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Courts	O
Duty	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
Lordship	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Prepare	O
him	O
self	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
Replyed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
time	O
since	O
his	O
Condemnation	O
had	O
been	O
spun	O
out	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
High	O
Sheriff	O
gave	O
him	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Surprizal	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
an	O
assurance	O
in	O
himself	O
he	O
should	O
receive	O
Pardon	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
determined	O
,	O
he	O
humbly	O
requested	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
bear	O
witness	O
of	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
acquaint	O
His	O
Majesty	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
could	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Judgment	O
was	O
determined	O
,	O
but	O
give	O
his	O
Lordship	O
timely	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
hoping	O
his	O
Lordship	O
would	O
Prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
remanded	O
back	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
Mr.	O
Edmond	O
Elliot	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Bayle	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
William	O
Rutland	O
,	O
Renatus	O
Harris	O
,	O
William	O
Ganly	O
,	O
John	O
Watts	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Tysoe	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
gave	O
Suerties	O
for	O
their	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
until	O
Christmas	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ingle	O
gave	O
Bayle	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
plead	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
Anne	O
Townsned	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
abundance	O
of	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
gave	O
in	O
Bayle	O
for	O
their	O
appearance	O
to	O
answer	O
their	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
Athenian	O
Mercury	O
;	O
Resolving	O
Weekly	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
Nice	O
and	O
Curious	O
Questions	O
proposed	O
by	O
the	O
Ingenious	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Peny-Post	O
Letters	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
in	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
This	O
Paper	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
constantly	O
on	O
Tuesdays	O
and	O
Saturdays	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
every	O
Volum	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
Numb	O
.	O
30.	O
we	O
design	O
to	O
add	O
the	O
Transactions	O
and	O
Experiments	O
of	O
several	O
English	O
Vertnoso	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
whatever	O
else	O
is	O
Curious	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
us	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
:	O
As	O
else	O
the	O
Acta	O
Eruditorum	O
Lipsiae	O
:	O
The	O
Paris	O
Journal	O
des	O
Scavants	O
:	O
The	O
Giornali	O
de	O
Letterati	O
,	O
printed	O
at	O
Rome	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Universal	O
Historical	O
Bibliotheque	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
Translating	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Plain	O
Christian	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
True	O
Religion	O
and	O
Undefiled	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Principal	O
and	O
most	O
useful	O
Branches	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
Belief	O
and	O
Practice	O
,	O
Briefly	O
stated	O
and	O
Explained	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Chief	O
Points	O
in	O
Dispute	O
between	O
Us	O
and	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
are	O
discussed	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmonbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
If	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
or	O
Ladies	O
of	O
Quality	O
are	O
desirous	O
to	O
learn	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
or	O
French	O
fluently	O
and	O
that	O
Truly	O
and	O
Properly	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Grammar	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Explain	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
Switerda	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
will	O
wait	O
on	O
them	O
twice	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
He	O
Teacheth	O
also	O
in	O
Clements-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Canon-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
next	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Coffee-House	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Goffs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Ax-Yard	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clairs	O
;	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
French	O
and	O
Latin	O
Historical	O
Cards	O
,	O
which	O
teacheth	O
to	O
turn	O
Latin	O
into	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
French	O
into	O
English	O
:	O
You	O
may	O
also	O
have	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Latin-Political-Cards	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
places	O
,	O
very	O
fit	O
for	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
seever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Waver	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kirlers	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
until	O
his	O
death	O
:	O
Who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
(	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Cures	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
parts	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venerial	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
bath	O
Cured	O
many	O
hundreds	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
evil	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
a	O
better	O
purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
ever	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
payns	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
;	O
with	O
another	O
Drink	O
at	O
1	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
he	O
Cures	O
all	O
Feavers	O
and	O
lot	O
Distempers	O
without	O
Bleeding	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
few	O
Bodys	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
