TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Johns	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lymbrey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
besides	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
of	O
Black-Fryers	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Gloves	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
as	O
a	O
Corroborating	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Prideaux	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ducane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
supposed	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
no	O
Felonious	O
intent	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thornely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Course	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
second	O
Charge	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hayles	I-pers
;	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bevis	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Dimmity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
restored	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictement	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
alias	O
Harris	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Hitchman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
some	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Mackdoll	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Anne	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Women	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
assaulted	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
violent	O
and	O
base	O
manner	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Poynt-Lace	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ear-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac't	O
Tippet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
credited	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
,	O
but	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
wicked	O
Life	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
alias	O
Morris	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Drawer	O
where	O
the	O
Mony	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Restitution	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
received	O
40	O
s.	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
producing	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Fenley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-pers
Witcheloe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
72	O
Yards	O
of	O
10	O
penny	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Fletcher	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stilwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Pillow-Bare	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Presbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Field	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Dowlace	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Shirts	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
another	O
Man	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
a	O
Sett	O
of	O
Serge	O
Curtains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Conjectured	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
easily	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Tremane	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gun	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Trelawny	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Child-Bed-Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
piece	O
of	O
Eight	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Tremane	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
Six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
compassed	O
their	O
Design	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Dog	O
bit	O
King	O
by	O
the	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
Tremane	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
further	O
made	O
out	O
by	O
one	O
Dun	O
,	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Treman	O
and	O
King	O
and	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
are	O
fled	O
)	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
Bullock	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Clerkenwel	O
Parish	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
informed	O
by	O
Bullock	O
of	O
the	O
Prize	O
abovesaid	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
that	O
Evening	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
:	O
But	O
Bullock	O
called	O
very	O
Creditable	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
Justifie	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
so	O
much	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girle	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Coldicot	I-pers
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
piece	O
afore	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pettycoat	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
impudent	O
in	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
though	O
Young	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
away	O
by	O
wicked	O
Company	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
end	O
she	O
was	O
Found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Thurston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farren	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
Edwards	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
Farren	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Edwards	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Farren	O
was	O
Tryed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
Deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Edwards	O
and	O
Counselled	O
him	O
to	O
Rob	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Reputable	O
Persons	O
to	O
justifie	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
Acquit	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
of	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
casting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Wounds	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Lawfully	O
Married	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
:	O
but	O
nothing	O
materially	O
to	O
her	O
advantage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Daniel	B-pers
Leery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
snatching	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perrywig	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
A	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
committed	O
by	O
Christopher	B-pers
Tremane	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
who	O
Robbed	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
of	O
Islington	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
Incerted	O
;	O
Dun	O
the	O
Theif	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
Tremane	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
honesty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Tremane	I-pers
alias	O
Trelawny	B-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
singly	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Gate	I-place
going	O
to	O
Chelsey	B-place
.	O
Mathews	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
swearing	O
most	O
desperate	O
Oaths	O
;	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
5	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Dram-Cup	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver-Chain	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Beavor	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Matthews	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Masters	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
.	O
Tremane	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
alias	O
Tomson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rugbey	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Rowney	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
ed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Pet	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
Linnen	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
lest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Bonnet	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Black	B-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bolton	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
see	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
Mony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tree	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tree	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Instant	O
a	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
other	O
Serge	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Childs	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
only	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
playing	O
at	O
Bowls	O
together	O
at	O
Mary-Bone	B-place
;	O
and	O
some	O
difference	O
happened	O
to	O
arise	O
about	O
the	O
Game	O
concerning	O
Betting	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Griffeth	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
lose	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
20	O
l.	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
precedent	O
Malice	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
David	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Wound	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
King	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Sword	O
was	O
besmeared	O
in	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Affront	O
before	O
any	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veville	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Shaftee	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Hasps	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Steples	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
Mary-Bone	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Irons	O
were	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
Posts	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Rayles	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
home	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
rather	O
a	O
Trespass	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cranbey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Knapper	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
as	O
Accessary	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
against	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
sufficient	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
;	O
First	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Covel	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
out	O
Susannah	B-pers
Throp	I-pers
,	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
things	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fun	I-pers
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
18	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lady	O
Dead	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
Legacys	O
,	O
and	O
Wheedled	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whilest	O
Robbed	O
their	O
Houses	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
wicked	O
Invention	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
confest	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Tryed	O
here	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Haughton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Jewel	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
three	O
Pearls	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Poynt	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
out	O
of	O
Worcestershire	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Veron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Easter-day	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Veron	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
Ipswich	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
proving	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Married	O
Woman	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Covering	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
Good	O
's	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff-High-way	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Feldoe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tissue	O
Stayes	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
accused	O
by	O
Congden	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gallon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Persons	O
more	O
at	O
Wappen	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Congden	O
now	O
hangs	O
in	O
Chains	O
near	O
Mile-End	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
came	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Staniard	I-pers
;	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Captain	O
John	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
Publishing	O
a	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
and	O
raise	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Entituted	O
A	O
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Reverend	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Beveridge	O
,	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
of	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
his	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Restitution	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Libel	O
was	O
found	O
most	O
base	O
and	O
reflecting	O
Language	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sparkes	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
Testified	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
material	O
Defence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
200	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
Suffer	O
Imprisonment	O
till	O
he	O
perform	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
William	B-pers
Macksfeild	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
,	O
of	O
Wappen-Chappel	B-place
,	O
for	O
Refusing	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oaths	O
,	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
the	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
till	O
he	O
should	O
perform	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Whip	O
maker	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
Free	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Edward	O
Griffeth	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
David	O
White	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
gave	O
Bayle	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
an	O
Appeal	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Nurther	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
Sureties	O
to	O
answer	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Edward	O
Elliot	O
found	O
Bayle	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Whip	O
maker	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
Free	O
Pardon	O
.	O
So	O
likewise	O
did	O
several	O
Criminals	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
50	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Criminals	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
thus	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
4	O
.	O
Edward	O
Booth	O
,	O
Anne	O
Thomas	O
alias	O
Morris	O
,	O
John	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hayes	O
,	O
Anne	O
Butcher	O
,	O
Jane	O
Walker	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Beard	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Tremane	O
,	O
John	O
King	O
.	O
Margret	O
Dean	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Anne	O
Cranbey	O
,	O
William	O
Feilding	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Morris	O
.	O
Agnes	O
Clarkson	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Beard	O
was	O
suspected	O
after	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Anne	O
Butcher	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
4	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Thornley	O
,	O
Jane	O
Presbury	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Johnston	O
,	O
Anne	O
Walker	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
Athenian	O
Mercury	O
:	O
Resolving	O
Weekly	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
Nice	O
and	O
Curious	O
Questions	O
proposed	O
by	O
the	O
Ingenious	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
by	O
Peny-Post	O
Letter	O
on	O
otherwise	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
in	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
This	O
Paper	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
constantly	O
on	O
Tuesdays	O
and	O
Saturdays	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
every	O
Volum	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
Numb	O
.	O
30.	O
we	O
design	O
to	O
add	O
the	O
Transactions	O
and	O
Experiments	O
of	O
several	O
English	O
Vertnoso	O
's	O
and	O
whatever	O
else	O
is	O
Curions	O
that	O
shall	O
he	O
sent	O
as	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Act	O
a	O
Eruditorum	O
Lipsix	O
.	O
The	O
Paris	O
Journal	O
des	O
Scavans	O
:	O
The	O
Giornali	O
de	O
Letorrati	O
,	O
printed	O
at	O
Rome	O
and	O
the	O
Universal	O
Historical	O
Bioliotheque	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
Translating	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Volum	O
will	O
be	O
Publisht	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
next	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
general	O
Title	O
,	O
Preface	O
and	O
Table	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
lateguity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expediciously	O
Cares	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
cureable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
lnspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testisie	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
care	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
Persons	O
can	O
seth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affrim	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
,	O
Maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Spitting	O
Drops	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
take	O
safely	O
and	O
go	O
abroad	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
powerfully	O
discharge	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Stomach	O
of	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
frees	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Gout	O
Dropsie	O
,	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
all	O
Infection	O
Venerial	O
,	O
or	O
Mercurial	O
physick	O
,	O
and	O
cures	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Pallar	O
;	O
Nose	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
vicers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
prevents	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
also	O
these	O
approved	O
Drops	O
for	O
care	O
of	O
Fistula	O
's	O
Piles	O
,	O
or	O
Hemorrboides	O
,	O
several	O
having	O
been	O
Cured	O
by	O
once	O
Applying	O
.	O
By	O
Doctor	O
Archer	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Bookselled	O
Every	O
Man	O
his	O
own	O
Doctor	O
:	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
taking	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
with	O
at	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
the	O
sadler	O
against	O
the	O
Muse	O
of	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
next	O
be	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
from	O
Nbon	O
till	O
5	O
.	O
Evening	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Knight	O
's	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
salls	O
not	O
his	O
Drops	O
,	O
but	O
administers	O
them	O
as	O
needful	O
.	O
He	O
freely	O
gives	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
