TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1691.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hamden	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mayen	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Sanford	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
French	B-pers
Gotobed	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Hemborrow	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Silkcock	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Francis	B-pers
Exhall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Three	O
Black	O
Cow	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Greentree	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
Last	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Bagshot	B-place
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confes	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
Water	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Frivilous	O
Excuse	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Twenty	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Rose	B-pers
Jeeve	I-pers
;	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jeeves	O
she	O
in	O
Bow	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
about	O
Week	O
after	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
party	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Denbigh	B-place
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Indicted	O
;	O
B	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
as	O
Principle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
as	O
Accessary	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
B	O
-	O
G	O
-s	O
Female	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Old	O
Ruined	O
Houses	O
,	O
in	O
Park-Street	B-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
being	O
a	O
most	O
amazing	O
Spectacle	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Covering	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
its	O
Tongue	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mouth	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
great	O
Violence	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
declaredby	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
Mrs.	O
B.	O
had	O
lived	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
Gripes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Deliver	O
'd	O
at	O
Richardson	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Bromley	O
carried	O
the	O
Child	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
Born	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
above	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
B	O
.	O
-	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
Charge	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
offered	O
any	O
Violence	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Bromley	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Delivered	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
Dead	O
,	O
But	O
whether	O
born	O
alive	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mrs	O
B	O
-	O
had	O
made	O
provision	O
for	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
;	O
So	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Gutter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	O
Bradley	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Topping	O
some	O
Chimneys	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Gutter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
alledged	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murther	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Good	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Austin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Dyaper	O
Napkin	O
Value	O
12	O
d.	O
Twelve	O
Larks	O
,	O
Two	O
Ducks	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Embroidered	O
Wastcoat	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
between	O
Hackney	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
violently	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
White	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
for	O
his	O
Credit	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Zicharia	O
Wisdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Four	O
Loyns	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Quart	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Ale	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wisdom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
:	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Law	O
being	O
tender	O
,	O
ere	O
the	O
person	O
Steals	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Victuals	O
for	O
meer	O
necessity	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Burglary	O
;	O
besides	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
Lockt	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
yards	O
of	O
stript	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
11	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
stript	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
who	O
d	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Malley	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Silk	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
42	O
rds	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
day	O
of	O
ember	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
better	O
colour	O
upon	O
her	O
gn	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
Sedan	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
ing	O
cheapened	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
of	O
Lace	O
above	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
playing	O
the	O
same	O
prank	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Rubey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Renolds	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Razer	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
besides	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Treley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
desperate	O
stripes	O
with	O
a	O
whip	O
and	O
a	O
Ropes	O
end	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
short	O
Ribs	O
and	O
Belly	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
beating	O
and	O
unnatural	O
Usage	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
languishing	O
till	O
the	O
24.	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
beaten	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
horrid	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
bruised	O
with	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
strokes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
swelled	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
this	O
cruel	O
Usage	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
grounded	O
upon	O
some	O
suspition	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
wait	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
to	O
run	O
of	O
Errands	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
his	O
stall	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Boy	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Moor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Farrier	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
drest	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
sore	O
shoulder	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Lady	O
Etheridge	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
feign	O
'd	O
story	O
in	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
sent	O
no	O
such	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
afterwards	O
absented	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
through	O
Ignorance	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
2.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
6	O
Holland	O
Coives	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
10.	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
sate	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
catched	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Falling	O
Sickness	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
Cloth	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloth	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bayliff	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Barebone	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Hilston	B-place
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Pea-hen	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
three	O
Turkeys	O
price	O
each	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Barebones	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Laurence	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Pea-hen	O
and	O
Turkeys	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
both	O
their	O
custodys	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
conceal	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Horsepool	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robing	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
goods	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
(	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dormers	O
)	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Atkyns	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
of	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
silver-Case	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloak	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
160	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chare	O
woman	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
rubing	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Keys	O
fell	O
down	O
from	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bedshead	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
this	O
three	O
Fellows	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
Chamber	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
with	O
Candles	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
most	O
horrible	O
Oaths	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
offer	O
to	O
molest	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
robed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
further	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
had	O
good	O
feathers	O
to	O
pull	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
being	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chatfield	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Beamore	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pemore	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrow	O
Hog	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Sow	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
9	O
.	O
Hogs	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
Hornchurch	B-place
in	O
Essex	I-place
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Hogs	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
gainsay	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
.	O
Tasters	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
.	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clasps	O
,	O
some	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Scarves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Pennington	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Clasps	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Sham	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bransbury	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Phillip	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
by	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
fled	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
e	O
,	O
with	O
Iron	O
Hinges	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
aboard	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
Brothers	O
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
murther	O
one	O
Susanah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
a	O
Girle	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
throwing	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Girle	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
within	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Goodmans	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Girle	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
a	O
Stone	O
at	O
some	O
Boys	O
that	O
were	O
flying	O
a	O
and	O
the	O
Girle	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Chyrurgeon	O
declared	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
throw	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
Tryal	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Malice	O
proved	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Matter	O
seemed	O
to	O
affect	O
Thomas	O
Clench	O
most	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
but	O
George	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Casewell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
with	O
Hickson	O
,	O
in	O
Bonn-street	B-place
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
the	O
said	O
Hickson	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
grudge	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
urged	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
24.	O
hours	O
before	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
stuck	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
matterial	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murther	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
fast	O
lockt	O
before	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
faulter	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Allegations	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
swear	O
but	O
to	O
One	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
easily	O
mistake	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Ralph	B-pers
Azowby	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
of	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
2	O
.	O
Silk	O
Scarves	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Tippet	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
setting	O
Fire	O
on	O
the	O
Barn	O
,	O
and	O
burning	O
the	O
Hay	O
therein	O
value	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Barn	O
and	O
Hay	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
of	O
Islington	O
above	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Barn	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
it	O
fell	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
Crying	O
out	O
,	O
Fire	O
,	O
fire	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Family	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
quench	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
save	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Parcels	O
beforementioned	O
;	O
he	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Third	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Seth	B-pers
Bunckley	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Napkins	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
;	O
besides	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Barn	O
burnt	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
theresented	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
most	O
Notorious	O
,	O
New-found	O
,	O
base	O
way	O
,	O
stealing	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Randale	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
.	O
e	O
Tankards	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
lame	O
Excuses	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harsey	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Sillock	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
all	O
bloody	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stabbed	O
the	O
Sillock	O
;	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
a	O
scuffle	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Sillock	O
was	O
stabbed	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
ound	O
,	O
but	O
Sillock	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
:	O
was	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stabbed	O
two	O
Persons	O
re	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	O
th	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
which	O
recovered	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
Smith	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
thing	O
may	O
be	O
Noted	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
friend	O
;	O
the	O
business	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
he	O
mis	O
and	O
stabbed	O
his	O
own	O
Friend	O
instead	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
Sillock	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
d	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
and	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
old	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
,	O
running	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
from	O
Door	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
nd	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
something	O
short	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harsey	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
London	O
side	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
his	O
friend	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
former	O
Tryal	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
drinking	O
till	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
as	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
;	O
and	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
four	O
Inches	O
deep	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murther	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hilsey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
of	O
a	O
black	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
1	O
Shirt	O
,	O
One	O
Womans	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
another	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
Satin	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
three	O
Nights	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
Persons	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
really	O
favour	O
'd	O
of	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
acquitted	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
K	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
P	O
-	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
high	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filling	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
The	O
discovery	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
finding	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
known	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
further	O
made	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
things	O
necessary	O
for	O
that	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
send	O
melted	O
Silver	O
abroad	O
to	O
sell	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Closet	O
was	O
her	O
Husbands	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
sending	O
melted	O
Silver	O
abroad	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
for	O
their	O
Trade	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Order	O
:	O
And	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
fled	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Maturely	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
probable	O
enough	O
that	O
P	O
-	O
himself	O
was	O
really	O
the	O
Clipper	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
fine	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Julian	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
Widow	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Hangings	O
stuffs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Hangings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
Pictures	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Picture	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
an	O
Iron	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
two	O
Rat	O
Traps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
some	O
Pot	O
Racks	O
and	O
Hangers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Frying	O
pan	O
and	O
some	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
houshold	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Hangings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Moss	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
feignedly	O
excused	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
paid	O
23	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
first	O
for	O
robing	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2dly	O
.	O
For	O
robing	O
Michael	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Patrick	O
Cock	O
at	O
Royston	O
(	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
where	O
she	O
toll	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	O
Edwards	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
her	O
Maiden	O
Name	O
,	O
confessing	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
Accounted	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
concerning	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
could	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
likewise	O
of	O
this	O
second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
reputed	O
Jesuite	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
evil	O
disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
disquiet	O
and	O
disturb	O
the	O
Peace	O
and	O
Tranquility	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
deter	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Liege	O
people	O
from	O
their	O
Obedience	O
to	O
our	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
Did	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
hire	O
a	O
Ship	O
to	O
convey	O
several	O
persons	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
open	O
and	O
prosest	O
Enemies	O
to	O
our	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
particularly	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
Collonel	O
Graham	O
(	O
the	O
Lord	O
Preston	O
's	O
Brother	O
)	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Penn	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	O
Wallis	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Ely	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
conveyed	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Franks	O
hired	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Fullers	O
Rents	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
bargained	O
with	O
for	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
Collonel	O
Grynes	O
and	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Ely	O
.	O
were	O
pusilanimous	O
Men	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Blinds	O
to	O
be	O
contrived	O
in	O
the	O
Rounds	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
furthermore	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
gave	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
understand	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
speaking	O
very	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
Sir	O
William	O
Wallis	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
leading	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
King	O
James	O
and	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
into	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
to	O
head	O
an	O
Army	O
,	O
against	O
our	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Major	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
head	O
an	O
Army	O
of	O
[	O
Pages	O
missing	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
