TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1690	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rapyer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Bingley	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
George	B-pers
Wareing	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mailes	I-pers
Strangeway	B-pers
Mudd	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cornock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Dynn	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Mynn	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitfeild	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hollins	I-pers
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Levingstone	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barrow	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
31	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
)	O
Two	O
Cloth	O
Coates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
some	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pardoe	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Charge	O
them	O
possitively	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
Vulture	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Lumbard-street	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Lynnen	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
looking	O
upon	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
a	O
Sleeve	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Lace	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Pardoe	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Extenuated	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
strongest	O
against	O
Pearson	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Acron	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saltmarsh	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Riggs	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Mony	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
possitively	O
against	O
Riggs	O
that	O
he	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
Charge	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
so	O
clearly	O
discover	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
Riggs	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Saltmash	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
Hicks	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
presently	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
till	O
Hicks	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
10	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
off	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pearses	O
Coat	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Pinners	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
cut	O
them	O
off	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
asking	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
forgiveness	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
a	O
severe	O
Check	O
given	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Busbey	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Noble	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Polonia	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Noble	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Morgan	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Noble	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tewder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
dark	O
coloured	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
now	O
a	O
sick	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Strange	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
amongst	O
them	O
shifted	O
away	O
the	O
Silk	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Wilson	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
her	O
Innocency	O
in	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
31	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
144	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
16	O
d.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	B-place
near	O
Basing-hall-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
lying	O
in	O
Basing-hall-street	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
imperfect	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
then	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
should	O
be	O
drawn	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
was	O
Conjectured	O
on	O
their	O
part	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
Abet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jarrott	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
coloured	O
brown	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
's	O
Man	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
several	O
High-way-men	O
,	O
upon	O
Shoot-up-hill	B-place
,	O
near	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drewry	O
Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Marsh	O
swore	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
lead	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Powel	B-pers
,	O
an	O
ancient	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Kitching	O
to	O
Butter	O
some	O
Ale	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Elinor	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
whilest	O
the	O
said	O
Watson	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
way	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
;	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
her	O
Mony	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Snuff-Dish	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
to	O
offer	O
some	O
Fringe	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
whilest	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Fringe	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
Harlington	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
another	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
footsteps	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
they	O
saw	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
persued	O
and	O
found	O
near	O
Brainford	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
begging	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Proof	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Lattymore	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Charles	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
concerned	O
besides	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
since	O
fled	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Lynnen	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Ladds	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
was	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
)	O
Admonished	O
,	O
to	O
beware	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kittle	I-pers
of	O
K	O
n	O
borrow	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Angel	O
Gold	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
Jones	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Spoon-handle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
discovered	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
London	O
:	O
yet	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thorp	B-pers
Croome	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
with	O
their	O
Throat	O
Cut	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Coffe-house	O
in	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
Gill	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
Face	O
in	O
the	O
Coffe-Room	O
,	O
and	O
Wilks	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stayrs	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
abused	O
the	O
said	O
Wilkins	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
somewhat	O
of	O
Courtship	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
fell	O
out	O
between	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
matter	O
look	O
the	O
more	O
Suspicious	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
fawn	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Throat	O
of	O
it	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Dog	O
would	O
hide	O
himself	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
sin	O
to	O
kill	O
them	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
kill	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Sculls	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
horrid	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
pretty	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
too	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Disceaseds	O
House	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Coral	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
chiefest	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
anothersaid	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Osborne	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
another	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Malchill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Daytime	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Malchill	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
an	O
Embroydered	O
Cushion	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
value	O
:	O
The	O
Ribbon	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
against	O
V.	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Joan	O
Brown	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lofftin	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
figured	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bizzle	I-pers
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
others	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
26	O
yards	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Lace-stall	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Godspeed	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
fad	O
coloured	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Abel	B-pers
Slaney	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Slaney	I-pers
,	O
Partner	O
s	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
possitive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
run	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Florne	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
in	O
Crutched	B-place
Friers	I-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
about	O
the	O
Office	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
within	O
the	O
Walls	O
of	O
the	O
Office	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
noted	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Rason	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Reason	B-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Glossenberry	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lasenberry	B-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Snuff-dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
Extinguishor	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Mustard	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Whitehall	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Whitehall	O
swore	O
that	O
several	O
Persons	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Plate	O
and	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
Rason	O
owned	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
Excused	O
Glossenbury	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
somewhat	O
obscure	O
as	O
to	O
Glossenbury	O
:	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Notorious	O
Criminal	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
several	O
Enormous	O
Evils	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
Pardon	O
,	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
now	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
Parsels	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
possitive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
Picklock-Key	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Point	O
Sleeves	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
threw	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Congden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
,	O
three	O
Several	O
Indictments	O
of	O
Murther	O
committed	O
at	O
Wappen	B-place
not	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
(	O
first	O
)	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
(	O
secondly	O
)	O
one	O
Elinor	B-pers
Eadon	I-pers
,	O
(	O
thirdly	O
)	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jallon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
contrived	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
sale	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Persons	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
they	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
;	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Bernard	B-pers
Chatfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
French	O
Pistoles	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Apothicary	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
John	O
Ray	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Coyning	O
'	O
of	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Stamps	O
to	O
Coyn	O
Mony	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
several	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
eight	O
pieces	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Clipt	O
Mony	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Boards	O
in	O
the	O
Flore	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Porch	O
,	O
that	O
enters	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
somewhat	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Treason	O
that	O
Coward	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Coward	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
but	O
fair	O
and	O
clear	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Washerwoman	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Coward	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Stephen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
50	O
Pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Holland	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
Convicts	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Knight	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
went	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wright	O
)	O
stampt	O
and	O
Coyn	O
the	O
Money	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
about	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stamps	O
and	O
some	O
false	O
Money	O
besides	O
a	O
Hammer	O
and	O
Sheers	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
is	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
Knight	O
and	O
Stephen	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
:	O
But	O
Elizabeth	O
Bradley	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Simon	B-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
Instant	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
that	O
Rob	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
did	O
Rob	O
and	O
privily	O
take	O
from	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Page	I-pers
in	O
Leadenhall	B-place
Market	I-place
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
:	O
but	O
Justice	O
Jame	O
's	O
Clark	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
one	O
Captain	O
Eregrick	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
since	O
fled	O
;	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
Gown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
and	O
took	O
away	O
five	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Crevats	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Newgate	O
Officers	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
once	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
noted	O
Criminal	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Febr	O
.	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Thymble	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
Confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
owned	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
:	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
Stippen	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Ducket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
possitive	O
against	O
Cole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
Woman	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
Cole	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Williams	O
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
Tomson	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Tovey	O
and	O
one	O
Jordan	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Table	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s	O
,	O
two	O
little	O
Dyamond	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
GoldWatch	O
with	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
Pictures	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Brest	O
Jewel	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Williams	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Information	O
was	O
Read	O
to	O
Court	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Tho	O
.	O
Turner	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Noon	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Turner	O
and	O
carried	O
a-away	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
so	O
Williams	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
Tomson	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Febr	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
short	O
in	O
their	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Alce	B-pers
Billingsley	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Crevats	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
Confessing	O
withal	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Long	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Floyd	B-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Peters	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Febr	O
.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
Laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Cap	O
which	O
was	O
possitively	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
V	I-pers
-	I-pers
alias	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
Circumstantial	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
before	O
the	O
Dare	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eaglestone	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Trase	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Howel	B-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Fettiplace	I-pers
of	O
abundance	O
of	O
Rich	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorethie	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
with	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Pettycoat	O
with	O
Gold	O
Frenge	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
10	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Silk	O
Pettycoates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
28	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
12	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Night	O
Royles	O
,	O
some	O
Scarfs	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
Poynt	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Fettiplaces	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Play	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Browne	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
Batchelor	O
went	O
away	O
)	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
Batchelor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Browne	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
under	O
Mrs.	O
Fettiplaces	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Browne	O
called	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Row	O
,	O
who	O
Deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Fettiplace	O
had	O
Discharged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Browne	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Fettiplace	O
which	O
was	O
apparent	O
enough	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
the	O
Broker	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Browne	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Pawn	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
'	O
although	O
they	O
did	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
Extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
ill	O
Women	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Batchelor	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Brown	O
,	O
Trase	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candle-Cap	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
William	O
Arrowsmith	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Richard	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Cobbin	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Feilds	I-place
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Ricaut	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Linen-Draper	O
,	O
near	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
Julie	O
,	O
and	O
second	O
year	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
K.	O
William	O
and	O
Q.	O
Marie	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Mortal	O
Bruises	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
Ribs	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
Hill	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
e	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
languishing	O
and	O
them	O
dyed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Ricaut	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
committed	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
abeting	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
mainteying	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
R.	O
Cook	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Linnen-draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
desired	O
their	O
Charity	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
more	O
importunate	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
bid	O
her	O
ask	O
that	O
Linnen-Draper	O
for	O
somewhat	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Children	O
Frocks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
over-hearing	O
,	O
returned	O
in	O
answer	O
,	O
Give	O
her	O
the	O
Tails	O
of	O
your	O
Shirts	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
on	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
sudden	O
Heat	O
and	O
fewd	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Draper	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Scufle	O
and	O
Combat	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
received	O
the	O
Bruises	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Apothecaries	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
Ricaut	O
gave	O
any	O
Blows	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
only	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Rabble	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
somewhat	O
doubtful	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
conjecture	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Injury	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
:	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
Mr.	O
Ricaut	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Hill	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
brought	O
an	O
Appeal	O
of	O
Murder	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Unto	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Bayl	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
.	O
Bench	O
Bar	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
thus	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
West	O
and	O
Lotryn	O
Gwynn	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
25	O
.	O
William	O
Goodspeed	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Busby	O
alias	O
Noble	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Edgerton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
George	O
Jerrot	O
al	O
.	O
Mesey	O
,	O
Susannah	O
White	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Simons	O
,	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Blagrave	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
,	O
Richard	O
Moor	O
,	O
Joan	O
Brown	O
,	O
George	O
Rason	O
,	O
William	O
Lasenbury	O
,	O
Charles	O
Hughes	O
,	O
Robert	O
Congden	O
,	O
John	O
Ray	O
,	O
Henry	O
Knight	O
,	O
Edward	O
Stephens	O
,	O
James	O
Cox	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Steele	O
,	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Batchelor	O
,	O
Frances	O
Brown	O
and	O
Anne	O
Trasey	O
.	O
After	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
had	O
passed	O
upon	O
these	O
25	O
Criminals	O
,	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
all	O
called	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Busbey	O
,	O
Esther	O
Edgarton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Jane	O
Browne	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Steel	O
,	O
Frances	O
Browne	O
,	O
alias	O
Eglestone	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	O
Trasey	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
7	O
.	O
William	O
Cole	O
,	O
Francis	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
William	O
Arrowsmith	O
,	O
William	O
Bizzle	O
,	O
William	O
York	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Barloe	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
R.	O
S.	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
James	O
Florne	O
and	O
John	O
Williams	O
fined	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
continue	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
performed	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
If	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
or	O
Gentlewoman	O
have	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
or	O
French	O
Truly	O
and	O
Properly	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Explain	O
any	O
Author	O
according	O
to	O
Grammar-Rules	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
but	O
spare	O
two	O
hours	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
Switerda	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Profesleth	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
and	O
casie	O
Method	O
to	O
teach	O
them	O
the	O
said	O
Language	O
in	O
one	O
Year	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
have	O
learned	O
formerly	O
may	O
recover	O
it	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
.	O
He	O
Teacheth	O
also	O
other	O
Languages	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
desires	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Grammar	O
in	O
2	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Grammatical	O
and	O
Historical	O
Cards	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
where	O
he	O
Teacheth	O
in	O
Clements	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Canon-Street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
next	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
convenience	O
for	O
six	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
Lodge	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
is	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
of	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
.	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
,	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
series	O
.	O
