TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
29th	O
and	O
30th	O
days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1692.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sarjeant	O
Lovewell	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lapley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cutlove	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
Zach	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burrowes	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cows	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hynks	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dynn	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Howlet	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Vigure	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fitz-Gerald	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blisset	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammidge	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
EDward	B-pers
Kallaway	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Little-All-hallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Wosted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
)	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
be	O
Colour	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Dye-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Dye-house	O
Door	O
in	O
Thames	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Blew	O
Coat-Hospital	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
vindicate	O
himself	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lerow	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Leroch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Drouster	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Booksellor	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
of	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
Lerow	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Drouster	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Lerow	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
Book	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sympson	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Sympson	O
having	O
lost	O
Money	O
before	O
and	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
markt	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
hiding	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
saw	O
Larow	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Drouster	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
Larow	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hazlewood	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Solomon	B-pers
Young	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candle-Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
another	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cup-board	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse-keeper	O
in	O
Young	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
keeper	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
Son	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
unlockt	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
happily	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Hair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
possitive	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
where	O
lay	O
a	O
bigger	O
Sum	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Horsewell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Horsewell	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
absence	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
and	O
unlock	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
14	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Higdon	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
Market	O
;	O
which	O
Woman	O
was	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Veale	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
of	O
a	O
Rasey	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Child	O
happening	O
to	O
straggle	O
abroad	O
alone	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stript	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Haverlin	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Parish	I-place
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Pane	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
opened	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Pane	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Ruth	O
Herne	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birgin	I-pers
,	O
near	O
Lime-House	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
away	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Pinners	O
,	O
some	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Caps	O
and	O
Coives	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
indifferent	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
encompassed	O
by	O
breaking	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
puting	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Algood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Gray	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Horses	O
were	O
brought	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Flying-horse	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
unknown	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Horses	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
one	O
Pilkington	O
and	O
Whitney	O
to	O
the	O
Livery-Stable	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Horses	O
feed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Thieves	O
:	O
The	O
Contents	O
of	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Pilkington	O
to	O
a	O
Drinking-house	O
near	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Flying-horse	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Horses	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
suspect	O
Pilkington	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Highway-Man	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Goodman	O
a	O
Criminal	O
in	O
Newgate	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
further	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
being	O
Stolen	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
fully	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolly	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ninth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woolly	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Silver	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Strutton	I-pers
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
scar	O
'd	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
hap	O
to	O
be	O
Discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Algood	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
price	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
in	O
Maidenhead	B-place
Thicket	I-place
;	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
three	O
Highway-Men	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
all	O
Vizards	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
at	O
the	O
Flying-horse	O
,	O
where	O
Squire	O
Langston	O
's	O
two	O
Horses	O
were	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
one	O
Holland	O
and	O
Reynolds	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Maidenhead-Thicket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
:	O
The	O
Servants	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
found	O
Broken	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
stole	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
left	O
behind	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
having	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Chisel	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
suspicious	O
Implements	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Refractory	O
,	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
were	O
as	O
careful	O
to	O
Apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
others	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Visit	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
accidentally	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
above	O
a	O
Mile-off	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
Witness	O
to	O
testifle	O
:	O
But	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
himself	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
hold	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
Fellows	O
to	O
Shoot	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
,	O
whereas	O
in	O
reality	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Joyner	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fled	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
before	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Starr	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Monke	I-pers
in	O
Grub-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty-fith	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
lost	O
were	O
one	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
l.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
broad	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
one	O
Kiffen	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
lately	O
absconded	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
Monk	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
one	O
wrong	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
yet	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Blechington	I-pers
of	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Blechington	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
positively	O
sworn	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Miles	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
of	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Watch	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
medled	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Manowry	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tewder	I-pers
in	O
Goodmans	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
threatning	O
Language	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Closets	O
and	O
Chests	O
open	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Nine	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
240	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
284	O
l.	O
180	O
Guneas	O
,	O
value	O
190	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
fourscore	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
whilst	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Done	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Maudlin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Amber-Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Stenton	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Necklace	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Deane	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
charge	O
Brown	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Raybould	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Willet	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Harriot	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Cheese-cake	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Small	O
beer-Ally	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Cobbin	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
Cobbin	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Mullinax	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lehitabel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
of	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
opportunity	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
used	O
their	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemain	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
Pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Burrows	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Hood	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
old	O
Shop-lifters	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Rob	O
one	O
Giles	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Instant	O
of	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Alamode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hurley	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
sixteen	O
Silver	O
Snuff-dishes	O
,	O
some	O
Table-Linen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
their	O
Rapiers	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Witness	O
that	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
did	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Hurley	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
invalidate	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-ways	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
Hownslow-heath	B-place
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
he	O
bound	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Gelding	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Paper-book	O
,	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
well	O
weighing	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
justified	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
Right	O
Shoulder	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Arm-hole	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Person	O
deceased	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
into	O
whom	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
concerning	O
Fencing	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Fencing-Master	O
s	O
)	O
and	O
immediately	O
upon	O
the	O
hot	O
words	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
Southampton-House	B-place
in	O
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
they	O
Fought	O
,	O
and	O
Heard	O
was	O
Kill	O
'd	O
;	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
lately	O
taken	O
a	O
Fencing-School	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
occasion	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
jealous	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
his	O
Scholars	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
partly	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
challenged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
a	O
Wager	O
,	O
and	O
urg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
defensive	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
any	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Stone-Horse	O
colour	O
'd	O
Grey	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
197	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
fully	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
Enfield	B-place
Chase	I-place
)	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
besides	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Pistol	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Pistol	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Windmil-Hill	O
by	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
who	O
lockt	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
their	O
Horses	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
was	O
Thomas	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
William	O
)	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
paid	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
Pistol	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
fellow	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Serving-Man	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
a	O
little	O
improbable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
Money	O
for	O
one	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbors	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
So	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Child	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripple	I-place
Gate	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Pewter-dishes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Lamb	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
street	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Alden	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
very	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
in	O
contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
words	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
King	O
but	O
King	O
James	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
a	O
Wager	O
that	O
King	O
James	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
White-hall	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
three	O
Months	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
call	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
but	O
know	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
declare	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pension	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
withal	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
charge	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Curnock	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Gold-Rings	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Caroll	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
.	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Reb	B-pers
.	I-pers
Scaret	I-pers
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
with	O
Silver-plate	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
three	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
pretending	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
his	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Mill	O
'd	O
half	O
Crown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
Marry	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
not	O
performing	O
the	O
Bargain	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Rings	O
freely	O
off	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
force	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
together	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
The	O
Taylor	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Coat	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Liquor-Pond-street	B-place
;	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
evidently	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Instruments	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
Files	O
and	O
Rubbing-stones	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Sheers	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Weights	O
and	O
some	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Maids	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
that	O
comming	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Arm	O
move	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
or	O
somewhat	O
else	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
both	O
Broad	O
Money	O
and	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
lie	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
any	O
Shears	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
see	O
her	O
actually	O
Clip	O
:	O
But	O
another	O
Witness	O
Swore	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
not	O
only	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
lie	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
and	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
snapping	O
of	O
Shears	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
plainly	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
rough	O
,	O
being	O
newly	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
that	O
her	O
Servants	O
had	O
been	O
hired	O
to	O
convey	O
such	O
things	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
new	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clip	O
'd	O
money	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
that	O
Nurse	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
and	O
had	O
Sworn	O
against	O
her	O
)	O
had	O
Robbed	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Pillow-beer	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
side	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Nurse	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
and	O
abscond	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
Prosecute	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
feared	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Some	O
other	O
Witness	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
good	O
money	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
evil	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
urged	O
her	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
mony	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
who	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
to	O
any	O
purpose	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
and	O
fair	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Brass	O
Skimmer	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
several	O
Pewter-dishes	O
and	O
Ladles	O
,	O
14	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
:	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Christian	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blackford	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blackford	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
diminushing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
William	O
Blackford	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Blackford	O
lodged	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blackford	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
Shears	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
necessary	O
Instruments	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dead	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
alone	O
am	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
Guilty	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisonerswas	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Beds	O
side	O
working	O
some	O
Needle-work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
let	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
his	O
Assistants	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
swore	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
actually	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blackford	O
,	O
was	O
sitting	O
upright	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Shears	O
in	O
his	O
Hand-fastened	O
to	O
a	O
Billet	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
other	O
Implements	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
Persons	O
very	O
Industrious	O
and	O
Diligent	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
their	O
Living	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
were	O
none	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Women	O
commit	O
any	O
Offence	O
:	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
Arraingned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
committing	O
an	O
Error	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
Endorsting	O
Billa	O
Vera	O
on	O
that	O
Bill	O
for	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
agreed	O
by	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Ignoramus	O
,	O
and	O
Billa	O
Vera	O
,	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
Bill	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
)	O
this	O
did	O
occasion	O
a	O
great	O
Controversie	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mistake	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Brethren	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
plead	O
perticularly	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
Error	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
therefore	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
,	O
would	O
suffer	O
no	O
particular	O
Damage	O
,	O
withal	O
excusing	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Brethren	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Judges	O
did	O
differ	O
somewhat	O
in	O
their	O
Opinions	O
,	O
fearing	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
altred	O
it	O
might	O
make	O
a	O
President	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
:	O
So	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
agree	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Rage	O
and	O
Malice	O
before-thought	O
,	O
In	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
did	O
Strike	O
,	O
Stab	O
and	O
Thrust	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hoyle	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Young	O
Devil-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
very	O
scurrilously	O
against	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
spake	O
very	O
unbecoming	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
pleased	O
if	O
this	O
King	O
would	O
not	O
please	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
now	O
hazarding	O
his	O
Life	O
for	O
Us	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
continuing	O
to	O
rail	O
against	O
all	O
Government	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
perswade	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
such	O
discourse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
,	O
very	O
unworthy	O
Language	O
and	O
provoking	O
Words	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Coward	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
rising	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
)	O
put	O
himself	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
to	O
be	O
pacified	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
)	O
pray	O
take	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
hear	O
this	O
Language	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
the	O
Lye	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
told	O
him	O
this	O
is	O
meer	O
Madness	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
's	O
to	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Proposals	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
Fight	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
two	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
together	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
going	O
towards	O
Temple-Barr	O
)	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Temple-Gate	B-place
,	O
they	O
fell	O
foul	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
first	O
taking	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
by	O
the	O
Crevate	O
,	O
tore	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
drawn	O
his	O
;	O
so	O
at	O
length	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
gave	O
account	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
went	O
off	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
first	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
life-time	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
called	O
seven	O
Peers	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
obliging	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
quiet	O
and	O
moderate	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
all	O
Company	O
,	O
no	O
ways	O
given	O
to	O
Passion	O
or	O
Revenge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
did	O
very	O
affectionately	O
declare	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Antipathy	O
,	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
great	O
Misfortune	O
he	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
that	O
happened	O
:	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
was	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
calling	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
,	O
Poultroon	O
,	O
Rascally	O
Coward	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
Rusty	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
like	O
aggravating	O
Language	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Care	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
withdrew	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
returned	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
was	O
only	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
petitioned	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Prayer	O
might	O
be	O
Recorded	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Appeal	O
for	O
Murther	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Bail	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Landale	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
secretly	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Cowborne	I-pers
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
it	O
was	O
drawing	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
(	O
missing	O
his	O
Mony	O
)	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Besides	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pretended	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
debauch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
medled	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hylton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
Milliner	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
most	O
Scandalous	O
,	O
Base	O
and	O
Cursed	O
Words	O
against	O
Their	O
present	O
Majesties	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
pronounce	O
these	O
English	O
Words	O
.	O
God	O
Damn	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
bless	O
King	O
James	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
Damn	O
all	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
bless	O
my	O
Self	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
'for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Robbey	I-pers
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Robbey	O
's	O
Shop	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
other	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
(	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
)	O
take	O
the	O
Cheese	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aaron	B-pers
Hush	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart-wheel	O
laden	O
with	O
Grains	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
one	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
Cripple-Gate	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruses	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
their	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
driving	O
up	O
White-Cross-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
off	O
Wheel	O
coming	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
fell	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
the	O
Child	O
Screek	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
endeavor	O
all	O
in	O
him	O
lay	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
protested	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
so	O
sad	O
an	O
Accident	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
Course	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Valentine	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Venning	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
by	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Venning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
threatning	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
slip	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
and	O
knockt	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
turbulent	O
and	O
an	O
unquiet	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Enemy	O
to	O
the	O
Present	O
Government	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Subjects	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
did	O
assert	O
,	O
declare	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
James	O
had	O
an	O
Army	O
of	O
40000	O
Men	O
in	O
Arms	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
who	O
intended	O
to	O
Land	O
in	O
England	O
the	O
following	O
Summer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
January	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
Drink	O
to	O
the	O
Health	O
and	O
Prosperity	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
and	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Restoration	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
his	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Royal	O
Embrio	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
an	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
and	O
Spleen	O
,	O
he	O
exprest	O
those	O
words	O
,	O
That	O
Hunch-Nose	O
William	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
and	O
a	O
Robber	O
,	O
and	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
Hanged	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Common	O
Thief	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
Stolen	O
Three	O
Kingdoms	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
of	O
our	O
present	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
he	O
spake	O
very	O
irreverent	O
words	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
base	O
Language	O
and	O
virulent	O
Expressions	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
altho	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Heating	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Randolph	B-pers
Alanakre	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
together	O
with	O
Lancelot	O
Hen-ly	O
co	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Mayle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Two	O
Serge	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
a	O
Baize	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
several	O
Aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Young	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goodsand	O
Pawned	O
them	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
excuse	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hempen	O
Smock	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
one	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Huik	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
year	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
a	O
Point	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
Swore	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
brags	O
amongst	O
his	O
Fellows	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bit	O
the	O
Biter	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
replyed	O
Andrew	O
Vaughan	O
the	O
Baily	O
upon	O
Saffron-hill	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bit	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Clank	O
(	O
meaning	O
a	O
Tankard	O
)	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
being	O
Affrighted	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Dubb	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
Pick-lock	O
Key	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
believe	O
her	O
Depositions	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
did	O
drink	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Consort	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
submitted	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Family	O
of	O
Children	O
,	O
besides	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
Commisserate	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
Fine	O
him	O
only	O
20	O
l.	O
Edward	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
the	O
Black	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
ten	O
Groats	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Discharged	O
paying	O
his	O
Fine	O
.	O
One	O
Cole	O
being	O
lately	O
Apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Clench	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
the	O
Black	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
ten	O
Groats	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Discharged	O
paying	O
his	O
Fine	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
a	O
Notorious	O
Highway-Man	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
Remain	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Titcomb	I-pers
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
Discharged	O
,	O
no	O
proof	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
Ministers	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
committed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
apply	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
for	O
coming	O
into	O
England	O
out	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
without	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Licence	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
apply	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Nottingham	O
for	O
Bail	O
.	O
Sir	O
Solomon	B-pers
Swaile	I-pers
committed	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
moved	O
by	O
his	O
Counsel	O
to	O
be	O
Discharged	O
or	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
was	O
referred	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Major	O
Culliford	O
Committed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
further	O
Orders	O
.	O
Knevet	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Rigbey	I-pers
,	O
having	O
the	O
usual	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Fidelity	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
tendred	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
Test	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
concerning	O
Transubstantiation	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
gave	O
Bail	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
they	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
Oaths	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
James	O
Lereen	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Drowster	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
James	O
White	O
,	O
William	O
Blathwait	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
)	O
Katherine	O
Davis	O
,	O
Nichalos	O
Legg	O
,	O
Nath	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
Anne	O
Hazlewood	O
,	O
Mary	O
Griffeth	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Clark	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Wright	O
,	O
Ruth	O
Herne	O
,	O
Anne	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Mullinax	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Burrowes	O
,	O
Anne	O
Nash	O
,	O
Elisabeth	O
Williams	O
,	O
Elisa	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
and	O
Anne	O
Sympson	O
,	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
John	O
Algood	O
,	O
Richard	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Hurley	O
:	O
Ruth	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Condemned	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
William	O
Blackford	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Edward	O
Kallaway	O
and	O
Elisabeth	O
Lee	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
Margaret	O
James	O
,	O
John	O
Valentine	O
,	O
Elisabeth	O
Landale	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	O
Mayle	O
.	O
Fined	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
James	O
Hicton	O
fined	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behavior	O
.	O
William	O
Coney	O
fined	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
John	O
Alden	O
being	O
Poor	O
and	O
Insufficient	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
The	O
Young	O
Student	O
's	O
Library	O
:	O
Containing	O
Extracts	O
and	O
Abridgments	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Valuable	O
Books	O
Printed	O
in	O
England	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Foreign	O
Journals	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1665.	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
:	O
Of	O
whom	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
Entire	O
Set	O
of	O
Athenian	O
Gazettes	O
and	O
Supplements	O
to	O
'em	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1691	O
.	O
(	O
or	O
single	O
Mercuries	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
)	O
Infants	O
Baptism	O
from	O
Heaven	O
,	O
of	O
Divine	O
Institution	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Brief	O
yet	O
Satisfactory	O
Answer	O
,	O
to	O
some	O
Objections	O
made	O
by	O
Hercules	O
Collins	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
Entituled	O
,	O
Believers	O
Baptism	O
from	O
Heaven	O
;	O
Infants	O
Baptism	O
from	O
Earth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
certain	O
Truths	O
proved	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
Entituled	O
,	O
Baptism	O
Anatomized	O
.	O
Propounded	O
in	O
Five	O
Queries	O
,	O
by	O
THO	O
.	O
WALL	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
William	O
Miller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gilded	O
Acorn	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
;	O
where	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Speeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
Discourses	O
and	O
State-Matters	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
Books	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
Church-Government	O
,	O
Humanity	O
,	O
Sermons	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
MDCXCIL	O
THese	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
that	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Head-Pill	O
;	O
which	O
Infallibly	O
Curecs	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
Contracted	O
;	O
speedily	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
,	O
preserves	O
,	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
oftending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
;	O
Strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
disburrhens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humours	O
;	O
thereby	O
rendring	O
the	O
Understanding	O
emore	O
clear	O
and	O
Vigorous	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditious	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
Curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
without	O
Drawing	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
by	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
for	O
George	O
Croom	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
near	O
Baynara	O
's	O
Castle	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
