TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
.	O
and	O
19th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Marloe	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Warting	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bickley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Grosvenour	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
.	O
Dorman	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Pollfrey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
evidenced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
;	O
where	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
which	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
(	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
)	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
tyed	O
up	O
about	O
Fifty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
charged	O
the	O
matter	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
who	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seized	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
her	O
;	O
went	O
into	O
Drink	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
who	O
spoke	O
very	O
favourably	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Blewet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Falconer	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
liking	O
out	O
of	O
meer	O
Charity	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
coming	O
as	O
a	O
Begger	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
s	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
unlockt	O
the	O
Drawer	O
where	O
the	O
Mony	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
met	O
uponLondon	O
Bridge	O
with	O
the	O
Mony	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
confest	O
before	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Segar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
3000	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Value	O
100	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Mooreland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Bundles	O
,	O
was	O
conveyed	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hoskins	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
There	O
were	O
others	O
also	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
discovered	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
bundle	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Morris	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
since	O
fled	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Parlor	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
James	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Morris	O
Moor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Griffeth	O
actually	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
as	O
Griffeth	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
were	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Womans	O
hood	O
Dress	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
another	O
Scarf	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Tippet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
Some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Griffeth	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Griffeth	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Robbed	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
Dubb	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
term	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
)	O
by	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
false	O
Keys	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
Liv	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Cook	O
by	O
Trade	O
)	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Willyer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Back	O
Silk	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baden	I-pers
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Fringes	O
,	O
Pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
,	O
bet	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
pitcht	O
upon	O
the	O
Fringe	O
abovementioned	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
another	O
time	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Baden	O
's	O
Son	O
being	O
busie	O
with	O
other	O
Customers	O
;	O
she	O
slipt	O
away	O
the	O
Fringe	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
missing	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Rothery	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
Mrs.	O
Rogers	O
in	O
Bishopgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
about	O
Noon-Tide	O
and	O
Rothery	O
jostled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Knight	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Third	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
confident	O
in	O
their	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
themselves	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
their	O
side	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
so	O
at	O
length	O
Rothery	O
was	O
Accquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Knight	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
manner	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Tate	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Parish	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
set	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Broad	O
Weaver	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
Parish	I-place
:	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Kings	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Baily	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
Whip	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Tate	O
several	O
Stripes	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
Loyns	O
and	O
Buttocks	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
his	O
prodigious	O
Malice	O
and	O
Wicked	O
Tyranny	O
not	O
being	O
qualified	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spindle	O
heated	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
did	O
burn	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Tate	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
blows	O
with	O
the	O
Whip	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
Malitiously	O
burning	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Instant	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
particularly	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
inhumane	O
manner	O
with	O
the	O
Whip	O
and	O
sometimes	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
;	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
so	O
close	O
as	O
he	O
expected	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
way	O
whereby	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
punish	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
which	O
hath	O
scarce	O
ever	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stone	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
about	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
Seven	O
Stone	O
and	O
two	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
frequently	O
tye	O
it	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
Lashing	O
him	O
forwards	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
Whip	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
Stone	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
enough	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
it	O
(	O
instead	O
of	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
allay	O
his	O
Passion	O
)	O
she	O
added	O
Fuel	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
by	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
:	O
Another	O
way	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
Exercise	O
his	O
unparalell	O
'd	O
Cruelty	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
burning	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
hot	O
Iron	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
and	O
Thighs	O
:	O
Also	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
would	O
prick	O
the	O
boy	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spindle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
Cruel	O
usage	O
was	O
performed	O
upon	O
the	O
poor	O
Boy	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
so	O
Low	O
and	O
Weak	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
subsist	O
any	O
longer	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
burnt	O
by	O
his	O
Mrs.	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
continued	O
till	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
Speechless	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
Chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
burn	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
hot	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
urge	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
Cruel	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
Resented	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
very	O
Unreasonable	O
,	O
Illegal	O
,	O
Inhumane	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
brutish	O
Correction	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Master	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
Curtain	O
before	O
the	O
boys	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
correct	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
lest	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Stone	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
ponderous	O
enough	O
;	O
He	O
would	O
add	O
another	O
little	O
one	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
great	O
Protestations	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
harm	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
never	O
wanted	O
any	O
necessary	O
Provisions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
a	O
sickly	O
distempered	O
boy	O
,	O
troubled	O
with	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
and	O
Runing	O
Sores	O
in	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
about	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
directed	O
seriously	O
to	O
weigh	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Morris	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
:	O
a	O
Silver	O
Beaker	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Four	O
Spoons	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
another	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Salt	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
13	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
Lac	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
value	O
34	O
l.	O
a	O
Cloak	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
onto	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
K	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stockdane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stockdane	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
took	O
away	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Mellincapp	I-pers
since	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
fully	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gascoigne	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Three	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Sleeves	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Night	O
Rayle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
besides	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
Threescore	O
and	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliott	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Branch	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
divers	O
places	O
;	O
Gascoigne	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
very	O
freely	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
Branch	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
Pawned	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
Gascoigne	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Witherman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackfadian	I-pers
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
an	O
Alamood	O
.	O
hood	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Lace	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunck	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
not	O
Lock't	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
positively	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riches	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
instant	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Hip	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
arose	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
jealousie	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Todd	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
more	O
familiar	O
than	O
it	O
became	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
Todd	O
)	O
had	O
sent	O
away	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Estate	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Sea	O
:	O
all	O
which	O
very	O
much	O
vexed	O
and	O
irritared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Sword	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
give	O
very	O
provoking	O
language	O
to	O
Rich	O
before	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
:	O
so	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kibey	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Goodyer	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
leading	O
the	O
Horse	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Goodyer	O
's	O
servant	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
still	O
his	O
year	O
was	O
expired	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
something	O
better	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Horse	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Goodyer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Geldings	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
Yet	O
this	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
accounted	O
Felony	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hurley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Shorter	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
all	O
three	O
young	O
Youth	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgan	I-pers
in	O
Ratcliff-High-way	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Burgan	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
were	O
One	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
brown	O
Cloth	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
s.	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muzlin	O
26	O
s.	O
Two	O
Holland	O
skull	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Muzlin	O
Comode	O
7	O
s.	O
2	O
silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Walking-Cane	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Household	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
one	O
Scofeld	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
with	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
Recanting	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Boy	O
,	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
of	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
ordered	O
,	O
immediately	O
to	O
prefer	O
an	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
weak	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
good	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
coloured	O
white	O
,	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
the	O
Ewe	O
,	O
entangled	O
in	O
the	O
Bryers	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
his	O
Family	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
starve	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
it	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
tied	O
in	O
the	O
Bryers	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
killed	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
such	O
great	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Food	O
for	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Magennis	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
only	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keating	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Hair	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Flanders	O
Lac't	O
Crevates	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Note	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Drinking	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
else	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
and	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Milledge	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
One	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
another	O
old	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Dowlace	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Bird	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
seeing	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Milledge	O
that	O
lay	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
directed	O
Dalton	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
White-Cross-street	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
particularly	O
against	O
Dalton	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Bird	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Conduit	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
named	O
Katharine	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
who	O
he	O
married	O
at	O
Knights	O
Bridge-Chappel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
1689	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Wife	O
;	O
named	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Springfield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
following	O
:	O
The	O
Clark	O
of	O
the	O
Chappel	O
produced	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Register	O
which	O
gave	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Daniel	O
Conduit	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
withal	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
itwas	O
usual	O
for	O
people	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
and	O
personate	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
sham	O
Marriages	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Conway	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Conway	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
vertuous	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
self	O
like	O
a	O
loving	O
Wife	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
insomuch	O
such	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
her	O
Hair	O
off	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
administer	O
to	O
his	O
Necessities	O
.	O
The	O
occassion	O
of	O
his	O
denying	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
expected	O
a	O
considerable	O
Fortune	O
with	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Springfield	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
denyed	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
held	O
some	O
private	O
Correspondency	O
with	O
Conway	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
really	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
nay	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Witness	O
affirmed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
marry	O
Conway	O
,	O
yea	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
without	O
help	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Weeks	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
where	O
he	O
then	O
Lodged	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
Moreover	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
averted	O
that	O
Conway	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Fortune	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
(	O
she	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
)	O
accompanied	O
with	O
an	O
eager	O
Expectation	O
of	O
Reaping	O
some	O
Gain	O
,	O
by	O
Receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Portion	O
)	O
had	O
now	O
indicted	O
him	O
fasly	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
unnecessary	O
Trouble	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
coherent	O
enough	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
(	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
)	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precincts	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
of	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
)	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Six	O
Pound	O
of	O
Dyer	O
's	O
stuff	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Archill	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Sea-coal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Workman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Dye-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
used	O
them	O
about	O
his	O
Masters	O
Business	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Scofield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
called	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Hurley	O
,	O
Butcher	O
and	O
Nun	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burgan	I-pers
's	O
House	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
25	O
l.	O
mentioned	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Hurley	O
,	O
Butcher	O
and	O
Nun	O
:	O
The	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Card	O
Matches	O
;	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Boys	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
his	O
share	O
:	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
fear	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
other	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
idle	O
pilfering	O
young	O
Youth	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Eastwick	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
one	O
Joan	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bynworth	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Sarn	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
instant	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Randale	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
suddenly	O
snatch't	O
his	O
Crevate	O
from	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
crying	O
ont	O
murther	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
solicited	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
;	O
She	O
called	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
before	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
usually	O
divert	O
himself	O
by	O
picking	O
up	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
furthermore	O
,	O
called	O
some	O
others	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Sempster	O
,	O
and	O
wrought	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
Reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Brodnix	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
they	O
lately	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
in	O
Liquor-Pond-Street	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
confest	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Griffith	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
before	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
single	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Stacy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
himself	O
:	O
Philips	O
,	O
Stacy	O
and	O
Morris	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
compleated	O
their	O
Work	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Robin	O
Hood	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
and	O
then	O
Griffith	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brodnix	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
34	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Remainder	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
stolen	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
very	O
frequently	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
of	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
unnecessary	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
;	O
for	O
Philips	O
and	O
Stacy	O
having	O
confest	O
their	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
under	O
any	O
penalty	O
,	O
neither	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
current	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Matthews	O
not	O
appearing	O
(	O
though	O
often	O
called	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
false	O
Half-pence	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
in	O
East-Cheap	B-place
,	O
and	O
offered	O
12.	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
more	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
knit	O
Stockins	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
considered	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
barbarous	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
Dr.	B-pers
Clench	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
strangled	O
and	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-street	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
very	O
good	O
grounds	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Also	O
one	O
Roe	O
a	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
so	O
Butcher-like	O
,	O
assassinated	O
the	O
Dr.	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
to	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
One	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
Robbing	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Waggon	O
,	O
near	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
Bail	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
nothwithstanding	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	O
Tate	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
peaceable	O
and	O
quiet	O
behaviour	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
A	O
Bill	O
being	O
preferred	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Canning	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
accused	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
for	O
Publishing	O
several	O
Scandalousand	O
Seditious	O
Libels	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Poyke	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morrice	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Canning	O
travers	O
'd	O
his	O
Indictment	O
till	O
next	O
Session	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
Adjourn	O
'd	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
being	O
met	O
,	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
These	O
following	O
persons	O
being	O
called	O
over	O
by	O
their	O
Names	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
Why	O
Execution	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
awarded	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Death	O
?	O
they	O
all	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
respective	O
Knees	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Maries	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Thirty	O
Five	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
Freely	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
,	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Trumball	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Matthias	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rea	B-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemingway	I-pers
.	O
Those	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
K.	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Horspoole	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Exhall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beneson	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Earsall	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Trivert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chatfield	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bransbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
alias	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
most	O
seasonable	O
Exhortation	O
,	O
pertinent	O
to	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
posture	O
of	O
submission	O
,	O
being	O
bowed	O
upon	O
their	O
Knees	O
;	O
hoping	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
also	O
relenting	O
in	O
their	O
Hearts	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
great	O
Offenders	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
against	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
an	O
All-seeing	O
God	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
call	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
strict	O
and	O
particular	O
Account	O
for	O
all	O
their	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
behoved	O
them	O
to	O
beg	O
Pardon	O
of	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
obtained	O
Mercy	O
from	O
the	O
Goodness	O
and	O
Clemency	O
of	O
so	O
Gracious	O
a	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
demonstrate	O
their	O
thankfulness	O
for	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Deliverance	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
holy	O
,	O
humble	O
,	O
and	O
honest	O
life	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
the	O
least	O
part	O
of	O
their	O
Duty	O
for	O
such	O
extraordinary	O
Pity	O
;	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
mind	O
how	O
many	O
notorious	O
Offenders	O
(	O
in	O
nature	O
like	O
to	O
themselves	O
)	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
to	O
the	O
fatal	O
tree	O
yet	O
They	O
were	O
spared	O
:	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
now	O
hoped	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
particular	O
Indulgence	O
to	O
them	O
would	O
work	O
such	O
a	O
thorow	O
change	O
upon	O
their	O
Hearts	O
and	O
Lives	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
whole	O
Life	O
should	O
be	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
temptation	O
whatsoever	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
aside	O
;	O
remembring	O
withal	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
shedding	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
Tears	O
here	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
satisfie	O
offended	O
Justice	O
,	O
except	O
they	O
universally	O
repent	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
to	O
God	O
with	O
all	O
their	O
Hearts	O
and	O
Souls	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
particularize	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Offences	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
ways	O
to	O
upbraid	O
their	O
former	O
dissolute	O
Lives	O
,	O
but	O
calmly	O
to	O
caution	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
heed	O
how	O
they	O
steer	O
'd	O
their	O
Course	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
split	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Rock	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
but	O
young	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
yet	O
old	O
Offenders	O
;	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
heed	O
of	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
like	O
Danger	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
receive	O
such	O
Pardon	O
,	O
as	O
now	O
happly	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
withal	O
:	O
And	O
furthermore	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
should	O
return	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
before	O
Seven	O
Years	O
were	O
expired	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
certainly	O
prove	O
a	O
great	O
detriment	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
if	O
overtaken	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
desperate	O
Adventure	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Another	O
amongst	O
them	O
was	O
more	O
particularly	O
remarked	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Ray	O
,	O
alias	O
Red	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
formerly	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coyning	O
the	O
current	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
He	O
receiving	O
such	O
Mercy	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
freely	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Transported	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
deserved	O
)	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
required	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
being	O
more	O
sensible	O
than	O
some	O
others	O
)	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
his	O
whole	O
Interest	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
:	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
undermine	O
the	O
true	O
Interest	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
feared	O
his	O
Religion	O
might	O
teach	O
him	O
)	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
find	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
this	O
Rock	O
have	O
I	O
built	O
my	O
Church	O
,	O
faith	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Conclusion	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
notwithstanding	O
their	O
Crimes	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
particulary	O
recounted	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
all	O
forwarned	O
by	O
this	O
particular	O
Grace	O
,	O
and	O
distinguishing	O
Favour	O
,	O
as	O
never	O
to	O
offend	O
any	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
Grace	O
to	O
serve	O
God	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
none	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
William	O
Franklin	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Riche	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Bunworth	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Edward	O
Bluet	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Stacy	O
,	O
James	O
Philips	O
,	O
Anne	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Scofield	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Willyer	O
,	O
from	O
New-gate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Gascoigne	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bird	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Lodge	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
Adjourn	O
'd	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
being	O
met	O
,	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
These	O
following	O
persons	O
being	O
called	O
over	O
by	O
their	O
Names	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
Why	O
Execution	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
awarded	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Death	O
?	O
they	O
all	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
respective	O
Knees	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Maries	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Thirty	O
Five	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
Freely	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
,	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Trumball	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Matthias	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rea	B-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemingway	I-pers
.	O
Those	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
K.	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Horspoole	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Exhall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beneson	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Earsall	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Trivert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chatfield	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bransbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
alias	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
most	O
seasonable	O
Exhortation	O
,	O
pertinent	O
to	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
posture	O
of	O
submission	O
,	O
being	O
bowed	O
upon	O
their	O
Knees	O
;	O
hoping	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
also	O
relenting	O
in	O
their	O
Hearts	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
great	O
Offenders	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
against	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
an	O
All-seeing	O
God	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
call	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
strict	O
and	O
particular	O
Account	O
for	O
all	O
their	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
behoved	O
them	O
to	O
beg	O
Pardon	O
of	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
obtained	O
Mercy	O
from	O
the	O
Goodness	O
and	O
Clemency	O
of	O
so	O
Gracious	O
a	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
demonstrate	O
their	O
thankfulness	O
for	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Deliverance	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
holy	O
,	O
humble	O
,	O
and	O
honest	O
life	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
the	O
least	O
part	O
of	O
their	O
Duty	O
for	O
such	O
extraordinary	O
Pity	O
;	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
mind	O
how	O
many	O
notorious	O
Offenders	O
(	O
in	O
nature	O
like	O
to	O
themselves	O
)	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
to	O
the	O
fatal	O
tree	O
yet	O
They	O
were	O
spared	O
:	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
now	O
hoped	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
particular	O
Indulgence	O
to	O
them	O
would	O
work	O
such	O
a	O
thorow	O
change	O
upon	O
their	O
Hearts	O
and	O
Lives	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
whole	O
Life	O
should	O
be	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
temptation	O
whatsoever	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
aside	O
;	O
remembring	O
withal	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
shedding	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
Tears	O
here	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
satisfie	O
offended	O
Justice	O
,	O
except	O
they	O
universally	O
repent	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
to	O
God	O
with	O
all	O
their	O
Hearts	O
and	O
Souls	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
particularize	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Offences	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
ways	O
to	O
upbraid	O
their	O
former	O
dissolute	O
Lives	O
,	O
but	O
calmly	O
to	O
caution	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
heed	O
how	O
they	O
steer	O
'd	O
their	O
Course	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
split	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Rock	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
but	O
young	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
yet	O
old	O
Offenders	O
;	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
heed	O
of	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
like	O
Danger	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
receive	O
such	O
Pardon	O
,	O
as	O
now	O
happly	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
withal	O
:	O
And	O
furthermore	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
should	O
return	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
before	O
Seven	O
Years	O
were	O
expired	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
certainly	O
prove	O
a	O
great	O
detriment	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
if	O
overtaken	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
desperate	O
Adventure	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Another	O
amongst	O
them	O
was	O
more	O
particularly	O
remarked	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Ray	O
,	O
alias	O
Red	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
formerly	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coyning	O
the	O
current	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
He	O
receiving	O
such	O
Mercy	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
freely	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Transported	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
deserved	O
)	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
required	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
being	O
more	O
sensible	O
than	O
some	O
others	O
)	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
his	O
whole	O
Interest	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
:	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
undermine	O
the	O
true	O
Interest	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
feared	O
his	O
Religion	O
might	O
teach	O
him	O
)	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
find	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
this	O
Rock	O
have	O
I	O
built	O
my	O
Church	O
,	O
faith	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Conclusion	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
notwithstanding	O
their	O
Crimes	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
particulary	O
recounted	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
all	O
forwarned	O
by	O
this	O
particular	O
Grace	O
,	O
and	O
distinguishing	O
Favour	O
,	O
as	O
never	O
to	O
offend	O
any	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
Grace	O
to	O
serve	O
God	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Notorious	O
Imposter	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
William	O
Norell	O
,	O
alias	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
of	O
Banbury	O
,	O
Chyrurgeon	O
,	O
who	O
lately	O
personated	O
Humphrey	O
Wickham	O
of	O
Swackley	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Oxford	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
1691	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Authentick	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prerogative-Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Funeral	O
in	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
yard	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
A	O
second	O
Part	O
thereof	O
,	O
compleating	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
Cheats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
some	O
further	O
passages	O
relating	O
to	O
his	O
Sickness	O
and	O
Death	O
(	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Part	O
.	O
)	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
his	O
Executors	O
.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
Abel	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
near	O
Templebar	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Farrier	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
compleat	O
Treaties	O
of	O
Horsemanship	O
:	O
in	O
Two	O
Books	O
,	O
Physical	O
and	O
Chyrurgical	O
.	O
Fitted	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
all	O
Farriers	O
,	O
Grooms	O
,	O
Jockeys	O
,	O
and	O
Breeders	O
of	O
Horses	O
;	O
with	O
Directions	O
for	O
the	O
choice	O
of	O
all	O
Stallions	O
and	O
Mires	O
,	O
their	O
Shapes	O
and	O
Colours	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
Instructions	O
for	O
Paring	O
and	O
Shooing	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Hoofs	O
,	O
shewing	O
where	O
in	O
that	O
Curiosity	O
doth	O
consist	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Virtue	O
of	O
both	O
Simple	O
and	O
Compound	O
,	O
appertaining	O
to	O
Farrying	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Alphabethical	O
lable	O
of	O
most	O
Simples	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
of	O
all	O
inward	O
and	O
outward	O
Diseases	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
much	O
enlarged	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
new	O
Receipts	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
and	O
Value	O
,	O
never	O
published	O
before	O
in	O
any	O
Author	O
.	O
By	O
.	O
R.	O
Gent	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Whirwood	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Little-britain	O
;	O
At	O
which	O
place	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Ready	O
Money	O
for	O
any	O
Parcel	O
or	O
Library	O
of	O
Books	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Dr.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
and	O
FAMILY	O
PILLS	O
and	O
FAMILY	O
POWDER	O
;	O
Those	O
so	O
Famously	O
known	O
throughout	O
England	O
for	O
the	O
Curable	O
Diseases	O
,	O
as	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Dropsey	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Made	O
and	O
Prepared	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
himself	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
near	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Family	O
Pills	O
and	O
Family	O
Powder	O
,	O
are	O
both	O
fitted	O
for	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Diseases	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Pills	O
work	O
more	O
gently	O
,	O
the	O
Powder	O
more	O
strongly	O
,	O
yet	O
both	O
very	O
safely	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
old	O
or	O
young	O
whether	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Child	O
,	O
given	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
Dose	O
.	O
They	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
swallow	O
the	O
pills	O
,	O
may	O
take	O
the	O
powder	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
who	O
like	O
not	O
the	O
Powder	O
,	O
may	O
take	O
the	O
Pills	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
being	O
Universal	O
Purgers	O
.	O
These	O
Famous	O
Family	O
Pills	O
and	O
Family	O
Powder	O
,	O
are	O
eminent	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
of	O
the	O
aforenamed	O
diseases	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
of	O
Agues	O
,	O
Green	O
Sickness	O
,	O
Catarrsh	O
,	O
Head-act	O
,	O
Lethargy	O
,	O
Rheuming	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Stinking-Breath	O
,	O
Want	O
of	O
Appetite	O
,	O
Illness	O
of	O
stomach	O
,	O
Stuffing	O
at	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
Fluxes	O
,	O
Foulness	O
of	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Hard-drinking	O
,	O
Sea-Sickness	O
,	O
Urine	O
stopt	O
,	O
Barrenness	O
,	O
Soiatica	O
,	O
Numbness	O
,	O
French-Pox	O
,	O
Gonerrbei	O
,	O
Swellings	O
,	O
Lameness	O
,	O
Prin	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
,	O
Pushes	O
,	O
Wheals	O
,	O
Botches	O
,	O
Scahs	O
,	O
lich	O
,	O
Tetarrs	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Leprosie	O
,	O
Marge	O
,	O
Salt-humours	O
,	O
All	O
breaking-out	O
,	O
Running-Sores	O
,	O
Old	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Fistulas	O
,	O
Jaundice	O
,	O
Kings-evil	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
Pills	O
,	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
Box	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Paper	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
24	O
Years	O
Practice	O
;	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHo	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Newse	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
light	O
by	O
inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
as	O
must	O
Eminent	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Pill	O
,	O
which	O
Insallibly	O
Cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
Contracted	O
;	O
Speedily	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
;	O
Preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
offending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
disburdens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humors	O
,	O
thereby	O
rendering	O
the	O
Understanding	O
more	O
clear	O
and	O
vigorous	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditions	O
way	O
in	O
Curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
without	O
drawing	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Month-Water	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
