TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
KING	O
and	O
QUEEN	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
In	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
1693.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Stancliff	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Emmett	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Turvill	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lapworth	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Allen	B-pers
Hackshaw	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Haycock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dynn	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunk	I-pers
John	B-pers
Biscoe	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Gunstone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dando	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
in	O
Falcon-Court	B-place
in	O
Shooe-Lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
arose	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
entered	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
searching	O
for	O
Clippings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
rifling	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
one	O
Caudle-cup	O
,	O
50s	O
.	O
one	O
Salt	O
,	O
5l	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30s	O
.	O
Six	O
Forks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3l	O
.	O
Nine	O
Knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
Mr.	O
Jacob	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
no	O
search	O
for	O
Clippers	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
carried	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Messengers	O
.	O
They	O
produced	O
the	O
Secretary	O
's	O
Warrant	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
on	O
their	O
behalf	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
their	O
Warrant	O
was	O
to	O
impower	O
them	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Warrant	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
had	O
they	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Batson	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
through	O
ignorance	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
not	O
long	O
deputed	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Clippers	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
search	O
of	O
Jacob	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
by	O
force	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
produced	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Deputation	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
acted	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
ought	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Plate	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
such	O
practices	O
as	O
these	O
were	O
of	O
dangerous	O
consequence	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
more	O
to	O
be	O
consider	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
)	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
va	O
2d	O
.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
17l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
3d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
Williams	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Country-man	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
sell	O
Teazles	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Chamberlaine	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
behind	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
the	O
Pillow	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
awoke	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
at	O
the	O
Beds-feet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
several	O
persons	O
that	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Dendy	O
,	O
a	O
Country	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
)	O
alledged	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
care	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
fasten	O
their	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
In	O
fine	O
,	O
The	O
Inn-Keeper	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
said	O
Williams	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
33l	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
Gross	O
of	O
Brass	O
Buttons	O
,	O
gilded	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
55	O
Ells	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
100	O
Ells	O
of	O
Offenbrig	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
28s	O
.	O
from	O
Agnes	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Instant	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ralph	B-pers
Tells	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tells	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
22s	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tells	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
notice	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
nor	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
so	O
clandestinely	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Sarah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fish-woman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
upon	O
Margaret	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
upon	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
their	O
lives	O
;	O
taking	O
from	O
Atkinson	O
21l	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
Sarah	O
Arnold	O
;	O
Atkinson	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
London	O
Bridge	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
four	O
men	O
then	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
whereof	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
upon	O
Fish-street	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pretending	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
that	O
they	O
charged	O
the	O
said	O
Atkinson	O
with	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
comes	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
,	O
and	O
declares	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
used	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
uncivil	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
abundance	O
of	O
ill	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
searcht	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Ireland	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
slip	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Treat	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
two	O
Fish-womens	O
health	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Booty	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
to	O
be	O
Arnold	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
searcht	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
fairly	O
searcht	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
suspicious	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Deputation	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
derived	O
from	O
it	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
heed	O
how	O
he	O
executes	O
that	O
power	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
upon	O
persons	O
of	O
those	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
upon	O
their	O
Goods	O
;	O
for	O
this	O
was	O
of	O
such	O
bad	O
Example	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
honest	O
persons	O
might	O
be	O
seized	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
had	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
quality	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Birth	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
a	O
Good	O
Family	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
by	O
several	O
worthy	O
persons	O
of	O
great	O
note	O
,	O
of	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
so	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
guilty	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Verdict	O
they	O
were	O
checkt	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
was	O
singly	O
tried	O
on	O
Middlesex	O
side	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
is	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsey	B-place
and	O
searcht	O
Mr.	O
Hick	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Plate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Pistols	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
such	O
matters	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pistols	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Killigrew	O
's	O
man	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Messenger	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
must	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
must	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dymblebee	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Coining	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
Jones	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Sutton-street	B-place
,	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
Tools	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
thousand	O
Crucibles	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
false	O
Half-Crowns	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
razed	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
above-mentioned	O
Utensils	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Rubbing-stones	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
such	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
one	O
Dumferling	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
concerned	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
dealt	O
with	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Sisters	O
;	O
Stebbing	O
being	O
Maid-servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Dymblebee	O
(	O
her	O
Sister	O
)	O
came	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
also	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
honest	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
concerned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Skillet	O
,	O
a	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Bowl	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
a	O
Little	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Gill	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Padlock	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
Gill	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
warning	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Padlock	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
five	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
Silver	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murther	O
one	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
deceased	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
one	O
Blacker	O
,	O
being	O
walking	O
along	O
Castle-street	B-place
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
last	O
Good-Friday	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
Jack-a-napes	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
pickt	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fight	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
Blaker	O
got	O
the	O
Black	O
's	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Davis	O
gave	O
Price	O
the	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Black	O
's	O
Fingers	O
were	O
cut	O
by	O
Blaker	O
's	O
drawing	O
the	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
Black	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Flanders	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
alledged	O
;	O
and	O
thinking	O
all	O
was	O
forgot	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Westminster	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
bad	O
Repute	O
.	O
The	O
Black	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
them	O
Sons	O
of	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
fought	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
most	O
affected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
hard	O
for	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Dinner	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Wilkinson	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Daughters	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
(	O
and	O
was	O
reprieved	O
,	O
being	O
pregnant	O
)	O
but	O
on	O
Evidence	O
could	O
affect	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crittenden	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	B-place
,	O
where	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Forge	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Clipt-money	O
,	O
half-finished	O
,	O
and	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Rubbing-stones	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
necessary	O
Implements	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
much	O
surprized	O
when	O
the	O
Officers	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
men	O
struck	O
dumb	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
did	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
spake	O
well	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tupham	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
Monument	O
steps	O
telling	O
Clipt-money	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
his	O
Colour	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt-money	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
dropt	O
from	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Money	O
upon	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
s.	O
o	O
n't	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Not-guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
also	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
27	O
s.	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
Good	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
to	O
some	O
Clippings	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Anns-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
met	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
was	O
found	O
pinn	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Tools	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
how	O
the	O
Clippings	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
pinn	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Skirt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Trick	O
put	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
truly	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wholly	O
innocent	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
Charge	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Nace	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
White	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rachel	B-pers
Nace	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes-place	I-place
,	O
four	O
Ells	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
Rachel	O
Nace	O
was	O
Mother-in-law	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Westminster	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
Crapes	O
,	O
with	O
Scarves	O
and	O
Fringes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
bought	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
fine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
also	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
written	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
White	O
from	O
Northampton	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
long	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
new	O
Rigging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
Northampton	O
,	O
but	O
withal	O
in	O
as	O
great	O
pomp	O
as	O
possibly	O
she	O
could	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
her	O
defence	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
Rachel	O
Nace	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
money	O
often	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
thought	O
now	O
she	O
might	O
make	O
bold	O
with	O
hers	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Dubelly	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
served	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dubelly	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
much	O
pressure	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
though	O
she	O
promised	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
but	O
a	O
days	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Trough	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Neckcloths	O
and	O
Crevats	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Gloves	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Windor	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Jack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gertrude	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Laces	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
contained	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
besides	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
's	O
in	O
Cripplegate	B-place
Parish	I-place
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Jury	O
following	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Mealand	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
Wifebeing	O
alive	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Deacon	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
Ceremonies	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dando	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
again	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
40	O
Guineas	O
from	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hicks	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
Chelsey	B-place
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seized	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
searching	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Clipper	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
taking	O
Hicks	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
;	O
This	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
legal	O
way	O
of	O
dealing	O
;	O
tho	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Treasonable	O
Persons	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
persons	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
their	O
money	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
Bedford	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
in	O
course	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pleading	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
through	O
ignorance	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
acquit	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
defrauding	O
and	O
seducing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Puplet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
21	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
have	O
seduced	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Puplet	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
Cash	O
keeper	O
to	O
Mr	O
Bernard	O
)	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
One	O
thousand	O
and	O
seventy	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bernard	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
at	O
Bristol	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
said	O
Puplet	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
his	O
Affairs	O
here	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
younger	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
Margaret	O
Summer	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bernard	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Seward	O
and	O
Rowland	O
,	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
one	O
A	O
-	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
they	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
the	O
said	O
Puplet	O
to	O
drink	O
himself	O
into	O
a	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Seward	O
borrowed	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
a	O
Horse	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
really	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Richmond	O
to	O
the	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
lent	O
them	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
finding	O
him	O
yielding	O
to	O
their	O
Designs	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
hire	O
a	O
Calash	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
ride	O
in	O
it	O
with	O
two	O
Gentlemens	O
Wives	O
,	O
whose	O
Husbands	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
to	O
Epsom	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
ride	O
by	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
effect	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
want	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Calash	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lent	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
some	O
Perriwigs	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
money	O
Mr.	O
Rowland	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Epsom	O
Journey	O
was	O
put	O
by	O
;	O
this	O
money	O
they	O
borrowed	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
encouraged	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Seaward	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Estate	O
in	O
Reversion	O
,	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
honestly	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rowland	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
Threescore	O
pounds	O
per	O
annum	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
whatever	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Seaward	O
would	O
ride	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
in	O
Wilts	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
sell	O
his	O
Reversion	O
to	O
repay	O
Mr.	O
Puplett	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
performed	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
shift	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
perswade	O
Mr.	O
Puplet	O
to	O
get	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
could	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Flanders	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
into	O
preforment	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
a	O
Commission	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Puplett	O
being	O
so	O
tricked	O
out	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Cash	O
against	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
return	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
comply	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
raised	O
several	O
Sums	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
1000	O
l.	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
shipt	O
off	O
from	O
Harwich	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
by	O
their	O
Counsel	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
allured	O
nor	O
inticed	O
Mr.	O
Puplet	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
they	O
know	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
forward	O
as	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
declared	O
upon	O
oath	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
their	O
side	O
;	O
that	O
did	O
them	O
no	O
kindness	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
consider	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
of	O
such	O
base	O
Practices	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Steward	O
and	O
Rowland	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sumner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Quilts	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Blankets	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pedly	I-pers
,	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clipt	O
Sixpence	O
found	O
in	O
Gold	O
's	O
Chamber	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
evil	O
behaviour	O
and	O
disaffected	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Church	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bon	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
wish	O
evil	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
the	O
occasion	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
Minister	O
having	O
read	O
a	O
Brief	O
,	O
and	O
pronouncing	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
God	O
save	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
conclusion	O
thereof	O
the	O
said	O
P.	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
The	O
Devil	O
take	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
sworn	O
he	O
spoke	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Pew	O
with	O
the	O
Witness	O
and	O
they	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
words	O
spoken	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
sate	O
with	O
Mr.	O
P.	O
in	O
his	O
Pew	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
heard	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
several	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
on	O
Mr.	O
P	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Minister	O
pronounced	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
God	O
save	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
said	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
that	O
gave	O
a	O
credible	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Oaths	O
to	O
Their	O
present	O
Majesties	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
well	O
affected	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Their	O
Government	O
;	O
particularly	O
Dr	O
Puller	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewkin	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lampkin	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
neck	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Montford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
about	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishop's-gate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
suddenly	O
her	O
Tippet	O
was	O
snatcht	O
from	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
running	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Tippet	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
Mrs.	O
Montford	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
good	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Credit	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
run	O
was	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
debt	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Duchfeild	I-pers
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
speaking	O
these	O
words	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Pocket-glass	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
there	O
is	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
listed	O
under	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
any	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
listed	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
These	O
words	O
were	O
declared	O
positively	O
to	O
be	O
spoken	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
:	O
All	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
yield	O
to	O
her	O
unlawful	O
desires	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
disproved	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Groome	I-pers
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male-infant	O
Bastard-child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
;	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
being	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
but	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
Sevennight	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
dead	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
shift	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sign	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
provision	O
of	O
Clouts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Except	O
such	O
Mother	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
by	O
one	O
Witness	O
as	O
least	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
accounted	O
guilty	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Lark	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lyon	B-pers
,	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
l.	O
another	O
10	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
9	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cummins	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
it	O
whilst	O
she	O
went	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
Goods	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
it	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
but	O
the	O
Gold	O
was	O
spent	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Cummins	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
so	O
much	O
ado	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
contented	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Law	O
with	O
her	O
with	O
their	O
own	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
ruin	O
them	O
therewith	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
but	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
band	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellory	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Edith	B-pers
Ellory	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Medbury	I-pers
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
thePrisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Washer	O
of	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
Medbury	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Finger	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Welsted	I-pers
were	O
both	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
on	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Minnim	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
Welsted	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Salter	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
Welsted	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Salter	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Welsted	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Grimstone	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Box	O
of	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
pickt	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Plate	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Swan-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Plate	O
was	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Salver	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Utherwell	O
in	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
in	O
Spittle	O
fields	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Silks	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Corroborating	O
Circumstances	O
gave	O
such	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Percivall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
(	O
that	O
lately	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Play-House	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
nor	O
weighing	O
his	O
Duty	O
and	O
Allegiance	O
to	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
;	O
but	O
endeavouring	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
deceive	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
falsly	O
and	O
traiterously	O
clip	O
,	O
cut	O
,	O
file	O
and	O
diminish	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
;	O
and	O
over	O
his	O
Bed's-head	O
was	O
found	O
another	O
little	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
showed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
as	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shears	O
and	O
the	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Bridgmans	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
askt	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
falling	O
into	O
their	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
easily	O
believed	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
From	O
William	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Aldgood	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Stephen	B-pers
Duncks	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
feloniously	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kyrbey	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
180	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Aldgood	O
and	O
Duncks	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kyrbey	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
German-street	B-place
to	O
search	O
for	O
one	O
Unit	O
a	O
Clipper	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
came	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
waiting	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
afterwards	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
suspicious	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Mrs.	O
Kyrbey	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
demeanour	O
amongst	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
others	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Aldgood	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
15	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
till	O
10	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
catch't	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Randale	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
;	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
Whore	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Fast-day	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Newtner	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
kill	O
Randale	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dando	I-pers
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
golden	O
Locket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Lockets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Forceps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
Instruments	O
,	O
besides	O
42	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Coppinger	I-pers
;	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
rude	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
Mr.	O
Marriott	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Marriott	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Coppinger	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
your	O
Husband	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
your	O
Soul	O
to	O
Hell	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Coppinger	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
searching	O
all	O
the	O
Drawers	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
away	O
;	O
Batson	O
and	O
Dando	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
Mrs.	O
Coppinger	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Clothes	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Bedford	O
(	O
being	O
more	O
civil	O
than	O
they	O
)	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
spake	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
Mr.	O
Batson	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
sealed	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
odd	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
bear	O
charges	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Killigrew	O
's	O
Man	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
fire	O
the	O
House	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
bring	O
Candles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
mistaken	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
further	O
than	O
they	O
had	O
power	O
,	O
but	O
withal	O
had	O
no	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Coppinger	O
had	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rollstone	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Settle	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
in	O
Beaufort	B-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Settle	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
was	O
perfectly	O
lame	O
,	O
being	O
maimed	O
in	O
the	O
Wars	O
last	O
Summer	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
waver	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barry	B-pers
,	O
was	O
singly	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Woollen	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Nicholls	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Deborah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Purfrey	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cart-load	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Wood	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skudamore	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Gowen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
erecting	O
and	O
setting	O
up	O
a	O
private	O
Printing-press	O
,	O
and	O
printing	O
therewith	O
,	O
or	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
several	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Pamphlets	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
dispersing	O
the	O
said	O
Scandalous	O
Pamphlets	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Press	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Douglas	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
printed	O
thereupon	O
several	O
Seditious	O
Papers	O
and	O
Pamphlets	O
;	O
one	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Jacobites	O
Principles	O
vindicated	O
;	O
and	O
Great	O
Britain	O
's	O
Just	O
Complaint	O
;	O
Another	O
Book	O
of	O
Paradoxes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Douglas	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Printing-room	O
whilst	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
printing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
make	O
more	O
haste	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
more	O
haste	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
Gloves	O
for	O
my	O
Mistress	O
the	O
Queen	O
;	O
and	O
Further	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Douglas	O
had	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Pamphlets	O
from	O
the	O
Printer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gowen	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Whim	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Jacobite	O
Principles	O
vindicated	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
several	O
Friends	O
appeared	O
for	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
in	O
general	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
men	O
that	O
followed	O
of	O
their	O
private	O
Trades	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
ways	O
disaffected	O
as	O
they	O
ever	O
apprehended	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Skudamore	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
though	O
often	O
called	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
discharged	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dando	I-pers
,	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
in	O
Shooe-Lane	B-place
;	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Godman	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile's-Cripplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
one	O
Alkereene	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Hair-fringe	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
White	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
43	O
s.	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
double	O
lockt	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Bayly	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Wythers	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chetwood	I-pers
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
two	O
Burglaries	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pullets	O
,	O
val	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Malner	I-pers
;	O
a	O
second	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Twiford	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
bailed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Twiford	O
's	O
Goose-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Geese	O
stole	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
the	O
Headborrow	O
of	O
Marrybone	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Goose-house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Geese	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
of	O
Twiford	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
short	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Vandore	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vandore	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barry	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
James	O
Bennet	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
another	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
James	O
Bennet	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Nichol	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
rushed	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Nichols	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
money	O
they	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
Vandore	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Woolley	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
indicted	O
but	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
James	O
Bennet	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
at	O
Cock-hill	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
abundance	O
of	O
Plates	O
of	O
Half-Crowns	O
newly	O
stampt	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Bars	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Flasks	O
and	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Tools	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
lay	O
,	O
Marsh	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
94	O
new	O
fresh-coined	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
essay	O
'd	O
and	O
valued	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
but	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
an	O
Ounce	O
:	O
Sherwood	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Lodgers	O
that	O
Lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Marsh	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Sherwood	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Slayman	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Denzy	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Mackdonel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hudbolt	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
:	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
came	O
to	O
Hudbols	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Lodging	O
;	O
telling	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
wanted	O
two	O
Fellows	O
that	O
were	O
run	O
from	O
their	O
Colours	O
:	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
sat	O
a	O
while	O
eating	O
and	O
drinking	O
civilly	O
,	O
in	O
comes	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
Mutiny	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
amongst	O
themselves	O
,	O
one	O
holding	O
a	O
Sword	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
into	O
disorder	O
and	O
fear	O
,	O
penning	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Mantua-Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
White	O
Hood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
shot	O
a	O
Pistol	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Mackdonel	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
feigned	O
himself	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Hudbolt	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
40	O
s.	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Hudbolt	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
they	O
forced	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
borrow	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chamber-door	O
and	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Linnens	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Drink	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Barrels	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
run	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
was	O
again	O
singly	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Musquetoone	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
of	O
Chelsey	B-place
:	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Deputy	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Massenger	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
above	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Musquetoone	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
withal	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
were	O
Convicted	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
nothing	O
suspicious	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Wine	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Ale	O
was	O
naught	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
scattering	O
,	O
selling	O
,	O
and	O
exposing	O
the	O
Picture	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
taking	O
Notes	O
under	O
the	O
Peoples	O
hands	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
when	O
King	O
James	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
again	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
Messenger	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
Copper-plates	O
with	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
Effigies	O
engraven	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Notes	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
West	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	O
James	O
shall	O
come	O
to	O
White-hall	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
hand	O
Elinor	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Notes	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Francis	O
West	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Publishing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entitled	O
,	O
An	O
Errata	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Bible	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Translation	O
Examined	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
were	O
many	O
most	O
base	O
,	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Expressions	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
the	O
disparagement	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
undervaluing	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
;	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Book	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
to	O
one	O
Matthew	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
near	O
Turn	O
stite	O
,	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdeameanor	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dando	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
again	O
arraigned	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Lid	O
of	O
a	O
Tankard	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Plate	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
confest	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
14	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Laborne	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvass-bags	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
:	O
They	O
were	O
Plaisterer	O
s	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
be	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
very	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clover	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
pair	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Kneves	I-pers
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
away	O
from	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
branded	O
before	O
;	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Clemens	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clemens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
Sixty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
;	O
and	O
Six	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Aldershaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
in	O
old	O
Pipes	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
9	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
askt	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Father	O
testified	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Common-shore	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
of	O
Tyn	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
Tin	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
them	O
in	O
payment	O
against	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
hearing	O
a	O
knocking	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
She	O
replied	O
,	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
beating	O
of	O
Pepper	O
to	O
boil	O
in	O
Milk	O
But	O
afterwards	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
work	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Water	O
that	O
would	O
turn	O
the	O
Farthings	O
into	O
Copper	O
colour	O
presently	O
.	O
The	O
Mold	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
made	O
Halfpence	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
was	O
singly	O
tried	O
for	O
changing	O
Broad	O
money	O
for	O
Narrow	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
it	O
in	O
payment	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Heretage	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heretage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Violin	O
from	O
Capt	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Berkley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
as	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
met	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Doorwith	O
the	O
Fiddle	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
tho	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Child	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
steal	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Smock	O
3	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
robbed	O
her	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
one	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Barn	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bright	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
containing	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
Two	O
Poringers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
Two	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bright	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Trunk	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Token	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
:	O
But	O
nothing	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dressing	O
box	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pedley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Statute	O
books	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
Poverty	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Shadrack	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
Curate	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
's	O
Hand	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Passport	O
,	O
to	O
convey	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Family	O
into	O
France	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mr	O
Cook	O
being	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Merryweathers	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
melt	O
Wax	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pull	O
a	O
Broad	O
Seal	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
press	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Wax	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Merryweather	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
look	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
fairly	O
done	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Witness	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
poor	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Seal	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Merryweather	O
,	O
you	O
Fool	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
's	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Witness	O
again	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
such	O
Seals	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Jacobites	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Furthermore	O
,	O
the	O
Blank	O
in	O
the	O
Passport	O
was	O
filled	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Davis	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
's	O
hand	O
was	O
fairly	O
written	O
under	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Principle	O
of	O
Conscience	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spragg	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
Mrs.	O
Spragg	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
wrong	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
being	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
goods	O
,	O
as	O
Scarves	O
,	O
Gowns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Young	O
Dutchwoman	O
,	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Parson	O
,	O
near	O
Ipswich	O
.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Session	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
Hold	O
up	O
thy	O
Hand	O
:	O
[	O
Which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
Thou	O
standest	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
thou	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
thine	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
instigated	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
thou	O
didst	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Powel	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
.	O
What	O
sayest	O
thou	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
art	O
thou	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cook	O
,	O
Not	O
guilty	O
,	O
Culprit	O
,	O
How	O
wilt	O
then	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
By	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
Countrey	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
God	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
Deliverance	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
the	O
Parson	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
upon	O
some	O
particular	O
affairs	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Dutch-Ordinary	O
)	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
the	O
Old	O
Woman	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Parson	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
dined	O
(	O
observing	O
the	O
Features	O
of	O
the	O
Dutchwoman	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
she	O
was	O
handsome	O
)	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
smitten	O
with	O
her	O
Beauty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
contain	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
Courting	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
declaring	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Creature	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
that	O
he	O
esteemed	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
truly	O
he	O
followed	O
his	O
business	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
match	O
was	O
suddenly	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
read	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Book	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Dutch	O
fashion	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Parson	O
grew	O
inflamed	O
,	O
in	O
Love	O
with	O
his	O
New	O
Bride	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
now	O
we	O
are	O
married	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
,	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
two	O
nights	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Parson	O
,	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
accommodate	O
his	O
new	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
behave	O
himself	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
some	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
adding	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
leave	O
you	O
;	O
God	O
Almighty	O
leave	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
reality	O
he	O
never	O
intended	O
.	O
For	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
delighted	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
fill	O
of	O
Love	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
grow	O
weary	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
his	O
Stock	O
grew	O
low	O
,	O
not	O
of	O
Confidence	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
Coriander	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
sudden	O
and	O
strange	O
Consternation	O
;	O
but	O
awaking	O
from	O
that	O
drowsy	O
fit	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
bestowed	O
before	O
on	O
his	O
dear	O
Mistress	O
:	O
Being	O
in	O
this	O
sorrowful	O
plight	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
the	O
Devil	O
put	O
is	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
Indict	O
his	O
Mistress	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
disgrace	O
of	O
his	O
Person	O
and	O
Character	O
;	O
For	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Diocesan	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
acquainted	O
what	O
a	O
fine	O
Clerk	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Diocess	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Dutchwoman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
poor	O
Parson	O
was	O
laught	O
at	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Foster	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Burrows	O
,	O
Mary	O
Nace	O
,	O
Doncas	O
Needham	O
,	O
Gertrude	O
Smith	O
,	O
John	O
Summers	O
,	O
James	O
Bell	O
,	O
Mary	O
Foreman	O
,	O
Martha	O
Ward	O
,	O
Jane	O
Lark	O
,	O
alias	O
Lyon	O
,	O
Mary	O
King	O
,	O
Hamnah	O
Woolly	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cloves	O
,	O
Ann	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Welsted	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
William	O
Noble	O
,	O
Mary	O
Salter	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Stephens	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Anderson	O
,	O
John	O
Aldgood	O
,	O
James	O
Robbins	O
,	O
John	O
Crittenders	O
,	O
Edward	O
Deer	O
,	O
James	O
Gardner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Compton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Baker	O
,	O
James	O
Grymstone	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Percival	O
,	O
Cornelius	O
Slayman	O
,	O
Arthur	O
Denzy	O
,	O
Philip	O
Mackdonnell	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Henderson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
John	O
Chetwood	O
,	O
James	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Ann	O
Clemens	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Tomlin	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Cornelius	O
Trough	O
,	O
Rebekah	O
Walker	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Heretage	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Rebekah	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
George	O
Windor	O
.	O
Mary	O
Compton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Clemens	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
impannelled	O
,	O
whose	O
Verdict	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Fined	O
.	O
James	O
Seaward	O
400	O
l.	O
John	O
Rowland	O
200	O
l.	O
And	O
10	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Dutchfeild	O
40	O
Mark	O
.	O
Walter	O
Batson	O
20	O
Mark	O
.	O
William	O
Dando	O
10	O
l.	O
Jeremiah	O
Bedford	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Riot	O
.	O
Fined	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
Riot	O
.	O
Dando	O
10	O
l.	O
Bedford	O
10	O
l.	O
Batson	O
20	O
Mark	O
.	O
David	O
Douglas	O
200	O
Marks	O
.	O
William	O
Gowen	O
100	O
l.	O
Francis	O
West	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Offence	O
100	O
Mark	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
second	O
100	O
Mark	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Vaughan	O
10	O
l.	O
Shadrack	O
Cook	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
;	O
The	O
Pillory	O
remitted	O
for	O
his	O
Function-sake	O
.	O
Ann	O
Smith	O
was	O
set	O
by	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Sentence	O
was	O
passed	O
,	O
these	O
four	O
Persons	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
upon	O
their	O
former	O
judgment	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ridgway	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
being	O
often	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
try	O
has	O
Traverse	O
,	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
issued	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
wherever	O
he	O
can	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
for	O
Writing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
News	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Disparagement	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	O
Skudamore	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Douglas	O
and	O
Gowan	O
,	O
appeared	O
after	O
their	O
Tryal	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
fresh	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kyrbey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Steno	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
Brent	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lighter	O
at	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Kybrey	O
struck	O
him	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Pole	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
fore-part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
sunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
seen	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Brent	O
struck	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Lighter	O
several	O
times	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
rise	O
,	O
and	O
stunn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
into	O
much	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
bailed	O
to	O
appear	O
whenever	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
man	O
be	O
sought	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
uncertain	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
drowned	O
,	O
yes	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
the	O
Midwife	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
