TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1693	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lapley	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Passell	I-pers
.	O
Azarias	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Benner	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ayeris	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Raycroft	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Farnborrow	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Fearne	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Polfrey	I-pers
.	O
Ri	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fitz	I-pers
Gerrald	I-pers
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Hamborrow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silk	O
Mantuas	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tobias	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Scart	I-pers
in	O
Hozier-Lane	B-place
,	O
of	O
22	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Guineas	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
dropt	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hatchet	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
coat	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Chest	O
and	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
therein	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ethye	I-pers
;	O
they	O
all	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
that	O
lay	O
near	O
Queen-Hithe	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boatman	O
being	O
asleep	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
presently	O
stopt	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
stifly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
Christ	B-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
trial	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
her	O
fault	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Linen	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
in	O
Cripplegate	B-place
Parish	I-place
;	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
in	O
a	O
Gallery	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hickling	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Instant	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
in	O
Tuttle	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
Arms	O
upon	O
the	O
Trained	O
bands	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
his	O
Musquet	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
rammer	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
But-end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Musquet	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
present	O
the	O
Musquet	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
jesting	O
manner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
have	O
at	O
thee	O
Jonathan	O
;	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
;	O
and	O
furthermore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
Loving	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
any	O
malice	O
found	O
nor	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
any	O
words	O
let	O
fall	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
malice	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
saluted	O
each	O
other	O
as	O
formerly	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
wont	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lamented	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
attested	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
considered	O
maturely	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Lydia	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
;	O
she	O
and	O
Edwards	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Apron	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Ticklet	I-pers
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
Kentin	O
Cloth	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Springhall	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
Tame	B-place
in	I-place
Oxfordshire	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Hanwell	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Chockalat	O
Cup	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tymbell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
value	O
18d	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Darney	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
4	O
Pewter-dishes	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
4	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
a	O
Morter	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mrs.	O
Darnay	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
lockt	O
on	O
the	O
Over-night	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
a	O
Wood-yard	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
declared	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
Smith	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Darney	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Darney	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
Jones	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Smith	O
produced	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Stoner	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
false	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
matter	O
home	O
upon	O
Jones	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Fellow	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Sawbridge	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sawbridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
murthering	O
her	O
Male-Infant	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Clay-pit	O
full	O
of	O
water	O
swimming	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
by	O
some	O
Workmen	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Clay-pit	O
;	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Dog	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
confest	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
several	O
Credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
sworn	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
why	O
she	O
so	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Labour	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
murthered	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Law	O
provides	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
appear	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
no	O
Bastard	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Amslet	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Amslet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Awdly	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
her	O
two	O
Daughters	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
100	O
Half-crowns	O
,	O
200	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
searcht	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
Mackeridge-street	B-place
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
above-stairs	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheares	O
,	O
Fillings	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Thumbstalls	O
,	O
Rubbing-Leathers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
things	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
answered	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Cook	O
did	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	O
Amslet	O
was	O
a	O
Labouring-woman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
let	O
Lodgings	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
abroad	O
a	O
Nurse-keeping	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
two	O
daughters	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Clippings	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
induced	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
credit	O
the	O
matter	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Naylor	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
(	O
upon	O
Saffron-Hill	B-place
)	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
besides	O
21	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
leapt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
why	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
a	O
man	O
do	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
?	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
plainly	O
made	O
manifest	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
whenever	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
his	O
innocency	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Name	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Coining	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metals	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Piece	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
another	O
false	O
Piece	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Great	O
Mill	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Westminster	O
in	O
his	O
Garret	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
flatten	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Mill	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Button-makeng	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Mill	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
proper	O
use	O
of	O
Coiners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
matter	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
upon	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
also	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lyddall	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Wrosted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
8	O
Cloth-Coats	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Portilla	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Easy	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wrosted	O
Camblet	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Chomley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
Hermondsworth	B-place
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Slocomb	I-pers
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
She	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Clippings	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
File	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Clippings	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Journeyman-Taylor	O
,	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
heretofore	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
rent	O
off	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Symon	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
and	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
Clipping	O
ofttimes	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Skales	O
,	O
Weights	O
,	O
Rubbing-Leathers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Searchers	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
Witness	O
declared	O
.	O
Turner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
but	O
little	O
good	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
likewise	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
little	O
effect	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
hurt	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Williams	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
whilst	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
seize	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
Witness	O
too	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
Turner	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Credit	O
,	O
nor	O
defend	O
themselves	O
against	O
what	O
was	O
so	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
fixt	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
newly	O
clipt	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Katharine	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
both	O
their	O
Arms	O
move	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Clipping	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Crevass	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
whilst	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
peremptorily	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
Clipping	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Clippings	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
shifted	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
presumed	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
received	O
good	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Gentlewoman	O
for	O
ought	O
they	O
knew	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
favour	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fryar	I-pers
at	O
Bartledown	B-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
March	O
last	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Cloak	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
14	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
12	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Fryar	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
about	O
20	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
bound	O
Mrs.	O
Fryer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
away	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
;	O
then	O
Arnold	O
accosted	O
her	O
Daughter	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
rude	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
ravished	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Youth	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
died	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
corroborated	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Arnold	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
least	O
share	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Younger	O
Brother	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
one	O
Hart	O
the	O
Carrier	O
of	O
Norfolk	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Fryer	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
into	O
Essex	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Assizes	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
being	O
notified	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
and	O
most	O
notorious	O
Thief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Rateen	O
Coat	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Gown	O
12s	O
.	O
5	O
laced	O
Crevats	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
40s	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
with	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
another	O
Pair	O
with	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Surtivant	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
at	O
Lime-house	B-place
Corner	I-place
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
were	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Gloves	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Gloves	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
two	O
Blue	O
Shirts	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
4	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
18l	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Warrington	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
convey	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Sea-man	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Sea-man	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
credited	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
first	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
coining	O
false	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
Farthings	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Tin	O
and	O
Copper	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Cripplegate	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Moulds	O
,	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
that	O
were	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
about	O
two	O
Ounces	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
shifted	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
All	O
the	O
Instruments	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Clippings	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
Corroborating	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
marry	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Instruments	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
disclose	O
his	O
Secrets	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
any	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Husband	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
at	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Trade	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mabbot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
6	O
pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
5	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Cheese	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
and	O
12	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Cider	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
Wall	O
about	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
might	O
likewise	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
suffice	O
his	O
Hungry	O
Appetite	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lookt	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
necessary	O
Provisions	O
,	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Padwick	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
six	O
Blue	O
Aprons	O
,	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
besides	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Padwick	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
Williams	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Angel	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
harbouring	O
and	O
Comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
one	O
Grace	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Michel	B-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Judgement	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Rolph	O
did	O
feloniously	O
take	O
and	O
receive	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
276	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
from	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Jolly	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Boyce	O
afterward	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
comfort	O
and	O
maintain	O
her	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Rolph	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
Dempsey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
Lace	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Rolph	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boyce	O
produced	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
arrest	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
of	O
his	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
upon	O
any	O
Evil	O
or	O
Felonious	O
Account	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
without	O
any	O
saddle	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
water	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
10	O
miles	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Gelding	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
Journey	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Clist	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Tabbey	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
theree	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
4l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
at	O
Greaves	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whist	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Greaves	O
Bond	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
)	O
fourscore	O
Iron	O
Bullets	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
18	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Captain	O
Francis	B-pers
Applebey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
How	O
was	O
found	O
aboard	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Hunt	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
stole	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
Iron-work	O
from	O
off	O
several	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hunt	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
saying	O
so	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
Hunt	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
How	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Owers	I-pers
in	O
Black-Fryars	B-place
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Shoes	O
were	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
that	O
for	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
day-light	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
removed	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pitford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
of	O
Stoak	B-place
in	O
Buckinghamshire	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
Instant	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
was	O
7	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
56s	O
.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
value	O
18l	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
val	O
.	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
val	O
.	O
5l	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
watches	O
value	O
15l	O
.	O
four	O
Spoons	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
fringed	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
Stript	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
7l	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
8l	O
.	O
two	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Wastcoats	O
val	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
besides	O
39s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
pursuing	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
within	O
five	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Barber	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
having	O
somewhat	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Fringed	O
Scarf	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Barber	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Pistols	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
's	O
Servants	O
swore	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
and	O
directly	O
evidenced	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
;	O
Barber	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Wickham	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
three	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
a	O
Burglary	O
be	O
committed	O
in	O
one	O
County	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
brought	O
by	O
them	O
into	O
another	O
County	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
accounted	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Offenders	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pitford	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
being	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Monies	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Mansell	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
an	O
amicable	O
Account	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
Squires	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Fuller	O
's	O
Rents	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
met	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
long	O
continue	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
more	O
privacy	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
Walks	I-place
;	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
High-walk	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
accommodate	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
although	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
offer	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
security	O
by	O
his	O
Bond	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
reasonable	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
his	O
Returns	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
;	O
yet	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
contented	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reply	O
upon	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
after	O
a	O
morose	O
manner	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
very	O
Scurrilous	O
Language	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
altogether	O
unfit	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
which	O
provoked	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
withdrew	O
himself	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
perceiving	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
danger	O
that	O
might	O
come	O
upon	O
him	O
)	O
leapt	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Lower	O
Walks	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Leg	O
short-off	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
other	O
hurt	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
was	O
removed	O
to	O
his	O
place	O
of	O
Abode	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
languished	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeons	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Misfortune	O
that	O
happened	O
much	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
doing	O
of	O
him	O
any	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Judges	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
Counsel	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
submit	O
his	O
Case	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
Then	O
the	O
Judges	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
agree	O
that	O
the	O
Matter	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
special	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Cause	O
;	O
Matter	O
of	O
Law	O
did	O
arise	O
thereupon	O
,	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
resolved	O
that	O
a	O
time	O
should	O
be	O
set	O
aside	O
for	O
the	O
Judges	O
to	O
consult	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Then	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Mansell	O
moved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
continue	O
upon	O
Bail	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
granted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
of	O
Shandois-street	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
declaring	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
more	O
that	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Widd	O
.	O
Was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
cutting	O
,	O
clipping	O
,	O
filing	O
,	O
and	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Clippings	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
Key	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
common	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Archer	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
heretofore	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
accounted	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nag	O
,	O
price	O
8l	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewer	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
She	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
him	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ingham	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Lovelace	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Fire-shovel	O
and	O
Tongues	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Watchman	O
found	O
Ingham	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
swore	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
Ingham	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Lovelace	O
formerly	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
Debt	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
hole	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
thereat	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Ellis	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Ingham	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
alias	O
Midleton	B-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
)	O
several	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnens	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Atkins	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
alias	O
Freeman	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Letman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather-shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Letman	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
lost	O
about	O
4l	O
.	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Letman	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Newman	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Swallow-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
Seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
a	O
double	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
themselves	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Thirteen	O
Guineas	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
Newman	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Newman	O
buy	O
Twenty	O
one	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
one	O
Townley	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
said	O
Newman	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
searcht	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Riddall	I-pers
(	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
)	O
6	O
Pewter-plates	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
Pewter-dish	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Riddall	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
the	O
Dog-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skullery-door	O
standing	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
being	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Plates	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Publishing	O
a	O
most	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
Entitled	O
,	O
Great	O
Britains	O
just	O
Complaint	O
for	O
her	O
late	O
Measures	O
,	O
present	O
Sufferings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
future	O
Miseries	O
she	O
is	O
exposed	O
to	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
safest	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
effectual	O
way	O
of	O
Securing	O
and	O
Establishing	O
her	O
Religion	O
,	O
Government	O
,	O
Liberty	O
,	O
and	O
Property	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
good	O
and	O
lawful	O
Foundation	O
,	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
discovered	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
Two	O
Late	O
Pamphlets	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
pretended	O
French	O
Invasion	O
.	O
Printed	O
at	O
Oxford	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
.	O
The	O
Libel	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Further	O
Testimony	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
very	O
abusive	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Expressions	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Captain	O
in	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
T	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Ireland	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
rise	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
witnessed	O
by	O
the	O
Girl	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
by	O
his	O
Counsel	O
called	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
regular	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
firm	O
Protestant	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
might	O
change	O
his	O
mind	O
since	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
perfect	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Gervisset	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Minster	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
,	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
composing	O
,	O
printing	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Catechism	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
contained	O
certain	O
Heretical	O
and	O
Schismatical	O
Sentences	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
dangerous	O
consequence	O
to	O
the	O
Youth	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
the	O
Council	O
argued	O
the	O
Matter	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
argued	O
that	O
the	O
Catechism	O
was	O
not	O
licenc	O
'd	O
according	O
to	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
neither	O
registered	O
in	O
the	O
Register	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Stationers	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
it	O
was	O
argued	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Words	O
excepted	O
against	O
in	O
the	O
Catechism	O
were	O
not	O
Heresy	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
tryed	O
in	O
an	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
That	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Men	O
were	O
not	O
proper	O
Judges	O
of	O
Heresy	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
ought	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
determin	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ludlam	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
The	O
Anatomy	O
of	O
a	O
Jacobite	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Jacobite	O
's	O
heart	O
laid	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
the	O
Messenger	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
s	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
civilly	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
what	O
Papers	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
his	O
Badge	O
,	O
which	O
certified	O
the	O
Authority	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
several	O
Papers	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
presently	O
marked	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Libel	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
likewise	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Papers	O
contained	O
an	O
Alphabet	O
of	O
Letters	O
,	O
directing	O
a	O
Founder	O
how	O
and	O
what	O
Letters	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Papers	O
contained	O
Queries	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
act	O
in	O
the	O
dispersing	O
of	O
Unlicens	O
'd	O
Papers	O
and	O
Books	O
,	O
without	O
coming	O
under	O
the	O
censure	O
of	O
a	O
Criminal	O
;	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Paper	O
,	O
mentioning	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
any	O
Person	O
to	O
any	O
Private	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
Printed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
denied	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
Name	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
,	O
offering	O
him	O
Monies	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
at	O
first	O
:	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
therefore	O
in	O
Law	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Press	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
use	O
to	O
any	O
ill	O
end	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
affront	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Franklin	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Babbington	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Blanch	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
(	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
)	O
5	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
42s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
going	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Law	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
three	O
other	O
Smocks	O
val	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
of	O
eleven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
twenty	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Stringer	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lay	O
all	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
Murray	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
Mrs.	O
Stringer	O
7l	O
.	O
to	O
reconcile	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
and	O
Avis	B-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Dust-gound	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
val	O
18s	O
.	O
five	O
Petticoats	O
val	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
val	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Peters	O
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Peters	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
who	O
were	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
thirsting	O
after	O
blood	O
too	O
,	O
they	O
murthered	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Peters	O
,	O
putting	O
Tobacco-pipes	O
and	O
a	O
Stone	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
crammed	O
Rags	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
and	O
choakt	O
him	O
to	O
death	O
;	O
the	O
Rags	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
others	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Davis	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
sweet	O
Life	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
old	O
Cull	O
out	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
her	O
business	O
effectually	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Pattins	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Dog	O
's	O
Room	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
meaning	O
Peters	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
presumed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
her	O
fortune	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
Davis	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hamsted	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Old	O
Cull	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
one	O
Jacob	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Old	O
Cull	O
fast	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
Hamsted	O
entertained	O
Davis	O
that	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
horrid	O
in	O
its	O
nature	O
and	O
circumstances	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
indicted	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
cried	O
and	O
lamented	O
her	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
al	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
Hamstead	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
Henry	B-pers
Hamsted	I-pers
,	O
Husband	O
to	O
Avis	O
Hamstead	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
by	O
his	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Davis	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
accuse	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
Davis	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hamsted	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
harbouring	O
and	O
entertaining	O
of	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
committed	O
.	O
[	O
Davis	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Hamsted	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Nunnella	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nunnella	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Picture	O
val	O
.	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Chyrurgeon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
that	O
his	O
Picture	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Goat-Court	B-place
near	O
Fleet-bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Anny-Seed-Clear	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
towards	O
Anny-Seed-Clear	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Picture	O
hang	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
and	O
Mr.	O
page	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Picture	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
over	O
the	O
Mantle-tree	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Blue-apron	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Keeling	O
Baford	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
past	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Henry	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murther	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
500	O
Mark	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
;	O
was	O
also	O
tried	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
maiming	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
strong	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
when	O
the	O
business	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
this	O
Sessions	O
to	O
answer	O
an	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Keeling	B-pers
Baford	I-pers
;	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
refusing	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Prejudice	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Surties	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Paling	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Exchanging	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
for	O
clipt	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
give	O
22s	O
.	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
21s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
furnisht	O
the	O
Clippers	O
withal	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
her	O
Master	O
Oliver	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
did	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
unto	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
val	O
.	O
6l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
trust	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
contrary	O
to	O
her	O
Faith	O
and	O
Trust	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
said	O
Master	O
,	O
imbezle	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
damage	O
of	O
her	O
said	O
Master	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evenor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
1.	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Common	O
Bawdy-House	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
For	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
in	O
entertaining	O
Lewd	O
Persons	O
therein	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
in	O
Guild-Hall	O
.	O
One	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
saying	O
these	O
words	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
City	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chin	O
in	O
blood	O
for	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
distemper	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
distracted	O
.	O
So	O
his	O
Trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
The	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Charles	O
Gale	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Jones	O
,	O
Henry	O
Tickler	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hodson	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
,	O
Tobias	O
Craddock	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
Ralph	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Ruth	O
Harris	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Turner	O
,	O
Charles	O
Williams	O
,	O
Alice	O
Lagley	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Higgs	O
,	O
Susanna	O
Williams	O
,	O
Ralph	O
Smith	O
,	O
John	O
Barber	O
,	O
William	O
Jones	O
,	O
John	O
Andrews	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Davis	O
,	O
John	O
Pitford	O
was	O
Respited	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
Mary	O
Turner	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Ann	O
Middleton	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Allison	O
,	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mary	O
Easy	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sturtivant	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bowen	O
,	O
Alice	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Roach	O
,	O
Avis	O
Hampsted	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Lyddal	O
,	O
George	O
Clist	O
,	O
John	O
Wilson	O
,	O
John	O
Jackson	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
John	O
Howe	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
Elizabeth	O
White	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bird	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Jordan	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Ingham	O
.	O
Fined	O
,	O
John	O
Ludlam	O
200l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Hugh	O
Hambleton	O
fined	O
200l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Paling	O
fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Alice	O
Langley	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Higgs	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Williams	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
were	O
searcht	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
One	O
Pickering	O
a	O
notorious	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sesions	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
William	O
Canning	O
and	O
Francis	O
Dormer	O
,	O
for	O
dispersing	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Last	O
Declaration	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
Published	O
singly	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
THe	O
Necessity	O
and	O
Advantage	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Victory	O
over	O
Satan	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
Rules	O
for	O
obtaining	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
to	O
an	O
Auditory	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
T	O
Cruso	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
Sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
.	O
The	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
Saviour	O
.	O
The	O
Great	O
Redeemer	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
Mediator	O
.	O
The	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Preaching	O
Christ	O
.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
By	O
Thomas	O
Cole	O
.	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
A	O
Practical	O
Discourse	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Sovereignity	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
ma	O
Points	O
deriving	O
thence	O
,	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
's	O
Hope	O
at	O
Death	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Death-Bed	O
Reflections	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Last	O
Sickness	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Doolittel	O
.	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
A	O
Short	O
Introduction	O
to	O
English	O
Orthography	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
True	O
Spelling	O
.	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
Common	O
Good	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Private	O
Grammer	O
and	O
Writing	O
School	O
in	O
White-Cross-Street	O
.	O
By	O
Richard	O
Mather	O
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
12	O
o	O
.	O
The	O
almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
in	O
some	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
Acts	O
26	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Blow	O
at	O
Prophaneness	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
R.R	O
.	O
Ezekiel	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
London-derry	O
.	O
12	O
o	O
.	O
Those	O
Six	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Leggs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
A	O
true	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
Cruelties	O
and	O
Barbarities	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
upon	O
the	O
Ebglish	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Journal	O
of	O
their	O
Travels	O
from	O
Dinant	O
in	O
Brittany	O
,	O
to	O
Toulon	O
Provence	O
:	O
And	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Situation	O
and	O
Fortifications	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Eminent	O
Towns	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Distance	O
.	O
Of	O
their	O
Prisons	O
and	O
Hospitals	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
died	O
under	O
their	O
Cruelty	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Places	O
of	O
their	O
Deaths	O
and	O
Burials	O
;	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Charity	O
and	O
Sufferings	O
of	O
the	O
Protestants	O
of	O
France	O
;	O
And	O
other	O
Material	O
Things	O
that	O
hapned	O
upon	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
and	O
Impartially	O
performed	O
by	O
Richard	O
Strutton	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Eye-Witness	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fellow-Sufferer	O
.	O
A	O
True	O
and	O
Exact	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Retaking	O
a	O
Ship	O
called	O
The	O
Friend	O
's	O
Adventure	O
of	O
Topsham	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Taken	O
six	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Coasts	O
of	O
France	O
with	O
it	O
four	O
Days	O
;	O
where	O
one	O
Englishman	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
set	O
upon	O
Seven	O
Frenchmen	O
,	O
killed	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Five	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
them	O
safe	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Customs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
amounted	O
to	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Performed	O
and	O
written	O
by	O
Robert	O
Lyde	O
,	O
Mate	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
.	O
The	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warrington	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
at	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Chester	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Letters	O
that	O
concern	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
his	O
Letters	O
.	O
With	O
short	O
notes	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Clearer	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Members	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
In	O
Order	O
to	O
Nevil	O
Pay	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
New	O
,	O
Plain	O
,	O
Short	O
,	O
and	O
Compleat	O
French	O
and	O
English	O
Grammer	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
Learner	O
may	O
attain	O
in	O
few	O
Months	O
to	O
speak	O
and	O
write	O
French	O
correctly	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
do	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
And	O
wherein	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
dark	O
,	O
superfluous	O
and	O
deficient	O
in	O
other	O
Grammars	O
,	O
is	O
plain	O
,	O
short	O
and	O
methodically	O
supplied	O
.	O
Also	O
very	O
useful	O
to	O
Strangers	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
desirous	O
to	O
learn	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
;	O
For	O
whose	O
sake	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Short	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
Exact	O
English	O
Grammar	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
By	O
Peter	O
Berhult	O
.	O
State-Tracts	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Part	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Treatises	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
Privately	O
printed	O
in	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Part	O
consisting	O
of	O
a	O
farther	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Choice	O
Treatises	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1660	O
to	O
1689	O
.	O
Now	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
Body	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
the	O
Revolution	O
and	O
our	O
Happy	O
Settlement	O
under	O
the	O
Auspicious	O
Reign	O
of	O
Their	O
majesties	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Disquisition	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
Nature	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Principles	O
and	O
Method	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
(	O
now	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Peterborough	O
's	O
)	O
Latin	O
Treatise	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
his	O
Consideration	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hobb	O
's	O
Principles	O
put	O
into	O
another	O
Method	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Author	O
's	O
Approbation	O
.	O
Travels	O
into	O
divers	O
parts	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
and	O
Asia	O
,	O
undertaken	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Order	O
to	O
discover	O
a	O
new	O
way	O
by	O
land	O
into	O
China	O
;	O
containing	O
many	O
curious	O
Remarks	O
in	O
Natural	O
Philosophy	O
,	O
Geography	O
,	O
Hydropathy	O
,	O
and	O
History	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
Great	O
Tartary	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
different	O
People	O
who	O
inhabit	O
there	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Supplement	O
extracted	O
from	O
Hakluyt	O
and	O
Purchas	O
;	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
several	O
Journeys	O
over	O
Land	O
from	O
Russia	O
,	O
Persia	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Moguls	O
Countrey	O
in	O
China	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Roads	O
and	O
distances	O
of	O
the	O
places	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Journal	O
.	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Monthly	O
Miscellany	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Consisting	O
of	O
News	O
,	O
History	O
,	O
Philosophy	O
,	O
Poetry	O
,	O
Musick	O
,	O
Translations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Vol	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
June	O
1693	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
Compleat	O
Sets	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
or	O
Single	O
ones	O
,	O
for	O
last	O
Year	O
.	O
These	O
Nine	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
,	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedied	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
false	O
Pretender	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
