TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
KING	O
and	O
QUEEN	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1693.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Winkly	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Swynfin	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Merryddall	I-pers
.	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Stynton	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Dovey	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Huffam	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Munn	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gotobed	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Fynch	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Evanes	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
A	O
Countrey	O
Fellow	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
Taunton	B-place
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Weather-sheep	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
Ham	B-place
Marshes	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
hired	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
Sheep	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
Williams	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Willowes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Winn	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Hawson	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
Instant	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawson	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
slight	O
of	O
hand	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
instead	O
thereof	O
;	O
being	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
swallowed	O
the	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
pincht	O
away	O
the	O
Shooes	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Shoes	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
himself	O
;	O
which	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vessel	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thatcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
Shrove-Tuesday	O
last	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thatcher	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Shop-lifters	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
sharp	O
eye	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
dropt	O
from	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Thatcher	O
verily	O
believed	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
presumption	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Reece	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Welshman	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
them	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Tan-kard	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Wales	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
some	O
Accounts	O
in	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Gager	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
of	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Rumbo	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
maliciously	O
beating	O
and	O
assaulting	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
lay	O
languishing	O
until	O
the	O
30th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
blows	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
Cart	O
at	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Doctors	O
and	O
Apothecaries	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
was	O
much	O
troubled	O
with	O
a	O
shortness	O
of	O
breath	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
some	O
disaffection	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
his	O
Lungs	O
being	O
putrified	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
external	O
hurt	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
So	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
presumed	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
bruises	O
;	O
besides	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
water	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
long	O
a	O
contracting	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
rather	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Emme	B-pers
Woodhall	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
offering	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
false	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
George	I-pers
Van-Eke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Arnold	B-pers
Endrick	I-pers
Van-Nive-Kein	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
living	O
but	O
24	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
numerous	O
Evidence	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
go	O
from	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
absented	O
himself	O
ever	O
since	O
(	O
till	O
now	O
he	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
)	O
without	O
giving	O
notice	O
to	O
his	O
Landlady	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
new	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
resort	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Circumstances	O
gave	O
great	O
suspicion	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
although	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
swear	O
the	O
Fact	O
fully	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
argued	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
that	O
had	O
proved	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
wounded	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
murther	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Joshua	B-pers
Banford	I-pers
his	O
Fellow	O
Soldier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
Person	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
together	O
,	O
quarrelling	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
towards	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
loath	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
coming	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Passes	O
were	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
end	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
Banford	O
dropt	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
Banford	O
when	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
shunn	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Law	O
provides	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
but	O
conceal	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
disgrace	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Woman	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
by	O
Persons	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
no	O
Evidence	O
did	O
affect	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chalwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Arwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Horshooe	B-place
Tavern	I-place
upon	O
Tower-hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
happened	O
to	O
quarrel	O
about	O
warning	O
Soldiers	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
the	O
Lie	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
slap	O
upon	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Decesed	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
give	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
matter	O
special	O
for	O
the	O
Court	O
further	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Albey	I-pers
in	O
Dacus-street	B-place
at	O
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Lute-string	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
escaped	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
witness	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Gamester	O
at	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Burglary	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ingle	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Becket	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kilbeck	B-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10l	O
.	O
a	O
Sugar-Castor	O
,	O
value	O
40.s	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sealy	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Sealy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Splay	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
23l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Atkins	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Thistleworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Theodore	B-pers
Devaux	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
Sir	O
Theodore	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
divers	O
persons	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
disturbed	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
hiding	O
himself	O
under	O
a	O
Heyrick	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Sir	O
Theodore	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Countrey	O
men	O
,	O
with	O
Sir	O
Theodore	O
's	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Brandford	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Thistleworth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
only	O
to	O
lye	O
under	O
the	O
Heyrick	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ellison	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Weather-Sheep	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
apiece	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
near	O
Redriff	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed-chamberin	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
fellow	O
,	O
one	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
20s	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
founnd	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Bay	O
Nag	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
Allen	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
Instant	O
;	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
swopt	O
him	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
near	O
London-Wall	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
Bishop-gate-Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Allegations	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
person	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Little	I-place
Grays-Inn-Lane	I-place
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
secretly	O
Stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beacon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handle	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
Witness	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Swyndall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
16	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
near	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
the	O
Fringe	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Fringe	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Gwynn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Tried	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chase	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Tower-hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Mr	O
Chase	O
having	O
first	O
Treated	O
the	O
said	O
Gwynn	O
at	O
the	O
Tydehouse	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Chase	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
an	O
Oaken	O
Plant	O
,	O
redoubling	O
the	O
blows	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
Mr.	O
Chase	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
dozen	O
blows	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
almost	O
dead	O
,	O
calling	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Chase	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Castor-hat	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owed	O
the	O
said	O
Hacket	O
some	O
small	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
where	O
Hacket	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Peruke	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
favour	O
'd	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
besides	O
Monk	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Symons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
privily	O
Stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
of	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
a	O
Shell-box	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
16d	O
.	O
and	O
7s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Grub-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
till	O
help	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
Excuse	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sealy	I-pers
alias	O
Matthews	B-pers
alias	O
Cooley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
alias	O
Cary	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
(	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
)	O
of	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
four	O
Spoons	O
45s	O
.	O
two	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
22s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
18s	O
.	O
three	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Poynt	O
Head-dressing	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
Sealy	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
all	O
lost	O
:	O
Sealy	O
hired	O
herself	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
she	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Sealy	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Hood	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
actual	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
Two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
East	O
Ardsley	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Ivey	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Married	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
in	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Haslam	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Cohabited	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
by	O
Haslam	O
;	O
the	O
Certificate	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
Minister	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
that	O
corroborated	O
the	O
Matter	O
fully	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Married	O
the	O
said	O
Haslam	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Haslam	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Inn	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
his	O
turn	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Ivey	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
divers	O
Coats	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Ripey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trap	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Strange	O
's	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
who	O
fairly	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
4l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
fairly	O
by	O
the	O
Coats	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Tibbals	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
price	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Mare	O
,	O
price	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
at	O
Mile-end-Green	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Smith	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Nag	O
at	O
Henly	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Mileend	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Smith	O
and	O
he	O
Vouched	O
for	O
one	O
another	O
at	O
Henly	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
presumed	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
honest	O
man	O
's	O
way	O
of	O
dealing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	O
Tibballs	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
(	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
The	O
Mare	O
was	O
valued	O
at	O
3l	O
.	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Fosset	O
's	O
Stable	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
Kingston	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
Tibballs	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
toucht	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
he	O
appealed	O
to	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Voucher	O
Kingston	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Taply	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
Robert	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
's	O
House	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
8s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
Osborne	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
lye	O
still	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Shirt	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Taply	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Stamford-Hill	O
by	O
the	O
Countreymen	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Oaken-stick	O
and	O
a	O
Razor	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Osborne	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Taply	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Names	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Thimble	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
4	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
besides	O
7s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
by	O
the	O
Coals	O
that	O
was	O
rak	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
presently	O
taken	O
at	O
Stamford-hill	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
two	O
Hours	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
such	O
drink	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
upon	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Birts	I-pers
House	O
Widow	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
8d	O
in	O
Money	O
(	O
all	O
the	O
poor	O
Woman	O
had	O
)	O
they	O
having	O
broke	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Quarrels	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
Window	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
after	O
much	O
forcing	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Taylor	O
bound	O
her	O
with	O
Packthread	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
in	O
one	O
Night	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucey	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
of	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Callico	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
Pawned	O
them	O
,	O
having	O
urgent	O
occasion	O
for	O
Money	O
for	O
a	O
Weeks	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
defence	O
she	O
made	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beames	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hurley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
Edward	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
's	O
House	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
Linnens	O
and	O
Woollen	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
neither	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Beames	O
and	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Beames	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
betwixt	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hurley	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Allen	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Linnens	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Pearpoint	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Blue	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burkin	I-pers
,	O
two	O
young	O
Girl	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
in	O
one	O
Indictment	O
for	O
secretly	O
stealing	O
from	O
Esther	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
5s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
Mrs	O
Burnham	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Burkin	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
seen	O
diving	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
conveyed	O
what	O
Money	O
she	O
found	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
tho	O
very	O
young	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoblin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fabyan	I-pers
one	O
Hool	O
's	O
Cato	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
one	O
Terrentius	O
Christianae	O
,	O
a	O
Sententiae	O
Pueriles	O
,	O
one	O
Ovid	O
de	O
Tristibus	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
School-books	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Books	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
coming	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Books	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Books	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
Books	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
besides	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
alias	O
Wade	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Widow	O
four	O
Alamode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Rundlet	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
120l	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
200l	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
for	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Stomach	O
Waters	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Cheese	O
and	O
Waters	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Butler	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Puddle-dock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Rundlet	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Wade	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
Butler	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
alias	O
Sympson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tryed	O
in	O
one	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregories	I-place
;	O
Crouch	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jolly	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
7	O
Bone-Lac	O
'd	O
Cravats	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
276	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
88l	O
.	O
19s	O
.	O
and	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Poynt-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
Croucher	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Dempsey	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Rolph	O
's	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
divided	O
the	O
Spoil	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joanna	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Hanson	O
's	O
House	O
In	O
Black-Fryars	B-place
several	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Filings	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
which	O
were	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
,	O
neither	O
any	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
especially	O
Lee	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
report	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
Mantua	O
's	O
&	O
c	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Ruddyer	I-pers
in	O
Ludgate-Street	B-place
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Remnant	O
to	O
cover	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Amos	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
apprehended	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Uphill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
discouragement	O
of	O
Alehouse-keeper	O
s	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
not	O
sell	O
drink	O
in	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
Uphill	O
's	O
License	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
Captain	O
Winter	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
lately	O
in	O
White-Fryars	B-place
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Chandlor	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
shot	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Blunderbus	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Calf	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Leg	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
1691	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
so	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
Winter	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Chandlor	O
died	O
the	O
7th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews	O
Wardrobe	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
a	O
Mutiny	O
raised	O
in	O
White-Fryars	B-place
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Inner-Temple	O
were	O
offended	O
at	O
a	O
Passage	O
that	O
leads	O
from	O
the	O
Fryars	O
into	O
the	O
Temple	O
Walks	O
,	O
so	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
White-Fryars	O
men	O
opposing	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
sent	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
High	O
Sheriffs	O
of	O
London	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
their	O
Authority	O
to	O
appease	O
the	O
Rout	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
peace	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
a	O
hot	O
Resistance	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
gathered	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
about	O
fourscore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
their	O
Captain	O
and	O
Leader	O
,	O
presenting	O
a	O
Blunderbus	O
against	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
Officers	O
,	O
shooting	O
it	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
Chandlor	O
being	O
unfortunately	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
High-Sheriffs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Winter	O
into	O
the	O
Calf	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
before	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Captain	O
Winter	O
that	O
shot	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Garb	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
White	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Equipage	O
the	O
said	O
Winter	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
all	O
was	O
very	O
clearly	O
and	O
particularly	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Captain	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
urge	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
shot	O
the	O
said	O
Chandlor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
others	O
shot	O
beside	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
point	O
of	O
Law	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
where	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Authority	O
shall	O
be	O
opposed	O
by	O
any	O
Riot	O
,	O
or	O
Riotous	O
Assembly	O
,	O
this	O
implied	O
Malice	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Persons	O
so	O
offending	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
equally	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
consequently	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
shoot	O
Chandlor	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
abet	O
,	O
promote	O
,	O
stir	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
maintain	O
such	O
a	O
Rebellious	O
and	O
Unlawful	O
Assembly	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
considered	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
instant	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
;	O
there	O
being	O
search	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
lost	O
Cock	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Excrement	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
searcht	O
by	O
the	O
Midwives	O
,	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Chil-bearing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
proving	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
naughty	O
wicked	O
Woman	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Dragon	I-place
in	O
Holborn	I-place
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Frazer	O
's	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Sadler	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
fortune	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peregrin	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Kington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Cloke	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
one	O
Story	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
more	O
,	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
before	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Sollicitor	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
.	O
value	O
10s.one	O
Allamode	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
laced	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
Smock	O
12d	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
and	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
House	O
where	O
M	O
-	O
Lodged	O
is	O
near	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
Heaven	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
H	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
's	O
closet	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
both	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
Rubbing-stones	O
,	O
Scales	O
,	O
Weights	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
necessary	O
Utensils	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Ancient	O
Trade	O
of	O
Clipping	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
affect	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
Let	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
possibly	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Clipper	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Clippings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Presley	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Notorious	O
House-breakers	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Morris	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
putting	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brabon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
600l	O
.	O
worth	O
of	O
Plate	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Monteths	O
,	O
value	O
50l	O
.	O
two	O
Basons	O
40l	O
.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
value	O
15l	O
.	O
eight	O
Candlesticks	O
;	O
value	O
18l	O
.	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Chafingdishes	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
seven	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
two	O
Cups	O
6l	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
Chamber-pots	O
10l	O
.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
20l	O
.	O
6	O
Porringers	O
12l	O
.	O
13	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
Gilt	O
4l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
two	O
Sugar-boxes	O
,	O
two	O
Ladles	O
,	O
two	O
Mustard-pots	O
,	O
Pepper-boxes	O
,	O
Skillets	O
,	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Shaggreen	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
11	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
100	O
Guineas	O
,	O
all	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
did	O
amount	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
600l	O
.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sir	O
John	O
Friend	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
four	O
Men	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
causing	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
lye	O
upon	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Presley	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Liquor-pond-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Parish	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
parted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
every	O
one	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
Moors	O
share	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Storton	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
to	O
melt	O
it	O
down	O
first	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Bench	O
Warrant	O
was	O
immediately	O
issued	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
One	O
Tovey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
large	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
one	O
Doyley	O
's	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
laid	O
the	O
Plot	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
Booty	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
first	O
House	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
was	O
Sir	O
John	O
Friend	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
own	O
share	O
and	O
Martin	O
's	O
by	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Friend	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Martin	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
behaving	O
himself	O
very	O
morosely	O
and	O
turbulently	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
for	O
at	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hold	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
.	O
Presly	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
but	O
Tovey	O
positively	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Moor	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Manuing	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ducks	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
;	O
they	O
drove	O
the	O
Ducks	O
out	O
of	O
Coats	O
's	O
Yard	O
into	O
a	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Heads	O
,	O
and	O
sealed	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
it	O
thus	O
:	O
These	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Coats	O
a	O
Yorkshire-man	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
waiting	O
upon	O
their	O
Masters	O
with	O
their	O
Coaches	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
somewhat	O
of	O
Malice	O
appear	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Stuff-gown	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Smith	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
his	O
Examination	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
men	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
Try	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
Charleton	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kene	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
Symon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blisset	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stopping	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
near	O
Acton	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
four	O
men	O
more	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
High-way	O
men	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
again	O
tried	O
upon	O
Coventry	O
's	O
Act	O
,	O
for	O
malicious	O
Maiming	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
disfigure	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
swearing	O
great	O
Oaths	O
,	O
shooting	O
off	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
nine	O
Pistols	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
shot	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Fob-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
another	O
shot	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Middle-finger	O
of	O
his	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
broke	O
it	O
in	O
pieces	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
by	O
the	O
flashing	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
shot	O
one	O
Keeling	B-pers
Baford	I-pers
dead	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
another	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
several	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
two	O
Watermen	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
Westminster	O
about	O
8	O
o	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
the	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
dined	O
there	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
So	O
after	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
consider	O
'd	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Syddings	I-pers
alias	O
Parker	B-pers
alias	O
Abigail	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hall	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
arose	O
from	O
Malice	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
quarrel	O
that	O
happened	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
Women	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Labour	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Church-warden	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
Parish	O
testify	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
their	O
Parish	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Nurse	O
and	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sutton	B-pers
alias	O
Cropper	B-pers
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Hadley	B-place
near	O
Barnet	I-place
,	O
upon	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
(	O
the	O
said	O
Walker	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
six	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
six	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
six	O
Nightroyls	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
three	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
four	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
13l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
did	O
positively	O
Swear	O
,	O
That	O
5	O
Persons	O
,	O
two	O
in	O
Red	O
,	O
two	O
in	O
Blue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fifth	O
in	O
an	O
Iron	O
gray	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
lightish	O
colour	O
'd	O
Periwig	O
,	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
in	O
rifling	O
Baker	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Smocks	O
and	O
Nightroyals	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
in	O
Grey	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
Baker	O
really	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
Sutton	O
take	O
these	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
serve	O
you	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
swore	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
upon	O
Finchly	O
Common	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Grey	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
Sworn	O
by	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
February	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
Boots	O
and	O
Mans	O
Cloths	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sutton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Bed-Chamber	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
till	O
Morning	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
severe	O
Reprimand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
required	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
nor	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
she	O
ever	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sutton	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
Mans	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replyed	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
Wooe	O
a	O
Widow	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lumkin	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Hamley	I-pers
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
he	O
left	O
an	O
old	O
Sute	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
as	O
pawn	O
,	O
with	O
Hamley	O
the	O
Taylor	O
,	O
for	O
5s	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
mend	O
another	O
Black	O
Sute	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stichcome	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
29s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Neal	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
jealous	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Neale	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
above	O
5l	O
.	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
Glostershire	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sir	O
Leonard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
in	O
Hogsden	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
three	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
Mortar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18d	O
.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Dunu	O
of	O
Bednal-Green	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Robberies	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
upon	O
Thom	B-pers
Henslow	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
both	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Acton	O
in	O
the	O
Stage-Coach	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Sun-set	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
5	O
more	O
High-way	O
men	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
Esq	O
;	O
Henslow	O
9s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Knowles	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Val	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
persons	O
robbed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Coach	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Henslow	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Knowles	O
's	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hylton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Baracourt	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Lawful	O
Coine	O
;	O
Lambert	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
found	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Skales	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Files	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Hilton	O
's	O
Bosome	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Files	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Lambert	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Drawer	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
30l	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
them	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
betwixt	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
suspected	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
ill	O
people	O
did	O
resort	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
J-	B-pers
K-	I-pers
were	O
tried	O
likewise	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
their	O
House	O
being	O
Searcht	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
Pick-a-Dilly	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Ticking	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crucible	O
and	O
Melting-pot	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
amazed	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Clippings	O
,	O
when	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
that	O
bore	O
them	O
ill-will	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
diskindness	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Musquets	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
two	O
Musquetoons	O
,	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Warer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Madam	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
in	O
Gravell-Street	B-place
,	O
did	O
let	O
in	O
two	O
Thieves	O
,	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
seized	O
upon	O
Young	O
Mrs	O
Conway	O
and	O
bound	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
throtled	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
disturbed	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
conveying	O
anything	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
hung	O
down	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
dejected	O
manner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dempsey	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mitchell	B-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Tryed	O
singly	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heyrick	I-pers
Coachman	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John-street	I-place
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Coral	O
8s	O
.	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
in	O
Holborn	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Suffling	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Berry	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Clippings	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
whole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Trumpetter	O
Lodged	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Daughter	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
)	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
another	O
young	O
Girl	O
playing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Look	O
what	O
a	O
sight	O
there	O
is	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Trumpetters	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
my	O
Mother	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
disperse	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
mony	O
which	O
was	O
Naught	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
found	O
upon	O
Abbot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Ireland	O
;	O
Abbot	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
Highgate	O
and	O
London	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Islington	O
fields	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
and	O
Citizen	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
and	O
Clippings	O
,	O
besides	O
Shears	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Cripplegate	B-place
Parish	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Swords	O
,	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Charged	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Baroness	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
assisting	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Martin	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
Committed	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
set	O
aside	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
here	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
's	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
two	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Watches	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
brought	O
a	O
Watch	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
hurt	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
diving	O
into	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Bedle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
4	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
16d	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Atkins	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Great	B-place
East-Cheap	I-place
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Lace	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Beames	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Committed	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
under	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
break	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
at	O
Wapping	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
Augres	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
bored	O
holes	O
in	O
the	O
Boards	O
and	O
broke	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
Rope	O
they	O
slided	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
not	O
now	O
Tryed	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Frances	B-pers
Salesbury	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Minister	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
most	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Virulent	O
Libel	O
;	O
Entitled	O
,	O
A	O
Letter	O
sent	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Tillotson	O
several	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
made	O
Publick	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Author	O
has	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Discourse	O
published	O
since	O
in	O
Defence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
which	O
Libel	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
several	O
Malicious	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
Expressions	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
Juries	O
,	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
the	O
Fleet	O
;	O
yea	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
concerned	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
to	O
the	O
Printing	O
Press	O
,	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Salesbury	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Roper	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
Libel	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roper	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Roper	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Libel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Publication	O
in	O
Law	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Salesbury	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Libel	O
in	O
a	O
Penny	O
Post	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bryant	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
22l	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
three	O
Razors	O
.	O
Brandon	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
walking	O
abroad	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
Home	O
the	O
Hair	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Skales	B-pers
6s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beames	I-pers
,	O
who	O
broke	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
is	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Christian	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
falsly	O
Accusing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
some	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Files	O
into	O
Jarvis	O
's	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
others	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Contrivance	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
Beames	O
had	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	O
Jarvis	O
,	O
they	O
combined	O
together	O
to	O
put	O
this	O
Trick	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Beames	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
Sworn	O
,	O
so	O
Beames	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Lad	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute-string	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
17l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
seven	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
broken	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Mistress	O
one	O
Katherine	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
in	O
Warwick-street	B-place
at	O
Charing	I-place
Cross	I-place
of	O
a	O
Poynt	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Pinner	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs	O
Ramsey	O
had	O
again	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rownd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Susan	B-pers
King	I-pers
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
instant	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d.a	O
Scarf	O
8s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
King	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Bucknall	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Spencely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
saying	O
and	O
attesting	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
60000	O
Armed	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Descent	O
into	O
England	O
;	O
the	O
words	O
were	O
spoken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
near	O
Wild-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Commission	O
to	O
Act	O
in	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
36	O
Battalions	O
of	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
65	O
of	O
Horse	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
amounted	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
30000	O
men	O
ready	O
here	O
in	O
England	O
to	O
join	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clegg	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
a	O
Cravat	O
from	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
about	O
20	O
;	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
by	O
Force	O
against	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Midwives	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produced	O
the	O
Warrant	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
her	O
;	O
And	O
his	O
Witness	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
dissolute	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Name	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Companion	O
of	O
Idle	O
and	O
Loose	O
Fellows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
well	O
weighed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Clifford	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Willow	O
,	O
Ann	O
Gaywood	O
,	O
Robert	O
Starkey	O
,	O
John	O
Ogle	O
,	O
Jane	O
Greene	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gardner	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Milton	O
,	O
Martha	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Ann	O
Terry	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sealey	O
,	O
Mary	O
Middleton	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
15	O
.	O
William	O
Read	O
,	O
Reece	O
Powell	O
,	O
John	O
Gold	O
,	O
William	O
Butler	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wayte	O
,	O
Richard	O
Sparks	O
,	O
George	O
Middleton	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
Ellison	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Allen	O
,	O
James	O
Steward	O
,	O
Peregrin	O
Parrot	O
,	O
John	O
Dennis	O
,	O
John	O
Wills	O
,	O
John	O
Clegg	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Walter	O
Stephens	O
,	O
John	O
Symmons	O
,	O
Francis	O
Wynter	O
,	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Burkin	O
,	O
Jane	O
Croucher	O
,	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
,	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
,	O
Robert	O
Beames	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Blunt	O
,	O
Francis	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Edward	O
Tibballs	O
,	O
William	O
Kingston	O
,	O
George	O
Tapley	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Taylor	O
,	O
H	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
William	O
Martin	O
,	O
Robert	O
Presley	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Mansfield	O
.	O
Grace	O
Dempsey	O
,	O
Jane	O
Croucher	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Jon	O
Noble	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hoblin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Carroll	O
,	O
Lucy	O
Whale	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Harwood	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Rownd	O
,	O
Charles	O
Swindale	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Henry	O
Thorncroft	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
and	O
free	O
Pardon	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cambell	O
;	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Gloves	O
after	O
the	O
usual	O
Custom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	O
Burke	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
find	O
Bail	O
for	O
his	O
Appearance	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
one	O
Susannah	O
Higginson	O
of	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Alexander	O
Milbourn	O
for	O
printing	O
a	O
Libel	O
,	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Francis	O
Salisbury	O
was	O
fined	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Ensuing	O
Sessions	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
begin	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
ADVETISEMENTS	O
Liturgia	O
Tigurina	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
and	O
Administration	O
of	O
the	O
Sacraments	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Rites	O
and	O
Ceremonies	O
,	O
usually	O
practised	O
,	O
and	O
solemnly	O
performed	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Churches	O
and	O
Chappels	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Canton	O
of	O
Zurick	O
in	O
Switzerland	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
some	O
other	O
Adjacent	O
Countries	O
;	O
as	O
by	O
their	O
Canons	O
and	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Laws	O
they	O
are	O
Appointed	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
by	O
the	O
Supream	O
Power	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Senate	O
of	O
Zurick	O
they	O
are	O
Authorised	O
,	O
Established	O
,	O
and	O
Commanded	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Orders	O
of	O
that	O
Church	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
translated	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hebraian	O
into	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
by	O
John	O
Conrad	O
Werndly	O
,	O
formerly	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
and	O
Dutch	O
Congregation	O
of	O
Santoff	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Axholme	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
:	O
And	O
now	O
Minister	O
of	O
Wraisbury	O
cum	O
Langley	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Bucks	O
.	O
Bibliotheca	O
Politica	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Discourse	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Dialogue	O
:	O
Being	O
a	O
Continuation	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Discourse	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Antiquity	O
of	O
the	O
Commons	O
in	O
Parliament	O
;	O
wherein	O
the	O
best	O
Authorities	O
for	O
it	O
are	O
proposed	O
and	O
examined	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Entrance	O
upon	O
the	O
Question	O
of	O
Non	O
Resistance	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Third	O
Part	O
.	O
Collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Approved	O
Authors	O
,	O
both	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
.	O
Dialogue	O
the	O
Eighth	O
.	O
Which	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
Second	O
,	O
Third	O
,	O
Fourth	O
,	O
Fifth	O
,	O
Sixth	O
and	O
Seventh	O
Dialogues	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
Lewis	O
of	O
Bourbon	O
,	O
late	O
Prince	O
of	O
Conde	O
.	O
Digested	O
into	O
Annals	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
Curious	O
Remarks	O
on	O
the	O
Transactions	O
of	O
Europe	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
60	O
Years	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
.	O
Memoirs	O
Concerning	O
the	O
Campaign	O
of	O
Three	O
Kings	O
,	O
William	O
,	O
Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
.	O
With	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Great	O
Endeavours	O
of	O
Lewis	O
the	O
14th	O
to	O
effect	O
his	O
Designs	O
,	O
of	O
James	O
the	O
IId	O
.	O
to	O
Remount	O
the	O
Throne	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
proper	O
Methods	O
for	O
the	O
Allies	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
to	O
hinder	O
both	O
.	O
