TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
KING	O
and	O
QUEEN	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1693.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashhurst	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plasted	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Symmonds	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Room	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tranter	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallpoole	I-pers
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pistoll	I-pers
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heames	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hender	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vyncent	I-pers
,	O
ll	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
l.	O
one	O
Laced	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
Mr.	O
White	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Vyncent	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
above	O
five	O
Weeks	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
induced	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
'	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
at	O
Billins-gate	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
except	O
Vincent	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
excused	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Marryiam	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wellings	I-pers
in	O
Exchange-Alley	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
strange	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
The	O
said	O
Wellings	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Welling	O
a	O
Watch	O
as	O
a	O
pawn	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Allen	B-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
containing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
Point	O
Laced-Head	O
dress	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Tippet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Locket	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Moor	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Epsom	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Grace	B-place
Church-street	I-place
the	O
Box	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
young	O
Fellows	O
were	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
person	O
could	O
change	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rippen	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
four	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
at	O
Wilsden	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
five	O
Geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
nine	O
Pullets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
Robert	O
Twyford	O
and	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Chetwood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stood	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goose-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Geese	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
presently	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
proof	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Geese	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
actually	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
Canon	O
's	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Joyers	I-pers
of	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
Hare	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
foreign	O
Story	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
Edward	B-pers
Brumbrick	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
20	O
l.	O
4	O
Serge	O
Coats	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
Necklace	O
10	O
s.	O
12	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
by	O
direction	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who-said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
swear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dead	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
silent	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Brumbrick	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Chappel	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Murrall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Night-Royl	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
John	O
Norris	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night-Royl	O
was	O
found	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
suddenly	O
stopt	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
Murrall	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
Norris	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
that	O
Norris	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Cabrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
of	O
six	O
Fur	O
Caps	O
,	O
val	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
presently	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Studdart	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shed	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Button	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
Studdart	O
sold	O
the	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
Carter	O
,	O
but	O
Carter	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
Studdart	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
contradicted	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
part	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Whalebone	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Lawr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harbord	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Allinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Blood-stone	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Breames	I-pers
,	O
Arnold	B-pers
Breames	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
in	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
JohnBreams	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
their	O
Majesties	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
what	O
a	O
barbarous	O
and	O
cruel	O
Murther	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stood	O
accused	O
of	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
)	O
found	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
demeaning	O
themselves	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
disorderly	O
manner	O
,	O
swearing	O
great	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Constable	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chair	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
three	O
men	O
swear	O
one	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
Damn	O
em	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
next	O
man	O
they	O
met	O
;	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
murther	O
was	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
persons	O
that	O
threatned	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
they	O
met	O
;	O
another	O
(	O
viz	O
)	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
one	O
Bill	O
,	O
that	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
admittance	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Hutton	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
his	O
Windows	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Breames	O
first	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stuck	O
his	O
Sword	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Sword	O
sticking	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
soon	O
stopt	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mrs.	O
Hutton	O
was	O
hanging	O
,	O
about	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
,	O
John	O
Breames	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
thrust	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
's	O
Body	O
8	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
stuck	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
himself	O
.	O
Thus	O
far	O
was	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
)	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
Report	O
of	O
their	O
former	O
behaviour	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
equally	O
ingaged	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
:	O
but	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Breames	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Hutton	O
the	O
fatal	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
given	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
very	O
distinctly	O
,	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
considerate	O
about	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
consequence	O
:	O
so	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Breames	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Edwards	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
Husbands	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
named	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Duke-place	I-place
;	O
the	O
second	O
was	O
one	O
Sebastian	B-pers
Judges	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
swore	O
it	O
plainly	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
married	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
besides	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
Judges	O
but	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
stayed	O
8	O
days	O
with	O
Adams	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
which	O
made	O
four	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
advised	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
safely	O
marry	O
another	O
Husband	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
convicted	O
before	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
Husbands	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
idle	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Slut	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
could	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trapps	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
upon	O
Henry	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hawtrey	I-pers
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
persons	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hawtrey	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
between	O
Stratford	O
and	O
Illford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hawtrey	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
High-waymen	O
that	O
assaulted	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
further	O
trouble	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
refer	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bullymore	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wether-sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pinchbank	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
stuck	O
the	O
Sheep	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wether-sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
of	O
Islington	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Islington	B-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Sheep	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
necessity	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hankin	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
be	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
)	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
val	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Brampton	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Charter-house	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
about	O
a	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
laid	O
a	O
wager	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
about	O
the	O
Shilling	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
one	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
a	O
paper	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
so	O
much	O
suspicion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
rambling	O
foreign	O
Story	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Clippings	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
that	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
somewhere	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
under	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Witness	O
that	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Clippings	O
;	O
yet	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
kneeling	O
down	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
God	O
I	O
may	O
never	O
come	O
here	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
steal	O
two	O
Barrow	O
Hogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Sow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
;	O
A	O
Butcher	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Hogs	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
William	O
Mayne	O
,	O
beyond	O
High-gate	O
with	O
the	O
Hogs	O
driving	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bargained	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
31	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
William	O
Mayne	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
the	O
Hogs	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Levingston	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
)	O
deposed	O
;	O
First	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
at	O
Tennis	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
distaste	O
was	O
taken	O
amongst	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
Buckle	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemens	O
Hats	O
,	O
which	O
increased	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
heighth	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Lord	O
Peterborough	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
wet	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
dead	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
only	O
breathed	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
by	O
leaping	O
over	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
water	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-ferry	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Prescot-street	O
;	O
he	O
declared	O
also	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
misfortune	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
night	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
played	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
)	O
very	O
good	O
friends	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
's	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Downing	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
him	O
where	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
Leger	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Levingstone	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
Field	O
about	O
Cupid	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
Leger	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
M.	O
Howard	O
calls	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
aside	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
whisper	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
led	O
him	O
a	O
dance	O
about	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
Leger	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
combined	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Levingstone	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
wave	O
the	O
fighting	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
still	O
urged	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
received	O
the	O
wound	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
had	O
several	O
wounds	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
above	O
an	O
inch	O
deep	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
slant	O
wound	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
kill	O
'd	O
too	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Levingston	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
quality	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
necessities	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
M.	O
Levingston	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
known	O
to	O
carry	O
himself	O
disrespectfullytowards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
favour	O
of	O
malice	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hulk	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Menfas	I-pers
in	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
they	O
were	O
tampering	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Bar	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Menfas	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
rose	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
mist	O
of	O
their	O
intended	O
Prize	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
Michaelmas-day	O
last	O
;	O
First	O
upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
;	O
Esq	O
;	O
Secondly	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Riding	O
to	O
Chelsey	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
accompanied	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Ladies	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
three	O
Persons	O
(	O
having	O
their	O
Faces	O
covered	O
with	O
Vizard	O
Masks	O
)	O
met	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
all	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
)	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
,	O
commanded	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
stand	O
,	O
demanded	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
readily	O
gave	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ruler	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Pencil	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
Five	O
Mathematical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Magnifying	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
these	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
were	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Hatband	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
Robbed	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
Masked	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
conjured	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Civil	O
to	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
Affright	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
demeanour	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
my	O
Lady	O
Pepys	O
saved	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
particular	O
Instrument	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
him	O
Sir	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
are	O
we	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
to	O
Morrow	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
there	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
did	O
send	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
left	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
sollicited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Purse	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
upon	O
this	O
design	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Witness	O
shifted	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
under	O
some	O
pretence	O
of	O
an	O
accidental	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
immediately	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
stop	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
pulled	O
off	O
their	O
Masks	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
feat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
their	O
Faces	O
plainly	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
let	O
them	O
the	O
Horses	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Three	O
Horses	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
Michaelmas-day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
Hired	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
returned	O
back	O
about	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Westminster	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
had	O
a	O
Pencil	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
his	O
Pencil	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
elsewhere	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hoyle	O
urged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Sworn	O
against	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Malice	O
that	O
was	O
ingrafted	O
in	O
the	O
bosome	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
that	O
happened	O
betwixt	O
them	O
about	O
beating	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
Physick	O
;	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
neither	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
nor	O
Child	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
mounted	O
the	O
Guard	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Corporal	O
to	O
declare	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
presumed	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Pistols	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Flanders	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
very	O
distinctly	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Ship	O
Masts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
which	O
he	O
Stole	O
from	O
off	O
Mr	O
King	O
's	O
Wharf	B-place
at	I-place
Horslie-Down	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
a	O
Waterman	O
Stole	O
the	O
Masts	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Convey	O
them	O
to	O
Queenhithe	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
story	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Heyden	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Cow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Brown	O
Cow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
;	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
168	O
Pound	O
of	O
Salt	O
Butter	O
,	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Hazzard	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Wooden	O
Firkins	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Highmas	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
(	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
near	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
containing	O
in	O
it	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Clipping	O
Instruments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Room	O
(	O
one	O
Johnson	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Searchers	O
came	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
him	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sherwin	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
his	O
Shears	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Tools	O
in	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Tyn	O
man	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
attested	O
by	O
his	O
Landlady	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Shears	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Moon	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whilest	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
busy	O
waiting	O
on	O
other	O
Guests	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
too	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
Smith	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
.	O
Moon	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
him	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Ale	O
house	O
at	O
Newgate	B-place
Lane	I-place
end	O
going	O
to	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
9	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
One	O
Clare	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
also	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Now	O
there	O
was	O
Malice	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Arrested	O
North	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Kill	O
and	O
Murder	O
one	O
Bryant	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Ryley	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
Monmouth	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
presently	O
after	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
their	O
Acquaintance	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
;	O
and	O
Harding	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
Urwin	O
was	O
Sober	O
;	O
and	O
Harding	O
told	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
wounded	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Ryley	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
Harding	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Man	O
offered	O
some	O
Clipt-money	O
for	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Jaume	O
of	O
a	O
Chymny	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
a	O
Thumb-stall	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt-money	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
only	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
one	O
James	O
Wats	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Innocency	O
:	O
And	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
lived	O
but	O
three	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Rossington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Fownes	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Buttock	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
14	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
May	B-place
Pole	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
following	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
deceased	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Nov.last	O
was	O
twelve	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
enough	O
to	O
hang	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
askt	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
Bullied	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Spanish	O
Tuck	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
palm	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Glove	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Friends	O
to	O
forgive	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
,	O
altho	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
barbarously	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
Sword	O
whilst	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
some	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fowens	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Quarreling	O
;	O
others	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
Mr	O
Fownes	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
that	O
degree	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
one	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
about	O
paying	O
a	O
Coach	O
one	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
distinctly	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
find	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
,	O
did	O
Bully	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
did	O
make	O
the	O
first	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fownes	O
had	O
a	O
spight	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
provoke	O
him	O
;	O
why	O
then	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Facey	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
A	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Loftus	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Foot-boy	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
for	O
her	O
Clogs	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
cleaned	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
)	O
as	O
was	O
expected	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
justifying	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
corrected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
gave	O
ill	O
Language	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
with	O
Madam	O
A	O
-	O
into	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
fell	O
a	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgions	O
gave	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fracture	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Depression	O
upon	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clod	O
of	O
Blood	O
which	O
prest	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spirits	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
free	O
motion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
A	O
-	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
misfortune	O
;	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
troubled	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
befallen	O
any	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
his	O
former	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
A	O
-	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
particularly	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
11	O
years	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
struck	O
him	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
because	O
his	O
Son	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
serve	O
him	O
before	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Persons	O
of	O
great	O
Quality	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
Mr.	O
A	O
-	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
serene	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
sedate	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Conversation	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
Penalty	O
due	O
to	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Michael	B-pers
Lance	I-pers
of	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Head	O
dress	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
Lodged	O
in	O
Lance	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Husband	O
being	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
Wife	O
did	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
Coertion	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Tryal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
robbing	O
James	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
full	O
proof	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
as	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sampson	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Patrick	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
:	O
One	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
William	O
Rock	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
Wheat	O
;	O
but	O
Rock	O
had	O
good	O
witness	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
Pointer	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashdowns	I-pers
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
discover	O
where	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
his	O
Mare	O
again	O
;	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
old	O
Proverb	O
is	O
)	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
29	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
at	O
Westminster	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	O
Weekes	O
Swore	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
presently	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
Two	O
Smoothing	O
Irons	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty-Larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdeameanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
Falsly	O
and	O
Maliciously	O
did	O
pretend	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Authority	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Trenchard	I-pers
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
certain	O
Places	O
,	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
Store-keeper	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Roger	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Land-waiters	O
Place	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
30	O
Guineas	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Blunt	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
;	O
he	O
further	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Trenchard	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
35	O
Places	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Trenchard	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Hand	O
and	O
Seal	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
?	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Original	O
has	O
John	O
Trenchard	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Sealed	O
;	O
the	O
words	O
of	O
it	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
;	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
Order	O
you	O
immediately	O
upon	O
sight	O
hereof	O
,	O
to	O
cause	O
your	O
present	O
Storekeepers	O
to	O
Rule	O
their	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
of	O
your	O
Land-waiters	O
,	O
having	O
others	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
their	O
places	O
.	O
Signed	O
,	O
J.	O
Trenchard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Trenchard	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cheat	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Committed	O
for	O
so	O
great	O
and	O
notorious	O
Offence	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdeameanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Frize-coat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Haward	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
in	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
Cup	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
she	O
hid	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Serfant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
:	O
Taking	O
away	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillow-bear	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Mantua	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mrs.	O
Whitaker	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
lockt	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
unwilling	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
did	O
affect	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bickerstaff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
affrighted	O
by	O
some	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
shelter	O
:	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wiggin	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
Seven	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
;	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Batson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
Napkins	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Racey	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
Brown	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Racey	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
Mantua	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Collingwood	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Collingwood	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Brown	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Fellowes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Thomazin	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Felony	O
Judith	O
Fellowes	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
Gale	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
Pynes	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Fellowes	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
swear	O
against	O
Gale	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Squibb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
five	O
Dowlace	O
Cloths	O
val	O
7	O
s.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
val	O
25	O
s.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew's-Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nag	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
one	O
Barrom	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Soldier	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Phillis	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
alone	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Springall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Springet	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Springall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Springet	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Filings	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sybey	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
;	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Casbert	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Broker's-Shop	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Ticket	O
made	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
good	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
impudently	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather-Sheep	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pynchbank	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
Price	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Wyllowbey	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Ansty	I-pers
of	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellyot	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
;	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Leesly	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Chellingworth	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
unto	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Now	O
follows	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
famous	O
Newsmonger	O
,	O
(	O
so	O
publickly	O
known	O
both	O
in	O
City	O
and	O
Countrey	O
)	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Composing	O
,	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
False	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
News	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Enemies	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
hearts	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Loyal	O
Subjects	O
from	O
their	O
Duty	O
and	O
Obedience	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
Bail	O
'd	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
sworn	O
to	O
Try	O
the	O
Issue	O
,	O
the	O
Proceeding	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
read	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
be	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
evil	O
affected	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
an	O
evil	O
disposition	O
,	O
maliciously	O
minding	O
and	O
intending	O
Sedition	O
to	O
raise	O
and	O
stir	O
up	O
among	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
Compose	O
,	O
Write	O
,	O
and	O
Publish	O
four	O
most	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libels	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
Words	O
;	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
Letter	O
,	O
The	O
Shallops	O
or	O
Well-Boats	O
which	O
have	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
diligence	O
been	O
fitted	O
out	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
up	O
again	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stores	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
ashore	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Letter	O
,	O
The	O
States	O
of	O
Amsterdam	O
have	O
made	O
their	O
Complaint	O
in	O
the	O
Assembly	O
of	O
the	O
States	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
condition	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
of	O
the	O
States	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
demand	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fleet	O
of	O
the	O
States	O
may	O
no	O
more	O
act	O
in	O
conjunction	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
Holland	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
prest	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
incline	O
the	O
other	O
Towns	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
which	O
't	O
is	O
believed	O
they	O
will	O
never	O
consent	O
to	O
till	O
France	O
is	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
lower	O
Estate	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Letter	O
,	O
Some	O
French	O
Privateers	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
since	O
landed	O
some	O
men	O
at	O
Altam	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
some	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Farmers	O
Daughters	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
soon	O
put	O
on	O
shore	O
again	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Letter	O
,	O
The	O
States	O
of	O
Amsterdam	O
are	O
still	O
of	O
the	O
sentiment	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Fleet	O
of	O
70	O
Men	O
of	O
War	O
at	O
Sea	O
next	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
act	O
apart	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
writing	O
those	O
scandalous	O
Reports	O
,	O
he	O
writ	O
another	O
Letter	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
now	O
Indicted	O
)	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
having	O
received	O
fresh	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
reflected	O
upon	O
by	O
scandalous	O
Scriblers	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictments	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
all	O
this	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
Coffee-men	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Letters	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
writ	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
himself	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
was	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
by	O
his	O
immediate	O
Order	O
sent	O
abroad	O
and	O
published	O
.	O
To	O
contradict	O
this	O
Charge	O
against	O
Mr	O
Dyer	O
,	O
his	O
Counsel	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
two	O
sorts	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Shallops	O
or	O
Well-boats	O
were	O
so	O
laid	O
up	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
:	O
The	O
second	O
was	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
very	O
well	O
affected	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
for	O
ought	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
found	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
write	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
very	O
ill	O
resented	O
the	O
Imprisonment	O
of	O
the	O
Bishops	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
irregular	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Reign	O
;	O
(	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
)	O
:	O
But	O
then	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
demonstration	O
of	O
his	O
Loyalty	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
200	O
l.	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
What	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
so	O
do	O
many	O
others	O
(	O
that	O
perhaps	O
,	O
are	O
no	O
Friends	O
nor	O
Well-wishers	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
)	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
benefit	O
they	O
receive	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
so	O
honest	O
as	O
he	O
hoped	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Court	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
very	O
distinctly	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
men	O
of	O
unbiass	O
'd	O
Principles	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
easily	O
be	O
wrought	O
upon	O
)	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
he	O
was	O
troubled	O
at	O
the	O
Imprisonment	O
of	O
the	O
Bishops	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
any	O
man	O
might	O
be	O
and	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
be	O
disaffected	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
how	O
sensible	O
the	O
Bishops	O
were	O
of	O
their	O
Troubles	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
known	O
too	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
acted	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
a	O
great	O
Defection	O
they	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
altho	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Friend	O
formerly	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
against	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
his	O
pretences	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
tended	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
weakning	O
of	O
this	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
States	O
of	O
Holland	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
their	O
Fleet	O
go	O
out	O
another	O
year	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
consequence	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
behoved	O
them	O
to	O
consider	O
well	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
believed	O
(	O
from	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
)	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Offence	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Noted	O
High-way	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
abroad	O
who	O
shot	O
the	O
Constable	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
once	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
;	O
was	O
now	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Henry	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawtrey	I-pers
between	O
Stradford	O
and	O
Illford	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Good	O
Services	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
since	O
his	O
Confinement	O
;	O
giving	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
the	O
Contents	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
must	O
expect	O
no	O
mercy	O
here	O
;	O
withal	O
exhorting	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
mind	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
another	O
World	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
Marryham	O
Hatley	O
,	O
William	O
Heyden	O
,	O
Ann	O
Chellingworth	O
,	O
Katharine	O
Moor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Vyncent	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Ann	O
Willowbey	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pritchard	O
Edward	O
Brumbrick	O
,	O
John	O
Bullymore	O
,	O
John	O
Allen	O
,	O
John	O
Powell	O
,	O
James	O
Levingston	O
,	O
Francis	O
Rossington	O
,	O
Edward	O
Prince	O
,	O
John	O
Wiggen	O
,	O
Prudence	O
Shorter	O
,	O
Alice	O
Jones	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Pember	O
,	O
Mary	O
Evanes	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Brown	O
,	O
Judith	O
Fellowes	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Dent	O
,	O
Ann	O
Duck	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Ellyott	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Mary	O
Rippen	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Powell	O
,	O
William	O
Truman	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
16	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Turner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Harris	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stokes	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Chappell	O
,	O
James	O
Benn	O
,	O
John	O
Sybey	O
,	O
Joan	O
Brown	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Stacey	O
,	O
John	O
Breames	O
,	O
Arnold	O
Breames	O
,	O
Richard	O
Kelsey	O
,	O
William	O
Trapps	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hoyle	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
John	O
Urwin	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Fined	O
.	O
John	O
Dyer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
was	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
40	O
Marks	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
continue	O
to	O
write	O
News-Letters	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
James	O
Perkins	O
was	O
fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-end	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Maypole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
next	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
,	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
F	O
Rabelais	O
,	O
MD	O
or	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Heroic	O
Deeds	O
and	O
Savings	O
of	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantagruel	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
by	O
Sir	O
Tho	O
.	O
Urchard	O
.	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
large	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Work	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
particularly	O
an	O
Explication	O
of	O
the	O
must	O
difficult	O
Passages	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
publish	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
Language	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
Whereas	O
Proposals	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
Printing	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
Third	O
and	O
Fourth	O
Volumes	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Book	O
of	O
Martyrs	O
,	O
or	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Famous	O
Edict	O
of	O
Nantes	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Subscription	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
with	O
the	O
First	O
lately	O
published	O
,	O
Compleat	O
the	O
Work	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
therefore	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
that	O
expect	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
these	O
Proposals	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
send	O
in	O
their	O
Payment	O
before	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
next	O
,	O
for	O
after	O
that	O
Day	O
no	O
Subscription	O
shall	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
Proposals	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Undertaker	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
most	O
Booksellers	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
the	O
Countrey	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Eliot	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Preacher	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
to	O
the	O
Indians	O
in	O
America	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Wonderful	O
Success	O
which	O
the	O
Gospel	O
has	O
had	O
amongst	O
the	O
Heathen	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Bishop	O
Barlow	O
's	O
Remains	O
:	O
Containing	O
near	O
an	O
Hundred	O
distinct	O
Subjects	O
,	O
Theological	O
,	O
Philosophical	O
,	O
Historical	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Letters	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Quality	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Resolution	O
of	O
many	O
abstruse	O
Points	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Directions	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Divine	O
for	O
his	O
Study	O
of	O
Divinity	O
and	O
Choice	O
of	O
his	O
Library	O
.	O
Published	O
from	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Original	O
Papers	O
.	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Library	O
Vol	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Containing	O
an	O
Histoaical	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Choicest	O
Books	O
Newly	O
Printed	O
in	O
England	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Foreign	O
Journals	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
The	O
State	O
of	O
Learning	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Continued	O
Monthly	O
.	O
This	O
for	O
July	O
,	O
August	O
,	O
September	O
,	O
October	O
and	O
November	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
W.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
These	O
Four	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Patience	O
and	O
Balm	O
of	O
Gilead	O
under	O
all	O
Afflictions	O
,	O
an	O
Appendix	O
to	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Contentment	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
The	O
whole	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Impression	O
with	O
Additional	O
Prayers	O
suitable	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Mary	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Bibles	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
1694	O
.	O
LIFE	O
,	O
Reign	O
and	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Mary	O
Queen	O
of	O
Scots	O
,	O
stitched	O
.	O
Folio	O
.	O
A	O
Demonstration	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Applications	O
of	O
the	O
Apocalypse	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
Ancient	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
fourth	O
Beast	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Daniel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Beast	O
in	O
the	O
Revelations	O
.	O
By	O
Drue	O
Cressener	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
4	O
to	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart-work	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel-minister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Annesley	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
things	O
not	O
seen	O
:	O
Or	O
divers	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
concerning	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Holy	O
men	O
after	O
Death	O
:	O
By	O
that	O
eminently	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Tongue	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr	O
Cary	O
against	O
Infant-Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
Mr	O
John	O
Flavell	O
's	O
Remains	O
being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
;	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Dev	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
layer	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
and	O
Repentance	O
;	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broadstreet	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
.	O
The	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Saviour	O
of	O
his	O
People	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
Mediator	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Cole	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
Christus	O
in	O
Corde	O
:	O
Of	O
the	O
Mystical	O
Union	O
between	O
Christ	O
and	O
Believers	O
considered	O
in	O
its	O
resemblances	O
,	O
bonds	O
,	O
seals	O
,	O
priviledges	O
and	O
marks	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
government	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
Spirit	O
:	O
Being	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
divers	O
Sermons	O
,	O
from	O
Eph	O
.	O
6.15.	O
and	O
Prov	O
.	O
6.23.	O
lately	O
preached	O
by	O
John	O
Faldo	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Learned	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Burwash	O
in	O
Sussex	O
.	O
These	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Leggs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
An	O
Eslay	O
concerning	O
Obedience	O
to	O
the	O
Supream	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Subjects	O
in	O
all	O
Revolutions	O
With	O
some	O
Consideration	O
touching	O
the	O
present	O
Juncture	O
of	O
Affairs	O
.	O
A	O
Compendious	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Taxes	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Opporestive	O
Methods	O
of	O
Raising	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
An	O
Impartial	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Advantages	O
and	O
Losses	O
that	O
England	O
hath	O
received	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
War	O
with	O
France	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Ric	O
.	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
In	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Door	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
(	O
hindring	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Cure	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Parts	O
,	O
Scabes	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
:	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
bath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundred	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
Lower	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
and	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
false	O
Pretender	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
