TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
KING	O
AND	O
QUEENS	O
COMMISSIONS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayley	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashhurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rudger	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Longbridge	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Keates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rollstone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Moorwood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hummerstone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cleeve	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Spencer	B-pers
Isles	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Minsham	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
Arrainged	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Mantua	O
12d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Dust	O
Gown	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Arrainged	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Crooked-lane	I-place
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
one	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
Shifts	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Peak	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Point	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
a	O
Seal	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
Baronet	O
;	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
at	O
Oxford	B-place
,	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Assize	O
Sermon	O
Another	O
Witness	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
a	O
Watchmaker	O
in	O
Guildhall-yard	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Fathers	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Doncaster	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Landlord	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
would	O
testify	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
his	O
Landlord	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
such	O
Account	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Owen	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bonelace	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
16s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
where	O
her	O
Maid	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
some	O
Lace	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
shifted	O
the	O
Lace	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
rising	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Lace	O
dragg	O
'd	O
after	O
her	O
:	O
however	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
followed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
in	O
Castle-Alley	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Lace	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Person	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
Credit	O
;	O
yet	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
the	O
Lace	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
F-	B-pers
L-	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
P-	B-pers
L-	I-pers
and	O
E-	B-pers
P-	I-pers
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thare	I-pers
of	O
60l	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Linen-Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
20l	O
weight	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Yarn	O
,	O
3l	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Thare	O
's	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
honestly	O
of	O
one	O
Cooper	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
L-	O
was	O
strongly	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
yet	O
none	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
discharged	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
of	O
4l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
M	O
Shuttleworth	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Knight-Rider's-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
lookt	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
were	O
standing	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
playing	O
with	O
Farthings	O
amongst	O
some	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
quite	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
taxed	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
O	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
challenge	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
says	O
Shuttleworth	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
Seeing	O
him	O
appear	O
so	O
fine	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
so	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
they	O
did	O
all	O
juggle	O
together	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
instant	O
:	O
They	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
lived	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
got	O
away	O
in	O
picking	O
the	O
said	O
Shuttleworth	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
commmonly	O
called	O
Tom	O
the	O
Dyer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
tried	O
for	O
his	O
life	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
;	O
was	O
now	O
indicted	O
again	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
50s	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Curson	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Ram-Ally	B-place
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Allen	O
behind	O
,	O
so	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
presently	O
mist	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Cup	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
for	O
himself	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Carson	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
trouble	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
abuse	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Edmund	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
Six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
died	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Silk	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
Barge	O
at	O
George-yard	B-place
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
so	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Barge	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
the	O
Well-stern	O
,	O
half	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Barge	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
only	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Well-stern	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Diers	O
man	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
Barge	O
but	O
him	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
one	O
Bridget	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
aged	O
8	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
and	O
abuse	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
and	O
consent	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gerrard	O
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
swore	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ravished	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
striving	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
stopt	O
her	O
breath	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
declared	O
upon	O
her	O
oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
search	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
sad	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
by	O
those	O
natural	O
Symptoms	O
that	O
are	O
incident	O
to	O
Women	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Gerrard	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
penetration	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Body	O
in	O
their	O
opinion	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Testimony	O
of	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
when	O
first	O
searcht	O
:	O
They	O
did	O
all	O
concur	O
,	O
both	O
Midwife	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
abused	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
very	O
sensibly	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
set	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
betwixt	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
breath	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pulled	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
run	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Body	O
with	O
his	O
Yard	O
:	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
,	O
an	O
eminent	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
his	O
Opinion	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
not	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
approached	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Clap	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Rape	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
preferr	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
tried	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
from	O
one	O
Mountague	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
The	O
Stockins	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Wood	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Scarfs	O
for	O
a	O
Funeral	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
pretended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Confederates	O
in	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
Smith	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
positive	O
against	O
Harrison	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Knight	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
;	O
Widow	O
Marsh	O
and	O
Miller	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
Howards	O
House	O
in	O
Seacole	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
Drink	O
and	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Tankard	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
argued	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
the	O
Woman	O
any	O
wrong	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Miller	O
was	O
fellow	O
Soldier	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
so	O
meeting	O
him	O
accidentally	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Syms	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitchingman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Doe-skin	O
Doublet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
being	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Journyman	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Kitchenman	O
's	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Buttons	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
several	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
a	O
Partition	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
between	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Kitchenman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
crept	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
all	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boy	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swynam	I-pers
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
deal	O
Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
one	O
Gown	O
4l	O
.	O
one	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
4l	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Box	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Sudbury	O
Coach	O
by	O
Carter	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Cooper	O
helpt	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Church-Lane	O
by	O
Stepney	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
William	O
Carter	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Cooper	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
stifly	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
though	O
but	O
young	O
Youths	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
against	O
Christian	O
Carter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Craw	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchenson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
24	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchenson	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Arraign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
Yards	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
Arraign	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
of	O
Westm	B-place
.	I-place
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
two	O
Table	O
cloths	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Buttons	O
was	O
rubbed	O
off	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
putting	O
back	O
the	O
Bolts	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
as	O
much	O
New	O
Linen	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
pay	O
above	O
5l	O
for	O
:	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Button	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Ogleby	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
were	O
but	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
40	O
False	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
for	O
making	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Metal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Wild	O
's	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Cherry-Tree	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Brass	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Brass	O
Clippings	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
False	O
money	O
spread	O
upon	O
the	O
Excrement	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Brass	O
money	O
all	O
Clipt	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Seale	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jesson	I-pers
,	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Stephens	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Service	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Stephens	O
was	O
to	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
whilst	O
Seal	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
stampt	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Under	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
several	O
Blank	O
Halfcrowns	O
unkempt	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
False	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blows	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
by	O
some	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Stephen	O
's	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
clipt	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
naught	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
of	O
False	O
Metal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Witness	O
against	O
them	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
Clip	O
or	O
Coin	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
Witness	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Stamp	O
to	O
Coin	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Seale	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
get	O
him	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
some	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
work	O
.	O
Wild	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
Let	O
his	O
Cellar	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Seale	O
to	O
make	O
Spurrs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Clipping	O
or	O
Coining	O
,	O
calling	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Edg	O
'd	O
Tools	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
being	O
shut	O
up	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
Arrested	O
for	O
Debt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
Report	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
said	O
some	O
for	O
Stephens	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
for	O
ought	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
saw	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
actually	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Clipping	O
or	O
Coining	O
Trade	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Crimes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Making	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
several	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Pewter	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
Five	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Clipping	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stuck	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bees-wax	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
False	O
Metal	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
Shoes	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
good	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Bees-wax	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peny	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
making	O
20	O
Shillings	O
of	O
False	O
and	O
Unlawful	O
Metal	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Garret	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
rubbing	O
an	O
Halfcrown	O
between	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Powder	O
the	O
Clippers	O
have	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
smooth	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Halfcrowns	O
that	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
ready	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
besides	O
a	O
Coining	O
Press	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Screws	O
,	O
Molds	O
and	O
Flasks	O
,	O
with	O
melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
Scissers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
several	O
Halfcrowns	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
False	O
Metal	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
full	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
undone	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
melting	O
Pot	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
things	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
fit	O
for	O
working	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alleg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
one	O
William	O
Peny	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coining	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Greenford	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
maliciously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
48	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24s	O
two	O
Lamb	O
Pies	O
2s	O
.	O
an	O
Applepye	O
1s	O
two	O
Bollard	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Windred	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Lamb-sack	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
first	O
was	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
his	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Doors	O
and	O
his	O
Windows	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
broke	O
into	O
a	O
Buttery	O
where	O
the	O
Bacon	O
and	O
the	O
Pies	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
got	O
three	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
watch	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flatly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Brandford	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
It	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J-	B-pers
B-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
maliciously	O
and	O
wilfully	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Horse-pond	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
water	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
,	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
cast	O
into	O
a	O
Horse-pond	O
,	O
near	O
Woodmonger	B-place
's	I-place
Hall	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Armpits	O
in	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
B-	O
had	O
cast	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
Pale	O
of	O
water	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
as	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Stables	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Women	O
,	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Frazier	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Frazier	O
declared	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
B-	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
very	O
ill	O
upon	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
oftentimes	O
had	O
Fits	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Affright	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Disease	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
others	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
healthy	O
Woman	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
that	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
Frazier	O
swore	O
that	O
B-	O
threatened	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
by	O
the	O
swing	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
cried	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
B-	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ruined	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
buried	O
without	O
any	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Frazier	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
reference	O
,	O
and	O
Frazier	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Searchers	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
again	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
hurt	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
others	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Pond	O
lay	O
shelving	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
easy	O
matter	O
for	O
any	O
person	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Pond	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Fudling	O
and	O
Tipling	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
things	O
put	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
weighed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
his	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Dowtey	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
wives	O
;	O
one	O
he	O
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bowe	O
,	O
namely	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Suddrey	I-pers
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
Marriage	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
namely	O
Ann	B-pers
Padle	I-pers
,	O
he	O
married	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
Chappel	I-place
;	O
which	O
was	O
evidenced	O
by	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Certificate	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clerk	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Others	O
proved	O
their	O
Cohabiting	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
Sarah	O
Suddrey	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Lawful	O
Wife	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
but	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
Why	O
he	O
would	O
marry	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
two	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ayliffe	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
His	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Change	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
few	O
Filings	O
of	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Working-room	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
Beams	O
for	O
Skales	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
abundance	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
35s	O
.	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Bit	O
of	O
Silver	O
was	O
found	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
Sheers	O
,	O
besides	O
Files	O
,	O
Thumb-stalls	O
,	O
Skales	O
,	O
Sheers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
evidenced	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Ayliffe	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
body	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Make	O
all	O
fast	O
above	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Utensils	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheers	O
were	O
ready	O
mounted	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
procured	O
some	O
persons	O
to	O
speak	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
nor	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clipper	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
well	O
satisfi	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thorp	O
swore	O
that	O
Hancock	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Attorney	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sweetapple	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
a	O
Judgement	O
in	O
the	O
Common	O
pleas	O
for	O
5140l	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
practice	O
such	O
Tricks	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
names	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
Concern	O
upon	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Scrivener	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Attorney	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Affadavits	O
annext	O
,	O
sworn	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Treby	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
an	O
Attorny	O
to	O
enter	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
Warrant	O
and	O
Affidavits	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Attorney	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6s	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
for	O
entering	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
Non	O
sum	O
Informatus	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
be	O
Cognovit	O
Actionem	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Attorny	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Witness	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
the	O
Affadavits	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Flying	O
Horse	O
in	O
Mitre-Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Judgement	O
was	O
never	O
enter	O
'd	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Attorney	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
fully	O
fixed	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
forged	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christain	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
alias	O
Parker	B-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Wid	O
.	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Change	I-place
where	O
Mr.	O
Ayliffe	O
lodged	O
,	O
before	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
as	O
Ayliffe	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
any	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ayliffe	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
of	O
Clipping	O
;	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
justified	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
two	O
Rooms	O
to	O
Ayliffe	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
workt	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
fetching	O
Drink	O
from	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
had	O
three	O
Children	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
arrainged	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
Brooksbanke	I-pers
of	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
90	O
yards	O
of	O
Manchester	O
Bays	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Clark	O
in	O
trust	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Blackfryers	B-place
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
discharged	O
from	O
that	O
Office	O
,	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
when	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
declared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ware	O
missing	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Clark	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
never	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
Accounts	O
with	O
Morgan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
maliciously	O
indicted	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
19s	O
.	O
5	O
Plates	O
4s	O
.	O
2	O
Candlesticks	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Keeb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Steel	O
Hilt	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
String	O
18d	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
first	O
Mr.	O
Bealing	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
in	O
James-Street	B-place
,	O
Covent	B-place
garden	I-place
,	O
by	O
some	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
man	O
,	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
Jenkins	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
Eades	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Richard	O
Jenkins	O
was	O
singly	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
upon	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hosey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hosey	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
six	O
persons	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
whereof	O
Jenkins	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
upon	O
Honslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
and	O
stript	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
his	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
nothing	O
but	O
three	O
Farthings	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
left	O
him	O
almost	O
naked	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Gardener	I-place
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
shooting	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
from	O
off	O
an	O
Apple-Tree	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
Garden	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Bednal-green	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
Rob	O
his	O
Orchard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gardener	O
shot	O
his	O
Gun	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
Neighbours	O
that	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
Knight	O
lying	O
dead	O
under	O
the	O
Tree	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Pockets	O
full	O
of	O
Apples	O
.	O
The	O
Gardener	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
proved	O
by	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Orchard	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
been	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
by	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
having	O
sustained	O
great	O
Losses	O
before	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Birding-piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
No	O
body	O
answering	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
went	O
off	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
threatned	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Thieves	O
before	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
found	O
Special	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Lydia	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
at	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
upon	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Orchard	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
steal	O
Apples	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shot	O
off	O
his	O
Gun	O
at	O
random	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Girl	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Wyndsor	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Collonel	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
in	O
Dean-street	B-place
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
3	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10l	O
.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
worth	O
about	O
400l	O
.	O
Nothing	O
being	O
positively	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
5	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
)	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Utensils	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Her	O
Neighbours	O
giving	O
a	O
credible	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pyper	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
coloured	O
brown	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
Black	O
,	O
10l	O
.	O
from	O
Osweld	B-pers
West	I-pers
in	O
Wiltshire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
Mute	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
prest	O
to	O
death	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
time	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Tried	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
West	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
just	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
a	O
Halfcrown	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
nor	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lloyd	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wood	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Claudius	B-pers
Moree	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Pendulum	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Knives	O
,	O
with	O
9l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
one	O
Johnson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
several	O
Clippers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
Bridewell-bridge	O
taught	O
her	O
to	O
Clip	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Moram	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
of	O
8	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Cloth	O
of	O
Gold	O
8l	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Duke	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
live	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
instruct	O
a	O
Woman	O
there	O
to	O
wash	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
,	O
its	O
possible	O
,	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Ladies	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
honourable	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dawtrey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dawtrey	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
at	O
Ratcliffe-Cross	B-place
on	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockins	O
10s	O
.	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
7	O
pair	O
about	O
Patrick	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
William	O
Dawtrey	O
's	O
Chamber	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Stocker	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
declared	O
that	O
William	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stockins	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
quartering	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
good	O
account	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
William	O
Dawtrey	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Getherington	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marchall	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Whattey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Valens	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
yet	O
Ann	O
Getherington	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Bomen	I-pers
of	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Beladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
that	O
Thomas	O
Gray	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
back	O
,	O
did	O
pull	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
50l	O
.	O
for	O
Composition	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
he	O
would	O
defend	O
their	O
Shop	O
from	O
being	O
robbed	O
hereafter	O
.	O
Gray	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Salesman	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Actor	O
s	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
severally	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
Buttons	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Gray	O
and	O
Slater	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
without	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
persons	O
of	O
ill	O
repute	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Actors	O
called	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appeared	O
;	O
so	O
Gray	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Actors	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
about	O
12l	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Bedding	O
and	O
other	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
Witness	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Boucher	O
hired	O
a	O
person	O
she	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Twopence	O
for	O
her	O
pains	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Thief	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
114	O
Foot	O
of	O
Purbeck	O
Stone	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pave	O
a	O
Kitchen	O
for	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
was	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilford	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pymm	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sherley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
5	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
val	O
.	O
50s	O
.	O
3	O
Aprons	O
7s	O
.	O
4	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
small	O
goods	O
,	O
owned	O
by	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Linnen	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
washing	O
to	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
in	O
Bell-Ally	B-place
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
all	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Robbed	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wilson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
double	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
Morgan	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
was	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Stockin	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Taking	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Reppington	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
late	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Arraigned	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Liberty	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Exceptions	O
against	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Issue	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Francis	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cleeve	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Spencer	B-pers
Iles	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
counted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clerk	O
read	O
the	O
Indictment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Edward	O
Reppington	O
.	O
Hold	O
up	O
thy	O
Hand	O
.	O
[	O
Which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
Gentlemen	O
:	O
You	O
that	O
are	O
sworn	O
,	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
hearken	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
He	O
stands	O
Indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Edward	O
Reppington	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
He	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
instigated	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Malice	O
before-thought	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	O
Dodd	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
Rapier	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
held	O
and	O
drawn	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Arm-hole	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Dodd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
thrust	O
in	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Dodd	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
Arm-hole	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Reppington	O
in	O
manner	O
and	O
form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murther	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Dodd	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
Their	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
Indictment	O
he	O
hath	O
been	O
arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
hath	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
;	O
And	O
for	O
his	O
Tryal	O
hath	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
God	O
and	O
his	O
Countrey	O
,	O
which	O
Countrey	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Your	O
Charge	O
is	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
he	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
stands	O
indicted	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
If	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
guilty	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chatels	O
,	O
Lands	O
or	O
Tenements	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murther	O
committed	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
since	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
find	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
he	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
he	O
be	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chatels	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
find	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
fly	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
hear	O
your	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Fact	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
how	O
malicious	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
all	O
parts	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
making	O
any	O
severe	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
;	O
the	O
chiefest	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
Three	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Inn	O
keeper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	B-place
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Groom	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
Eye-witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Evidence	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
confirmation	O
.	O
But	O
first	O
let	O
us	O
begin	O
with	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
You	O
must	O
note	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
of	O
kin	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
conversant	O
together	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
had	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
,	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
liked	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
20	O
Guineas	O
;	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
Groom	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
earnest	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
tried	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
complained	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
stumbled	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
Cousin	O
Reppington	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
fault	O
may	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
shoeing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Farrier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shall	O
look	O
upon	O
his	O
Feet	O
;	O
Nay	O
,	O
repl	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
I	O
wont	O
agree	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
this	O
Evening	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
you	O
shall	O
stand	O
fast	O
to	O
the	O
Bargain	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
seemed	O
to	O
yield	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
Groom	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
his	O
turn	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
arrested	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
this	O
relished	O
so	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
grew	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Groom	O
again	O
at	O
Mr	O
Dodds	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
tell	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
injured	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
should	O
decide	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
behind	O
Montague	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wore	O
a	O
Sword	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
indisposed	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
angry	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
's	O
Footman	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Inn	O
Gate-way	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
calling	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Groom	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
immediately	O
approached	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
,	O
he	O
very	O
kindly	O
saluted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
Cousin	O
Reppington	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
most	O
humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
putting	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
loving	O
Respects	O
imaginable	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
made	O
but	O
little	O
return	O
of	O
his	O
Courtesie	O
,	O
only	O
just	O
mov	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
shewing	O
a	O
stern	O
Countenance	O
;	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
very	O
mildly	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Button	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
might	O
be	O
friendly	O
accommodated	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
shall	O
decide	O
the	O
Controversie	O
;	O
immediately	O
throwing	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
drew	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
to't	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
making	O
the	O
first	O
pass	O
at	O
Mr	O
Dodd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
by	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
came	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
defending	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr	O
Reppington	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
held	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Armhole	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Goodchild	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Footboy	O
and	O
Groom	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Dung-fork	O
at	O
the	O
Stables	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Instrument	O
,	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
beat	O
down	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
mortal	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dropt	O
down	O
dead	O
the	O
blood	O
issuing	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
mouth	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
immediately	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
offering	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
least	O
flight	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
murther	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
groom	O
and	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Goodchild	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
cross-examined	O
the	O
witness	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
in	O
him	O
lay	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
proof	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
;	O
She	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
accidentally	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
weary	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
at	O
the	O
Inn-Gate	O
to	O
rest	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
her	O
head	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Ingagement	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Pass	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
;	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Godchild	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Footman	O
and	O
Groom	O
;	O
who	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
Woman	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
confident	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Woman	O
at	O
all	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
Juncture	O
of	O
time	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
indulged	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
patiently	O
heard	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
declaring	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
his	O
beloved	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
propense	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
Lamenting	O
the	O
loss	O
,	O
of	O
so	O
precious	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
Persons	O
of	O
no	O
mean	O
Quality	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
testimony	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Conversation	O
heretofore	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
declaration	O
concerning	O
him	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
,	O
composed	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
injured	O
any	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
begged	O
their	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
ample	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
very	O
strenuously	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
time	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
hours	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
very	O
patiently	O
hearing	O
him	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
very	O
distinctly	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
tenderness	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
(	O
first	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
certain	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
:	O
But	O
then	O
the	O
question	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
amount	O
to	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
Law	O
?	O
Whether	O
to	O
Murther	O
or	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
?	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
opinion	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
precedent	O
disgust	O
or	O
malice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
pursuance	O
thereof	O
draw	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
murther	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
So	O
that	O
if	O
so	O
be	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
Verdict	O
accordingly	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
satisfied	O
in	O
their	O
Consciences	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
disgust	O
or	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
acquit	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
murther	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Reppington	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
upon	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
remanded	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
15	O
.	O
John	O
Harris	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Browne	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Payne	O
,	O
Prudence	O
Turner	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
William	O
Walker	O
,	O
William	O
Dawtrey	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Gray	O
,	O
William	O
Pym	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Jane	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
Jane	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Long	O
,	O
Ann	O
Getherington	O
,	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
12	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Budd	O
,	O
Richard	O
Clements	O
,	O
William	O
Brewer	O
:	O
Isaac	O
Sims	O
,	O
William	O
Ayliffe	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Penny	O
,	O
Richard	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Eades	O
,	O
Ann	O
Boucher	O
,	O
Francis	O
Piper	O
,	O
Ann	O
Goddard	O
alias	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Edward	O
Reppington	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Several	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
kept	O
to	O
strict	O
Reading	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
4	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Allen	O
,	O
Erasmus	O
Townsend	O
,	O
William	O
Carter	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Fined	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Mercer	O
,	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
An	O
Historical	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
Transactions	O
in	O
Christendom	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
;	O
will	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
every	O
Saturday	O
in	O
Half	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
for	O
the	O
conveniency	O
of	O
Postage	O
:	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
of	O
News	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
of	O
New	O
Inventions	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Considerable	O
Matters	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
Gedeonis	O
Harvei	O
,	O
MD	O
.	O
Medici	O
Regis	O
&	O
Reginae	O
ad	O
Terrim	O
,	O
Ars	O
Curandi	O
Morbos	O
Expectatione	O
;	O
Item	O
de	O
Vanitatibus	O
,	O
Dolis	O
&	O
Mendaciis	O
Medicorum	O
.	O
Accedunt	O
his	O
praecipi	O
e	O
Suppofita	O
,	O
&	O
Phaenomena	O
,	O
quibus	O
veterum	O
recentiorumque	O
Dogmata	O
de	O
Febribus	O
,	O
Tufli	O
,	O
Phthisi	O
,	O
Asthmate	O
,	O
Apoplexia	O
,	O
Calculo	O
renum	O
&	O
vesicae	O
,	O
Isehuria	O
,	O
&	O
Passione	O
hysterica	O
convehuntur	O
;	O
aliaque	O
verisimiliorn	O
traduntur	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
James	O
Partridge	O
;	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Post-House	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Pantagruel	O
's	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
and	O
Fifth	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
Frantis	O
Rebelias	O
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
With	O
the	O
Pantagruelian	O
Prognostication	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Verse	O
and	O
Prose	O
by	O
that	O
Author	O
:	O
Also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
Compleating	O
all	O
his	O
Works	O
that	O
are	O
Extant	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
.	O
With	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
on	O
every	O
Chapter	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Four	O
Epistles	O
of	O
A.G.	O
Busbequtus	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Embassy	O
into	O
Turky	O
.	O
Being	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Religion	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Riches	O
,	O
Strength	O
,	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
that	O
People	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
their	O
Chief	O
Cities	O
,	O
and	O
Places	O
of	O
Trade	O
and	O
Commerce	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Advice	O
how	O
to	O
Manage	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Turks	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Bounds	O
set	O
to	O
France	O
by	O
the	O
Pyrenean	O
Treaty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
Confederates	O
not	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
Offers	O
of	O
Peace	O
made	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
short	O
Reflections	O
,	O
showing	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
England	O
is	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Restitution	O
of	O
that	O
Treaty	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
Towns	O
and	O
Countries	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
have	O
taken	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
These	O
Three	O
Sold	O
by	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
EUtropii	O
Historie	O
Romana	O
Breviarum	O
ab	O
urbe	O
Condita	O
usque	O
ad	O
Valentinianum	O
Auguster	O
;	O
ex	O
recensione	O
&	O
cum	O
notalus	O
Tan	O
Fabri	O
,	O
ut	O
&	O
Sexti	O
Antchi	O
Victorts	O
de	O
Viris	O
Illustribus	O
Liber	O
in	O
usum	O
Scholarum	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
John	O
14	O
1	O
.	O
Wherein	O
something	O
is	O
also	O
briefly	O
attempted	O
for	O
clearing	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Faith	O
,	O
of	O
Justification	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Assurance	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
;	O
and	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Conversion	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Holiness	O
.	O
By	O
H.	O
Lukin	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Act	O
;	O
26.28	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Blow	O
at	O
Prophaneness	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
R.R	O
.	O
Ezekiel	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Londonderry	O
.	O
Phedri	O
Augusti	O
Casari	O
Liberti	O
Fabularum	O
Aesopiarum	O
Libri	O
Quinque	O
,	O
Interpretatione	O
&	O
Notis	O
illustravit	O
,	O
Petrus	O
Danet	O
Jussim	O
Christianissimi	O
Regis	O
in	O
Usum	O
Serenissimi	O
Delphini	O
.	O
English	O
Exercises	O
for	O
School-Boys	O
to	O
Translate	O
into	O
Latin	O
,	O
comprizing	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Grammar	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Necessary	O
Observations	O
ascending	O
gradually	O
from	O
the	O
meanest	O
to	O
the	O
higher	O
Capacities	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Garretson	O
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
,	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
against	O
Infant	O
Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
These	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
MAtthew	O
Jones	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
19	O
,	O
of	O
low	O
stature	O
,	O
wears	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
being	O
dark	O
brown	O
and	O
lank	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
heavy-ey	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
an	O
upright	O
scar	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
his	O
forehead	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Whoever	O
gives	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Parents	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Nags-head	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
10s	O
.	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lad	O
kindly	O
received	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Fleece	O
Inn	O
in	O
Tuttle-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
convenient	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
Let	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Dennett	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
Tenements	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
paved	O
Wash-house	O
with	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
Water	O
at	O
hand	O
.	O
Storage	O
for	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
Coals	O
.	O
An	O
Oven	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Dwelling	O
partly	O
Furnish	O
d.	O
A	O
Large	O
Shop	O
,	O
Stalls	O
,	O
and	O
Dining	O
Room	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Rooms	O
,	O
and	O
large	O
Closets	O
to	O
each	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Coach-houses	O
and	O
Stables	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
an	O
Ostler	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
also	O
Conveniency	O
for	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Apartments	O
will	O
be	O
let	O
very	O
cheap	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
forever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarison	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet	O
Bridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitae	O
.	O
An	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrisices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
humane	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
BL	O
