TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDING	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1694.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashhurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Empson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pardue	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hulbard	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stancliffe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Greenougla	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wyan	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Halbrook	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Illford	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Aubrey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Stockdon	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Pelsome	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
val	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Wid	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Worsted	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Stockins	O
under	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Flesh	O
hook	O
also	O
to	O
hook	O
any	O
thing	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
:	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Hook	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
a	O
Butcher's-stall	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Ruttey	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
:	O
Ruttey	O
confest	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
Arraignment	O
;	O
Lester	O
was	O
afterwards	O
Tried	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
and	O
slipt	O
away	O
the	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
Ruttey	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fling	O
the	O
Goods	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
.	O
Larceny	O
.	O
[	O
Lester	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Ruttey	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Towle	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Arrows	I-place
Brewhouse	I-place
in	O
Golden-Lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Counting	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
Cooper	O
to	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
)	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Drawers	O
were	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
strictly	O
examin	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Clerk	O
50	O
s.	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
advantage	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Button	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Button	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
making	O
100	O
Shillings	O
of	O
False	O
Metal	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
Button	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
Brewers-street	B-place
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
a	O
Forge	O
,	O
and	O
Parsons	O
standing	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
was	O
found	O
Two	O
Papers	O
of	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
newly	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
Shears	O
,	O
Melting-Pots	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Button	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clockmaker	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
the	O
Tools	O
about	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Parsons	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
merciful	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Selman	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
aged	O
5	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
Child	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
that	O
suck	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
nurse	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Penetration	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
actual	O
Gonorrhea	O
;	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
Felony	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
new	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferr	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Tried	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Danvers	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Durrham	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
The	O
second	O
was	O
laid	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
five	O
Spoons	O
,	O
12Knives	O
,	O
30	O
s	O
:	O
12	O
Forks	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
nine	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Madam	O
Danvers	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Parlor	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cry	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Four	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Half-moon-street	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
was	O
seen	O
lying	O
near	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
but	O
strong	O
suspition	O
of	O
being	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
London	B-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Middleton	B-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
former	O
were	O
tried	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
that	O
woman	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ber	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
Pistols	O
gag	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stript	O
him	O
naked	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
10	O
s.	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Crevat	O
,	O
besides	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
going	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
near	O
Rose-Alley	O
he	O
met	O
Elliot	O
with	O
his	O
Shoes	O
on	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
Leonard	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Bullen	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Leper	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
.	O
An	O
Inkhorn	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Elliot	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pearsons	O
.	O
And	O
Pearsons	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Leonard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hathand	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
Pearson	O
swore	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Leonard	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
Elliot	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
that	O
Pearson	O
should	O
know	O
their	O
Faces	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Keat	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Quarters	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Others	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Pistols	O
Elliot	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
.	O
So	O
Pearson	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
strenuous	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
such	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
men	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Story	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lodwick	I-pers
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wright	B-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Tabby	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
and	O
Partner	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
L'Roose	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6.	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Graham	O
was	O
sitting	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
pickt	O
the	O
Compter	O
with	O
a	O
Whalebone	O
liquor	O
'd	O
with	O
Bird-lime	O
or	O
Turpentine	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
Besides	O
,	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wits	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
good	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meade	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Meade	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Coat	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
from	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boat	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Cranes	I-place
Stairs	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Morrell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cambridge	B-pers
Mall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
of	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
Andrews	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Shoe-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
women	O
,	O
came	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Hancock	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked-Billet	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
;	O
but	O
Andrews	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
drank	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
O	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
sad	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
suffer	O
for	O
that	O
which	O
another	O
woman	O
did	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
for	O
Andrews	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
him	O
when	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
,	O
declared	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Andrews	O
into	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
an	O
ill	O
woman	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
by	O
picking	O
of	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pockets	O
in	O
her	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Halfhundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Iron	O
Weight	O
from	O
off	O
Dyers	B-place
Key	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
Jones	O
wr	O
the	O
Iron	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
it	O
from	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
ship	O
Mates	O
,	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
now	O
on	O
Ship-board	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Jones	O
having	O
his	O
Iron	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ayland	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Point	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oswelstone	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Drawers	O
so	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
in	O
but	O
her	O
,	O
summed	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Oswelstone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Oswelstone	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
her	O
own	O
Sister	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
being	O
searched	O
in	O
Panton-street	B-place
near	O
Picadily	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
there	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
there	O
were	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Clipt	O
money	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
Sheets	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Beds	O
feet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
concerned	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
an	O
Acquintance	O
of	O
hers	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
what	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
but	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mayheu	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blue	O
Linen	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
.	O
Spooner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
indeed	O
the	O
Apron	O
and	O
Cloth	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Grymes	I-pers
upon	O
Chadwell	B-place
Common	I-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
two	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Kneaves	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
22	O
l	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
ten	O
Highway	O
men	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Butcher	O
s	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
failing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Halfcrown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Shilling	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
Grimes	O
swore	O
was	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
besides	O
32	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
Bullets	O
and	O
Powder	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Kneaves	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nine-pence	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Arms	O
.	O
How	O
should	O
he	O
be	O
a	O
Highway	O
man	O
then	O
?	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
a	O
Gardener	O
that	O
helpt	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Had	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
men	O
Robbed	O
besides	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
Robberies	O
were	O
done	O
about	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
2	O
,	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
They	O
stopt	O
the	O
Post-Boy	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
one	O
Susanna	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
33	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
be	O
being	O
newly	O
married	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
begin	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Bullets	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
used	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Highway	O
men	O
,	O
only	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Kneaves	O
swore	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
money	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
alledged	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
at	O
Colchester	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mayor	O
thereof	O
(	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
here	O
)	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
fair	O
Testimony	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
added	O
moreover	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
might	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
the	O
defence	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
,	O
availed	O
him	O
nothing	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
near	O
Chadley	B-place
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
Grymes	O
and	O
Kneaves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Butcher	O
s	O
were	O
robbed	O
near	O
Rumford	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
.	O
Manning	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
aHalf-Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
Bullet	O
Mold	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
found	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Stratford	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
his	O
Mare	O
that	O
he	O
rid	O
upon	O
falling	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
foot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Conntrey	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
loose	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
men	O
pursuing	O
some	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Mare	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
story	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Peter	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Stringer	O
swore	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Musick	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
got	O
pretty	O
merry	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
enticed	O
,	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Elbow-Lane	B-place
near	O
Cock-hill	B-place
,	O
but	O
first	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
he	O
being	O
heavy	O
to	O
sleep	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
clock	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
freer	O
than	O
Gift	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Rings	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
appeared	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
Pains	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
but	O
indeed	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
said	O
Stringer	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
tho	O
it	O
were	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
stones	O
throw	O
;	O
All	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
agreed	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
drunk	O
too	O
,	O
throwing	O
his	O
Money	O
about	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
crack	O
brain	O
'd	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
presently	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
of	O
5	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
some	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
all	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
entrusted	O
her	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
a	O
Drunken	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wrongfully	O
accused	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
a	O
Lascivious	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
her	O
due	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
-	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Piggen	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
upon	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
first	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
one	O
Eudall	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
,	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Clippers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
went	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Assistants	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
in	O
Crown-Ally	B-place
in	O
Upper	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
Mr.	O
Sherwin	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
searched	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
above	O
Forty	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Burnishing	O
Tool	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Whitening	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
stuff	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
about	O
Coining	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Piggen	O
's	O
Room	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flatting-Mill	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
stuff	O
called	O
Fage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Powder	O
of	O
Argyle	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellsars	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
was	O
found	O
an	O
Ingot-Mold	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
Implements	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Piggen	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Search	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
of	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Sherwin	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Tin-man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
Toys	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
late	O
he	O
studied	O
Physick	O
.	O
Piggen	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Higget	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Ireland	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bridgeman	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Attey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Murrey	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Wine	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Red	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Attey	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Farrier	O
,	O
and	O
liveth	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
with	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
Murrey	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
drank	O
no	O
Red	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
White	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
was	O
this	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
Farrier	O
having	O
caused	O
Bridgeman	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
Picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
she	O
,	O
was	O
much	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Attey	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Robert	O
Attey	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
discharged	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
Bridgeman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
because	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Indicted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
an	O
ill	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
doth	O
suppose	O
did	O
steal	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
although	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
light	O
person	O
,	O
yet	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
say	O
she	O
ever	O
pickt	O
a	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
owning	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
Reprimanded	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stopping	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
Four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
52	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
swore	O
that	O
William	O
Hall	O
and	O
Thomas	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
bargained	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
William	O
Hall	O
and	O
Thomas	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
removed	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
,	O
where	O
G	O
-	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
he	O
bespoke	O
,	O
they	O
keeping	O
the	O
said	O
Styles	O
in	O
discourse	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
understood	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
thus	O
.	O
Says	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
money	O
at	O
a	O
Race	O
at	O
Bamstead	O
Downes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
vext	O
,	O
I'le	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
shall	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
procure	O
you	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Styles	O
refusing	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
their	O
counsel	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
personating	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Macey	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
set	O
his	O
Breech	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
searcht	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
threatning	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
set	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
lay	O
the	O
Clippings	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
mischief	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
great	O
Fear	O
.	O
That	O
G	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
swore	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
submit	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
menacing	O
language	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
proved	O
that	O
G	O
-	O
Hall	O
and	O
Styles	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
friendly	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Then	O
Styles	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
went	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
threatning	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
severe	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Styles	O
swore	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
G	O
-	O
took	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
Captain	O
Platt	O
could	O
prove	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
G	O
-	O
alledged	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
was	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Styles	O
was	O
represented	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Broad-money	O
Changer	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Tavern	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
get	O
matter	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
ill	O
man	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
called	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
himself	O
honest	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
such	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
a	O
Verdict	O
that	O
G	O
-	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
Point	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Concern	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Etheridge	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
caught	O
taking	O
and	O
killing	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Tallow	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ripping	O
up	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
raised	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
of	O
us	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
under	O
a	O
Haycock	O
,	O
being	O
weary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
espied	O
the	O
Sheep	O
ript	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Sheep	O
lay	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
a	O
small	O
Excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larceny	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
owned	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Inn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
Chamber-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prisonerafterwards	O
was	O
taken	O
Robbing	O
an	O
Orchard	O
at	O
Elling	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Inn	O
's	O
Wastecoat	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Apples	O
,	O
which	O
Wastecoat	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
Wastecoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Lye	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Blundall	I-pers
three	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Covering	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
trayterously	O
Coin	O
and	O
make	O
several	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
false	O
Metal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
only	O
an	O
Ingate	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Brass	O
Pieces	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Bridgwaters-Gardens	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Crucible	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Implements	O
to	O
make	O
Buttons	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
bath	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
Coining	O
false	O
money	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
40	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Ewdall	O
the	O
Constable	O
declared	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Lester	O
's	O
house	O
9	O
l.	O
lacking	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
of	O
most	O
base	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
few	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Stamps	O
to	O
make	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
likewise	O
an	O
Ingate	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
207	O
l.	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
good	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Lester	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Ingate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Clockmaker	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
Clipt	O
any	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jylks	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l	O
nine	O
Spoons	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Plate	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
confest	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
Instant	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
;	O
and	O
a	O
Drawer	O
being	O
opened	O
,	O
she	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
clapt	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Cellar	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
her	O
Credit	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
manifest	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
also	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
Black-Fryers	B-place
,	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Clippings	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
custody	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
leapt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
:	O
O	O
God	O
:	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Constetnation	O
and	O
Trembling	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
near	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Harford	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
might	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Westbrook	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
colour	O
of	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
favouring	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
I	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Cutting	O
and	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
without	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Forestreet	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
suspition	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
)	O
he	O
searcht	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
false	O
Halfcrowns	O
ready	O
cast	O
for	O
stamping	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
some	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
whereon	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
Rubbed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
ready	O
Clipt	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
seven	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
one	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
12	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
12	O
Coifs	O
,	O
6	O
Muslin	O
Nightroils	O
val	O
42	O
s.	O
4	O
Peticoats	O
40	O
s.	O
20	O
Hoods	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Gold	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
W	O
-	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
landed	O
at	O
Harwich	O
,	O
her	O
Trunk	O
(	O
wherein	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
)	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
away	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Saracens-Head	O
Inn	O
at	O
Algate	O
several	O
persons	O
came	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
asking	O
Mrs.	O
W	O
-	O
,	O
What	O
News	O
from	O
Holland	O
?	O
Then	O
she	O
taking	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	O
with	O
Two	O
Gentlewomen	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
Braces	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
were	O
cut	O
in	O
Paternoster-row	B-place
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
amongst	O
the	O
Crowd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Burton	O
and	O
Thompson	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
helped	O
the	O
Gentlewomen	O
to	O
another	O
Coach	O
.	O
Burton	O
and	O
Thomson	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flanders	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3.	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
September	O
the	O
23th	O
she	O
came	O
occasionally	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Hood	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
to	O
be	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wittway	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walsham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
30	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockins	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walsham	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
Witway	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	O
Gilbert	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
one	O
Pair	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stockins	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
jostled	O
her	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Gold	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gathorne	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
six	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
with	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Mallett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Mallet	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nurse	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Press	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
satisfied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Captain	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Musick-house	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	B-place
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
Bar	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
comes	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
for	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
mischief	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
Mr.	O
R	O
-	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
through	O
the	O
Door-way	O
,	O
then	O
Morrison	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
Mr.	O
R	O
-	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Weapon	O
but	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
with	O
Mr.	O
R	O
-	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
Murther	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
Cole	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
assault	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Couch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Lad	O
of	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
Accident	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
manner	O
:	O
Some	O
time	O
since	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
money	O
,	O
left	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
that	O
then	O
was	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
Ring	O
Morrison	O
wore	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
the	O
Bar-keeper	O
seeing	O
him	O
wear	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
jesting	O
manner	O
,	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
keeping	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
abroad	O
with	O
Captain	O
G	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
the	O
Priner	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
owned	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Morrison	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
.	O
Morrison	O
then	O
being	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
living	O
in	O
another	O
Service	O
,	O
took	O
occasion	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
old	O
Masters	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
Captain	O
R	O
-	O
talking	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
the	O
Bar-keeper	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Captain	O
R	O
-	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
some	O
body	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
R	O
-	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
)	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
R	O
-	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
nothing	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
rough	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
R	O
-	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
Morrison	O
fended	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
Morrison	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
Chyrurgion	O
made	O
Oath	O
that	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
days	O
died	O
.	O
Then	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
the	O
Lad	O
stood	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Harrison	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
first	O
Passes	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
R	O
-	O
stab	O
theDeceased	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
favourable	O
Report	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
owning	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Mortimer	O
was	O
but	O
his	O
Mistress	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
made	O
a	O
notable	O
Defence	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
proved	O
what	O
he	O
alledged	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
Persons	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Brother	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
divers	O
credible	O
Persons	O
to	O
confront	O
them	O
with	O
some	O
former	O
Actions	O
,	O
he	O
desisted	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
were	O
heard	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
matter	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Hearing	O
,	O
his	O
Lordship	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
the	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
three	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
140	O
Twenty	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
140	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
looking	O
into	O
his	O
Trunk	O
again	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
Diamonds	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gold	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
left	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
a	O
Suspition	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
in	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
three	O
Guinea	O
's	O
upon	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Diamond	O
upon	O
Ann	O
Charlton	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Charlton	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
ill	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
leave	O
her	O
Lodging	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
She	O
produced	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Isabella	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
buried	O
under	O
a	O
board	O
in	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Pot	O
was	O
found	O
some	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clipping	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
about	O
Mrs.	O
Ross	O
was	O
found	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Shillings	O
that	O
were	O
newly	O
clipt	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
Purse	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Piece	O
of	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Filings	O
of	O
Silver	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
suspicious	O
found	O
upon	O
Mr	O
Ross	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
used	O
to	O
Clip	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Tub-man	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
affected	O
Mr	O
Ross	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Wood	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
lately	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
killing	O
her	O
Son-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
vow	O
'd	O
Revenge	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
very	O
substantial	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
both	O
their	O
Reputations	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
Laborious	O
People	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Demeany	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Demeany	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Santrey	I-pers
and	O
Claud	B-pers
Santrey	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
drinking	O
at	O
Roberts	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
before	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
only	O
Santrey	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
good	O
Witness	O
to	O
their	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flanders-Lace	O
Head-dress	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l	O
an	O
Apron	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Lace-Crevat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Southerne	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
in	O
Duck-Lane	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Countrey	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
they	O
laid	O
this	O
Felony	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
.	O
Southerne	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
also	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Trial	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
before	O
Tried	O
on	O
London-side	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
again	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
20	O
l.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Davis	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
preceding	O
Trial	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Pound	O
and	O
Fourteen	O
Ounces	O
of	O
dy	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
only	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Latchfeild	I-pers
Sollicitor	O
at	O
Law	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Ballendyne	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Belwood	I-pers
,	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
cheat	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rood	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
s	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
divers	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bellandine	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bill	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Belwood	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
Abchurch	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
is	O
not	O
paid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
said	O
Latchfield	O
Guilty	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
acted	O
more	O
than	O
became	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Concern	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Jane	O
Ruttey	O
Joseph	O
Towle	O
G	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
Elinor	O
Stockdon	O
Elinor	O
Alford	O
Ann	O
Wilson	O
Jane	O
Jylks	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Mary	O
Murrell	O
,	O
alias	O
Cambridge	O
Mall	O
.	O
W	O
-	O
I	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
James	O
Leonard	O
,	O
alias	O
London	O
.	O
James	O
Elliott	O
John	O
Weaver	O
Richard	O
Gardner	O
Richard	O
Piggen	O
Samuel	O
Sherwin	O
Elinor	O
Pelsome	O
Elizabeth	O
Story	O
Elizabeth	O
Edwards	O
Mary	O
Shepherd	O
Lewis	O
l'Roofe	O
.	O
Mary	O
Murrell	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Pelsome	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Story	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Mary	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
were	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgment	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Transportation	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Humphrey	O
Burton	O
John	O
Thompson	O
William	O
Whitway	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Lester	O
James	O
Hughes	O
Jonathan	O
Gibbons	O
Katharine	O
Stephens	O
Edward	O
Clark	O
John	O
Bailey	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
General	O
Pardon	O
pleaded	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
Convicts	O
;	O
a	O
Particular	O
Account	O
of	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Presentment	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Inquest	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Collonel	O
Founteine	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pepper	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nowell	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wharton	O
,	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
THE	O
Instrumentality	O
of	O
Faith	O
asserted	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
and	O
preferr	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Conditional	O
Relation	O
thereof	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Pardon	O
and	O
Happiness	O
.	O
Delivered	O
in	O
several	O
Sermons	O
,	O
by	O
W	O
Cross	O
M	O
A	O
.	O
Good	O
Deeds	O
done	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
on	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Butt	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
appointed	O
for	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Fleet	O
.	O
By	O
Ed	O
.	O
Veal	O
.	O
Are	O
both	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
suddenly	O
published	O
.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
John	O
14	O
.	O
I	O
By	O
Henry	O
Lukin	O
.	O
12	O
o	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Infant	O
Baptism	O
God	O
's	O
Ordinance	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
clear	O
Proof	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
Believing	O
Parents	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
.	O
By	O
Michael	O
Harrison	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
in	O
P	O
's	O
P.	O
12	O
o.	O
Eutropij	O
Historiae	O
Romance	O
Breviarium	O
ab	O
urbe	O
Conditum	O
usque	O
ad	O
Valentianum	O
&	O
Valentem	O
Augustos	O
.	O
Ex	O
recensione	O
&	O
cum	O
Norulis	O
Tanquilli	O
Fabri	O
ut	O
&	O
Sexti	O
Aurelii	O
Victoris	O
de	O
Vires	O
Illustribus	O
.	O
Liber	O
in	O
Usum	O
Scholarum	O
.	O
12	O
o.	O
Phaedri	O
Augusti	O
Caesaris	O
Liberti	O
Fabularum	O
AEsopiarum	O
Libri	O
Quinque	O
.	O
Interpretatione	O
&	O
Notis	O
illustravit	O
Petrus	O
Danet	O
Academicus	O
Jussu	O
Christianissimi	O
Regis	O
.	O
In	O
Usum	O
Serenissimi	O
Delphini	O
.	O
A	O
Week	O
of	O
Soliloquies	O
and	O
Prayers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preparation	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Communion	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Devotions	O
added	O
to	O
this	O
Edition	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Parts	O
.	O
English	O
Exercises	O
for	O
School-boys	O
to	O
translate	O
into	O
Latin	O
,	O
comprising	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Grammar	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	O
Garretson	O
Schoolmaster	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart	O
work	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel	O
Minister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr	O
Annesley	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Things	O
not	O
seen	O
:	O
Or	O
divers	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Holy	O
Men	O
after	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
eminently	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
,	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Tongue	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Poems	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pastoral	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Tutelin	O
.	O
A	O
succinct	O
and	O
seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
against	O
Infant	O
Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antimonian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavel	O
's	O
Remains	O
;	O
being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
:	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
united	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
,	O
and	O
Repentance	O
;	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broadstreet	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
;	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
know	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
;	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
Saviour	O
,	O
The	O
only	O
Mediator	O
,	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Geography	O
Anatomized	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
compleat	O
Geographical	O
Grammer	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
short	O
and	O
exact	O
Analysis	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
body	O
of	O
Modern	O
Geography	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
new	O
,	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
easy	O
method	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
attain	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
that	O
most	O
noble	O
and	O
useful	O
Science	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoined	O
the	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
European	O
Plantations	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
and	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
reasonable	O
Proposed	O
for	O
the	O
propagation	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
in	O
all	O
Pagan	O
Countries	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divers	O
Maps	O
.	O
By	O
Patrick	O
Gordon	O
,	O
M	O
A	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Christ	O
necessary	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
Curse	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
,	O
by	O
Tho	O
.	O
Doolittle	O
,	O
M	O
A	O
.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Assemblies	O
Shorter	O
Catechism	O
;	O
with	O
Practical	O
Inferences	O
from	O
each	O
Question	O
;	O
by	O
John	O
Flavell	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
a	O
Paper	O
written	O
by	O
Count	O
of	O
Avaux	O
.	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Ambassador	O
in	O
Sueden	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Proposals	O
of	O
Peace	O
made	O
by	O
France	O
to	O
the	O
Confederates	O
.	O
Bibliotheca	O
Politica	O
:	O
Or	O
an	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Antient	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Government	O
;	O
Both	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
just	O
extent	O
of	O
Regal	O
Power	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
and	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
Wherein	O
all	O
the	O
Chief	O
Arguments	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
against	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Revolution	O
,	O
are	O
impartially	O
represented	O
and	O
considered	O
,	O
in	O
Thirteen	O
Dialogues	O
.	O
Collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Best	O
Authors	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Antient	O
as	O
Modern	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
F.	O
Rabelass	O
,	O
M	O
D.	O
In	O
Five	O
Books	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Heroick	O
Deeds	O
and	O
Sayings	O
of	O
the	O
Good	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantagruel	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
As	O
also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
Printed	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Four	O
Epistles	O
of	O
A.	O
G.	O
Busbequint	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Embassy	O
into	O
Turky	O
.	O
Being	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Religion	O
,	O
Customs	O
Riches	O
,	O
Strength	O
,	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
that	O
People	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
their	O
Chief	O
Cities	O
,	O
and	O
Places	O
of	O
Trade	O
and	O
Commerce	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Advice	O
how	O
to	O
Manage	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Turks	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Bounds	O
set	O
to	O
France	O
by	O
the	O
Pyrenean	O
Treaty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
Confederates	O
not	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
Offers	O
of	O
Peace	O
made	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
short	O
Reflections	O
,	O
showing	O
how	O
far	O
England	O
is	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Restitution	O
of	O
that	O
Treaty	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
Towns	O
and	O
Countries	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
have	O
taken	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Letters	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
Written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Milton	O
,	O
To	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Sovereign	O
Princes	O
and	O
Republicks	O
of	O
Europe	O
From	O
the	O
Year	O
1649	O
.	O
Till	O
the	O
Year	O
1659	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Poems	O
;	O
And	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
his	O
Works	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
Printed	O
.	O
A	O
Compendious	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Taxes	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Opressive	O
Methods	O
of	O
Raising	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
An	O
Impartial	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Advantages	O
and	O
Losses	O
that	O
England	O
hath	O
received	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
Present	O
War	O
with	O
France	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Journal	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Monthy	O
Miscellany	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
Consisting	O
of	O
News	O
,	O
History	O
,	O
Phylosophy	O
,	O
Poetry	O
,	O
Musick	O
,	O
Translations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Septemb	O
.	O
1694	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
R.	O
Baldwin	O
,	O
Where	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
compleat	O
Sets	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
years	O
,	O
or	O
single	O
ones	O
for	O
every	O
Month	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Henry	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warrington	O
.	O
Lately-lost	O
,	O
A	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
number	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Steel	O
Seals	O
:	O
Whoever	O
brings	O
them	O
to	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
Reward	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
Practice	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whole	O
Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
Elixir	O
Satutis	O
,	O
Basamum	O
Vita	O
,	O
Tinotura	O
Vitoe	O
An	O
excellent	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Effences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
L	O
.	O
