TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1694.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
Follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Tobias	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Swinsen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dovey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cranstone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Osseter	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammidge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Akres	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hembrick	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tippes	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Skellum	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
20	O
Buck	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
Partner	O
s	O
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Walter	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
notorious	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
Hose	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barnell	I-pers
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
69	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute-string	O
,	O
value	O
13l	O
.	O
50	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
11s	O
.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
20s	O
.	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gawze	O
,	O
30s	O
.	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
19s	O
.	O
two	O
Womens	O
Black-Laced	O
Tippets	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
Shirts	O
10s	O
.	O
1000	O
Pins	O
9d	O
.	O
12	O
Silk	O
Scarfs	O
24s	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
Strip't	O
Hair-Shagg	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Frucher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Arnold	B-pers
Rabbey	I-pers
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Shagg	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Nags-head	O
in	O
Grubstreet	O
,	O
was	O
first	O
Tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Petts	I-pers
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
King's-Evil	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Tried	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Petts	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
her	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	B-place
alone	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
great	O
Violence	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ravish	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
although	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
strugled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
stab	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cease	O
her	O
Noise	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
her	O
daughter	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
much	O
abused	O
in	O
her	O
privy	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
issued	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
some	O
Violence	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
proceed	O
merely	O
from	O
a	O
Natural	O
Cause	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
swore	O
the	O
Rape	O
and	O
Robbery	O
very	O
home	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
so	O
foul	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ill	O
resented	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
prove	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
to	O
suffer	O
such	O
evil	O
doings	O
to	O
go	O
unpunished	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Rape	O
and	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lansdell	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
of	O
Eight	O
French	O
Pistoles	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
Nine	O
Twenty-shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
20	O
Broad-pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
150	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
263l	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lansdell	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Gold	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
above	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
above	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Maid	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
and	O
Gold	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
his	O
Wife	O
behind	O
him	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
pretending	O
more	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
than	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
deluded	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
fine	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
32	O
Guinea	O
's	O
from	O
her	O
without	O
Bond	O
or	O
Note	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Reputation	O
,	O
a	O
Hatter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Gold	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Gold	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
January	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
in	O
one	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Owen	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Garlickhithe	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Stephens	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
January	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
whereupon	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
tri	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Stiching	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
Silk	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
's	O
Shop	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
)	O
and	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
was	O
matching	O
his	O
Cloth	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
he	O
slipt	O
the	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Silk	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
wept	O
and	O
expressed	O
his	O
sorrow	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Laskey	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
al	O
also	O
Amy	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
(	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
)	O
2	O
Silver	O
Basons	O
,	O
value	O
16l	O
.	O
2	O
Salvers	O
11l	O
.	O
3	O
Porringers	O
9l	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Candlestick	O
Sconces	O
8l	O
.	O
a	O
Sugar-box	O
55s	O
.	O
a	O
Pepper-box	O
55s	O
.	O
two	O
salts	O
20s	O
.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
8l	O
.	O
9	O
Spoons	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
10	O
Forks	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
15s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
H	O
-	O
and	O
Laskey	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
put	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
Exeter	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Laskey	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
date	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
the	O
Maid	O
H	O
-	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
immediately	O
missing	O
;	O
Martin	O
Raymond	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
5l	O
.	O
in	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
either	O
he	O
or	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
and	O
Rebecca	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
actually	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Langly	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
8d	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
50s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
Edwards	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
finding	O
he	O
had	O
Cash	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
first	O
tempted	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
in	O
Church-Lane	B-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
at	O
the	O
John	O
Baptist's-head	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
about	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
debauch	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
feigned	O
Stories	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
Sea	O
;	O
but	O
Edwards	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
a	O
5s	O
.	O
piece	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
yet	O
Edwards	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
his	O
Piece	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lain	O
one	O
Night	O
there	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
his	O
Command	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edith	B-pers
Tyteman	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyley	I-pers
(	O
together	O
with	O
Dynah	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
24	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
7	O
Petwer	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
were	O
both	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rigbey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridget	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
27	O
yards	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Lutestring	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
unto	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Bird	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
of	O
16	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
course	O
Worsted	O
Cruel	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wade	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
Wades	O
Neighbour	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wade	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Turvit	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Pymm	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
of	O
a	O
14	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Pitsfield	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pymm	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Weight	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Strange	O
Woman	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Repute	O
amongst	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
seemed	O
obscure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
Knight	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
flower	O
'd	O
Laced	O
pink	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
an	O
Indian	O
silk	O
Gown	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Petticoat	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
10l	O
.	O
a	O
watch	O
5l	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
18l	O
.	O
a	O
Cup	O
4l	O
.	O
two	O
Spoons	O
19s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilt	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
3l	O
.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
rich	O
Nightroyle	O
6l	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Smock-sleeves	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Handkerchief	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Twenty-shilling	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
besides	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
Bridges	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
making	O
love	O
to	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
robbed	O
him	O
whilst	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
was	O
abroad	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
was	O
found	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
neck	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
abetting	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
formerly	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shewglass	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Ashfield	I-pers
near	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
contained	O
3	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18l	O
.	O
4	O
Turkey	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
36l	O
.	O
6	O
other	O
Rings	O
18l	O
.	O
a	O
Garnet	O
Ring	O
12s	O
.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
14l	O
.	O
3	O
Cornelian	O
Rings	O
36s	O
.	O
and	O
22l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ashfield	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
three	O
more	O
men	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
shifted	O
his	O
Lodging	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
presently	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
Tavern	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
shared	O
amongst	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
fairly	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
strenuous	O
enough	O
against	O
him	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Harlachy	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Draper	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Hitchin	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
driving	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
against	O
the	O
Left	O
Leg	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Hewetson	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hewetson	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
langish	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
did	O
accidentally	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
wilfully	O
,	O
by	O
expressing	O
his	O
sorrow	O
for	O
so	O
sad	O
an	O
Accident	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
dark	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Mennel	I-pers
of	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mennet	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Nunns	I-place
and	I-place
Hare	I-place
in	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Saracens-head	O
Inn	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
and	O
bargained	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
Linen	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
20l	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Mennel	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Trick	O
put	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Mennel	O
,	O
for	O
really	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
keep	O
the	O
said	O
Inn	O
;	O
yet	O
by	O
her	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemain	O
,	O
she	O
pincht	O
away	O
the	O
Muslin	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
speak	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hair-colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
8l	O
.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Petticoat	O
3l	O
.	O
one	O
Night-Gown	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
3l	O
.	O
with	O
5l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holles	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Holles	I-pers
were	O
Tri	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
was	O
were	O
,	O
viz	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
a	O
Picture	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
5l	O
.	O
four	O
gold	O
Rings	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
diamond	O
Rings	O
10l	O
.	O
three	O
Spoons	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
8s	O
.	O
two	O
gold	O
Ear-rings	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
Bodkins	O
3s	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
Watches	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
containing	O
40	O
Jacobus	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
47l	O
.	O
and	O
31	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Holles	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
possibly	O
might	O
well	O
enough	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Holles	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Holles	O
repli	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Witness	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
Life	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Holles	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
time	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Centry	O
together	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
private	O
Soldier	O
s	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
Mrs.	O
Owen	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mary	O
Holles	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
wholly	O
innocent	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
Hammer	O
behind	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Owen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
affirm	O
'd	O
was	O
her	O
Hammer	O
.	O
Besides	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
a	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Abryhals	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Owen	O
:	O
But	O
all	O
this	O
being	O
circumstantial	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Rich	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Scarf	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
alter	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Fringe	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
by	O
her	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fringe	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Crowder	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
credited	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Easden	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
instigated	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
great	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
both	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
her	O
against	O
a	O
wooden	O
Step	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
bruised	O
in	O
her	O
Womb	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
which	O
Easden	O
pretended	O
to	O
do	O
(	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
)	O
because	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
money	O
)	O
to	O
whit	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
26s	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
arrest	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
besides	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
)	O
had	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
Perjured	O
Rogue	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bawd	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
an	O
Anchor-Smith	O
,	O
and	O
maintained	O
her	O
by	O
his	O
honest	O
Labour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
deni	O
'd	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
touch	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
after	O
the	O
Hurt	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
malice	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
was	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
owned	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Easden	O
did	O
her	O
no	O
harm	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lawe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Gent	O
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
commonly	O
called	O
Beaux	O
Wilson	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
which	O
by	O
common	O
Report	O
of	O
Fame	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
six	O
Horses	O
,	O
maintained	O
his	O
Family	O
in	O
great	O
Splendor	O
and	O
Grandeur	O
,	O
being	O
full	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
their	O
Debtor	O
;	O
yet	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
what	O
hand	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Effects	O
which	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
Equipage	O
,	O
is	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
determined	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
difference	O
hapned	O
to	O
arise	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
concerning	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
Instant	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
fought	O
a	O
Duel	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
opportunity	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Letters	O
sent	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
,	O
or	O
given	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Letters	O
were	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Invectives	O
,	O
and	O
Cautions	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
to	O
beware	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
design	O
of	O
Evil	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Letters	O
sent	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
house	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Sack	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Master	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
with	O
somewhat	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
Captain	O
Wightman	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
gave	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
familiar	O
Friend	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilsons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Captain	O
Wightman	O
took	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
drove	O
towards	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
stept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
into	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
together	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
immediately	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
pass	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
making	O
but	O
one	O
pass	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Letters	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
full	O
of	O
Aggravations	O
on	O
both	O
parts	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Name	O
subscribed	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Dual	O
fought	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
was	O
killed	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
the	O
Duel	O
was	O
fought	O
and	O
never	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
occasioned	O
about	O
the	O
Letters	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
meeting	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
was	O
merely	O
an	O
accidental	O
thing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
misfortune	O
did	O
arise	O
only	O
from	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
of	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
from	O
any	O
Propense	O
Malice	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Agreement	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
though	O
Wilson	O
drew	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
construction	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
)	O
guilty	O
of	O
murder	O
:	O
For	O
if	O
two	O
men	O
suddenly	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
kill	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
this	O
would	O
be	O
but	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
case	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
otherwise	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
continual	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
carried	O
on	O
betwixt	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
therefore	O
must	O
be	O
accounted	O
a	O
malicious	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
design	O
of	O
murder	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
killed	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
likewise	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
long	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarreling	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
a	O
Verdict	O
very	O
seriously	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lawe	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lutestring	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
his	O
Wife	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
likelihood	O
his	O
Wife	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
by	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
working	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
(	O
being	O
an	O
Inkhorn-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Maklin	O
Lace	O
40s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Lace	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
ado	O
here	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
silly	O
Lace	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
but	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
yet	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
and	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
4l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bourn	O
before	O
she	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Owen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
53s	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
an	O
Evil	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
Story	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
were	O
both	O
arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
White	B-place
Fryers	I-place
in	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Whicheat	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
fortune	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
False	O
Money	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistole	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Hart	O
went	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
little	O
stir	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
good	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
frivolous	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
colour	O
of	O
a	O
misdemeanour	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Captain	O
Gardner	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Coining	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Shears	O
and	O
melting-pots	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
as	O
a	O
Corroborating	O
Evidence	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
false	O
Pieces	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
found	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
false	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
the	O
Stamp	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Coiner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
further	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Tools	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
commit	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Coining	O
False	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
100	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
pieces	O
called	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stamps	O
and	O
molds	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
mr.	O
Pattison	O
was	O
found	O
flatting	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
wash	O
it	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Captain	O
Gardner	O
had	O
a	O
private	O
Press	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
Coin	O
False	O
money	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Chamber	O
broke	O
open	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
James	O
Pattison	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
somewhat	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Stamp	O
with	O
a	O
Head	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Figures	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
False	O
shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Fault	O
upon	O
one	O
Clark	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
Jane	O
Pattison	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
James	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jane	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
have	O
succoured	O
the	O
Poor	O
of	O
the	O
Said	O
Parish	O
;	O
yet	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
indigent	O
sickly	O
Woman	O
in	O
his	O
said	O
Parish	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Pass	O
)	O
that	O
wanted	O
succour	O
and	O
nourishment	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
neglect	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
sustenance	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
coroner	O
gave	O
account	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Jury	O
sate	O
upon	O
the	O
Corps	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
sad	O
spectacle	O
,	O
eat	O
to	O
death	O
with	O
Vermin	O
almost	O
All	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
another	O
Pass	O
from	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
taking	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Barn	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
drawn	O
by	O
one	O
Horse	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
being	O
zealous	O
for	O
the	O
security	O
of	O
his	O
Parish	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
if	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
fleet	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
bury	O
her	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
sate	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
Spectacle	O
to	O
behold	O
,	O
being	O
starved	O
and	O
famished	O
to	O
death	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sustenance	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
cover	O
her	O
Nakedness	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
she	O
had	O
necessary	O
Food	O
allowed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
living	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
cautioned	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
merciful	O
in	O
his	O
Office	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Tendring	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Tendring	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
pursued	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
seen	O
Rowing	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
upon	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
naked	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
that	O
his	O
Employment	O
was	O
worth	O
300l	O
.	O
per	O
annum	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Dancing-master	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
meer	O
malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Indict	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Scandal	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
good	O
Evidence	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Guineas	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
was	O
Accused	O
for	O
Imbezzling	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Provisions	O
and	O
Habiliments	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bridgwater	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridgwater	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
14l	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
8l	O
.	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
being	O
lockt	O
up	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Name	O
given	O
her	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
Rag-gathering	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
that	O
colour	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
rob	O
people	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Crittenden	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Five	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Six-pences	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
bad	O
Repute	O
in	O
Green-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
some	O
Filings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bedmatt	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissers	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
corroborating	O
and	O
astringent	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
comes	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
wholly	O
innocent	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believed	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
from	O
Onyon	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Wroth	I-pers
and	O
Margery	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
stand	O
Attainted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
)	O
did	O
Clip	O
,	O
Cut	O
,	O
File	O
and	O
Diminish	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-Crowns	O
found	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
sick	O
in	O
Bed	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
Clipping	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
composing	O
,	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
certain	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
pamphlet	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
Great	O
Britain	O
's	O
Just	O
Complaint	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Trunk	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Hall	O
's	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
though	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
pamphlet	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
other	O
Libels	O
,	O
and	O
scandalous	O
papers	O
.	O
Neither	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Printer	O
or	O
Composer	O
of	O
the	O
Libel	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
publish	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
cloth	O
wastecoat	O
40s	O
.	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
8l	O
.	O
from	O
Frederick	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
mrs	O
Frederick	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Russell	O
's	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
abroad	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
else	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
feloniously	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
55s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
blue	O
wastecoat	O
35s	O
.	O
Green	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
(	O
being	O
not	O
well	O
)	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
5	O
.	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
John	O
Lawe	O
James	O
Pattison	O
Jane	O
Pattison	O
Susannah	O
Crittenden	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
21	O
.	O
William	O
Towers	O
Edward	O
Lock	O
Sarah	O
Tanner	O
Mary	O
Stephens	O
Elizabeth	O
Gardner	O
Elizabeth	O
Hudson	O
Elizabeth	O
Towers	O
Margaret	O
Wright	O
Margaret	O
Rutherford	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
al	O
.	O
Bird	O
Ralph	O
Lee	O
Thomas	O
Cooper	O
H	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
Amy	O
Laskey	O
Edith	O
Tyteman	O
Elinor	O
Johnson	O
Martha	O
Evans	O
Elizabeth	O
Holt	O
Mary	O
Bridgwater	O
Katherine	O
Ashley	O
Parnel	O
Crowe	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
Isaac	O
Skellum	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
William	O
Stafford	O
Jane	O
Pattison	O
,	O
and	O
Susannah	O
Crettenden	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
Empannelled	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Verdict	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Pattison	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
THE	O
Ladies	O
Dictionary	O
:	O
Being	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Entertainment	O
for	O
the	O
Fair	O
Sex	O
;	O
Work	O
never	O
attempted	O
before	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Design	O
of	O
this	O
Work	O
is	O
universal	O
,	O
and	O
concerns	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
whole	O
Sex	O
of	O
Men	O
in	O
some	O
regard	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
Women	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
neatly	O
,	O
that	O
twill	O
be	O
serviceable	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
their	O
Concerns	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
Life	O
,	O
Houses	O
,	O
Conversations	O
.	O
The	O
Author	O
throughout	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
intermixes	O
abundance	O
of	O
Secret	O
Occurrences	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
here	O
all	O
the	O
Humours	O
of	O
the	O
Times	O
at	O
the	O
bare	O
expence	O
of	O
reading	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Dunston	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
Pleasure	O
with	O
Profit	O
:	O
Consisting	O
of	O
Recreations	O
of	O
divers	O
kinds	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Numerical	O
,	O
Geometrical	O
,	O
Mathematical	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Astronomical	O
,	O
Arithmetical	O
,	O
Cryptographical	O
,	O
Magnetical	O
,	O
Authentical	O
,	O
Chymical	O
,	O
and	O
Historical	O
.	O
Published	O
to	O
Recreate	O
Ingenious	O
Spirit	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
induce	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
further	O
scrutiny	O
how	O
these	O
(	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
)	O
Sublime	O
Sciences	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
divert	O
them	O
from	O
following	O
such	O
Vices	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Youth	O
(	O
in	O
this	O
Age	O
)	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
inclin	O
'd	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Laybourn	O
,	O
Philomathes	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Work	O
is	O
also	O
Annext	O
,	O
a	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Algebra	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
lite	O
Improvements	O
,	O
applied	O
to	O
Numerical	O
Questions	O
and	O
Geometry	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
New	O
series	O
for	O
the	O
speedy	O
Extraction	O
of	O
Roots	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Converging	O
Series	O
for	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Numerical	O
Equations	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Mathematical	O
School	O
in	O
Adam	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Broadstreet	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Dutton	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
,	O
and	O
Repentance	O
.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad	O
street	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
,	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Saviour	O
of	O
his	O
People	O
from	O
Sin	O
,	O
Christ	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
the	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ne	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
preaching	O
Christ	O
.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
,	O
by	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Incomprehensibleness	O
of	O
Imputed	O
Righteousness	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
by	O
Reason	O
,	O
till	O
inlightned	O
by	O
the	O
Spirit	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
Sermons	O
,	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Reasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
against	O
Infant	O
Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
(	O
3	O
)	O
A	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
being	O
from	O
Sermons	O
,	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Assemblies	O
shorter	O
Catechism	O
,	O
with	O
Practical	O
Questions	O
.	O
By	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
of	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Christ	O
necessary	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
Curse	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Dolittle	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
N	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Diretory	O
,	O
guiding	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
way	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Extremes	O
,	O
Defect	O
and	O
Excess	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
for	O
his	O
Dead	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Mommers	O
Soliloquy	O
.	O
By	O
Thomas	O
Dolittle	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
's	O
Hope	O
at	O
Death	O
,	O
amended	O
and	O
improved	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Comfort	O
of	O
dying	O
Christians	O
,	O
and	O
Support	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Death-Bed	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
for	O
a	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
last	O
Sickness	O
.	O
By	O
Sam	O
.	O
Dolittle	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
in	O
several	O
Occasions	O
:	O
By	O
John	O
D.	O
D.	O
The	O
Almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Acts	O
20	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
By	O
Ezekial	O
Hopkins	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Londonderry	O
,	O
12o	O
.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
John	O
14	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Wherein	O
something	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
briefly	O
of	O
Justification	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Assistance	O
,	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
:	O
By	O
H.	O
Lukins	O
.	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
suddenly	O
published	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
Intituled	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ad	O
Annum	O
ejusdem	O
urbis	O
M.	O
C.XIX	O
ex	O
succesione	O
&	O
c	O
cum	O
Noblilis	O
T.	O
Fabri	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Those	O
Printed	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
Rickson	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Key	O
,	O
explaining	O
the	O
most	O
difficult	O
Passages	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
Compleat	O
in	O
Thirteen	O
Dialogues	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
large	O
Table	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
.	O
Letters	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Milton	O
,	O
to	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Sovereign	O
Princes	O
and	O
Republicks	O
of	O
Europe	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Year	O
1649.	O
till	O
the	O
Year	O
1652	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Poems	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
his	O
Works	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Grammar	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Henry	O
,	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warrington	O
.	O
The	O
Antiquity	O
and	O
Justice	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
of	O
Arbritration	O
.	O
Bishop	O
William	O
's	O
Mathematical	O
Works	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Secret	O
and	O
swift	O
Messenger	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Mathematical	O
Magick	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
World	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
Tragedy	O
,	O
in	O
Two	O
Books	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Journal	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
,	O
and	O
1693	O
.	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
last	O
Declaration	O
,	O
dated	O
at	O
St.	O
Germains	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
S.	O
N.	O
1693	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
Obedience	O
to	O
the	O
Subpoena	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Subjects	O
in	O
all	O
Revolutions	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Consideration	O
touching	O
the	O
present	O
Juncture	O
of	O
affairs	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
Nations	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Soveraigns	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Council-Board	O
by	O
the	O
Civilians	O
upon	O
the	O
Question	O
,	O
Whether	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
taken	O
at	O
Sea	O
acting	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
,	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
looked	O
on	O
as	O
Pirates	O
?	O
With	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Arguments	O
of	O
Sir	O
T.	O
P.	O
and	O
Dr.	O
Ol	O
.	O
By	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Laws	O
.	O
Those	O
Printed	O
for	O
R.	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
that	O
W.	O
Elmay	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operations	O
,	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
with	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
attends	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
On	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Elixis	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitae	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Water	O
and	O
C	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
At	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Door	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
a	O
Collegetic	O
Physician	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
till	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pills	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
whom	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
1694	O
.	O
