TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashhurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
so	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fainborrow	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bryly	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gotobed	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Newill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
;	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Bed-side	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Wind-pipe	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
choked	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
raised	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
naked	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
feigned	O
Stories	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
by	O
violence	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Meadowes	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tippet	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Green	O
Ribon	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dickson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lucock	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk-flower	O
'd	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Jacob	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Felony	O
she	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
consist	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
when	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
two	O
Head	O
Dresses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Allome	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
one	O
Mapleback	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Shift	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gown	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
which	O
Mary	O
Hill	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
Ann	O
Allome	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
affecting	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Ann	O
Hill	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kyte	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
l	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
of	O
Queenhithe	B-place
,	O
a	O
Bargeman	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
only	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Martha	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Lancett	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
one	O
Branch	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
was	O
also	O
arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tompkin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
8	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Philip	B-pers
Jennoo	I-pers
Clerk	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
Hampsted	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Bruges	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
in	O
Nettlebed	B-place
Wood	I-place
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Wastecoat	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bruges	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
)	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Nettlebed	O
Wood	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
discover	O
'd	O
at	O
Kensington	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Mr	O
Bruges	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cast	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
one	O
Gibson	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
availing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
exprest	O
his	O
sorrowful	O
Sense	O
of	O
so	O
heinous	O
an	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inticed	O
and	O
allured	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
High-way	O
man	O
by	O
evil	O
Company	O
,	O
therefore	O
hoped	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
his	O
Case	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
,	O
alias	O
Hyatt	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
price	O
7	O
l.	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
was	O
pursued	O
from	O
Paddington	O
to	O
Hampsted	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
the	O
Commitment	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Linvil	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
Abingdon	O
Road	O
at	O
Nettlebed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Countrey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Gent	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
shot	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pistoll	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Goddard	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Instant	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
Newton	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goddard	O
's	O
Chamber	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
familiar	O
Friends	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Goddard	O
catcht	O
at	O
the	O
Pistol	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
jesting	O
way	O
)	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
said	O
Goddard	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
meerly	O
by	O
Accident	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
his	O
own	O
Fault	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
thereupon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chune	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Cornet	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
Nichols	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Report	O
amongst	O
those	O
that	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-Bobs	O
and	O
a	O
Coif	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
afterwards	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Lady	O
Turner	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
deni	O
'd	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
again	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
North	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wallpoole	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
were	O
5	O
flaxen	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Towel	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wallpoole	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
near	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
almost	O
half	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Islington	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Report	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wallpoole	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fly	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
matter	O
particularly	O
debated	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
depth	O
eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
Their	O
most	O
Sacred	O
Majesties	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Roberts	O
was	O
found	O
kill	O
'd	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
Lincoln-Inn	B-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
but	O
more	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
said	O
.	O
Another	O
(	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Tovey	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
executed	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pynes	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Scamper	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
he	O
could	O
Rifle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seized	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
adding	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
Men	O
were	O
so	O
poor	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
said	O
Roberts	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
Pynes	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Tovey	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
swear	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
discover	O
the	O
Murder	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
the	O
Murder	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
Pynes	O
's	O
Associates	O
should	O
Murder	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
fit	O
now	O
to	O
divulge	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
witness	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
Lincolus-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
Roberts	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Tovey	O
met	O
Pynes	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Execution	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
would	O
now	O
swear	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Shooter	O
and	O
Roberts	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
an	O
Answer	O
thus	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Pardon	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
care	O
not	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
Ann	O
Tovey	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
Pynes	O
cofest	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
one	O
Roberts	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
tried	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Shooter	I-pers
,	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Tovey	O
and	O
Butler	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Tryal	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Adderton	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
Murther	O
;	O
and	O
Pynes	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
casting	O
Lots	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
upon	O
Robert	O
Adderton	O
,	O
who	O
wore	O
the	O
said	O
Sword	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Pynes	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Adderton	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Tovey	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Williams	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
condemned	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
swore	O
out	O
of	O
pure	O
malice	O
;	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Malson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
100	O
Half-crowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
John	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
King's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
it	O
a	O
melting	O
Pot	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
not	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
melting	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
suspicious	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
whereas	O
in	O
the	O
Womens	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Pickering	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
Clip	O
money	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
conceal	O
'd	O
it	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
,	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
discover	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
broad	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
persons	O
to	O
Clip	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
Clip	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
said	O
broad	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
Malson	O
brought	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Clippings	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Eight	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
buy	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Confederates	O
had	O
got	O
unlawfully	O
;	O
particularly	O
,	O
several	O
that	O
Pickering	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
Convict	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Gaol	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
tried	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
Matson	O
was	O
a	O
Clipper	O
,	O
only	O
had	O
Cuppings	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Luck	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
John	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Mary	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
coining	O
and	O
making	O
of	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Groats	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
's	O
Groats	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
said	O
Groats	O
publickly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Exchange	O
for	O
Counters	O
,	O
for	O
People	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
withal	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
3	O
d.	O
per	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
any	O
ways	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
design	O
or	O
prejudice	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Day	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Day	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Cornfield	O
near	O
Edmunton	B-place
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Dam	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
?	O
so	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
Robbed	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Country	O
people	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
and	O
Osver	B-pers
Ogleby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Porton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
Chattels	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
seven	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Porten	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
Lawrence	O
Spencer	O
was	O
one	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
either	O
he	O
or	O
Ogleby	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
near	O
the	O
Horse-Ferry	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pursu	O
'd	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mary-bone	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
taken	O
with	O
great	O
difficulty	O
.	O
Spencer	O
shot	O
two	O
Pistols	O
off	O
at	O
those	O
who	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Ogleby	O
run	O
one	O
man	O
through	O
the	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
slanting	O
wound	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
as	O
to	O
Ogleby	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Spencer	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Staines	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard-Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
choking	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Kennel	O
of	O
dirty	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
there	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
first	O
taxed	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
Plaister	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Breasts	O
to	O
dry	O
up	O
the	O
Milk	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
hers	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
body	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
upright	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
dirty	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
prest	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Spade	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
abundance	O
of	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
to	O
corroborate	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
murthering	O
the	O
Child	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
blows	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
died	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
quarrel	O
that	O
happened	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
Rent	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
over	O
the	O
Quarter	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
Padlockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
for	O
her	O
Clothes	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
languished	O
of	O
the	O
Blows	O
;	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
wrong	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
her	O
any	O
injury	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Searchers	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
nothing	O
of	O
harm	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
;	O
others	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
a	O
Shoemaker	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	B-place
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
)	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Groine	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
Mrs	O
Floyd	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
about	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
between	O
Floyd	O
and	O
one	O
William	O
Davis	O
:	O
Davis	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
Floyd	O
2	O
s	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
bargain	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
afterwards	O
would	O
give	O
but	O
18	O
d.	O
but	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
appeased	O
;	O
and	O
Wood	O
being	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
Mr	O
Floyd	O
and	O
he	O
quarrelled	O
anew	O
;	O
Wood	O
first	O
beginning	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Fool	O
,	O
or	O
silly	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
the	O
said	O
Floyd	O
to	O
box	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
a	O
boxing	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
had	O
Floyd	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney-corner	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Wood	O
stabbed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
,	O
first	O
holding	O
up	O
the	O
Lapit	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Look	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
death	O
's	O
wound	O
;	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
Wood	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
extenuated	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Floyd	O
ran	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Floyd	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
on	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
see	O
there	O
Deceased	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Finger	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Floyd	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wood	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
thrust	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Sword	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
as	O
a	O
Corroborating	O
Proof	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
Father-in-law	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
which	O
Wood	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
declared	O
too	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
summed	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
(	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
had	O
Persons	O
in	O
Court	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
malice	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
30	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Nine-pences	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
hearing	O
some	O
noise	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Clipper	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
through	O
a	O
Chink	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
a	O
Clipping	O
;	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
search	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Garret	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
fyling	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
more	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
newly	O
clipt	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
filed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Nine-pences	O
,	O
besides	O
Files	O
,	O
Shears	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
clip	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
.	O
Being	O
under	O
fear	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
practised	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
again	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
clip	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Grub	O
street	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
allow	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
for	O
Clipping	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
strived	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
fear	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pennington	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
.	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Turnstyle	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Cap	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Sleves	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pynner	O
and	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyeton	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Betty	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
an	O
Iron	O
to	O
wri	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
or	O
Chests	O
,	O
used	O
by	O
most	O
House	O
breakers	O
)	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
dozen	O
of	O
Padlocks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Padlocks	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Spurrell	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
upon	O
oath	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Spurrell	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Joan	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
price	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Horse	O
wast	O
lost	O
near	O
Gloster	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
for	O
London	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
two	O
miles	O
of	O
Windover	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
swopt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
to	O
boot	O
for	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
and	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
of	O
one	O
Clark	B-pers
of	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
some	O
Tippets	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
good	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Bayliff	I-pers
,	O
as	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
80	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
Cloth	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
80	O
yards	O
of	O
Manchester	O
Bays	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Bayliffe	O
having	O
no	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
trust	O
by	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Tom	O
the	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pennell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witness	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Beech	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Pennell	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
part	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Allen	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Pennell	O
,	O
nor	O
with	O
Thompson	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
Pennell	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
somewhat	O
obscure	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Swords	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
joined	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Swords	O
to	O
May	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
morning	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
May	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Swords	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
May	O
's	O
Chamber	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
lookt	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
defective	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ethelbert	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
aged	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
full	O
proof	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
her	O
any	O
real	O
hurt	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bakebind	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
10	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Denn	I-pers
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
near	O
Clothfair	B-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
;	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
saying	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
strongest	O
man	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
rambling	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
witness	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
aged	O
about	O
Nine	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
first	O
the	O
Chyrurgions	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
much	O
abused	O
;	O
having	O
a	O
large	O
Tumor	O
in	O
the	O
Lower	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
fetid	O
stinking	O
Matter	O
issued	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Secret	O
Parts	O
were	O
much	O
lacerated	O
and	O
turn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
also	O
declared	O
her	O
Opinion	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Chyrurgeons	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
enticed	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Currance	O
,	O
and	O
thenher	O
Body	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
hold	O
her	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
more	O
Currance	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
injur	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
the	O
Child	O
the	O
Mother	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
put	O
the	O
Girl	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
show	O
them	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
misus	O
'd	O
:	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
strait	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Door	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Eales	O
lived	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eales	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
proves	O
First	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
Indictment	O
charged	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
of	O
Evil	O
Repute	O
.	O
And	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
modest	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
ingenious	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Account	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Eales	O
give	O
such	O
ample	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
a	O
Verdict	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
near	O
Chelsey	B-place
a	O
place	O
called	O
Bloody-Bridge	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1692.	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
several	O
Guinea	O
's	O
a	O
silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
Chelsey	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Soldier	O
's	O
habit	O
,	O
who	O
past	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Crawley	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Civil	O
;	O
Ay	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
stript	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Ditch-side	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Reading	O
Gaol	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
strived	O
to	O
invalidate	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
besides	O
he	O
broke	O
Reading	O
Gaol	O
.	O
Philip	O
Macquire	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Crawley	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Bowen	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Ireland	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturges	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Wilmot	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Wilmot	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
Jenkins	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
Wilmot	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Notorious	O
woman	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jewster	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Paul	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Le-grand	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jane	B-pers
Le	I-pers
grant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
Liberty	I-place
;	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
900	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Madam	O
Le	O
grand	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	B-pers
Larroe	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
betwixt	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Some-body	O
knockt	O
at	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
(	O
who	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
500	O
l	O
)	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Composition	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
thrust	O
some	O
Rags	O
and	O
a	O
ty	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
,	O
which	O
choked	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Bags	O
of	O
money	O
and	O
filled	O
their	O
Pockets	O
,	O
some	O
falling	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
but	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Larroe	O
lay	O
upon	O
her	O
Face	O
through	O
Fear	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
kill	O
'd	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
dead	O
within	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
likewise	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
lookt	O
very	O
suspiciously	O
,	O
walk	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
Jewster	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
yet	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
thus	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
consenting	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Butler	O
,	O
Paul	O
Grove	O
,	O
Edward	O
Hinton	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Francis	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
five	O
persons	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
William	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
concerned	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
expressed	O
with	O
great	O
Reluctancy	O
,	O
wringing	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
John	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
dead	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
tied	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mouth	O
full	O
of	O
Rags	O
,	O
tied	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mouth	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
Rags	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
full	O
as	O
to	O
choke	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
found	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
's	O
Neck	O
tied	O
fast	O
to	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
twisted	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
drawn	O
through	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
and	O
ugly	O
sight	O
to	O
behold	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Butler	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
seen	O
near	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
and	O
Burglary	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sword	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
Old	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Sword	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
altered	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
again	O
Arraigned	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Jewster	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
again	O
repeated	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Butler	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Offer	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Le-grand	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
compounding	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
John	O
Jewster	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
or	O
keep	O
Guard	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
told	O
how	O
that	O
Madam	O
Le-grand	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
Money	O
enough	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Frances	O
Jewster	O
,	O
but	O
presumptive	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
Butler	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
John	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Kems	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hellowes	I-pers
House	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Headclothes	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
Mr.	O
Hellowes	O
and	O
his	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
over	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
rifled	O
the	O
Trunks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
swearing	O
great	O
Oaths	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Lord	O
's	O
Pocket	O
within	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hellowes	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wilson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holsters	O
with	O
Housing	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
Hyatt	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mr	O
Allens	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Acton	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Mare	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
'rid	O
out	O
with	O
,	O
which	O
lookt	O
very	O
suspicious	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
other	O
coloured	O
Beasts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Linvell	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
at	O
Nettlebed	O
,	O
beyond	O
Henly	O
upon	O
Thames	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Hyat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hyat	O
brought	O
his	O
Mare	O
to	O
Acton	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
three	O
Yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Satchel	O
lying	O
before	O
John	O
Newell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
searching	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
therein	O
five	O
large	O
Ingots	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
weighing	O
726	O
Ounces	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
seized	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Serjeant	O
Bonithans	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
his	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
divers	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ingots	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
to	O
create	O
Fire	O
to	O
melt	O
Silver	O
withal	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
found	O
melting	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
strong	O
Doors	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
Foot	O
betwixt	O
them	O
to	O
hinder	O
any	O
sudden	O
passage	O
.	O
John	O
Newell	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
Horse-Coursing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Newell	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
:	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
[	O
John	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Sarah	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
Common-Pleas	O
Court	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Hat	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk-wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
Perukes	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath-gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
said	O
his	O
Housewas	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
taking	O
an	O
Iron-bar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Black-a-more	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
;	O
viz	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Hancherchief	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
theives	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doyley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hedgcock	I-pers
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
they	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
Mooney	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
dress	O
Hedgcock	O
's	O
Children	O
;	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Mooney	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
Lodged	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
face	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Doyley	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Mooney	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
of	O
3	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Taffaty	O
Ribon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scarlets	O
for	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
process	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
found	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Butterfeild	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Batly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
cloth	O
Caps	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
foolish	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Baily	O
's	O
Daughter	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
me	O
a	O
Black	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tippet	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
a	O
Dancing-School	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Play	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Rambling	O
Story	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Witness	O
;	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Parliament	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
of	O
10	O
Ells	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Williams	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Botley	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
no	O
Fees	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Chair	O
man	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
snipping	O
of	O
Shears	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
stood	O
just	O
opposite	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
hanging	O
loosly	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Head-cloaths	O
all	O
off	O
,	O
much	O
surprized	O
.	O
Hewet	O
had	O
a	O
Straw-Hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
Hancock	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
loose	O
about	O
her	O
too	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Rug	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
to	O
rub	O
the	O
Money	O
with	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
plainly	O
evidenced	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
all	O
deni	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
calling	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
themselves	O
fairly	O
in	O
their	O
Dealings	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
Hewet	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
accidentally	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hancock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
Clipping	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Hancock	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Hancock	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Osbert	B-pers
Oglevey	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
were	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
before	O
tried	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
50	O
s	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Rich	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
kill	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
Vizard	O
Caps	O
on	O
which	O
came	O
over	O
their	O
Faces	O
with	O
Mouth-holes	O
and	O
Eye-holes	O
,	O
of	O
divers	O
Colours	O
,	O
very	O
frightful	O
to	O
behold	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
Rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
bound	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
100	O
l	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
in	O
the	O
single	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Lawrence	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
,	O
whose	O
Husband	O
was	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
such	O
sorts	O
of	O
Vizard-Caps	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
commonly	O
changed	O
among	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
his	O
share	O
being	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
seemed	O
not	O
very	O
credible	O
in	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
Opinion	O
,	O
she	O
alledging	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
her	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Lavenoe	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ell	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
6	O
Frocks	O
,	O
10	O
dozen	O
of	O
wosted	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Brin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Pynes	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
sworn	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
Clipping	O
a	O
Half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
Clippings	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Another	O
Woman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Walter	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
to	O
her	O
Broad	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
seemed	O
somewhat	O
forward	O
in	O
their	O
prosecution	O
,	O
favouring	O
of	O
Envy	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
tried	O
alone	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Mary	O
Walters	O
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Pynes	O
,	O
alias	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
actually	O
a	O
Clipping	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
attested	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Shears	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Woman	O
)	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
first	O
taken	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
Clipping	O
was	O
a	O
Crime	O
against	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Sin	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proffer	O
'd	O
her	O
7	O
s.	O
Week	O
,	O
Meat	O
,	O
Drink	O
,	O
Washing	O
and	O
Lodging	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
change	O
Money	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
knock	O
any	O
Man	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
her	O
Shears	O
,	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
Clipping	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
plain	O
and	O
positively	O
sworn	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
from	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
value	O
about	O
6	O
l.	O
Hunt	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Alexander	O
Reynold	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
enticed	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Coffee	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Night-royles	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
Alexander	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
bad	O
Repute	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
Infamous	O
Woman	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bilcon	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
Found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Tippet	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hebben	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Grimes	B-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
Laced	O
Head-dresses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
23	O
.	O
William	O
Brown	O
John	O
Cook	O
Martha	O
Shorter	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
Charles	O
Pynes	O
Robert	O
Adderton	O
P	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Lawrence	O
Spencer	O
Matthew	O
Davis	O
William	O
Butler	O
John	O
Jewster	O
Hugh	O
Bowen	O
Sarah	O
Wilmot	O
William	O
Lord	O
John	O
Kems	O
Edward	O
East	O
John	O
Newell	O
Sarah	O
Newell	O
John	O
Wilkinson	O
Mary	O
Wilkinson	O
Jane	O
Hancock	O
Mary	O
Walters	O
Charles	O
Norman	O
.	O
Called	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
Four	O
,	O
who	O
likewise	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	O
Davis	O
Christian	O
Caffey	O
Elizabeth	O
Higgs	O
Susan	O
Williams	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
16	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Bishop	O
Elizabeth	O
Meadows	O
Elizabeth	O
Osbourne	O
Elizabeth	O
Hickson	O
Mary	O
Hill	O
Ann	O
Allome	O
Elizabeth	O
James	O
John	O
Wood	O
George	O
Briggs	O
Mary	O
Cheshire	O
Elizabeth	O
Yeomans	O
Jane	O
Steward	O
Katherine	O
Sutton	O
Elinor	O
Clark	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
Thomas	O
Barloe	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
7	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Chune	O
Ann	O
May	O
Charles	O
Povey	O
Mary	O
Mooney	O
Mary	O
Foster	O
Martha	O
Butterfield	O
Ann	O
Bilton	O
.	O
Mary	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Newell	O
,	O
Jane	O
Hancock	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Walters	O
;	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Empannelled	O
and	O
Sworn	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
who	O
returned	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Pantagruel	O
's	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
and	O
Fifth	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
Francis	O
Rebelias	O
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
With	O
the	O
Pantagruelian	O
Prognostication	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Verse	O
and	O
Prose	O
by	O
that	O
Author	O
:	O
Also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
Compleating	O
all	O
his	O
Works	O
that	O
are	O
Extant	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
.	O
With	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
on	O
every	O
Chapter	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
EUtropii	O
Historia	O
Romana	O
Brevarum	O
ab	O
urbe	O
Conditd	O
usque	O
ad	O
Valentinianum	O
&	O
Valentem	O
Augustos	O
;	O
ex	O
recensione	O
&	O
cam	O
notalis	O
Tan	O
.	O
Fabri	O
,	O
ut	O
&	O
Sexti	O
Aureln	O
Victoris	O
de	O
Viris	O
Illustribus	O
Liber	O
in	O
usum	O
Scholarum	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
Diseburse	O
on	O
John	O
14	O
Wherein	O
something	O
is	O
also	O
briefly	O
attempted	O
for	O
clearing	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Faith	O
,	O
of	O
Justification	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Assurance	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
;	O
and	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Conversion	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Holiness	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
English	O
Exercises	O
for	O
School-Boys	O
to	O
Translate	O
into	O
Latin	O
,	O
comprizing	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Grammar	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Necessary	O
Observations	O
ascending	O
gradually	O
from	O
the	O
meanest	O
to	O
the	O
higher	O
Capacities	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Garretson	O
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Week	O
of	O
Soliloquies	O
and	O
Prayers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preparation	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Communion	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Devotions	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
this	O
Edition	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Peter	O
Dumoulin	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Gradus	O
ad	O
Pernassum	O
five	O
Novus	O
Synonimorum	O
Epitheterum	O
Phrasium	O
&	O
Poetarum	O
at	O
Versution	O
Thesaurus	O
,	O
Smetium	O
,	O
Januam	O
Musarum	O
,	O
Delectum	O
Epithetorum	O
,	O
Parnassuin	O
Poeticum	O
,	O
Eligantias	O
Poeticas	O
,	O
Thesaurum	O
Virgilis	O
;	O
aliosque	O
ommes	O
id	O
genus	O
Libros	O
ad	O
Poesin	O
Necessarios	O
complecteris	O
.	O
Ab	O
uno	O
e	O
Societate	O
Jesu	O
.	O
Editio	O
Novissima	O
.	O
Geography	O
Rectified	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Kingdoms	O
,	O
Provinces	O
,	O
Countries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
their	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Present	O
Names	O
,	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
Scituations	O
,	O
Histories	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Governments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
their	O
Commodities	O
,	O
Coins	O
,	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
compared	O
with	O
those	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Seventy	O
Eight	O
New	O
Maps	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
enlarged	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Compleat	O
Geographical	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
Alphabetically	O
digested	O
.	O
4to	O
.	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart-Work	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel	O
Minister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Annesley	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Things	O
not	O
seen	O
:	O
Or	O
divers	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Holy	O
Men	O
after	O
Death	O
:	O
By	O
that	O
eminently	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
,	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Tongue	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Poems	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pastoral	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Tutelin	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
,	O
Rife	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
against	O
Insant	O
Baptisin	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavel	O
's	O
Remains	O
,	O
being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
:	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
,	O
and	O
Repentance	O
,	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad	O
street	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
Cole	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
;	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
Cole	O
Christus	O
in	O
Corde	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Mystic	O
Union	O
between	O
Christ	O
and	O
Believers	O
considered	O
in	O
its	O
References	O
,	O
Bonds	O
,	O
Seals	O
,	O
Priviledges	O
and	O
Marks	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
the	O
Gospel	O
of	O
Peace	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
Spitis	O
:	O
Being	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
divers	O
Somon	O
,	O
from	O
Eph	O
6	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
Prov	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
32.	O
lately	O
preached	O
by	O
John	O
Faldo	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Precious	O
Faith	O
considered	O
in	O
its	O
Nature	O
,	O
Working	O
,	O
and	O
Growth	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhall	O
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
Liturgies	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
,	O
Mr.	O
David	O
Clerkson	O
.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Assemblies	O
Shorter	O
Catechism	O
,	O
with	O
Practical	O
Inferences	O
from	O
each	O
Question	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
.	O
These	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
The	O
Four	O
Epistles	O
of	O
A.	O
G.	O
Busbequens	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Embassy	O
into	O
Turky	O
.	O
Being	O
Remarks	O
upon	O
the	O
Religion	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Riches	O
,	O
Strength	O
,	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
that	O
People	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
their	O
Chief	O
Cities	O
,	O
and	O
Places	O
of	O
Trade	O
and	O
Commerce	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Advice	O
how	O
to	O
Manage	O
War	O
against	O
the	O
Turks	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Taylor	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Wyat	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Churchyard	O
.	O
1694	O
.	O
The	O
Bounds	O
set	O
to	O
France	O
by	O
the	O
Pyrenean	O
Treaty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
Confederates	O
not	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
Offers	O
of	O
Peace	O
made	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
short	O
Reflections	O
,	O
showing	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
England	O
is	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Restitution	O
of	O
that	O
Treaty	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
Towns	O
and	O
Countries	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
have	O
taken	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
;	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
Can	O
testifis	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarisin	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Discases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vice	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vicae	O
.	O
An	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
Pawders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
the	O
casing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
humane	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
L	O
.	O
