TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Randal	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Helder	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Aubrey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Fowkes	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Scale	I-pers
Twenty	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin-Cloath	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Lumbardstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
being	O
abroad	O
about	O
his	O
occasions	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
rang	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
Servant	O
if	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
expected	O
her	O
master	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
Brown	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
unknown	O
to	O
Hutton	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
alledged	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Broker-Woman	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
for	O
Three	O
Shillings	O
Six-pence	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
Brown	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Hutton	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridget	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Faringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Leonard	B-pers
Fitzbugh	I-pers
one	O
Iron	O
Fire-grate	O
with	O
Brasses	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
her	O
way	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Fitzbugh	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
wounding	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Hancks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
One	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Three	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
talking	O
about	O
Bishops	O
,	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
lied	O
;	O
Howard	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
parted	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Howard	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
struck	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
former	O
malice	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Bedfellows	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
expressed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
for	O
committing	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Knife	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Canvas-bag	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesad	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
pinn	O
'd	O
within	O
side	O
her	O
Shift	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Pick-locks	O
and	O
a	O
Chizzel	O
found	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
taking	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Common-Pleas	O
Bar	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
pretending	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
familiarity	O
with	O
evil	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
by	O
Magick	O
Arts	O
she	O
could	O
discover	O
where	O
Treasure	O
was	O
hid	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
wander	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
until	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
next	O
following	O
;	O
with	O
her	O
Insinuations	O
she	O
persuaded	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Daughter	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Treasure	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
She	O
likewise	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-hafted	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
bid	O
the	O
young	O
Damsel	O
put	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Treasure	O
was	O
hid	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
secretly	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
supposed	O
Treasure	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockins	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gunport	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Crevat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
;	O
it	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-loft	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
climb	O
over	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
open	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
called	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
clip	O
above	O
hundred	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
White-Fryars	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
she	O
had	O
Clippings	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
woman	O
:	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Franck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
above	O
20	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
three	B-place
Sugar-loaves	I-place
in	O
Bond	I-place
Stables	I-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
Three	B-place
legged	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	O
New-street	I-place
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
charged	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
from	O
behind	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
her	O
Bodies	O
.	O
and	O
Clip	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
20	O
s.	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
Clip	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Party	O
had	O
their	O
Money	O
again	O
with	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
advance	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
much	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
York	I-pers
alias	O
Anguish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
Clip	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaves	I-place
in	O
Bond	I-place
Stables	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Clipped	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
an	O
ill	O
liver	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Goreing	I-pers
alias	O
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
not	O
weighing	O
the	O
Duty	O
and	O
Allegiance	O
to	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
did	O
Clip	O
,	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
Diminish	O
,	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
Lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
York	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Clip	O
together	O
at	O
one	O
anothers	O
house	O
in	O
Three	B-place
legged	I-place
Ally	I-place
in	O
Newstreet	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Ill	O
Liver	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bruerton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
One	O
SilverTankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
Two	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
3	O
l.	O
Four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
2	O
l.	O
Three	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Three	O
Silver	O
Casters	O
9	O
l.	O
Three	O
Silver	O
Saltsellers	O
1	O
l.	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
hastily	O
away	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
Manning	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
her	O
Master	O
should	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
passionate	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Henfrey	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boy	O
s	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Black-friars	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Winchester	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Diamond	O
Earing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
tempted	O
the	O
Boy	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
Pictures	O
,	O
and	O
Henfrey	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Arm	O
round	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ear	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1170	O
yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
476	O
yards	O
of	O
Hair	O
Camblet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Alvarin	B-pers
Decostin	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Allhallows-Barkin	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murther	O
and	O
Wilful	O
Poysoning	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Artis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
most	O
cruel	O
and	O
barbarous	O
Man	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
evil	O
treating	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
beaten	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Horse-whip	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
sufficient	O
Testimonies	O
of	O
his	O
hatred	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
beaten	O
her	O
very	O
sore	O
with	O
at	O
Bulls	O
Pizzel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
Miscarry	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
base	O
Wretch	O
would	O
suffer	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
her	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
ill	O
Liver	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Assizes	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
said	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
seemingly	O
shewed	O
more	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
admire	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Sweet	O
meats	O
,	O
called	O
Gelley	O
of	O
Rasberries	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
infused	O
the	O
White	O
Mercury	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
mistrusting	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
eat	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Night	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
Lightness	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
violent	O
Vomiting	O
and	O
Looseness	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
so	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Husband	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
something	O
that	O
should	O
make	O
her	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Opium	O
in	O
a	O
drinking	O
Potion	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Opium	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
Spoonfuls	O
of	O
Poppy-water	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Drops	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Hartshorn	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
any	O
wrong	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Morris	O
and	O
Anderson	O
came	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
where	O
Jefferson	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
drest	O
with	O
Coleworts	O
.	O
Morris	O
brought	O
Jefferson	O
some	O
meat	O
upon	O
a	O
Trencher	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
attempted	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Loyns	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
fetcht	O
Anderson	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
catcht	O
hold	O
on	O
Jefferson	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Stick	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
whilst	O
Anderson	O
run	O
his	O
Sword	O
into	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Jefferson	O
having	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
struck	O
first	O
Anderson	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Anderson	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Morris	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
alias	O
Burd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather-Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Crlpplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Burdet	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
printed	O
Stuff-Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
Woollen-Blanket	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Johnson	O
took	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
Jones	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Rent	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
unto	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
went	O
away	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Floyd	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
Johnson	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
39	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin-Cloath	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
Pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
were	O
stopt	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Starving	O
and	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Arnold	O
being	O
imprisoned	O
in	O
Tooley	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	B-place
,	O
the	O
said	O
Tooley	O
did	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
sufficient	O
Sustenance	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
allowed	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
day	O
for	O
his	O
Subsistence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
deprive	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Insurrection	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
Tooley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
and	O
destroyed	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
released	O
his	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
deceased	O
Arnold	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
famished	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
feeble	O
and	O
weak	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
Tooley	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
most	O
doleful	O
Cries	O
in	O
Tooly	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
poor	O
Wretch	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
that	O
runthrough	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stuck	O
to	O
his	O
Back	O
like	O
a	O
Searcloath	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
as	O
Leather	O
.	O
Another	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
in	O
Tooley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
allowed	O
no	O
more	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
Porringer	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
for	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
300	O
Men	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
trepand	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Tooley	O
,	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
usage	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bread	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
was	O
full	O
size	O
;	O
that	O
each	O
Man	O
had	O
a	O
Penny-loaf	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Cheese	O
for	O
his	O
Breakfast	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Mess	O
of	O
Broath	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Penny-loaf	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
good	O
Beef	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sick	O
men	O
were	O
very	O
carefully	O
looked	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
their	O
Stomacks	O
were	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
eat	O
Meat	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
Water-Gruel	O
,	O
Mace-Ale	O
,	O
Thick	O
Milk	O
,	O
Sugar-Sops	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bellet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
coyned	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
called	O
Half-Crowns	O
;	O
forty	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
called	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
twenty	O
other	O
pieces	O
,	O
called	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
a	O
Sledge	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
ready	O
mounted	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Clipt-money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Filings	O
of	O
Silver	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
lately	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Rabbets	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
and	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
37	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
West	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
Peruque	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Casement	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
prove	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
into	O
one	O
Bed	O
bound	O
and	O
Gagged	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
one	O
as	O
guard	O
over	O
them	O
whilst	O
they	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Butler	O
had	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
bind	O
them	O
.	O
Butler	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
T	O
-	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
testified	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Hedgerley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Bucks	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
one	O
Morris	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
.	O
Rawson	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Moneys	O
was	O
,	O
upon	O
Norton	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aubrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
was	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
Coach-harness-maker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journey	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
wrought	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
kept	O
Men	O
at	O
work	O
privately	O
making	O
of	O
Harness	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Journey-men	O
themselves	O
that	O
Kemp	O
had	O
employed	O
,	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
Kemp	O
gave	O
them	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
after	O
work	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
enjoyned	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
corrupted	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
spun	O
Flax	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
,	O
to	O
spin	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Silk	O
Grass	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
disposed	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
charged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
,	O
who	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
likewise	O
got	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
very	O
fine	O
Harness	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
any	O
rate	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
proved	O
the	O
very	O
Buckles	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
Kemp	O
's	O
Trust	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
it	O
plainly	O
appeared	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
Master	O
great	O
wrong	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Aubrey	O
leave	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Action	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Heston	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
falsely	O
and	O
traiterously	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
forge	O
and	O
stamp	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Gold	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfet	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
used	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
Bayl	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Constable	O
desired	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
accordingly	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
covered	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mill	O
'd	O
Shilling	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Coin	O
;	O
and	O
four	O
foot	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
Earth	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Manager	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Fly	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
askt	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bespoke	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Elm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
directions	O
for	O
cutting	O
of	O
Mortices	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Timber	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Mill	O
in	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Draught	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Carpenter	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
What	O
need	O
you	O
care	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Trench	O
made	O
under	O
ground	O
a	O
hundred	O
foot	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Trap-door	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
escape	O
into	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
Danger	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
for	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
for	O
one	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
those	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
wasindicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico-Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Printed-Cloath	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Customers	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cecil	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ladds	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
assaulting	O
and	O
wounding	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mugglestone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
their	O
Duty	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messengers	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Hay-market	I-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rescue	O
some	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
open	O
Street	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Centinels	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
Dutch	O
Dogs	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
sacrifice	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Land	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
get	O
you	O
gone	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
here	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
discharge	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
replyed	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
set	O
there	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Orders	O
he	O
must	O
obey	O
.	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Centinel	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Counsel	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
designed	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Leo	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Forging	O
and	O
making	O
Three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
other	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
information	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
with	O
Metal	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
Rubbing	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Comb-Case	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
the	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
Rubbing	O
Leather	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
Trade	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Battson	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Battson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
10	O
peices	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
called	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
mistrusting	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Trade	O
,	O
acquainted	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
under	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
six	O
great	O
lumps	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
her	O
husband	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
hath	O
not	O
been	O
seen	O
since	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bettridge	I-pers
Forty	O
Shillings	O
of	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Indempnity	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
Bar	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
Reginald	B-pers
Shevery	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Villers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Riot	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
lane	I-place
.	O
And	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fenwick	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
in	O
Execution	O
until	O
payment	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Mary	O
Mitchell	O
Mary	O
Booker	O
Ann	O
York	O
Dorothy	O
Goreing	O
Edmund	O
Allen	O
Elizabeth	O
Mitchell	O
David	O
Anderson	O
Sarah	O
Morris	O
Charles	O
Bellet	O
Richard	O
Butler	O
John	O
Moore	O
Leo	O
Norman	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
S	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
Alice	O
Steephens	O
Jane	O
Browne	O
Samuel	O
Howard	O
Elizabeth	O
Bruerton	O
Mary	O
Hering	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
Sarah	O
Floyd	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Walker	O
Edward	O
Toms	O
Elizabeth	O
Steward	O
William	O
Green	O
Richard	O
Henfrey	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Cecil	O
Bishop	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
;	O
Walter	O
Hastings	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
;	O
John	O
Ladds	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
;	O
Edward	O
Ley	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
:	O
And	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
they	O
Pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
Mary	O
Booker	O
,	O
Ann	O
York	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Goreing	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Morris	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
Impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockersh	O
,	O
Sent	O
&	O
Jun	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
A	O
Free	O
Discourse	O
against	O
Customary	O
Swearing	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Diffuasive	O
from	O
Cursing	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Honourable	O
Robert	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
8vo	O
.	O
Sermons	O
preached	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Conant	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Geography	O
Rectified	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Kingdoms	O
,	O
Provinces	O
,	O
Countries	O
,	O
Islands	O
,	O
Cities	O
,	O
Towns	O
,	O
Seas	O
,	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Bays	O
,	O
Capes	O
,	O
Ports	O
,	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
Scituations	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Commodities	O
,	O
Government	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
about	O
80	O
Maps	O
.	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Morden	O
.	O
4to	O
.	O
A	O
Demonstration	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Principles	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Applications	O
of	O
the	O
Apocalypse	O
.	O
By	O
Drue	O
Cressener	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
4to	O
Conformity	O
of	O
the	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Discipline	O
of	O
the	O
Reform	O
'd	O
Churches	O
of	O
France	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Primitive	O
Christians	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Laroque	O
.	O
4to	O
.	O
A	O
Practical	O
Grammar	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Easiest	O
and	O
Shortest	O
way	O
to	O
Initiate	O
Young	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Latine	O
Tongue	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
Geography	O
Anatomiz	O
'd	O
;	O
Or	O
a	O
compleat	O
Geographical	O
Grammar	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
short	O
and	O
exact	O
Analysis	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Body	O
of	O
Modern	O
Geography	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
new	O
,	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
easy	O
method	O
;	O
whereby	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
attain	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
that	O
most	O
noble	O
and	O
useful	O
Science	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoined	O
the	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
European	O
Plantations	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
and	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
reasonable	O
Proposal	O
for	O
the	O
Propagation	O
of	O
the	O
blessed	O
Gospel	O
in	O
all	O
Pagan	O
Countries	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divets	O
Maps	O
.	O
By	O
Patrick	O
Gordon	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
Man	O
after	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
.	O
Essays	O
on	O
Trade	O
and	O
Navigation	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Francis	O
Brewster	O
,	O
Knight	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Future	O
State	O
:	O
A	O
Discourse	O
attempting	O
some	O
display	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
's	O
Happiness	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
that	O
Eternally	O
Progressive	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
is	O
among	O
the	O
Blessed	O
in	O
Heaven	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Countrey	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Reasonableness	O
of	O
Personal	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Conversion	O
.	O
The	O
true	O
Method	O
of	O
making	O
all	O
men	O
happy	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
By	O
J.	O
F.	O
English	O
Exercises	O
for	O
School-boys	O
to	O
Translate	O
into	O
Latin	O
,	O
comprizing	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Grammar	O
,	O
and	O
othet	O
necessary	O
Observations	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Garretson	O
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nathanael	O
Heywood	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
Ormeskirk	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
.	O
Who	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
44th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
,	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Hugh	O
Lord	O
Willoughby	O
,	O
by	O
Sir	O
H.	O
Ashhurst	O
,	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Acts	O
26	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Blow	O
at	O
Prophaneness	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Ezekiel	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Londonderry	O
.	O
A	O
Week	O
of	O
Soliloquies	O
and	O
Prayers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preparation	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Communion	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Peter	O
Du	O
Moulen	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
A	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
English	O
Protestant	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
principal	O
Points	O
of	O
both	O
Religions	O
are	O
truly	O
proposed	O
and	O
examined	O
.	O
By	O
Matthew	O
Pool	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
Synopsis	O
Criticerum	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
Introduction	O
to	O
English	O
Orthography	O
,	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
True	O
Spelling	O
.	O
By	O
Richard	O
Masher	O
.	O
Familtaria	O
Colloquia	O
,	O
opera	O
Christopheri	O
Helvici	O
,	O
D	O
&	O
Professoris	O
Gressensis	O
cum	O
ex	O
Erasmo	O
Roterodamo	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Instrumentaliry	O
of	O
Faith	O
asserted	O
,	O
proved	O
,	O
explained	O
,	O
compared	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
preferred	O
to	O
a	O
Conditional	O
Relation	O
thereof	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Pardon	O
and	O
Happiness	O
,	O
when	O
strictly	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Legal	O
or	O
Foederal	O
sense	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Cross	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
on	O
the	O
Resurrection	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
By	O
Walter	O
Cross	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Good	O
Deeds	O
done	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Butt	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
appointed	O
for	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Fleet	O
.	O
By	O
Ed	O
.	O
Veal	O
.	O
Infant-Baptism	O
God	O
's	O
Ordinance	O
;	O
or	O
clear	O
proof	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
believing	O
Parents	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
Baptism	O
the	O
now	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Infant-Seed	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
had	O
to	O
Circumcision	O
,	O
the	O
then	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
.	O
By	O
Michael	O
Harrison	O
.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
in	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
John	O
14.	O
s.	O
Wherein	O
something	O
is	O
also	O
briefly	O
attempted	O
,	O
for	O
clearing	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Faith	O
,	O
of	O
Justification	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Afforance	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
;	O
and	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Conversion	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Holiness	O
.	O
By	O
Henry	O
Lukin	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
against	O
their	O
late	O
Speaker	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Ancient	O
Constitution	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
As	O
well	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
Administration	O
,	O
as	O
Succession	O
thereof	O
.	O
Set	O
forth	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Dialogue	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
men	O
of	O
ordinary	O
Learning	O
and	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
true	O
Lover	O
of	O
his	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Remarkable	O
Sayings	O
,	O
Apothegms	O
and	O
Maxims	O
of	O
the	O
Eastern	O
Nations	O
;	O
Abstracted	O
and	O
translated	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
Books	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
Arabian	O
,	O
Persian	O
and	O
Turkish	O
Language	O
;	O
With	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Monsieur	O
Galland	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
many	O
years	O
in	O
those	O
Countries	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
.	O
The	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Declaration	O
for	O
settling	O
the	O
general	O
Poll-Tax	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
his	O
Edict	O
,	O
ordering	O
all	O
Communities	O
,	O
both	O
Regular	O
and	O
Secular	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
particular	O
Persons	O
(	O
who	O
have	O
any	O
Water	O
from	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Springs	O
,	O
and	O
Fountains	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
whether	O
for	O
the	O
Ornament	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
or	O
Improving	O
of	O
their	O
Estates	O
)	O
to	O
pay	O
such	O
Sums	O
as	O
shall	O
be	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
Council	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Waters	O
confirmed	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Given	O
at	O
Fountainbleau	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
1694.	O
and	O
Recorded	O
in	O
Parliament	O
.	O
The	O
Wooks	O
of	O
F.	O
Rabelais	O
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
in	O
five	O
Books	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Heroic	O
Deeds	O
and	O
Sayings	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantugruel	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Mottoux	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
Printed	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elony	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
Practice	O
,	O
leveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolve	O
,	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Bad	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
THE	O
person	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
Is	O
now	O
removed	O
into	O
Essex	O
Court	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
hand	O
,	O
where	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Deutrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
,	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
L	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freekles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
is	O
likewise	O
sold	O
at	O
these	O
places	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Milners	O
in	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Suttons	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Exchange-Ally	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
Cane-shops	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hamptons	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Miners	O
Semstress	O
in	O
the	O
Inner	O
Temple	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Labrahams	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Blew	O
Anchor	O
Alley	O
,	O
overagainst	O
the	O
Artillery-Ground	O
,	O
on	O
Bunhill	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Palmers	O
House	O
on	O
Clay-hill	O
at	O
Epsom	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
mistakes	O
and	O
counterfeits	O
,	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
In	O
Grays	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
Door	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
may	O
read	O
him	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Athenian	O
Mercury	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
all	O
Coffee-Houses	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
unto	O
all	O
that	O
write	O
or	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
LOST	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Griffet	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sugar-loaf	O
near	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
White	O
Italian-Greyhound	O
Dog	O
,	O
Walley	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
dark	O
blue	O
Spots	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
almost	O
in	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Triangle	O
.	O
Whoever	O
brings	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
gives	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffet	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Coffee	O
house	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Reward	O
.	O
