TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1695.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
;	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plaisted	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Pendle	I-pers
William	B-pers
Roome	I-pers
Nathanael	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Wister	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Raworth	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sherrey	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Dormer	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
Crispe	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hatebett	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Elias	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
are	O
these	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Green	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Keymer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
forty	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
Medal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
eight	O
Pound	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
Box	O
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
seal	O
eight	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cover	O
of	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuffdish	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
double	O
Gilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
Sable	O
Muss	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Golden	O
Locket	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Precious	I-pers
alias	O
Browne	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Star	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
White-Fryers	B-place
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
Drinking	O
,	O
Precious	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catcht	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Precious	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Breeches	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
fell	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Blewit	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Night-walkers	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
lived	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Chrstian	B-pers
Brothers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Moore	O
,	O
Directed	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
Jane	O
Moore	O
,	O
entitling	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
receive	O
Moore	O
's	O
Wages	O
at	O
Sea	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
divers	O
false	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
considerable	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
into	O
her	O
Hands	O
.	O
Her	O
method	O
was	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
some	O
Under-Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Dead	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
Absented	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
would	O
contrive	O
immediately	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
above	O
twenty	O
false	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
two	O
Pence	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
People	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalene	I-place
Milkstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Milkstreet-Market	B-place
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
turnedher	O
Back	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
conveyed	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Stays	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hovey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Quinter	I-pers
one	O
Pocket	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
Nails	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
alias	O
Ball	B-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Neck	O
nigh	O
the	O
Coller-Bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Pall-Mall	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kiss	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
ruder	O
,	O
he	O
tore	O
her	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
assisting	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
retreat	O
back	O
to	O
a	O
Bulk	O
and	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Prudence	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
warm	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Rogers	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
for	O
29	O
s.	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
s.	O
more	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lott	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
the	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
Calamanca	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
three	O
Womens	O
Shifts	O
,	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Nightingale	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
Dinner	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
seen	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
mistrusted	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street-street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
drove	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Serge	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
,	O
one	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
two	O
Red	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Black	O
Cow	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cows	O
were	O
stolen	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Kentish-Town	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-bobbs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Page	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Victuals	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Exon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Salmond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
lighting	O
of	O
some	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Ladder	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
frighted	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Hodge	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Portugal	O
Ambassador	O
's	O
Chappel	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Thimble	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Roll	O
of	O
his	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Shooes	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
at	O
Shrewsbury	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Monesses	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
quiet	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Phillip	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooe-Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
travelling	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
Stone-Bridge	B-place
between	O
Acton	B-place
and	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
and	O
Morgan	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
Butcher	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
use	O
him	O
kindly	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
the	O
Mist	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
exchange	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Point	O
Gravats	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Point	O
Ruffles	O
40	O
s.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
that	O
did	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Prim	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Star-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Rosemary-Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eleven	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
4	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Starker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sivall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
41	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
called	O
Serge	O
Desway	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Gravemens	O
Night	O
gowns	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Colours	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macknoll	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
Clipping	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Clockmaker	O
's	O
Boy	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
by	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
through	O
the	O
Glass	O
a	O
Clipping	O
in	O
another	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
upon	O
the	O
Beds	O
Teaster	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
newly	O
clipt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
large	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Leister	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Basishaw	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Martingale	I-pers
one	O
Course	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloath	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
was	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Afternon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
220	O
peices	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Six	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
25	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
16	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
20	O
s.	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Roker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorowgood	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Conspiring	O
and	O
Practising	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Rickaby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Orange-flower-water	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
drinking	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Garter	B-place
Coffee	I-place
house	I-place
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Delow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
askt	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Orange-water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
replied	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
thankt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Bottle	O
,	O
but	O
Delow	O
and	O
theDeceased	O
did	O
drink	O
it	O
very	O
immoderately	O
in	O
great	O
Glasses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
did	O
compel	O
or	O
force	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
greedy	O
lover	O
of	O
such	O
Liquors	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hardly	O
leave	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Delow	O
drinking	O
a	O
great	O
Glass	O
,	O
desired	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Alderman	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
with	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
was	O
overcome	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Castle-Alley-End	O
and	O
there	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Nose	O
fell	O
a	O
bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Teeth	O
did	O
knit	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Abetting	O
and	O
Comforting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
by	O
concealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
that	O
was	O
stollen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Yalden	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
alias	O
Browne	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Povey	B-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
Silk	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
Head	O
was	O
turned	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Silk	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Black-Fryers	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
Shoplifters	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Silk	O
between	O
Povey	O
's	O
Legs	O
.	O
Browne	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
both	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Persons	O
that	O
followed	O
that	O
way	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Jenkins	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jones	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Pattentees	O
of	O
the	O
Farthing	O
Office	O
,	O
six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Copper	O
Money	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
35	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
unlock	O
the	O
Chest	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burchin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Portlock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Steel-stamps	O
for	O
Shillings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Steel-stamp	O
for	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Steel-punches	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
discovered	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
make	O
false	O
Stamps	O
for	O
Clippers	O
and	O
Coyners	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hill	O
to	O
prefer	O
his	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
had	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pickt	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
Stones	O
and	O
Brick-bats	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglarly	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
an	O
Emrauld	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Chambers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Lamp-iron	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Archibal	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
44	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
16	O
l.	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
's	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
Lady	O
who	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bundled	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Long-Acre	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
pretended	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
those	O
things	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
had	O
the	O
Boy	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Bedfordbury	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
going	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
and	O
almost	O
Strangled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Leah	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
seven	O
several	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attornies	O
of	O
Seamen	O
,	O
with	O
Wills	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
means	O
had	O
fraudulently	O
obtained	O
200	O
l.	O
pretending	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Moneys	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
those	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Abetting	O
and	O
Comforting	O
Diana	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Sherrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
concealing	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Crotchet	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Picture	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Micheal	B-pers
Bosse	I-pers
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Serge	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Porrige	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Carpet	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Scotch	O
Pad	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amey	B-pers
Angell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Ten	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Ten	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Goodman's-fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Forge	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
further	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Ingots	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
a	O
Rubbing	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
little	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
clip	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
twice	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cap	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
some	O
Milkwomen	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
who	O
mistrusting	O
something	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
strip	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
;	O
What	O
need	O
you	O
care	O
?	O
And	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
searcht	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
with	O
a	O
Shilling	O
just	O
entred	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Skales	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Laced	O
Cornets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
selling	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
four	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Roch	I-pers
Spinster	O
.	O
Four	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whatton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Truelove	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Anne	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Twenty	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Paper	O
of	O
small	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
clip	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hardly	I-pers
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Caster-hat	O
20	O
s.	O
Turtleshell	O
box	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Steel	O
spurs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Brothers	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Pay	O
of	O
one	O
Frederick	B-pers
Roven	I-pers
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
received	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurford	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
72	O
yards	O
of	O
White	O
Serge	O
,	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
White	O
Plush	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Plush	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7	O
Richard	O
Arrowsmith	O
Thomas	O
Butcher	O
William	O
Morgan	O
William	O
Ingram	O
John	O
Jones	O
alias	O
Hodge	O
John	O
Macknoll	O
Thomas	O
Reeves	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
Prudence	O
Brookes	O
John	O
Bolton	O
William	O
Burchin	O
Mary	O
Bayley	O
Timothy	O
Cotton	O
Mary	O
Dix	O
Mary	O
Dutton	O
Margaret	O
Edwards	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
alias	O
Povey	O
George	O
Hovey	O
Mary	O
Hunt	O
Elizabeth	O
Miller	O
alias	O
Green	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Pearce	O
Mary	O
Richardson	O
Elizabeth	O
Robinson	O
Margaret	O
Ward	O
Elizabeth	O
Yalden	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
Ann	O
Richardson	O
.	O
For	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
John	O
Bolton	O
William	O
Burchin	O
George	O
Hovey	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Lott	O
Jane	O
Precious	O
alias	O
Brown	O
Jane	O
Blewitt	O
Jane	O
Jenkins	O
alias	O
Browne	O
Mary	O
Middleton	O
.	O
Christian	O
Brothers	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
upon	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Cheapside	O
Conduit	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Premises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Of	O
Contentment	O
,	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
By	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Late	O
of	O
Trinity	O
College	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Duty	O
of	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
Divine	O
Will	O
in	O
Afflictions	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Cure	O
of	O
Distractions	O
in	O
Attending	O
upon	O
God	O
.	O
In	O
several	O
Sermons	O
.	O
By	O
Nathaniel	O
Vincent	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Aso	O
several	O
Sermens	O
against	O
the	O
Love	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Vincent	O
,	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
being	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
.	O
A	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
Divine	O
Perfections	O
,	O
Illustrating	O
the	O
Glory	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
and	O
Revelation	O
.	O
In	O
several	O
Meditations	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Lord	O
President	O
States	O
,	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Father	O
:	O
Our	O
Counsel	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
Directing	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
Passages	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
E.	O
C.	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Forms	O
of	O
Prayer	O
for	O
every	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Week	O
,	O
Morning	O
and	O
Evening	O
;	O
Composed	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Families	O
.	O
Also	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Thanksgivings	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
longer	O
and	O
shorter	O
Morning	O
and	O
Evening	O
Prayer	O
for	O
particular	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Meriton	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Contemplations	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
Immortality	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Manchester	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Great	O
Concern	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
serious	O
warning	O
to	O
a	O
timely	O
and	O
thorough	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Death	O
;	O
with	O
Helps	O
and	O
Directions	O
in	O
order	O
thereunto	O
.	O
By	O
E.	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
B.	O
Liburn	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
removed	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
who	O
prepareth	O
and	O
selleth	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Warms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
Elixir	O
Salutes	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vita	O
,	O
tinctura	O
Vita	O
;	O
and	O
Excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
is	O
likewise	O
sold	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
Countrey	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prevent	O
mistakes	O
and	O
counterfeits	O
,	O
take	O
notice	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
The	O
price	O
Three	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
Bottle	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
