TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
30th	O
,	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
30th	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1695	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Justice	B-pers
Otgor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langbridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whittell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rolston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Moorwood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkhurst	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dewing	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Goodwyn	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cleve	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ousley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bifeild	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gotobed	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Penner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Northey	I-pers
Widow	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin-Cloath	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josias	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
alias	O
Scolthrope	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
St.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dawzy	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Dawzy	O
coming	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
pursued	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
searcht	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
very	O
fain	O
have	O
been	O
naught	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	O
Jenkins	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
forty	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
House-Rouse	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Lawrence	I-place
Old	I-place
Jury	I-place
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
on	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Grezet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
disliked	O
;	O
and	O
Hutton	O
having	O
spied	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Companion	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
Silk	O
,	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
excuse	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
and	O
conveyed	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
Brown	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Hutton	O
believed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Silk	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wellings	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Great	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Dowgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
or	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
Rabbet-skins	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hazelwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Work-woman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Lodging	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Rabbet	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
treat	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bland	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
spied	O
her	O
prey	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
very	O
fairly	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
Parsley	O
and	O
Onions	O
for	O
the	O
Rabbet	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Rabbet	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bland	O
presently	O
mistrusted	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stocken	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
dress	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland-sleeves	O
value	O
1s.	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blaxley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lever	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Stocken	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
untruss	O
a	O
point	O
,	O
and	O
Lever	O
's	O
Wife	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
readily	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
he	O
unlatcht	O
Blaxley	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Lever	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
sent	O
Mrs.	O
Blaxley	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
and	O
missed	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
pursued	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Stocken	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Lawrence	I-place
Old	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloaths	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Davis	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
opportunity	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Sisters	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Parret	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
and	O
140	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calamanco	O
value	O
14l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitten	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
open	O
a	O
pack	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
discovered	O
in	O
Bell-alley	O
,	O
near	O
Token-house-yard	O
:	O
And	O
they	O
met	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
nine	O
pence	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
near	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Barret	O
,	O
and	O
Thompson	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
peeping	O
afterwards	O
about	O
Moorgate	O
;	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
Barret	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
unlikely	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
careless	O
Dog	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
Things	O
so	O
?	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Bell-alley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
and	O
Conversations	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Birchin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Birchin	O
was	O
going	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
through	O
the	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thrust	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
by	O
this	O
Dodd	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
him	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Penner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olaves	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
value	O
12l	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Spikes	O
of	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
Mrs	O
Smith	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
any	O
Goods	O
;	O
replied	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
at	O
the	O
matter	O
till	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
no	O
good	O
liver	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
of	O
Devonshire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
a	O
Dyer	O
for	O
5l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Sarcacen	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
Friday	O
Street	O
,	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dukes	O
man	O
for	O
7l	O
.	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Merriam	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Merriam	O
and	O
one	O
Salter	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	B-place
Wheatsheaf	I-place
in	O
Bishopsgate	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
drunk	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
sixth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Stays	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Crape	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Plumtree-street	B-place
in	O
St.Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
one	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
she	O
left	O
all	O
things	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
never	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Carters	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Oliphant	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Hannah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Penknife	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Oliphant	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
coming	O
over	O
Stepny-fields	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
did	O
abuse	O
Mrs.	O
Oliphant	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oliphant	O
asked	O
the	O
deceased	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Oliphant	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oliphant	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
great	O
Dog	O
and	O
flew	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
parted	O
they	O
went	O
each	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
killed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Ayliffe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
and	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
beating	O
he	O
languished	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
going	O
over	O
Brook-field	B-place
Faer	I-place
,	O
by	O
Hide	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
picked	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
beat	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
bled	O
at	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
voided	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
their	O
behalf	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Church-wardens	O
and	O
other	O
eminent	O
men	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
their	O
behalfs	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
and	O
the	O
Searcher	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
die	O
of	O
the	O
Spotted	O
Feaver	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Edmunds	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
alias	O
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Twenty	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Ten	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mix	O
'd	O
Metals	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Coiner	O
in	O
Black-lion-yard	B-place
,	O
in	O
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
several	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
drawn	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
afterwards	O
filed	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
work	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
one	O
Shelton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
Miles	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
eight	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
one	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
and	O
Joan	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Joan	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
clip	O
Twenty	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Forty	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
use	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	O
Bayley	O
,	O
in	O
Brook	B-place
field	I-place
,	O
two	O
Papers	O
of	O
Clippings	O
that	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Skales	O
,	O
Rubbing-leathers	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Filings	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
taking	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Bayley	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Horten-street	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Rubbing	O
leather	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Ralph	O
Bayley	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
livelihood	O
.	O
And	O
Thomas	O
Bayley	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
brought	O
by	O
his	O
late	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
pressed	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
for	O
bringing	O
his	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
words	O
,	O
(	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clipper	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
owned	O
the	O
Rubbing-leather	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
a	O
Buck	O
's	O
Skin	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Trade	O
.	O
And	O
called	O
several	O
People	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
certain	O
Shears	O
and	O
Files	O
did	O
Clip	O
and	O
diminish	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mumbay	O
by	O
Islington	B-place
Wells	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
went	O
every	O
Sunday	O
night	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
clip	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
her	O
Husband	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
clipt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
this	O
Rebecca	O
Berry	O
clip	O
every	O
Sunday	O
night	O
for	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mumbay	O
,	O
derogating	O
from	O
her	O
former	O
Testimony	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
denying	O
upon	O
Oath	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
suborned	O
,	O
committed	O
her	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
an	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
Perjury	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
amend	O
her	O
life	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gregory	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Conyers	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Emilia	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Frimley	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
50	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Sixpences	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Clippers	O
at	O
Wade	O
's	O
House	O
by	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Shears	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Flore	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Gregory	O
had	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
Bullion	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Carew	O
had	O
Clippings	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
Wade	O
and	O
Gregory	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Carew	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
;	O
Wade	O
and	O
Hartford	O
called	O
several	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Juxon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
clipping	O
10	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Clippers	O
in	O
Lambs-Conduit	B-place
Passage	I-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Shears	O
and	O
Rubbing	O
Leathers	O
with	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Tools	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
spake	O
very	O
well	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
Daniel	O
Juxon	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
White	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lyall	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lark	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Peticoat	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Headcloath	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
9s	O
.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Merrey	I-pers
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
one	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
opportunity	O
broke	O
open	O
Mrs.	O
Merrey	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Mrs.	O
Merrey	O
her	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
F	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
with	O
Sheers	O
and	O
Files	O
they	O
did	O
clip	O
and	O
diminish	O
Three	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Twelve	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
Letter	O
form	O
an	O
unknown	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Parish	O
,	O
which	O
acquainted	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Clippers	O
in	O
S	O
-	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
's	O
Warrant	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
S	O
-	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
several	O
Sheers	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
further	O
clipt	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
work	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
left	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
speak	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
liver	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
affected	O
Woolfe	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
Twenty	O
Halfcrowns	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Clippers	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Royston	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Dunnings-alley	B-place
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Royston	O
,	O
who	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
some	O
Pales	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
High-Trason	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
flew	O
back	O
and	O
shut	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
two	O
Papers	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
great	O
Candles	O
lighted	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
with	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Money	O
half	O
Clipt	O
,	O
and	O
Stools	O
and	O
Chairs	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
confused	O
manner	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
frighted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avil	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Forging	O
and	O
Making	O
Twenty	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Twenty	O
false	O
Sixpences	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
an	O
Information	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Work-room	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Flasks	O
a	O
drying	O
over	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
false	O
Metal	O
and	O
a	O
Mould	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
Metal	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
make	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
of	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
for	O
himself	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
only	O
to	O
support	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olaves	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Karrsone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
and	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Karrsone	O
buying	O
some	O
Oranges	O
on	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
Box	O
and	O
Monies	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
being	O
by	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
askt	O
Mrs.	O
Karrsone	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Monies	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Knee	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olaves	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woolen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
set	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
clip	O
about	O
Fourteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
an	O
information	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
White-Lion	B-place
Yard	I-place
in	O
Barbican	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
Shears	O
,	O
Skales	O
and	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Trade	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
clipt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
file	O
and	O
diminish	O
about	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Halfcrowns	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
livelihood	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Welsed	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hill	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
clip	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Shillings	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
filing	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
transported	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
20	O
Sillings	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
staires	O
in	O
hast	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
aware	O
of	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
their	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
11l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moare	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
words	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
arise	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
his	O
Ways	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Wine	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
pacify	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Being	O
come	O
upon	O
the	O
paved	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fall	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
some	O
Chairmen	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
Chairman	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Company-keeper	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
lie	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
supported	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
worthy	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Unica	B-pers
Franklyn	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
one	O
pair	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Andrew	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
redeem	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pastmore	I-pers
and	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Pastmore	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
Eighteen	O
false	O
Halfcrowns	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
having	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Bear	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
Ingot	O
of	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
man	O
buttoned	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Eagle-street	B-place
,	O
near	O
Red-Lyon-Fields	I-place
and	O
found	O
a	O
Stamp	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
cut	O
the	O
said	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
flatted	O
Plate	O
fitted	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
allowed	O
12d	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
Thirty	O
false	O
Halfcrowns	O
for	O
Twenty	O
good	O
ones	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
clip	O
above	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
afterwards	O
file	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
clipt	O
and	O
filed	O
several	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
livelihood	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Cane-Chairmaker	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Rosamond	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bilby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
1695	O
,	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statutes	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
buy	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
Twenty	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clippings	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
12d	O
.	O
for	O
every	O
Ounce	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Twenty	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Halfmoon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
false	O
clipt	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
clip	O
Sixty	O
or	O
Seventy	O
Pounds	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
livelihood	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
formerly	O
kept	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
on	O
Snowhill	O
,	O
but	O
falling	O
into	O
decay	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
making	O
of	O
Tips	O
for	O
Essence	O
Bottles	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
Ludgatehill	O
by	O
the	O
Three	O
Tun	O
Tavern	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
Defence	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Old	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Lincoln-Inn	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
one	O
Emrauld	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
one	O
Stoel	O
Seal	O
10s	O
.	O
six	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
3l	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
6s	O
.	O
Sir	O
James	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Clerk	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
lockt	O
up	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
nine	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
his	O
Chamber	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Sir	O
James	O
sent	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Robbers	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Hoglane	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Lamp	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
to	O
one	O
Dearnell	O
,	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
for	O
30s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
lay	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
36l	O
.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bence	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
Trunk	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
great	O
Trunk	O
mist	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
affect	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Chiswick	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
laced	O
Headdress	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Vizard	O
Mask	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbered	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chambers	I-pers
going	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Worcester	O
Coach	O
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
in	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
her	O
Journey	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
hanged	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
rod	O
round	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Headcloaths	O
and	O
tore	O
them	O
off	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
ends	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Headcloaths	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
alias	O
Earl	O
of	O
Banbury	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
at	O
Turnham	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
four	O
more	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
of	O
Banbury	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
His	O
Lordship	O
shot	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
o	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olaves	I-place
Southwark	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Stretcher	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
striking	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
by	O
some	O
young	O
Women	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Ovaries	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
rowed	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
bad	O
him	O
let	O
the	O
Boat	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
Oar	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
made	O
him	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
Oar	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Stretcher	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rowed	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
landed	O
his	O
Fare	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Ovaries	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Marygold	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
Oars	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
who	O
landed	O
them	O
at	O
Essex-stairs	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Water	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rowed	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
bid	O
him	O
keep	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catching	O
up	O
the	O
Stretcher	O
did	O
give	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
blow	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Goby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
lace	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Serge	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Munton	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Newport-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
sent	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
continued	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Clip	O
divers	O
Sums	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
accidentally	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
filing	O
of	O
Guinea	O
's	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Clipping	O
in	O
his	O
Work	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jeffery	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
in	O
Jewen-street	B-place
about	O
6l	O
.	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
brought	O
20	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Broad	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sate	O
down	O
and	O
Clipt	O
it	O
,	O
giving	O
the	O
persons	O
their	O
own	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
9d	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Clippings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
a	O
month	O
afterwards	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
find	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bale	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Calico	O
for	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
shuffled	O
them	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
go	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
lived	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Butolph	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
procure	O
and	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
500l	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Evil	O
Intent	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Unlawful	O
Gain	O
thereof	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
22l	O
.	O
Advance	O
for	O
Broad	O
mony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Intent	O
the	O
same	O
should	O
be	O
Clipt	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
a	O
Correspondence	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
drive	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Canting	O
Letters	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
no	O
Discovery	O
made	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
hapned	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
coming	O
to	O
search	O
Mr.	O
Southgate	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Norwich	O
Wagoner	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
did	O
light	O
upon	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
marked	O
A.	O
L.	O
directed	O
to	O
John	O
Goodall	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
stuft	O
with	O
Straw	O
and	O
Litter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
money	O
with	O
Notes	O
in	O
it	O
tied	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
did	O
express	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
45l	O
.	O
Best	O
,	O
and	O
7l	O
.	O
Midling	O
.	O
The	O
Commissioners	O
suspecting	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
ordered	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
should	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
Mr.	O
Goodall	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
dated	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
by	O
two	O
Letters	O
J.	O
G.	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
exprest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Goodall	O
45	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Silk	O
Naps	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
construed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
45l	O
.	O
of	O
Broad	O
old	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
seven	O
middling	O
Naps	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
construed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
7l	O
.	O
of	O
middling	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
marked	O
A.	O
L.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
by	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
Corresponding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
above	O
550l	O
since	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartcliff	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
1695.	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
did	O
buy	O
of	O
divers	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Information	O
was	O
given	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oved	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ovid	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Rawbone	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
did	O
Clip	O
50	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
having	O
Information	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
Mr.	O
Ovid	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
by	O
Golden	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
Soho	B-place
,	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
behind	O
some	O
Hangings	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
with	O
Clippings	O
and	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Trade	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
money	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Ovid	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Rawbone	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lawman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
wander	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
calling	O
himself	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
for	O
himself	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
German	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Egyptian	O
;	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
wander	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
following	O
,	O
calling	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
,	O
and	O
king	O
of	O
the	O
Egyptians	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Barn	O
,	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Egyptian	O
Women	O
sitting	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
they	O
discovered	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pulled	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Straw	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Scinsteer	O
,	O
and	O
Rich	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Mare	O
likewise	O
hard	O
by	O
that	O
was	O
worth	O
20l	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
fully	O
proving	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
30	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Seventh	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Russel-street	I-place
in	O
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
bigger	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
People	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Furnace	O
,	O
Melting-pot	O
red	O
hot	O
,	O
Filings	O
and	O
Ingotts	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Chair	O
or	O
Stool	O
for	O
to	O
sit	O
upon	O
throughout	O
the	O
which	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
urged	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
was	O
in	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Constable	O
searcht	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
,	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
mistrusting	O
somewhat	O
,	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
File-dust	O
and	O
Skales	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Seventh	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
knowingly	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
evaded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Naseby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
30s	O
.	O
four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Sheeres	O
in	O
Gravesend	O
for	O
20s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
matter	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Henhouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
stealing	O
thence	O
one	O
Cock	O
,	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Chickens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Greene	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Henhouse	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr	O
Greene	O
's	O
Neighbour	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
Copper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shed	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
Peticoat-lane	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
kickt	O
something	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Greene	O
's	O
Fowls	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
.	O
He	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
lambs	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tame	O
Fawn	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
upon	O
his	O
Search	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Cellar-stairs	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jackson	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Hurst	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Page	O
for	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
Victuals	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twittenham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Cow	O
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
plainly	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
another	O
Cow	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Abbey	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Falcony	I-pers
a	O
Swede	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Forging	O
Six	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Coin	O
,	O
in	O
likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
calling	O
several	O
persons	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Munford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
coming	O
from	O
France	O
after	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1690.	O
without	O
the	O
Licence	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Sl	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
France	O
nine	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Germany	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Shipwash	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mews	I-pers
and	O
Jane	O
W	O
er	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parson	I-pers
12	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
They	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
several	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
like	O
to	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
the	O
Tripeman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Corral	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dagg	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Syson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
40l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Howell	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Howell	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
making	O
and	O
procuring	O
four	O
false	O
Stamps	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shillings	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Clipping	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilmott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
In	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
D	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
so	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
affect	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	O
B	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
sett	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
both	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Dity	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bunnian	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Demsdale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
counterfeit	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Filbutt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
;	O
she	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Juxon	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
10	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
having	O
30	O
Ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
having	O
11	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
and	O
Emilia	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
having	O
30	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Shipside	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
conspire	O
to	O
poison	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plume	I-pers
Dr.	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
pleased	O
God	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
timely	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
one	O
Rowland	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
having	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
did	O
melt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
Persons	O
following	O
having	O
formerly	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
their	O
time	O
being	O
expired	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Oakelshot	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ballet	B-pers
,	O
Ursula	B-pers
Whitfeild	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Pettishall	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
death	O
Sixteen	O
.	O
Mary	O
Newman	O
,	O
William	O
Penner	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Herne	O
,	O
John	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Jane	O
Juxon	O
,	O
Robert	O
Royston	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Barnes	O
,	O
John	O
Carter	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Burrows	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pastmore	O
,	O
Rosamond	O
Pastmore	O
,	O
Duke	O
Cooke	O
,	O
William	O
Burton	O
,	O
Peter	O
Lawman	O
,	O
Francis	O
Buckle	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Demsdale	O
.	O
A	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
whether	O
Sarah	O
Burrows	O
,	O
Jane	O
Juxon	O
,	O
Rosamond	O
Pastmore	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Demsdale	O
were	O
with	O
Child	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
Quick-Child	O
.	O
These	O
Persons	O
following	O
having	O
formerly	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
their	O
time	O
being	O
expired	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Oakelshot	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ballet	B-pers
,	O
Ursula	B-pers
Whitfeild	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Pettishall	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Seventeen	O
.	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
Jane	O
Browne	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hutton	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Robinson	O
,	O
John	O
Stocken	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Percivall	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Barrett	O
,	O
Mary	O
Seager	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
James	O
Scott	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Perkins	O
,	O
Edward	O
Naseby	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Babb	O
,	O
Mary	O
Syson	O
,	O
Edward	O
Howell	O
,	O
Bridget	O
Griffin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bond	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
Five	O
.	O
John	O
Stocken	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Barrett	O
,	O
Edward	O
Naseby	O
,	O
William	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
Edward	O
Howell	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Seven	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Wellings	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
Unica	O
Frankilin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Collins	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bale	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
alias	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Edward	O
B	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
for	O
running	O
through	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
K.	O
William	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
exchange	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
Conduit	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
his	O
fine	O
.	O
John	O
Scott	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
William	O
Grantham	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	O
Collins	O
fined	O
900	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
without	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
respited	O
the	O
Judgement	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Criminals	O
,	O
for	O
melting	O
and	O
having	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
farther	O
time	O
.	O
