TOKEN	NE
THE	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plaistead	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Whisker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Raworth	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Warpoole	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanies	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Diaper	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moodey	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Levingstone	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
red	O
Heifers	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Heifer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
pied	O
Bullock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Steer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Steer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
sixth	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Bull	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gin	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
seventh	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
black	O
Heifers	O
and	O
2	O
red	O
ones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
eighth	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brindle	O
Steer	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
where	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
a	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
and	O
Salt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet-Pall	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Stephens	B-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mansfelt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Speck	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
16	O
Dressed	O
Calve-Skins	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
6	O
Skins	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
mistrusting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Speck	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
Goods	O
offered	O
to	O
Sell	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chicken	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
an	O
Amber-Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
45	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
31st	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tuns	I-place
in	O
Shandois-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
discourse	O
arose	O
amongst	O
them	O
about	O
chusing	O
Parliament	O
Men	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
debated	O
so	O
hot	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lye	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
fray	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
ask	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
since	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alleged	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
threw	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
catcht	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
and	O
thrust	O
his	O
Fingers	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
alias	O
Willoughby	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Fosters	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
3	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
:	O
Upon	O
search	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
Clayton	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
alias	O
Lane	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Lumbard-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Yardley	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Vintry	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
empty	O
wooden	O
Barrel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
in	O
Kings-Head-Court	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
wherewithal	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Transported	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Stall	O
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
alias	O
Griffin	B-pers
alias	O
Harding	B-pers
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
7	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dobinson	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Thread	O
Buttons	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Moll	B-pers
Rabyes	I-pers
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Harlo	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Indian	O
Gown	O
lined	O
with	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
St.	B-place
Martins-lane	I-place
they	O
spied	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
being	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Powell	O
,	O
Walton	O
,	O
Marshall	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Spires	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Spires	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
5	O
s.	O
8	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
want	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
leave	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alleged	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
alias	O
Chandler	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
laced	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Robbed	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Head-dress	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Dust-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lockt	O
his	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
Dust-Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodburne	I-pers
for	O
5	O
s	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
roan	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lose	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Swop	O
:	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
Stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Court-yard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
behind	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Betty	O
upon	O
him	O
tied	O
with	O
a	O
Rope	O
cross	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
Squire	O
Tench	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Locks	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
Razor	O
about	O
him	O
which	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Betty	O
in	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
Fire	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Razor	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cap	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Middle-Temple	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
and	O
Bolster	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
5	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Neale	O
was	O
Laundress	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
in	O
the	O
Vacation	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
they	O
Pawned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
Sold	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Moneys	O
they	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
New-street	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Muslin	O
Neck	O
cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Fustion	O
Frock	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
loose	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Coat	O
hanging	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
the	O
Broker	O
desired	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Man	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
cried	O
old	O
coats	O
in	O
Jewen-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
gilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
Spinster	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Mucking	I-place
Hadley	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
Coral	O
,	O
12	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
8	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Money	O
by	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
mentioned	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bedow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
Kemeys	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Collar-bone	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Muslin	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Distracted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butterick	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
laden	O
with	O
a	O
leaden	O
Bullet	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Fore-head	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
Died	O
.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Butcehrs	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
talking	O
shith	O
the	O
Butcher	O
and	O
holding	O
her	O
Daughter	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brains	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
hands	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
hope	O
not	O
so	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
discharge	O
the	O
Pistol	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Muzzle	O
downwards	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Bullet	O
grazed	O
and	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
bean	O
Accident	O
and	O
meerly	O
done	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Cherrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
Strangling	O
and	O
Choaking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Skrews	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
about	O
,	O
found	O
something	O
soft	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloath	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Flesh	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
shewed	O
it	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Stillborn	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
Bury	O
it	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
no	O
ways	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
cry	O
out	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
heard	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
hire	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
provided	O
against	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Suits	O
of	O
Stuff	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chittey	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Out-house	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Stole	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
black	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perry	O
wig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rennol	I-pers
of	O
a	O
black	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Tillotson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Ewe-Sheep	O
and	O
eight	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Scott	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
put	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drove	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
by	O
Islington	B-place
into	O
Durham	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Skins	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
being	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
her	O
Husbonds	O
's	O
Commands	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ezeklel	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
5	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
's	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
bolt	O
his	O
Back-door	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Back-door	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Taken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Digood	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Lenthall	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Sargeant	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lose	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
brag	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Bit	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Women	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
tell	O
the	O
Man	O
but	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
which	O
they	O
bit	O
her	O
of	O
,	O
meaning	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
run	O
so	O
much	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Score	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cloth	B-pers
Doll	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
Taken	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
cup	O
,	O
3	O
gilt	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Rings	O
and	O
40	O
Guinea	O
's	O
;	O
4	O
20	O
s	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
10	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
word	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Mary	O
Seager	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
and	O
Jonas	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Tippet	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
an	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
drive	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
coin	O
Half-crowns	O
and	O
1	O
Shilling	O
of	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
cast	O
it	O
with	O
Spawd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
William	O
below	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Melting-pot	O
red	O
hot	O
,	O
with	O
Metal	O
ready	O
melted	O
and	O
other	O
trade	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Francis	O
coming	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fell	O
down	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
into	O
some	O
Old	O
coal	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Braziers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
stike	O
a	O
New	O
Shilling	O
between	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
impression	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
curious	O
in	O
casting	O
of	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
think	O
to	O
try	O
an	O
Experiment	O
with	O
it	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Coin	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
several	O
times	O
(	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
London	B-place
wall	I-place
,	O
in	O
Baldwins	B-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Clement's-Lane	I-place
)	O
divers	O
quantities	O
of	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Edge	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
counterfeit	O
Guinea	O
's	O
of	O
Silver	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
divers	O
Tools	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
follow	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hease	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Wilsden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Lambs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gretteridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drive	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Adey	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
John	B-pers
Braseburne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Totenham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
Pig	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Ware	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
at	O
Stanford-Hill	B-place
by	O
six	O
Highway-Men	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
by	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
beat	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
force	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
under	O
the	O
Gibbet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
refuse	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pig	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
rifling	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pig	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
look	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
a	O
Cart	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
with	O
two	O
Hampers	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
some	O
Figs	O
and	O
other	O
Fruit	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
Gibbet	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Rifling	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
Liberal	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
the	O
Ladies	O
with	O
Wine	O
and	O
Fruit	O
.	O
Mr	O
Pig	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
formerly	O
being	O
his	O
School-fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fain	O
havemade	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
it	O
very	O
lamely	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cavenah	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
clipping	O
and	O
coining	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
his	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Abbis	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Abbis	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
and	O
a	O
Cellar	O
by	O
Golden-Square	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
did	O
Coin	O
new	O
Crown-pieces	O
,	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Nine-pences	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Woman	O
Coin	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
6	O
Canns	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bridewell	B-place
Precinct	I-place
;	O
There	O
was	O
false	O
Money	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Mans	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stamps	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Edger	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Edward	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Dorothy	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Coin	O
;	O
He	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
alias	O
Wing	B-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hiliyard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
and	O
coining	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Wynne	O
did	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Comical	O
Joe	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
oldest	O
Clipper	O
and	O
Coiner	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
both	O
Clip	O
and	O
Coin	O
in	O
Long-lane	B-place
and	O
Red-Lion	B-place
street	I-place
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stamps	O
and	O
an	O
Edger	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Sick	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
could	O
speak	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Gibbons	O
and	O
Hillyard	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Wynne	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Bourdevill	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lutterel	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
imployed	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
Rubbish	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Plate	O
and	O
Jewels	O
that	O
were	O
buried	O
in	O
the	O
Ruines	O
,	O
and	O
Bourdevill	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
up	O
:	O
They	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Byddal	I-pers
alias	O
Gardiner	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollynton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Paddington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Plomer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbred	O
;	O
The	O
second	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
27	O
s.	O
Plomer	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Harrow	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
narrow	O
Lane	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
Damn	O
him	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
Biddal	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
Then	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
his	O
Horse	O
loose	O
,	O
but	O
meeting	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
they	O
soon	O
helpt	O
him	O
to	O
catch	O
it	O
;	O
Then	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
into	O
Westminster-lane	O
by	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Twyford	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
between	O
Holsdon-Green	B-place
and	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Plomer	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Offenders	O
in	O
this	O
Kind	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Polhampton	I-pers
alias	O
Pollynton	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
May	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
95	O
yards	O
of	O
Shag	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
untiled	O
the	O
Dye-House	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
11	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Pollynton	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
loose	O
Livers	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	O
Holliday	O
alias	O
Browne	O
of	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Wilsdon	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Niccols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Vallens	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Serge	O
Vallens	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Niccolls	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Bell-Man	O
going	O
his	O
Round	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
about	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crept	O
up	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
crept	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
shelter	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Penney	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
clipping	O
and	O
coming	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Clip	O
and	O
Coin	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
Another	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
Artist	O
in	O
England	O
for	O
making	O
of	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
show	O
him	O
a	O
Stamp	O
to	O
Coin	O
a	O
Two-pence	O
with	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
making	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Duncks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
and	O
coining	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Lame	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
alias	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mekam	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Boddice	O
Coat	O
,	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
,	O
from	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stript	O
the	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
another	O
time	O
to	O
sell	O
more	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
Stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Polhampton	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
120	O
yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
32	O
yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
seventh	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	O
Stanley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blarton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Harwoods	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kipworth	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Play-House	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Purple	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Red	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Dancing-Master	O
at	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
came	O
acquainted	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Bedside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
Lie	O
with	O
your	O
Face	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Wardrobe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Buckridge-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
White-Friers	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
he	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
:	O
Besides	O
he	O
had	O
absented	O
himself	O
from	O
his	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Haddox	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
Biting	O
the	O
deceased	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
Finger	O
of	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
buying	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
at	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
washolding	O
her	O
Hands	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
Bite	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Finger	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
it	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fright	O
caused	O
a	O
malignant	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
so	O
small	O
it	O
needed	O
no	O
Plaister	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
complain	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
Stomach	O
sometime	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
beat	O
and	O
evil	O
entreat	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereas	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
perceiving	O
that	O
her	O
confession	O
was	O
extorted	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Costin	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
by	O
the	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Timnerd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
30	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
cloth	O
,	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Costin	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
such	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Maddox	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Dated	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1696	O
,	O
for	O
70	O
l.	O
upon	O
Demand	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
William	O
Laws	O
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
easie	O
matter	O
to	O
forge	O
Mr.	O
Maddox	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
write	O
Mr.	O
Maddox	O
's	O
Name	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
Hedges	O
's	O
Name	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
Presence	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
formerly	O
cheated	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Cask	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
Prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sampson	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Whittel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lutestring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hearne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pound	O
of	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
at	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
Forswearing	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
She	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sylvanus	B-pers
Hauscomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Cheating	O
David	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
of	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Token	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	O
Stanley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blarton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hunnocks	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hunnock	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Knockverges	B-place
,	I-place
by	O
Stepney	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Stamp	O
about	O
45	O
Shillings	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
by	O
Aniseed-Clare	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Freshwater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Clip	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
that	O
is	O
Unborn	O
,	O
and	O
prosecuted	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Spight	O
and	O
Malice	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Chessing-dish	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Veare	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Willkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul's-Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Bolt	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
remove	O
it	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Taken	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Stockins	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mawd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
100	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Taken	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
Stamps	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
false	O
Half-Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
gilt	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
false	O
Gold	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
coining	O
the	O
currant	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
coin	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Sheer	I-place
Court	I-place
by	O
Puddle-dock	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
altogether	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Prosecuted	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
and	O
spight	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Folkman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Town	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Turner	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gill	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
Taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
Taken	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
yards	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Pardoned	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Hampton	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Coined	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
feaged	O
it	O
over	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Hampton	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
against	O
Fenton	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hampton	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexis	B-pers
alias	O
Alexander	B-pers
Shad	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
drive	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
melted	O
Metal	O
,	O
Flasks	O
,	O
a	O
Feaging	O
Pot	O
,	O
scratching	O
Brush	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
17	O
l.	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Practice	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Crime	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Jesuit	B-place
's	I-place
Groundin	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
Coining	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Coining	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingerley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
no	O
Bastard	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
Born	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
torn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
levied	O
an	O
Execution	O
on	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cove	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fathers	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
another	O
little	O
Boy	O
named	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Oneziphorus	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuffe	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Coral	O
Necklace	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Fringe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Mantle	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Lask	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
secretly	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
Buying	O
of	O
Stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
and	O
coining	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
both	O
clip	O
and	O
coin	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
cast	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
in	O
Flasks	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
Coin	O
in	O
Carnaby	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
Guinea	O
's	O
to	O
teach	O
a	O
Woman	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Sucket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jevill	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jewell	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
divers	O
scandalous	O
and	O
dangerous	O
Words	O
against	O
His	O
Majesty	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
fully	O
proved	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
200	O
l.	O
upon	O
counterfeit	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
did	O
forge	O
Indorsements	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
Bailed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Sollicitor	O
excepting	O
against	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Bail	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
respited	O
for	O
a	O
further	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
23	O
.	O
William	O
Archer	O
,	O
Francis	O
Archer	O
,	O
Edward	O
Abbis	O
,	O
John	O
Braseburne	O
,	O
Philip	O
Biddal	O
,	O
John	O
Hampton	O
,	O
William	O
Holliday	O
,	O
Richard	O
Hadley	O
,	O
John	O
Marshall	O
,	O
John	O
Mawd	O
,	O
Robert	O
Powel	O
,	O
Richard	O
Pollynton	O
,	O
William	O
Penny	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Phillips	O
,	O
James	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
John	O
Pool	O
,	O
Alexis	O
Shad	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Walton	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Wynne	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Wood	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Abbis	O
,	O
Mary	O
Chambers	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hampton	O
:	O
The	O
3	O
last	O
Women	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Mary	O
Wood	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Abbis	O
,	O
Mary	O
Chambers	O
and	O
Ann	O
Hampton	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
Impanneled	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
quick	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Barnes	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Ball	O
,	O
Giles	O
Bourdeville	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Costin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cuffe	O
,	O
S	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
Williams	O
Donson	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Drake	O
,	O
Edward	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Jasper	O
Folkman	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hughs	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hense	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hearne	O
,	O
Mary	O
Johnson	O
,	O
William	O
Kingham	O
,	O
Jane	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Neale	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Mansell	O
,	O
Ann	O
Nichols	O
,	O
Mary	O
Phillet	O
,	O
Susanna	O
Peirson	O
,	O
James	O
Sibley	O
,	O
Susan	O
Smith	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Steal	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Spires	O
,	O
Philadelphia	O
Maria	O
Smith	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
William	O
Scott	O
,	O
Mary	O
Talbot	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Robert	O
Winter	O
and	O
Ezekiel	O
Waller	O
.	O
For	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Parnes	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Ball	O
,	O
Giles	O
Bourdeville	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Costin	O
,	O
William	O
Dodson	O
,	O
Edward	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Jasper	O
Folkman	O
,	O
William	O
Kingham	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Mansell	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Steel	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Spires	O
,	O
Robert	O
Winter	O
,	O
Ezekiel	O
Waller	O
,	O
Sylvanus	O
Hanscomb	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Burgis	O
,	O
and	O
George	O
Wilkinson	O
Thomas	O
Carter	O
Fined	O
1000	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Cheap-side	O
Conduit	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Robert	O
French	O
Fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Places	O
.	O
William	O
Jevill	O
,	O
alias	O
Jewill	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
a	O
Noble	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Marshall	O
was	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
You	O
that	O
do	O
want	O
a	O
Cure	O
and	O
Physician	O
need	O
.	O
If	O
that	O
you	O
come	O
betimes	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
cur	O
'd	O
with	O
speed	O
He	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lowerend	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Claps	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numerous	O
Attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
productt	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
mine	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
Death	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
irregular	O
and	O
base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
of	O
foolish	O
and	O
unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
therefore	O
to	O
Advertise	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Disease	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
to	O
repair	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
performeth	O
the	O
true	O
nd	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
thereof	O
,	O
without	O
kindrance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
all	O
desireable	O
and	O
imaginable	O
speed	O
and	O
secrefie	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prizes	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
requisite	O
.	O
His	O
Diet	O
Drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
pains	O
or	O
stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
in	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
