TOKEN	NE
THE	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winmard	I-pers
,	O
Zacharias	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sweemsin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Attley	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Hodgden	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rednap	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
134	O
yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Povey	I-pers
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
79	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleady	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Povey	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Catherine	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Tall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Matthews	I-place
Friday-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elianor	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Freeman	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
95	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Langhorne	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Glinn	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleady	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnes	I-place
by	O
the	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Ditton	B-place
near	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Poor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olaves	I-place
Hart-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Towson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
and	O
bolted	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
about	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
utterly	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
never	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
two	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
Prison	O
:	O
As	O
for	O
her	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Helens	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Lace	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
being	O
presently	O
mist	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
one	O
Betty	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
utterly	O
disowned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Hood	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lace	O
Pinner	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Alms-woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Shettle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Attee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trantam	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowder	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
overturn	O
a	O
Wherry	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
said	O
Ely	O
was	O
drowned	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burnifold	I-pers
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Burnifold	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Impress	O
Men	O
for	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
and	O
their	O
Gang	O
went	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
Barge	O
belonging	O
to	O
Abingdon	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Barge	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
ifthey	O
were	O
Priviledged	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refused	O
;	O
when	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
came	O
Men	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Barge	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Knock	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
them	O
with	O
Staves	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
sunk	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
drowned	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fisherman	O
's	O
Boy	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
floating	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
aboard	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
hold	O
Pistols	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
at	O
them	O
with	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
word	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Press	O
master	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
come	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Barge	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
charge	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Kemeys	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Mulgrave	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bedow	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
silk	O
from	O
Jacob	B-pers
Banes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
who	O
having	O
occasion	O
for	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
match	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
forth	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
woman	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ernley	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Gauze	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Persian	O
silk	O
Gown	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
stuff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cyrus	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Madivo	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Musquettoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
hiden	O
with	O
Gun	O
Powder	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
leaden	O
Bullets	O
,	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
7	O
inches	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
12	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lean	O
on	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Artilleny-lane	B-place
towards	O
the	O
French	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
struggle	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Musquettoon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
discharge	O
it	O
against	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Son-in-Law	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
wicked	O
act	O
:	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
search	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mortal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Bullets	O
did	O
go	O
through	O
his	O
Liver	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Guts	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sewed	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
falling	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
owed	O
him	O
above	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Mediator	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
in	O
no	O
ways	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
dead	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
occasion	O
might	O
come	O
from	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Inconstancy	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Loverance	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Muslin	O
Nightroyl	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
avoid	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
happening	O
a	O
shower	O
of	O
Rain	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
to	O
shelter	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
the	O
Wet	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
flaxen	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
Blue	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Grazet	O
Gown	O
and	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Winford-street	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lent	O
by	O
Glover	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
silver	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
liver	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Starr	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Oshorne	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Portmanteau	O
and	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
540	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
meet	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
sold	O
Lace	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Hoster-lane	O
,	O
but	O
pretending	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
ready	O
Money	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
parcel	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Saffron-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
strangled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Woman	O
took	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
Sell	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
for	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
needs	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
consent	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Stutter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
laced	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Pater-Noster-Row	B-place
,	O
she	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
thrust	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
it	O
his	O
practice	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
every	O
night	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Quinter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Foster	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Floyer	I-pers
,	O
11	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Starke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
snatcht	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
13	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
90	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
they	O
sold	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
the	O
best	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
31	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Grant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
that	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
Hind	O
did	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
a	O
Betty	O
.	O
Spires	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
Hind	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elianor	B-pers
Dick	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dike	B-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Petison	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Paddington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Westburn-Green	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Dick	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
declare	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
meet	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Dick	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
White	B-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Omer	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardgate	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Henchman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco-Box	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
being	O
something	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
She	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	O
Allen	O
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Broken-back	O
Nan	O
,	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Bromeley	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Offinbridge	O
Pillowbers	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Pattison	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
ragg	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
Hay-making	O
;	O
but	O
Pattison	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Rags	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
washed	O
them	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
Sell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Allen	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
.	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
an	O
Embroidered	O
Purse	O
with	O
a	O
Dollar	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Lacy	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
that	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
her	O
advantage	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Lent	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
call	O
any	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jessam	I-pers
four	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Porringer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Witney	B-pers
Waterfeild	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Earrings	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Coachman	O
that	O
did	O
drive	O
Newington	O
Stage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
did	O
remove	O
it	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Newington	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Avis	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ultra	B-pers
Boyne	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Long	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Neck	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
buy	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
who	O
did	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
did	O
offer	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Istleworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Churchwardens	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
suspecting	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
lately	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
Belly	O
,	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
their	O
Beadle	O
and	O
a	O
Midwife	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Midwife	O
taking	O
some	O
Women	O
with	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
miscarried	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Cart-rutt	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
observed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
little	O
Dunghil	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
hid	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
think	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
hurt	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
cry	O
,	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Unitt	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Clipper	O
and	O
Coiner	O
for	O
ten	O
Years	O
past	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
coin	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Old	B-place
Ford	I-place
,	I-place
by	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
both	O
by	O
stamping	O
and	O
casting	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
stamp	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Gravel-pit	O
,	O
called	O
Five	B-place
Acres	I-place
by	O
Cambridge	B-place
Heath	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Clip	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Clipping	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Copper	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
did	O
aver	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
drove	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
and	O
find	O
some	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Utensils	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
never	O
saw	O
same	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Evidence	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
upon	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
follow	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Unitt	O
in	O
coining	O
of	O
false	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
helpt	O
him	O
to	O
mould	O
the	O
Flasks	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
and	O
watch	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
when	O
Unitt	O
was	O
coining	O
in	O
the	O
Gravel	O
pit	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
bring	O
Stuff	O
called	O
Spawd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Screws	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
coin	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
at	O
Cambridge	B-place
Heath	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deni	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
days	O
of	O
her	O
breath	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
Heath	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Browne	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
a	O
Womans	O
Smock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Loadstone	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Urian	B-pers
Pulford	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Cannon-gate	O
in	O
Staffordshire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
hire	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Staffordshire	O
at	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Copper	O
from	O
Joshua	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
selling	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pero	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stennett	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Trunk	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Mansfield	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Erwin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Findall	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
TheEvidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Rind	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hiron	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ursula	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
waking	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
flight	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Iles	I-pers
a	O
Quaker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
meet	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
shuffed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Canst	O
thou	O
not	O
go	O
about	O
thy	O
Business	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
defended	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Holland	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
Robinson	O
pacified	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
while	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
his	O
Stick	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
;	O
afterwards	O
leapt	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
broke	O
his	O
head	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
unfortunately	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Holland	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harris	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
out	O
Bills	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
same	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
stop	O
the	O
Party	O
that	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Heston	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
committed	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hosey	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
2	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
they	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Saddle	O
under	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fat	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
dead	O
before	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
killed	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
the	O
Saddle	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Budley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
getting	O
Dyes	O
for	O
the	O
Coining	O
of	O
False	O
Guinea	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Harts-horns	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
Barnet	B-place
,	O
and	O
did	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
some	O
drink	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
shewed	O
them	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hostler	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
for	O
any	O
good	O
use	O
,	O
would	O
throw	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
pursuing	O
her	O
Journey	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Hedge	O
.	O
Being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
where	O
she	O
threw	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Coined	O
several	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
False	O
money	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
almost	O
a	O
month	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
Garden-Allies	B-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
in	O
Noble-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
use	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
make	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
could	O
cast	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
formerly	O
keep	O
an	O
Ironmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
fail	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
off	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
did	O
live	O
upon	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Prudence	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duglett	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Tilson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
and	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
Clip	O
above	O
1000	O
l.	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
allow	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
for	O
Clipping	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Clip	O
in	O
a	O
middle	O
room	O
in	O
Garden-Allies	B-place
by	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
carried	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
melted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
drive	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
whereon	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
Rubbed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Clippings	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
did	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Comb	O
Case	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
lump	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
that	O
was	O
naught	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
rub	O
it	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
or	O
no	O
:	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bevin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Victualler	O
in	O
Grub-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
by	O
strangling	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
3	O
men	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
something	O
for	O
their	O
Supper	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sausages	O
fried	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Drinking	O
of	O
Hot	O
Pots	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
;	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
cried	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
laid	O
hands	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Strangled	O
him	O
till	O
his	O
Tongue	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
and	O
tied	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
bound	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Robberies	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Love	O
Court	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
in	O
no	O
ways	O
avail	O
him	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Murrfey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
of	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Smithfield	B-place
during	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thrust	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Hospital-Gate	O
by	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
men	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
suspecting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Swear	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Essex	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
did	O
borrow	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brockhouse	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
an	O
Iron-grate	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
Baronet	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Grate	O
with	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
loosned	O
it	O
;	O
seizing	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
to	O
Bloomsbury	O
Square	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
theyfound	O
a	O
Betty	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipt	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Betty	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
useful	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Chamberlaine	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
South-Mims	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
a	O
small	O
Sum	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
lone	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Highway-side	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Dye	O
at	O
Joe	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
was	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Glove	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
money	O
all	O
of	O
one	O
sort	O
of	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
surprized	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Glover	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sheggy	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Castor	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hamstead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
seditious	O
and	O
wicked	O
words	O
against	O
His	O
Most	O
Serene	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
the	O
words	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faux	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fox	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
Major	O
Lowick	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
divers	O
seditious	O
and	O
dangerous	O
words	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Blythe	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollyland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
the	O
Crown	O
Inn	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Clipt	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
almost	O
2000	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
called	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
at	O
Chipping	O
Onger	O
in	O
Essex	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Clip	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
his	O
Son-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
Clip	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
fixt	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
falling	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
wasted	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
spend	O
it	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
fully	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Devine	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Whitaker	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Coining	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Unitt	O
at	O
Cock-hill	B-place
by	O
Ratcliff	B-place
,	O
did	O
Clip	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
helpt	O
him	O
to	O
Coin	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
averring	O
she	O
did	O
never	O
Clip	O
nor	O
Coin	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Atkins	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Clipping	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coining	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
at	O
the	B-place
Moted-house	I-place
beyond	O
Tuttle-fields	B-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
by	O
cunning	O
having	O
got	O
entrance	O
,	O
they	O
seized	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
a	O
searching	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
by	O
a	O
Plank	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Mote	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Discovery	O
where	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
sunk	O
in	O
the	O
Mote	O
at	O
the	O
Root	O
of	O
a	O
Willow-tree	O
,	O
where	O
searching	O
again	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Board	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
divers	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
Coined	O
about	O
260	O
l.	O
and	O
Clipt	O
150	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
Artist	O
,	O
having	O
learned	O
her	O
Trade	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
ago	O
of	O
one	O
Devorall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
people	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Henry	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jane	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Waugh	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Rescue	O
of	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
corrupt	O
one	O
Munday	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
20	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
to	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Centinels	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Macullow	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
let	O
him	O
escape	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Pope's-Head	O
Tavern	O
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
their	O
money	O
up	O
12	O
Guinea	O
's	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Periwigs	O
;	O
made	O
them	O
pull	O
off	O
their	O
Soldiers	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
away	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Munday	O
60	O
Guinea	O
's	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Emmerton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
Broad	O
and	O
Clipt	O
money	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Broad	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
Clipt	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
got	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Book	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
400	O
l.	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
520	O
l.	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
600	O
l.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
1400	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Clippings	O
he	O
got	O
made	O
into	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
further	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
200	O
l.	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
300	O
l.	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Grazier	O
,	O
took	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
Little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
return	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Woodcock	O
,	O
Receiver-General	O
for	O
Leicestershire	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Long-Crandon	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
lived	O
at	O
Old	O
Bethlehem	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
for	O
Broad	O
money	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
Bar	O
.	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Conspiring	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
Pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
The	O
Court	O
gave	O
him	O
notice	O
to	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
his	O
Trial	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Henry	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
alias	O
Atkins	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Atkinson	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Barlow	O
.	O
John	O
Bevin	O
.	O
Adam	O
Chamberlaine	O
.	O
George	O
Hind	O
.	O
Edward	O
Holland	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Holland	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hutton	O
.	O
Henry	O
Mansfeild	O
.	O
John	O
Norris	O
.	O
Anne	O
Povey	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Perry	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Price	O
.	O
Urian	O
Pulford	O
.	O
Peter	O
Paul	O
.	O
Cyrus	O
Simon	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Starr	O
.	O
William	O
Unit	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Wright	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Bates	O
.	O
Paul	O
Bowles	O
,	O
Deborah	O
Burgis	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bentley	O
.	O
Prudence	O
Brookes	O
,	O
Grace	O
Cook	O
.	O
Elinor	O
Crisp	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Crow	O
.	O
Elinor	O
Dick	O
alias	O
Dike	O
.	O
John	O
Erwin	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
.	O
Rachel	O
Griffin	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
,	O
alias	O
Harris	O
,	O
Jane	O
Miller	O
.	O
Richard	O
Quinter	O
.	O
William	O
Tall	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Wood	O
.	O
Judith	O
Wallis	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
.	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ley	O
.	O
Rachel	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
.	O
Frances	O
Woolley	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
John	O
Cumberland	O
.	O
W	O
-	O
P	O
-	O
Thomas	O
Peirce	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Townsend	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Starr	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Perry	O
,	O
Anne	O
Povey	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hutton	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Wright	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Richard	O
Emmerton	O
,	O
Fined	O
1000	O
l.	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Robert	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
Fined	O
200	O
l.	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	O
Brockhouse	O
,	O
Fined	O
four	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Faux	O
,	O
alias	O
Fox	O
,	O
Fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Maypole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Westminster-Hall-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Waugh	O
,	O
Fined	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Seriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Duty	O
of	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
Divine	O
Will	O
in	O
Afflictions	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
:	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Cure	O
of	O
Distractions	O
in	O
Attending	O
upon	O
God	O
.	O
In	O
several	O
Sermons	O
.	O
By	O
Nathanael	O
Vincent	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Also	O
several	O
Sermons	O
against	O
the	O
Love	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Vincent	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Also	O
his	O
Sermon	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
Enchiridion	O
Medicum	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Manual	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Art	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Parts	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Wherein	O
Is	O
briefly	O
shewed	O
;	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Derivation	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Causes	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Signs	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prognosticks	O
.	O
And	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
more	O
approved	O
Authors	O
both	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
.	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Med	O
.	O
Professor	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Concordance	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
and	O
useful	O
Places	O
which	O
one	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
new	O
Method	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Concern	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
serious	O
Warning	O
to	O
a	O
timely	O
and	O
thorough	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Death	O
;	O
with	O
Helps	O
and	O
Directions	O
thereunto	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Warning	O
to	O
Clippers	O
,	O
Coiners	O
,	O
and	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
Two	O
Penitent	O
Criminals	O
;	O
Daniel	O
Chapman	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
David	O
Tanner	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Executed	O
at	O
Glocester	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
1696	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Meeting	O
of	O
Protestent	O
Diffenters	O
,	O
called	O
Quakers	O
,	O
in	O
Turner	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Month	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Publick	O
Day	O
of	O
Thanksgiving	O
for	O
the	O
Deliverance	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
By	O
George	O
Keith	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Fidelity	O
and	O
Subjection	O
to	O
King	O
William	O
the	O
IIId	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
People	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
themselves	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Persuasion	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
An	O
Exact	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
Turners-Hall	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
called	O
June	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Disputes	O
and	O
Speeches	O
there	O
,	O
between	O
George	O
Keith	O
and	O
other	O
Quakers	O
,	O
differing	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
Religious	O
Principles	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Published	O
and	O
Revised	O
by	O
George	O
Keith	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
containing	O
some	O
New	O
Passages	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Opponents	O
guilty	O
of	O
Gross	O
Erros	O
and	O
Self-Contradictions	O
.	O
The	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Father	O
:	O
Or	O
Counsel	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
Directing	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
Passages	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
E.	O
C.	O
Gent	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Prosaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
gave	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheton	O
,	O
D	O
D.	O
Contemplations	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
Immortality	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Manchester	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
Edition	O
,	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
An	O
Admirable	O
Water	O
against	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Falling	O
Sickness	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Secret	O
kept	O
in	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Family	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
for	O
general	O
good	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Aylmer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
The	O
smaller	O
Bottle	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
David	O
Povey	O
,	O
Operator	O
for	O
the	O
Teath	O
liveth	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Goat-Tavern	O
;	O
who	O
has	O
an	O
easie	O
speedy	O
,	O
and	O
safe	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
,	O
without	O
Stoping	O
,	O
Drawing	O
,	O
or	O
Burning	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
an	O
easie	O
,	O
speedy	O
,	O
and	O
safe	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Sore	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Yellow-Jaundice	O
,	O
Canker	O
and	O
Ulcer	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
Liveth	O
W.	O
Elvry	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noises	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
The	O
Ear	O
is	O
the	O
Organ	O
of	O
Hearing	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
Spiritual	O
Sense	O
,	O
the	O
Agent	O
of	O
Understanding	O
,	O
the	O
Gate	O
through	O
which	O
Sense	O
,	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
Virtue	O
,	O
hath	O
its	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
Soul	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
:	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
Offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
:	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
;	O
takes	O
away	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gour	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resist-Feavers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
;	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
