TOKEN	NE
THE	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hulbert	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cutlove	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Bywater	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Chattey	I-pers
Bartholomew	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rennolds	I-pers
George	B-pers
Norcott	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
William	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Susan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Half-Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pullock	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
I	I-pers
-	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Copping	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
belly	O
near	O
the	O
groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
11th	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
by	O
the	O
Middle	B-place
Temple-Hall	I-place
,	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
lie	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
lie	O
here	O
?	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
roared	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
raving	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
his	O
raving	O
condition	O
,	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
strong	O
waters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I.	O
did	O
alledge	O
,	O
That	O
Slade	O
had	O
been	O
arrested	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
for	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
Slade	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Attorney	O
to	O
defend	O
the	O
Suit	O
:	O
And	O
having	O
Nonsuited	O
the	O
deceased	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
an	O
Appearance	O
,	O
did	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
an	O
Execution	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Costs	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
overheard	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
did	O
spit	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
run	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
belly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I.	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
twenty	O
seven	O
Swords	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Shop	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
word	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Swords	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
priviledged	O
place	O
by	O
Pepper-Alley	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Turner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
Hastings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lodged	O
but	O
two	O
Nights	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Adams	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Ruby	O
Prize	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Harris	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
ashore	O
sick	O
from	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Guernsey	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Turner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
transported	O
the	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
on	O
the	O
said	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Horse	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pocket	O
Pistols	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wattmore	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Willes	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
breeches	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Marrett	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Marshall	O
,	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber-window	O
by	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
strings	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
whil'st	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
and	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Cow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
Heifer	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smither	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
instant	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Doller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cazall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Willes	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marrit	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
one	O
Wattmore	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
cut	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
part	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kertley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Erlesman	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
flowered	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
red	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
and	O
Lace	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
thrown	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Lace	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
hanging	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cheney	I-pers
an	O
infant	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Ten	O
years	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
desire	O
the	O
Childs	O
Grandmother	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
his	O
foul	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
be	O
washt	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Coat	O
before	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
over	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
forced	O
her	O
backwards	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
effecting	O
his	O
purpose	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
her	O
Body	O
:	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
Child	O
complained	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Clap	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
thereupon	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
throw	O
the	O
Child	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Rape	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Braceby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cossoy	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Ashfield	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
into	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
Confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Millicent	B-pers
Hummerston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Fustian	O
Petticoat	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Wastecoat	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bambor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Bambor	O
's	O
daughters	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lace	O
Cravat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silk	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Durdell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Aprons	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pockets	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
some	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afore	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
met	O
her	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
,	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Hildebrand	B-pers
Horden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
forthat	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Cecil	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	O
were	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
Elizeus	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Burgis	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
said	O
Hildebrand	O
Horden	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Breast	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
Tavern	I-place
by	O
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
presented	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Palm	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
did	O
arise	O
,	O
and	O
Burgis	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
Captain	O
Griffin	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
broken	O
in	O
the	O
fray	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
tarried	O
there	O
:	O
Then	O
Burgis	O
fought	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
Pass	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coyning	O
and	O
Casting	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Hicks	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
little	O
Half-Crowns	O
were	O
designed	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
false	O
Six-pences	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
apiece	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Metal	O
called	O
Spelter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
above	O
50	O
l.	O
of	O
that	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
House	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Flasks	O
for	O
Hicks	O
when	O
he	O
poured	O
in	O
the	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Hicks	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Drops	O
for	O
Cabinets	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
Cast	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
particularly	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
Guinea	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
having	O
information	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
drive	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
Trade	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
Haymow	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Plate	O
wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
under	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Blocks	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Dyes	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
under	O
ground	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
make	O
Money	O
of	O
Clippings	O
and	O
some	O
Copper	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
Work	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
Haymow	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
place	O
made	O
4	O
yards	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Trap-Door	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mill	O
with	O
a	O
Fly	O
and	O
a	O
Cutter	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
removed	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Lewis	O
's	O
House	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
false	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
were	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
laid	O
there	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Achurch	O
:	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigail	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
alias	O
Ley	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Criplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Damps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Damps	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrapt	O
round	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old-Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastecoast	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Paul	B-pers
Duesoin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
shun	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Creditors	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Hummerstone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Bambor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bengal	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bengal	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bambor	I-pers
;	O
and	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Winifred	B-pers
Bambor	I-pers
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bambor	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
Casting	O
of	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
at	O
Henry	O
Hicks	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
New-Gravel-lane	B-place
,	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
bring	O
the	O
Metal	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Hicks	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
further	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
Work	O
together	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
in	O
Coining	O
of	O
Oliver	O
's	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
for	O
striking	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
him	O
square	O
pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
like	O
Dyes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Spread-Eagle	O
cut	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
an	O
Engraver	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
down	O
for	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Dyesto	O
Coin	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
3	O
l.	O
more	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
strike	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Dyes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
into	O
a	O
Kennel	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
making	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cutting	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
cut	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
directions	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
think	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
did	O
mind	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
workt	O
hard	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Brasier	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
and	O
troubled	O
with	O
a	O
Distemper	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clancy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
discouraging	O
George	B-pers
Ubank	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Spitting	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcherly	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
did	O
help	O
to	O
Butcher	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Suborn	O
Captain	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
meet	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Posts	O
in	O
Mitre-Court	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
Captain	O
Porter	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
very	O
easie	O
under	O
this	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
he	O
would	O
procure	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Pardon	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
300	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
300	O
l.	O
more	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
land	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
allowed	O
300	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
his	O
subsistence	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
met	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Dog	O
and	O
Partridge	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
before	O
Cook	O
's	O
Tryal	O
came	O
on	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
provide	O
him	O
3	O
Bills	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
Monies	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
show	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
stealed	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
subscribed	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
K.	O
James	O
did	O
know	O
the	O
Letter	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
subscribed	O
by	O
.	O
Then	O
Captain	O
Porter	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Vernon	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
proceed	O
further	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
effected	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
find	O
a	O
blank	O
Paper	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
exactly	O
like	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Seal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
divers	O
seditious	O
and	O
scandalous	O
words	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
against	O
His	O
Majesty	O
and	O
His	O
Government	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
1695.	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
impressing	O
Men	O
for	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
them	O
to	O
desert	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
as	O
Deserters	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
did	O
get	O
considerable	O
Sums	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
allowed	O
by	O
the	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
such	O
as	O
should	O
be	O
imprest	O
and	O
sent	O
on	O
board	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
every	O
Deserter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ibbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
divers	O
seditious	O
and	O
dangerous	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
broad	O
money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hurley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
two	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
a	O
Nightroyl	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Garlickhithe	I-place
,	O
were	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
the	O
Dyers-Arms	B-place
in	O
Thames-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
Coin	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
9	O
d	O
's	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Charcoal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
broken	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Spawd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Argill	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
money	O
with	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
they	O
did	O
Coin	O
in	O
all	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
in	O
no	O
ways	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Edward	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Anne	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Licence	O
first	O
had	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
France	O
at	O
St.	O
Germains	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
England	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
the	O
News	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
that	O
our	O
late	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
of	O
blessed	O
memory	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
100	O
pistols	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
clipt	O
and	O
broad	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
a	O
baser	O
mixt	O
metal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
considerable	O
Sums	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
did	O
amount	O
to	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
a	O
thousand	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
sometimes	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
s	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
good	O
money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
evaded	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutorfor	O
monies	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
then	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
in	O
no	O
wise	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Axton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
iron	O
Vice	O
,	O
three	O
lodring	O
Irons	O
,	O
a	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Pewter	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
did	O
rub	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
shoe	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Clippings	O
lay	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
25	O
s.	O
of	O
Narrow	O
Money	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
Broad	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
never	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Vernarde	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
composing	O
and	O
printing	O
filthy	O
obscene	O
Cards	O
and	O
Books	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
N	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blythe	I-pers
at	O
Play	O
with	O
False	O
Dyes	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Robert	O
Adams	O
,	O
John	O
Brewer	O
,	O
Henry	O
Cope	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Harris	O
,	O
Edward	O
Jones	O
,	O
Anne	O
Jones	O
,	O
William	O
Marshall	O
,	O
James	O
Peirce	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Turner	O
,	O
John	O
Wattmore	O
,	O
Jacob	O
Whitlock	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Pike	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
quartered	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Cazall	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Doller	O
,	O
Millicent	O
Humerstone	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Hurley	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Warner	O
,	O
Susan	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
B	O
-	O
I	O
-	O
Respited	O
before	O
Judgment	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Abigail	O
Kelley	O
,	O
Susan	O
Braseby	O
.	O
Anne	O
Jones	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
John	O
Clancy	O
,	O
Fined	O
500	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Palace-yard	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Powell	O
,	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Robert	O
Leeson	O
,	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Ibbart	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Premises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
D.	O
D.	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
D.	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Volume	O
.	O
Containing	O
Forty	O
five	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
compleating	O
his	O
English	O
Works	O
.	O
Now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
in	O
Michaelmas	O
Term	O
,	O
An	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Apostles	O
Creed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
(	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
Volume	O
of	O
Sermons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
added	O
.	O
His	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ten	O
Commandments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Printing	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
.	O
Practical	O
Dilcourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Left	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
by	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Duty	O
of	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
Divine	O
Will	O
Afflictions	O
,	O
Also	O
by	O
D.	O
Bates	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
30.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Cure	O
of	O
Distractions	O
in	O
Attending	O
upon	O
God	O
.	O
several	O
Sermons	O
By	O
Nathanael	O
Vineent	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
10	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s	O
Also	O
even	O
Sermons	O
against	O
the	O
Love	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
N.	O
Vincent	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Also	O
his	O
Sermon	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
Enchiridion	O
Medieum	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Manual	O
of	O
Physicking	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Art	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Parts	O
.	O
s.	O
l.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
cast	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Wherein	O
briefly	O
shewed	O
;	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Derivation	O
.	O
The	O
Causes	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Signs	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prognosticks	O
.	O
d	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
approved	O
Authors	O
both	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
.	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Med	O
.	O
Professor	O
Price	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Coocordance	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
and	O
useful	O
Places	O
which	O
one	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
new	O
Method	O
.	O
My	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Concern	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
serious	O
Warning	O
to	O
a	O
timely	O
and	O
thorough	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Death	O
;	O
with	O
Helps	O
and	O
Directions	O
thereupon	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Warning	O
to	O
Clippers	O
,	O
Coiners	O
,	O
and	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
Two	O
Penitent	O
Criminals	O
;	O
Daniel	O
Chapman	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
David	O
Tanner	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Executed	O
at	O
Glocester	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
1696	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Father	O
:	O
Or	O
Counsel	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
Directing	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
Passages	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
E	O
C	O
Gent	O
.	O
In	O
12	O
s.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
,	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Ashton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheton	O
,	O
D	O
D.	O
Contemplations	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
Immortality	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Manobester	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
Edition	O
,	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Natural	O
Method	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Latin	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Accidence	O
in	O
Questions	O
and	O
Answers	O
explained	O
,	O
amended	O
,	O
abridged	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
Capacity	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Lowest	O
Form	O
.	O
Into	O
which	O
is	O
inserted	O
a	O
Vocabulary	O
of	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
Words	O
under	O
each	O
Part	O
of	O
Speech	O
:	O
Also	O
Sentence	O
Purtles	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Words	O
put	O
in	O
plain	O
Sentences	O
under	O
every	O
Syntactick	O
Rule	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Hoodly	O
Teacher	O
of	O
a	O
School	O
in	O
Hackney	O
in	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Blew	O
Bad	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
Liveth	O
W.	O
Ebny	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noises	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolve	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
The	O
Ear	O
is	O
the	O
Organ	O
of	O
Hearing	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
Spiritual	O
Sense	O
,	O
the	O
Agent	O
of	O
Understanding	O
,	O
the	O
Gate	O
through	O
which	O
Sense	O
.	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
Virtue	O
,	O
hath	O
its	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
Soul	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
,	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
insallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
:	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
Offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
:	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
;	O
takes	O
away	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gour	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Feavers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
;	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
