TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
1695/6	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1695/6	O
.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
;	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thaire	I-pers
,	O
Thomus	B-pers
Umfrevile	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
Randall	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Westfeild	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Higgens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Nayler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merritt	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ogier	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Winckle	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Bahow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
are	O
these	O
:	O
Christopher	B-pers
Billop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
three	O
Certificates	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Tiplady	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Whitson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Captain	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
His	O
Majesty	O
allowing	O
Bounty	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
Widows	O
,	O
whose	O
Husbands	O
had	O
been	O
slain	O
in	O
Battel	O
,	O
he	O
contrived	O
by	O
Forgery	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bounty-money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
effect	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
three	O
Certificates	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
men	O
slain	O
on	O
Board	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
getting	O
two	O
women	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
Widows	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
slain	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
cunning	O
Wiles	O
obtained	O
from	O
the	O
Overseers	O
and	O
Church-wardens	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Danes	O
,	O
and	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
Certificates	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Widows	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
slain	O
in	O
Battel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
noble	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
done	O
great	O
Service	O
for	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Persons	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
Quality	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
worthy	O
Citizens	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
100	O
Halfcrowns	O
on	O
the	O
Four	O
and	O
twentieth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Garlick	O
Cloath	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
some	O
Clipt-money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
refuse	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Spinks	O
,	O
who	O
discovering	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
newly	O
clipt	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
clipt	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
Cloath	O
at	O
Rochester	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Billop	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billop	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
three	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
with	O
Wills	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Humphry	O
Humble	O
,	O
William	O
Watkins	O
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	O
Ley	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
making	O
ten	O
more	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knowland	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holly	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Castle-Baynard	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
a	O
Silver	O
Scissar	O
Cafe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Essence	O
Bottle	O
2	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fingered	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Wife	O
missed	O
the	O
Scissar-Case	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Servants	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leaping	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
dropt	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Essence	O
Bottle	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
notbring	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Chesnut-coloured	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Stable	O
at	O
Clayworth	B-place
in	O
Nottinghamshire	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Harts	O
Horns	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Tolbooth	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Rixon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
86	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
20	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
Eleven	O
Pound	O
15	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rixon	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
through	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
by	O
Bear-key	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
presently	O
finding	O
his	O
Pocket	O
something	O
lighter	O
,	O
cast	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Bosome	O
his	O
Bag	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
Glove	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
call	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrath	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
two	O
Watches	O
with	O
silver	O
Cases	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Northton	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
two	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Soap	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Cordwiner	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
13	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
58	O
s.	O
and	O
120	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Whitewine	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
dozen	O
and	O
10	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Usquebaugh	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duverge	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Crey	I-pers
:	O
The	O
woman	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
but	O
Kilby	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Davies	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
get	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Celler-door	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
to	O
Kilby	O
,	O
who	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
Kilby	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bad	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Duverger	O
's	O
Clark	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
appointed	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
upon	O
Dudly	O
and	O
Duverge	O
's	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigal	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Baily	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Grig	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mark	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
;	O
the	O
last	O
as	O
Accessary	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Grenow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
120	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Grenow	O
missed	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
Breadstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
got	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbous	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
and	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
woman	O
unlockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
sacks	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
soon	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
Fenton	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
Fenton	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Battey	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
Kettle	O
to	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
concluded	O
to	O
buy	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
own	O
at	O
a	O
Brasier	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
challenged	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Brasier	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
(	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
)	O
till	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Thief	O
:	O
Some	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
that	O
way	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Journyman-Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigal	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sindry	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Tabby	O
Mantle	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
Seven	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Fenton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
more	O
were	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Stanhop-street	O
by	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Fenton	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Mollet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Nicholas	I-place
Acon	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Langborne	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
Mollett	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
Mug	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Drink	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
into	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
Room	O
in	O
Frying-Pan-Alley	B-place
in	O
Red	B-place
Cross-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
of	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
the	O
Letters	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
clip	O
several	O
times	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
abscond	O
himself	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
givinghim	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
nigh	O
the	O
Collar-bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Pinder	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
take	O
up	O
their	O
Hats	O
and	O
walk	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
disarmed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
both	O
the	O
Swords	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Sword	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
be	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
yield	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stept	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
fighting	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
go	O
backwards	O
above	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
met	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
himself	O
and	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
next	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
alledge	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Little-Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Lambs-Conduit	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bliford	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
false	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
ordered	O
into	O
custody	O
till	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
murthering	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
was	O
smothered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
some	O
women	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
Milk	O
in	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
at	O
last	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Trance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
born	O
;	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
expect	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
given	O
her	O
Master	O
warning	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Vosse	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
by	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
with	O
one	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
call	O
for	O
some	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
roasted	O
Orange	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Cup	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
squeeze	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Canary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Cup	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
busy	O
about	O
his	O
occasions	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tied	O
a	O
Rope	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
slid	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
leave	O
his	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
10	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
information	O
given	O
that	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
was	O
used	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
searcht	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
a	O
forge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Lodger	O
who	O
dwelt	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ivett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Smock	O
and	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
crept	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
shelter	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	I-place
alias	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
clipping	O
10	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
information	O
given	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Clipping	O
;	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Ingots	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt	O
money	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Rubbing-board	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
they	O
searcht	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
D	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
hear	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
that	O
did	O
commit	O
great	O
Insolencies	O
,	O
they	O
tarried	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
longer	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
free	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
afterwards	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
them	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
scuffling	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
blow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
civil	O
young	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
ways	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Henry	O
Norton	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
nigh	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
blood	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
and	O
Elizab	B-pers
.	I-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
;	O
Askew	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Silk	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Askew	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Silk	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
Grimes	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Askew	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Grimes	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Knowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Dolswell	I-pers
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Round-toed	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
opportunity	O
conveyed	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Felix	B-pers
Tike	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
;	O
they	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
seeing	O
himself	O
pursued	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
.	O
Damask	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
no	O
great	O
Credit	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ruddells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
to	O
remove	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cross	O
the	O
Timber	O
,	O
and	O
catcht	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
strangled	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wittall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Stocking	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
through	O
a	O
chink	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
clip	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
Broad	O
Money	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
clipt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
send	O
from	O
Lincoln	O
150	O
Ounces	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
Grazing	O
;	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Walton	B-pers
Sise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Huddlestone	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Emmerton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Heston	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
15	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
Meakins	O
's	O
Stable	O
the	O
15	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Carkasses	O
hanging	O
up	O
.	O
Meakins	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Sheep	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
he	O
readily	O
consented	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
affect	O
Emmerton	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
three	O
Bever	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Bever	O
Muss	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Hats	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
running	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
snatcht	O
the	O
Muff	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
6	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
drunk	O
into	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
a	O
Wager	O
,	O
did	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
False	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
mistrusted	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Coyner	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Fob	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
9	O
Counterfeit	O
milled	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
declared	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
one	O
Smith	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
lurked	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Porters	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
melted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stept	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
100	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hewlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
degrees	O
did	O
filch	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Evidence	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Fire-shovel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
Fender	O
and	O
Hooks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carborow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
under	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Owen	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
Knights	O
,	O
High	O
Sheriffs	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
letting	O
one	O
Catharine	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barber	O
,	O
alias	O
Barnet	O
,	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goal	O
:	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quashed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Connaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
7	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
into	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
mist	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	O
Glass	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
cheating	O
John	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
of	O
23	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
persons	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
dropt	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
shares	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
into	O
the	O
Naggs-Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
ingaged	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
amongst	O
them	O
they	O
laid	O
a	O
Wager	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
held	O
his	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
shuffled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lay	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Wager	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
called	O
Sweetners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
by	O
tying	O
the	O
same	O
about	O
the	O
throat	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
strangled	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Grubstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sawcidges	O
for	O
their	O
Supper	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
Hot-Pots	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
almost	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
draw	O
any	O
more	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
pressed	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cried	O
Come	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
Watch-word	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
hands	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
the	O
Neckcloth	O
about	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
Tongue	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
three	O
blows	O
upon	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
upon	O
the	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
now	O
he	O
would	O
lye	O
quietly	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Kinswoman	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
gagged	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
name	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
tarry	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Green	O
Apron	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
that	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
brushed	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
hair	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
hair	O
to	O
fight	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
absconded	O
from	O
his	O
Lodging	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Warrants	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Clipping	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
West	O
;	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Sindon	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinner	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Rocket	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bliford	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	B-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
94	O
Guineas	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
A	O
-	O
did	O
decoy	O
the	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
means	O
they	O
did	O
get	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
reputed	O
Gamester	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
it	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Murfey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Eldred	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
with	O
Gold	O
Flowers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
8	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
Lay-in	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keepers	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Extortion	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
by	O
colour	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
did	O
extort	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
33	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Fees	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
Goal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gawden	I-pers
and	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
from	O
Catherine	B-pers
Toung	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
Majesty	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Goodlife	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Glasse	B-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
sixth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
come	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tasters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
l.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dickett	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
pair	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Johnson	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beasley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Shaw	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Evisham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Rahcell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
William	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wifeild	I-pers
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr	O
John	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
Andrews	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Gloves	O
after	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Peter	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Michael	O
Hall	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Jordan	O
,	O
Richard	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Robert	O
Maynard	O
,	O
George	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Wittall	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
Carr	O
,	O
Hilliard	O
Cooland	O
,	O
Catherine	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Mark	O
Fenton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Johnson	O
,	O
James	O
Knowland	O
,	O
William	O
Kilby	O
,	O
Felix	O
Tike	O
,	O
Abigal	O
Kelley	O
,	O
James	O
Mollet	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
,	O
William	O
Meakins	O
,	O
George	O
Ruddles	O
,	O
John	O
Sharpe	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
George	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
John	O
Carrol	O
,	O
James	O
Gawden	O
,	O
Jane	O
Higden	O
,	O
Richard	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Carr	O
,	O
Hilliard	O
Cooland	O
,	O
Mark	O
Fenton	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Johnson	O
,	O
James	O
Knowland	O
,	O
William	O
Kilby	O
,	O
Felix	O
Tike	O
,	O
James	O
Mollet	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
,	O
George	O
Ruddles	O
.	O
James	O
Pullen	O
fined	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
.	O
Charles	O
Stanley	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
and	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Williams	O
fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Wittall	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
These	O
Persons	O
following	O
were	O
convicted	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardox	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
,	O
with	O
condition	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
serve	O
His	O
Majesty	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
desert	O
or	O
come	O
into	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
pain	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
John	O
Marshal	O
,	O
George	O
Derack	O
,	O
John	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Humphey	O
Burton	O
,	O
William	O
Ingram	O
,	O
Richard	O
Scot	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
,	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
alias	O
Davy	O
,	O
John	O
Shaw	O
,	O
John	O
Terry	O
,	O
William	O
Wake	O
,	O
alias	O
Dimock	O
,	O
Peter	O
Lawman	O
,	O
Francis	O
Buckley	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
John	O
Jones	O
,	O
alias	O
Hodge	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Butcher	O
,	O
William	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Contemplations	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
Immortality	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Manchester	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
Edition	O
,	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Flamstead	O
of	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
his	O
exact	O
Correct	O
Tide-Table	O
;	O
shewing	O
the	O
true	O
Times	O
of	O
the	O
High-Water	O
at	O
London-Bridge	O
to	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1696	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
(	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
publick	O
Houses	O
)	O
.	O
AN	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Nature	O
and	O
Obligation	O
of	O
Legal	O
Rights	O
:	O
With	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Popular	O
Pleas	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
K.	O
James	O
's	O
Remaining	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
R.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Two	O
Sermons	O
preach	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Condem	O
'd	O
Criminals	O
at	O
Newgate	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
By	O
B.	O
Crooke	O
,	O
M.	O
A.	O
Rector	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
's	O
Woodstreet	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Benj	O
.	O
Took	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Middle	O
Temple	O
Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
An	O
Admirable	O
Water	O
against	O
Convulsion	O
Fitts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Falling	O
Sickness	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Secret	O
kept	O
in	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Family	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
for	O
general	O
good	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Aylmer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
The	O
smaller	O
Bottle	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
removed	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
near	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
who	O
prepareth	O
and	O
felleth	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vita	O
,	O
tinctura	O
Vita	O
;	O
and	O
Excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
is	O
likewise	O
sold	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
Countrey	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prevent	O
mistakes	O
and	O
counterfeits	O
,	O
take	O
notice	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
The	O
price	O
Three	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
Bottle	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
Liveth	O
W.	O
Ebny	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noises	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
The	O
Ear	O
is	O
the	O
Organ	O
of	O
Hearing	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
Spiritual	O
Sense	O
,	O
the	O
Agent	O
of	O
Understanding	O
,	O
the	O
Gate	O
through	O
which	O
Sense	O
,	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
Virtue	O
,	O
hath	O
its	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
Soul	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
:	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
Offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
:	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
;	O
takes	O
away	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Feavers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
;	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
