TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1696/7	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1696/7	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaler	I-pers
William	B-pers
Essington	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Hambury	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wandell	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
Nathanael	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Furbisheir	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thorowgood	I-pers
George	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ferrars	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Streater	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hinder	I-pers
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hatchett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
John	B-pers
Uncles	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Ells	O
of	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Adreah	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Minister	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant-Bastard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House-of-Office	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House-of-Office	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
delivered	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
Murder	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
provided	O
against	O
her	O
lying-in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Poltney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked	I-place
,	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloone	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pettitt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
washing	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
leave	O
this	O
upon	O
a	O
Horse	O
on	O
the	O
Wharf	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
another	O
Person	O
losing	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	O
,	O
a	O
Dier	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Bewland	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
Bewland	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
)	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Guinea	B-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
imploy	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Hosier-Lane	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
livelihood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Avis	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
accessary	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
two	O
Rugs	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morfey	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hired	O
Coe	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
for	O
her	O
into	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
her	O
Goods	O
would	O
be	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Landlord	O
:	O
afterwards	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Benson	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
Barnet	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Benson	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Coe	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaseby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Manlove	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Squire	O
Manlove	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hackney	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
rifled	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gaseby	O
in	O
particular	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Finger	O
of	O
the	O
Squires	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
snack	O
'd	O
the	O
Guineas	O
at	O
the	O
Gun	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Gaseby	O
and	O
Evans	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
Ayres	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
so	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Evan	O
Evans	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Gaseby	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Hassell	I-pers
,	O
now	O
in	O
Custody	O
at	O
Welch-Pool	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
Finchly-Common	B-place
.	O
The	O
first	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Laced	O
Head	O
dress	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
rob	O
for	O
four	O
Hours	O
together	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
,	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Cups	O
,	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
a	O
Sugar-Box	O
,	O
Mustard-Box	O
,	O
8	O
Spoons	O
,	O
6	O
Forks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mountfort	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Istleworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas-bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
his	O
Mother	O
turned	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Counter-Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
and	O
Flower	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
hind	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Austins	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Lidget	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloath-hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Steel-hilt	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Helens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Five-pound	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skulthrope	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Sea-Chest	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harveys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
Bottel	O
of	O
Wine	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
poured	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
wish	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
never	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Heaven	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
they	O
should	O
disclose	O
it	O
:	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
bought	O
her	O
self	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
together	O
with	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeareth	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
;	O
she	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
kist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
felt	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
break	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
lose	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
White	O
Bonelace	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
of	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
High	B-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
dropt	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosome	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
15	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Soldier	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
another	O
of	O
Base	O
mettal	O
gilt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creeley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
there	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
;	O
he	O
comeing	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
following	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
neither	O
Stick	O
nor	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pemfret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Casters	O
,	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
two	O
Cups	O
,	O
4	O
Salts	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stoke	I-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowlis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Padington	B-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
an	O
Agate-handle	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
and	O
Saddle	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Brass-heads	O
of	O
Andirons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
nigh	O
the	O
Groyne	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
killed	O
by	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Shirts	O
2	O
Cravats	O
,	O
some	O
Childrens	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
George	B-pers
Fitzwaters	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lose	O
his	O
Cloak	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
his	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
to	O
Griffin	O
's	O
Mother-in-Law	O
,	O
Allen	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
hard	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Mason	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
:	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Sound	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Mart	I-pers
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
(	O
and	O
putting	O
Patience	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Sett	O
of	O
Casters	O
,	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
4	O
Salts	O
,	O
2	O
Cups	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Mart	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Sign	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
lookt	O
about	O
for	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Desk	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
divers	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
further	O
alledged	O
that	O
Mart	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Dam	O
them	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
stand	O
to	O
bind	O
them	O
,	O
kill	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
two	O
Salts	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Windrobe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Charles	B-pers
Parrit	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Anglesey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Park	O
Hall	O
in	O
Essex	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
in	O
White	O
Chappell	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Countess	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
down	O
Leaden-hall	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Tumult	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
transported	O
about	O
14	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
even	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coachman	O
's	O
Cloth	O
Clock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Calamanca	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
R	O
-	O
stole	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
from	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Bull	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Holborne	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Holborne	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
thereof	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hostler	O
did	O
proffer	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mires	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
R	O
-	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Boyler	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
Muggs	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
his	O
Change	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Boyler	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
his	O
Eyes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
some	O
dealings	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Castle-yard	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
false	O
Halfcrowns	O
of	O
base	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
boiled	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
Argil	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
look	O
white	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
proffered	O
him	O
18	O
Halfcrowns	O
which	O
were	O
spotted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
at	O
Kingston	O
Assizes	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Fact	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
knowingly	O
uttering	O
8	O
pieces	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
three	O
more	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
false	O
Shilling	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
11	O
d.	O
in	O
Farthings	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Farthings	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
a	O
Nieghbour	O
being	O
by	O
,	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
upon	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
Naughty	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
the	O
East-India	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quessenborow	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Insurrection	O
of	O
the	O
Weavers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	B-place
House	I-place
and	O
broke	O
a	O
Pannel	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
over	O
the	O
Portcullis	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
yard	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
rifle	O
the	O
Treasury	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
notice	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Multitude	O
was	O
dispersed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Quessenborow	O
then	O
shut	O
the	O
Gate	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
finding	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
the	O
Arm	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Stick	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
detainid	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Multitude	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
a	O
Dividend	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
one	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Prudence	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bedingfeild	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thornecroft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Languished	O
to	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
one	O
Pleasant	B-pers
Sessions	I-pers
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
a	O
Spinster	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
15	O
Years	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plater	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
great	O
Quantities	O
of	O
small	O
Money	O
for	O
less	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Tale	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
off	O
for	O
the	O
full	O
Tale	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
600	O
l.	O
all	O
in	O
such	O
small	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
like	O
could	O
scarcely	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bromely	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Gasely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Hall	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
rest	O
put	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
in	O
Woods	O
Close	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Carcasses	O
cut	O
into	O
Joynts	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Skins	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
besides	O
they	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Spotted	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Veres	I-pers
.	O
Reed	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapned	O
some	O
Silk	O
for	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
alledged	O
his	O
innocence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Line	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
Harvey	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Piccard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Spurrier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Pierce	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
the	O
Escape	O
of	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Sutton	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Sir	O
James	O
Montgomery	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Sutton	O
by	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Secretary	O
Trenchard	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
procured	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
Bribe	O
the	O
Sentinels	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
gave	O
him	O
Ten	O
pound	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
a	O
great	O
piece	O
of	O
service	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
for	O
King	O
James	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
effect	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
for	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Lieutenant	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
Bribed	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
let	O
him	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pricket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
Clipt-Money	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
800	O
l.	O
in	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
Guinea	O
's	O
at	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
really	O
go	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Five	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
and	O
had	O
30	O
of	O
them	O
Shillings	O
for	O
every	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
Money	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
away	O
in	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Egon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
assisting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Birkenhead	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
for	O
Conspiring	O
the	O
Assassinating	O
His	O
Majesty	O
)	O
in	O
making	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coining	O
,	O
That	O
Bush	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
500	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
a	O
Divorce	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
by	O
Consent	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
admired	O
they	O
should	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Proposal	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
replied	O
,	O
We	O
can	O
soon	O
get	O
you	O
out	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
Birkenhead	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
you	O
into	O
France	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Egon	O
was	O
in	O
Flanders	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Escape	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
committed	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Jones	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
and	O
Bush	O
called	O
a	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
well	O
affected	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
Guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
Swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Holdman	I-pers
,	O
Two	O
Soldier	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Cursing	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Hannah	O
Pitham	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Discourse	O
about	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
Monarch	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
love	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
yet	O
they	O
aledged	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
Rescous	O
committed	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	B-place
in	O
Arundel-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
Rescuing	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Somersetshire	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
their	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
sent	O
to	O
this	O
Gurney	O
to	O
the	O
Clubb	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rising-Sun	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
desired	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
8	O
men	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
White-Friars	O
men	O
accordingly	O
went	O
to	O
Rescue	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Rose	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
;	O
but	O
missed	O
of	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
werein	O
Arundel-street	O
;	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Temple-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
Boats	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Dorset-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Gurneys	O
House	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
,	O
they	O
pursuing	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Fryers-men	O
beat	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
lasted	O
long	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Coats	O
,	O
12	O
half	O
Thick	O
Coats	O
,	O
6	O
Frize-Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Micklethwarte	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kindley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapned	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
other	O
Customers	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
honesty	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Maxfeild	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rouse	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Storme	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Baden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Neckcloaths	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
extorted	O
a	O
confession	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
New	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cockerey	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Indictment	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
Act	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Pint	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bernet	B-pers
Carroon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
thirteen	O
Groats	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
looking	O
in	O
some	O
Rubbish	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
stirring	O
the	O
Dust	O
heard	O
something	O
chink	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
hard	O
by	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Molds	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
coined	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocency	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Baker	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Artimore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Salver	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
Spoons	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
against	O
Miller	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
her	O
Husbands	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hercules	B-pers
Stodder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Pistols	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
gild	O
Cobs	O
,	O
and	O
quarter	O
Cobs	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
did	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
for	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Scarf	O
,	O
four	O
Cornets	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloath	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Crelly	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
John	O
Ayres	O
,	O
John	O
Allen	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Brian	O
,	O
George	O
Carter	O
,	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
Evan	O
Evans	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Gaseby	O
,	O
William	O
Griffin	O
,	O
John	O
Mart	O
,	O
Robert	O
Pomfret	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Sound	O
,	O
William	O
Thomas	O
,	O
John	O
Towers	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Adreah	O
,	O
Avis	O
Barnet	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
B	O
Thomas	O
Brook	O
Mary	O
Cook	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
,	O
Gabriel	O
Hill	O
,	O
Ann	O
Langley	O
,	O
Eli	O
zabeth	O
Line	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Mason	O
,	O
George	O
Maxfield	O
,	O
Ann	O
Miller	O
,	O
Prudence	O
Nichols	O
,	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
,	O
William	O
Poltney	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Prosper	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Rowman	O
,	O
T	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
Elizabeth	O
Reed	O
Grace	O
Stephens	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Bromely	O
,	O
Edmund	O
Evans	O
,	O
Richard	O
Gaseby	O
,	O
Elisha	O
Hall	O
,	O
Abigail	O
Jones	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Perrey	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Bromeley	O
,	O
Elisha	O
Hall	O
,	O
Gabriel	O
Hall	O
,	O
George	O
Maxfeild	O
T	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
James	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Brian	O
humbly	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
on	O
Condition	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
transport	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
John	O
Austin	O
and	O
William	O
Holdman	O
,	O
were	O
fined	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Westminster-Hall	O
Gate	O
.	O
Edward	O
Bacon	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
William	O
Forster	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
;	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Gurney	O
fined	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
to	O
the	O
Damag	O
of	O
the	O
Contempt	O
.	O
William	O
Norman	O
fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Petrce	O
Roe	O
fined	O
500	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Hercules	O
Stodder	O
fined	O
200	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
times	O
is	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
,	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Premises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
D.	O
D.	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Volume	O
.	O
Containing	O
Forty	O
five	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
compleating	O
his	O
English	O
Works	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Apostles	O
Creed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
College	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
(	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
Volume	O
of	O
Sermons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
his	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ten	O
Commandments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
.	O
In	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Cure	O
of	O
Distractions	O
in	O
Attending	O
upon	O
God	O
.	O
In	O
several	O
Sermons	O
.	O
By	O
Nathanael	O
Vincent	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Also	O
several	O
Sermons	O
against	O
the	O
Love	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Vincent	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Also	O
his	O
Sermon	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
Enchiridion	O
Medicum	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Manual	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Art	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Parts	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
briefly	O
shewed	O
;	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Derivation	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Causes	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Signs	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prognosticks	O
.	O
And	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
more	O
approved	O
Authors	O
both	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
.	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Med	O
.	O
Professor	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Concordance	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
and	O
useful	O
Places	O
which	O
one	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
new	O
Method	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
.	O
M.A	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Concern	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
serious	O
Warning	O
to	O
a	O
timely	O
and	O
thorough	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Death	O
;	O
with	O
Helps	O
and	O
Directions	O
thereunto	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Pearse	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Warning	O
to	O
Clippers	O
,	O
Coiners	O
,	O
and	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
Two	O
Penitent	O
Criminals	O
;	O
Daniel	O
Chapman	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
David	O
Tanner	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Executed	O
at	O
Glecester	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
1696	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Father	O
:	O
Or	O
Counsel	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
Directing	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
Passages	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
E	O
C.	O
Gent	O
.	O
In	O
12	O
s.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheton	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Natural	O
Method	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Latin	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Accidence	O
in	O
Questions	O
and	O
Answers	O
explained	O
,	O
amended	O
,	O
abridged	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
Capacity	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Lowest	O
Form	O
.	O
Into	O
which	O
is	O
inserted	O
a	O
Vocabulary	O
of	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
Words	O
under	O
each	O
Part	O
of	O
Speech	O
:	O
Also	O
Sententic	O
Pueriles	O
,	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
put	O
in	O
plain	O
Sentences	O
under	O
every	O
Syntactick	O
Rule	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Hoadly	O
,	O
Teacher	O
of	O
a	O
School	O
in	O
Hackney	O
,	O
in	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
10	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Flamsteed	O
's	O
Correct	O
Tide-Table	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
true	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Water	O
at	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
every	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary-le-Bow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
On	O
Rom	O
.	O
3.8	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Bradford	O
,	O
Rector	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Church	O
.	O
You	O
that	O
do	O
want	O
a	O
Cure	O
and	O
Physician	O
need	O
.	O
If	O
that	O
you	O
come	O
betimes	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
cur	O
'd	O
with	O
speed	O
He	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower-end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Claps	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numerous	O
Attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
product	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
ruin	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
Death	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
irregular	O
and	O
base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
of	O
foolish	O
and	O
unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
therefore	O
to	O
Advertise	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Disease	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
to	O
repair	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
performeth	O
the	O
true	O
and	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
thereof	O
,	O
without	O
hindrance	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
all	O
desireable	O
and	O
imaginable	O
speed	O
and	O
secrefie	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
requisite	O
.	O
His	O
Diet	O
Drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
pains	O
or	O
stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
in	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
