TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1698	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
1698	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Frye	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cafold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Everingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Byfeild	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heams	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wingfeild	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lunt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Franklyn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ripping	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Greemes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Allhallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Perrier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Crape	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
throng	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
Taster	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Katheren	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cary	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pather	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hardin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Mantle	O
Gown	O
,	O
4	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Clerk	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
whither	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Trunk	O
full	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
earnest	O
to	O
have	O
kept	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
occasion	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
gagging	O
and	O
binding	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
Clerk	O
broke	O
open	O
9	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
shared	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
Clerk	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
against	O
Douglas	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sherly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
from	O
Allen	B-pers
Wooten	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
handle	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
,	O
whilst	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lion	B-pers
Pollack	I-pers
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
22	O
Peuter	O
Platters	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
3	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
2	O
Persons	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Theodore	B-pers
Pouland	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Headdress	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
5	O
Papers	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
took	O
the	O
Advantage	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
but	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Worsted	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
before	O
the	O
Girl	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
took	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
.	O
Having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Saddle	O
covered	O
with	O
Velvet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Sheerlane	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
jostled	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
arrested	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brothers	O
Debt	O
,	O
occasioned	O
some	O
Difference	O
between	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
enraged	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
Fire-shovel	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
retired	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
Passion	O
might	O
be	O
over	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
threw	O
the	O
Poker	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
taking	O
up	O
,	O
threw	O
back	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
great	O
Love	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
greatly	O
provok	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Conniers	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lemell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
bredth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
some	O
Words	O
past	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Provocation	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
surprizing	O
manner	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
hot	O
pursuit	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ludlab	I-pers
of	O
Shadwel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Neck-cloths	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Line	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wigens	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Fire	O
hapned	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Holburn	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
offered	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
if	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
;	O
and	O
notice	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
expose	O
their	O
Goods	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
May	I-pers
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Antereen	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barro	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barro	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Herrien	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Faircloth	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
two	O
brass	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard-door	O
was	O
lifted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Buttery	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
when	O
pursued	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dryver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
Skellet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Black	I-pers
Guard	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
30	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stocking	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Thomas	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
watched	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
their	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
Thomas	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Devereux	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butterworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
25	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Shiply	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoos	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
Newton	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Shoos	O
,	O
while	O
Bruce	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Servants	O
Back	O
was	O
turned	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
the	O
Shoos	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nex	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discovered	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seywell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
4	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Hens	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Barthrop	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tatnam	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Husk	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Simpson	O
and	O
Musgrave	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wagon	O
,	O
as	O
coming	O
over	O
Stamford-hill	B-place
,	O
they	O
cut	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Packs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
alighted	O
from	O
the	O
Wagon	O
were	O
missed	O
by	O
the	O
Wagoner	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
them	O
drop	O
from	O
about	O
their	O
middle	O
.	O
Barthrop	O
was	O
also	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Deiy	I-pers
of	O
Hillingdon	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Millward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
3	O
Houses	O
being	O
near	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
them	O
all	O
open	O
in	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
immediately	O
making	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Uxbridg	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
in	O
a	O
Church	O
yard	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
of	O
Farringdon	B-place
within	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
disposed	O
of	O
by	O
Murray	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
divided	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
any	O
Person	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Graycock	I-pers
of	O
Cripplegate-Parish	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Wray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Felonies	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Name	O
scratch	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
among	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
broughthim	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Woodburn	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Ridly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
6th	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bentiman	I-pers
of	O
Fullham	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
some	O
Drink	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
continuing	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
were	O
removed	O
to	O
another	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
for	O
a	O
Company	O
who	O
usually	O
dined	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bedchamber	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boutcher	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
arraigned	O
on	O
3	O
other	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edwin	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
others	O
:	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Caleb	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
assisting	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Rammer	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
that	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
6	O
others	O
were	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
River-house	O
beyond	O
Islington	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
levelling	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
common	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
pass	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
some	O
words	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wil	O
.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
engaged	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
Wil	O
.	O
Clifton	O
said	O
he	O
valued	O
not	O
what	O
the	O
law	O
could	O
do	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Passage	O
was	O
no	O
common	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
upon	O
suslerance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
gave	O
great	O
Provocation	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
sudden	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Harison	O
and	O
John	O
Clifton	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
William	O
Clifton	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfiting	O
Spanish	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
cheat	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Forfeiture	O
of	O
lands	O
and	O
goods	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Discharge	O
under	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
and	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
discharge	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Oston	I-pers
from	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Maidston	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreed	O
with	O
Oston	O
's	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
Discharge	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
brought	O
them	O
an	O
Order	O
signed	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
disowned	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
Houblon	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
purse	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
3	O
Miles	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Torcester	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
desirous	O
of	O
Company	O
,	O
bore	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Charges	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
besides	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
communicated	O
to	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
them	O
safe	O
thither	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
threatning	O
to	O
cut	O
their	O
Throats	O
with	O
a	O
Razer	O
,	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mother	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
frequently	O
visited	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
furnished	O
with	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
for	O
refusing	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Slinsby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
bredth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Chancery-lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
another	O
Quart	O
of	O
Wine	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
room	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
mist	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
quarrelled	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
3	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
sitting	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
being	O
jealous	O
,	O
ript	O
open	O
his	O
Brest	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
Wound	O
:	O
Immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
murdered	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Provocation	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
whom	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
entring	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
pointing	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
requiring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
beg	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
prepeuse	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
sudden	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
declaring	O
his	O
Unwillingness	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
given	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Newin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Maxfield	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
Burchet	O
cut	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
Maxfield	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
delivered	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
distributed	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ethrington	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tunbridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hecker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
250	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tinn	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
5	O
dozen	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Calf	O
Skins	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
elephants	O
Teeth	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
hired	O
a	O
Carman	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Battle-bridg	O
to	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
the	O
Tinn	O
to	O
a	O
Peuterer	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspecting	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
stopt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Ethrington	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Boat	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
several	O
times	O
robb	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
10	O
days	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Warbattle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Day-labourer	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
search	O
found	O
his	O
Shoes	O
on	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
's	O
Warrant	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Beef	O
and	O
a	O
Cleever	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Slaughter-house	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
frequented	O
,	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Beef	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
Walford	O
to	O
be	O
dress	O
'd	O
for	O
Dinner	O
.	O
But	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Brown	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Walford	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Short	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Peter	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
ofMarch	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Periwig	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	B-place
Martins-lane	I-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
escaped	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	O
Web	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
brought	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
137	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
understanding	O
some	O
Theeves	O
frequented	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Colston-Court	O
near	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
opposit	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
from	O
her	O
Land-Lady	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Potfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
15	O
Hens	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Johns	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
a	O
brass	O
Kettle	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
Indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
a	O
brass	O
Kettle	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
defective	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ingrum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mosley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
3	O
Callicoa	O
Peticoats	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
whose	O
Dog	O
barking	O
,	O
they	O
fled	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbouring	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
to	O
hide	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Door	O
last	O
against	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
a	O
Betty	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Ingrum	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ness	I-pers
2	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
French	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Kertaly	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
placed	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
their	O
rounds	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
for	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
did	O
not	O
plainly	O
appear	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Buthen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
4	O
Muslen	O
Cravats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
they	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
each	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
discovered	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
F	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
washing	O
and	O
diminishing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
call	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
poisonous	O
Liquor	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
meeting	O
accidentally	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Pallmal	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Discourse	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Mathematicks	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
excellent	O
Receipt	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
Vineger	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
more	O
Discourse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
visit	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
an	O
excellent	O
Liquor	O
that	O
would	O
diminish	O
Guineas	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
without	O
defacing	O
the	O
Characters	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Banker	O
to	O
furnish	O
them	O
with	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
wash	O
500	O
a	O
day	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
to	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Schomberg	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Banker	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
bespoke	O
one	O
;	O
who	O
seemingly	O
engaged	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Meeting	O
being	O
appointed	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
again	O
discoursed	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Banker	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Experiment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
each	O
Guinea	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Guineas	O
diminished	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Schomberg	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Grace	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Majesty	O
viewed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Secretary	O
Vernon	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Order	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Experiment	O
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
Guineas	O
into	O
Water	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
stirr	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
;	O
having	O
weighed	O
them	O
both	O
before	O
the	O
washing	O
and	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
Deanstreet	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Druggs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Order	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Secret	O
being	O
enough	O
to	O
ruin	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
chosen	O
Banker	O
,	O
to	O
supply	O
him	O
with	O
Guineas	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
furnish	O
him	O
with	O
400	O
Guineas	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
worth	O
his	O
while	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
diminished	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
being	O
too	O
much	O
diminished	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
condescended	O
they	O
should	O
only	O
be	O
diminished	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
18	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
covering	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
he	O
had	O
washed	O
might	O
be	O
exposed	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
designed	O
suddenly	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
leave'em	O
the	O
Secret	O
for	O
their	O
pains	O
,	O
they	O
allowing	O
him	O
30	O
l.	O
per	O
Month	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
remit	O
thither	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
all	O
the	O
Profit	O
while	O
he	O
staid	O
here	O
should	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Guineas	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
diminished	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
4	O
s.	O
too	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
tried	O
the	O
Experiment	O
:	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
lessen	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
suborn	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
swear	O
falsly	O
against	O
one	O
Camelle	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Druggs	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
being	O
writ	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
Pocket	O
books	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharen	B-pers
Alederidge	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
Knees	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
picking	O
Kingston	O
's	O
Husband	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
pulling	O
her	O
down	O
gave	O
her	O
several	O
Blows	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
an	O
Imposthumation	O
contracted	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Liver	O
being	O
spotted	O
,	O
the	O
Chyrurgeons	O
gave	O
it	O
as	O
their	O
opinion	O
,	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
fresh	O
Wounds	O
being	O
observed	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
of	O
Great	B-place
Stanmore	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
maim	O
George	B-pers
Red	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
by	O
lying	O
in	O
wait	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
falling	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sherly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Searle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Tibbets	I-pers
a	O
Mare	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
appear	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ballion	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Rouse	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Montague	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Cruchly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sara	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
Sara	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
S.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Yarborough	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
dressing	O
Box	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Lester	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
:	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
W.	O
and	O
Shaw	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stopt	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Lester	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Duncamb	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
from	O
Sara	B-pers
Ingrum	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
11	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
W.	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Norman	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
both	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jones	O
as	O
to	O
Hodges	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clarege	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
One	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
drew	O
him	O
into	O
Coining	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wrought	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
removed	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
Coined	O
several	O
Species	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
some	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
from	O
one	O
Sherwood	O
to	O
be	O
coined	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Sherwood	O
rough	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
finished	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Potbrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Cravat	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickeson	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
18	O
Canvas	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
250	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mackdonald	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
make	O
a	O
Purchase	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Lock	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
each	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
to	O
Mackdonald	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
Dickeson	O
confest	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
In	O
Whitechappel	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
Burd	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
by	O
a	O
Ladder	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
were	O
frightned	O
and	O
dropt	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Dickesons	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Streton	I-pers
,	O
100	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Pork	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
3	O
stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
gold	O
Rings	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
lockt	O
has	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
one	O
Clerk	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
her	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
confest	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
6	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Havata	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sanguinisca	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
John	I-pers
Baptista	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Moses	B-pers
Francher	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Charity	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
below	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
who	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
1691.	O
during	O
the	O
War	O
with	O
France	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
as	O
a	O
false	O
Traitor	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
pass	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
France	O
without	O
Licence	O
from	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
his	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Statute	O
against	O
Corresponding	O
with	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Enemies	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
in	O
Aug.	O
95.	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
accouter	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
again	O
about	O
5	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Christmass	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
late	O
K	O
James	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Pr	O
.	O
of	O
Wales	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
over	O
with	O
him	O
37	O
Commissions	O
from	O
K.	O
James	O
for	O
his	O
Friends	O
here	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Evidence	O
see	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
carried	O
over	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
Names	O
from	O
Ireland	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
above	O
130	O
l.	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
K.	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
K.	O
William	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
her	O
word	O
that	O
now	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Trial	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
;	O
which	O
Letter	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
loan	O
of	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
Hide-park-gate	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Impression	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
Clay	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
one	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
wait	O
and	O
kill	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
at	O
Liberty	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
many	O
Poor	O
men	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
her	O
for	O
advising	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
A	O
3d	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Valenciens	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
swore	O
to	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Governor	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
known	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
end	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
did	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Bouts	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Venner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Douty	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutten	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Sun-Tavern	B-place
on	O
Snow	I-place
hill	I-place
;	O
and	O
Words	O
hapning	O
between	O
Bouts	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
followed	O
by	O
Venner	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Noise	O
being	O
suddenly	O
heard	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
bleeding	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
Bouts	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
Blow	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bruise	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
his	O
Skull	O
being	O
deprest	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
deposing	O
they	O
saw	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
Bouts	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
great	O
Provocation	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Venner	O
and	O
Douty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
latter	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Bouts	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bonn	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Devell	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
24	O
Ells	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenings	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenings	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodged	O
3	O
Weeks	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Return	O
surprized	O
them	O
,	O
finding	O
him	O
coining	O
Half-Crowns	O
;	O
who	O
perceiving	O
himself	O
discovered	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
coined	O
some	O
hundreds	O
of	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
practised	O
it	O
14	O
Years	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coined	O
several	O
pieces	O
in	O
his	O
sight	O
;	O
that	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
fearing	O
a	O
Discovery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
removed	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
Materials	O
for	O
that	O
hellish	O
Trade	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Utensils	O
also	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
coin	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
wrought	O
hard	O
for	O
their	O
Living	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Howard	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ladley	I-pers
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Muslen	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bencomb	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Dresdalt	I-pers
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Losters	I-pers
4	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dalt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
7	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Seaman	O
's	O
Ticket	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
two	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Dey	O
,	O
Edward	O
Short	O
,	O
Mary	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
Ann	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Eliz	O
Hall	O
,	O
F.	O
P.	O
Peter	O
Mackdonald	O
,	O
John	O
Dickeson	O
,	O
John	O
Bouther	O
,	O
Will	O
Howell	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Clerk	O
,	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Jenings	O
.	O
The	O
4	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
37	O
.	O
John	O
Miller	O
,	O
Will	O
Brown	O
,	O
Rob	O
.	O
Graycock	O
,	O
Arthur	O
Slingsby	O
,	O
will	O
.	O
Burchet	O
,	O
John	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Ethrington	O
,	O
Jos	O
.	O
Tunbridg	O
,	O
Peter	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Harbert	O
Herren	O
,	O
Charles	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Flower	O
,	O
Ann	O
Wiggens	O
,	O
Martha	O
Farecloth	O
,	O
Diana	O
Barthrop	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Musgrave	O
,	O
Mary	O
Simpson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bradford	O
,	O
Mary	O
Warbattle	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hamphrys	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Barrow	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Rouse	O
,	O
S	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
,	O
Sara	O
Shaw	O
,	O
Sara	O
Lester	O
,	O
Mary	O
Norman	O
,	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
,	O
Eliz	O
Hadley	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Sutton	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Clifton	O
,	O
Henry	O
Boats	O
,	O
Mary	O
Greemes	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ward	O
,	O
Mary	O
Shepheard	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wood	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bencomb	O
,	O
Howard	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
John	O
Sherly	O
,	O
Richard	O
Ludlab	O
,	O
George	O
Newton	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Bruce	O
,	O
John	O
Walford	O
,	O
James	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
John	O
Price	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
3	O
.	O
John	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Wills	O
,	O
Emanuel	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
during	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
forfeit	O
all	O
his	O
lands	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	O
Worley	O
was	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
Maypole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
Charingcross	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Seaman	O
's	O
Ticket	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
was	O
fined	O
10	O
Groats	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
two	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
both	O
Ecclesiastical	O
and	O
Civil	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
earliest	O
Accounts	O
of	O
Lime	O
to	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
Taken	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
Antient	O
Records	O
,	O
Manuscripts	O
and	O
Historians	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
Memorials	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
both	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrrel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Fol	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
A	O
Detection	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
during	O
the	O
4	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interregnum	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
Coke	O
Esq	O
;	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
An	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
Sir	O
Walter	O
Raleigh	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
in	O
5	O
Books	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Gauging	O
and	O
Measuring	O
made	O
Easie	O
:	O
being	O
a	O
brief	O
Compendium	O
of	O
Measuring	O
of	O
Surfaces	O
and	O
Solids	O
after	O
a	O
more	O
concise	O
and	O
intelligible	O
Manner	O
than	O
commonly	O
practised	O
.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
thereof	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
1676	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Reswick	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Mankind	O
in	O
Matters	O
of	O
Religion	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reasons	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
Diffenters	O
not	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Churches	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
General	O
Naturalization	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Postscript	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Convocation-man	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
attaining	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
containing	O
such	O
Precepts	O
as	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
Languages	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
what	O
is	O
more	O
peculiar	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
By	O
A	O
.	O
Lane	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
:	O
A	O
Treatise	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
By	O
Marius	O
D'Assigny	O
B.	O
D.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Short-hand	O
yet	O
shorter	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-writing	O
advanced	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
swift	O
,	O
easy	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Method	O
than	O
bitherto	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Ridpath	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Diseases	O
of	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Child-bed	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
best	O
means	O
of	O
helping	O
them	O
in	O
natural	O
and	O
unnatural	O
:	O
abors	O
.	O
With	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
Indispositions	O
of	O
new-born	O
Babes	O
.	O
With	O
divers	O
fair	O
Figures	O
in	O
Copper	O
A	O
Work	O
more	O
perfect	O
than	O
any	O
extant	O
in	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
necessary	O
for	O
Chirurgeons	O
and	O
Midwives	O
.	O
Translated	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
.	O
Price	O
in	O
Calf	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
Rutherford	O
's	O
Letters	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Fulfilling	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Providences	O
of	O
God	O
towards	O
this	O
Nation	O
in	O
introducing	O
the	O
True	O
Religion	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Slingsby	O
Bethel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
a	O
Vacuum	O
;	O
wherein	O
is	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
demonstrated	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Vacuum	O
Interspersum	O
runs	O
through	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
in	O
all	O
Bodies	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Lover	O
of	O
the	O
Corpuscular	O
Philosophy	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Militia	O
Reform	O
'd	O
;	O
or	O
an	O
easy	O
Scheme	O
of	O
Furnishing	O
England	O
with	O
a	O
constant	O
Land-force	O
,	O
capable	O
to	O
prevent	O
or	O
to	O
subdue	O
any	O
Foreign	O
Power	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
maintain	O
perpetual	O
Quiet	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
without	O
endangering	O
the	O
Publick	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
shewing	O
that	O
a	O
Restraint	O
on	O
the	O
Press	O
is	O
absolutely	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
The	O
Grounds	O
and	O
Occasions	O
of	O
the	O
Controversy	O
toaching	O
the	O
Unity	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Methods	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
manag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
to	O
compose	O
it	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	O
FIRMIN	O
and	O
other	O
Unitarians	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Whitlock	O
near	O
Stationers-hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cross	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
quality	O
can	O
testify	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
Prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
though	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrare	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditors	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
hundred	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
cured	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
Famous	O
City	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
way	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offer	O
five	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
:	O
Takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
also	O
an	O
Expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
