TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1698	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
1698	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Casebird	I-pers
.	O
Price	B-pers
Seywell	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Neel	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Petit	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Savel	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Tallman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchenson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Alderige	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollins	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Houlet	I-pers
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Clap	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barks	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
in	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Faringdon	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Valentine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
fringe	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Fringe	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lestall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
discoursing	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
casting	O
his	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Box	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
28	O
ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gremes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Boswel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Didia	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
83	O
yards	O
of	O
Callico-cloth	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
24	O
Iron	O
Locks	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
assistance	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingrum	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Raden	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
11	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Raden	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Masters	O
shop-door	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
tyed	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Chair	O
till	O
he	O
made	O
fast	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
her	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Chair	O
kept	O
her	O
legs	O
betwixt	O
his	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
tore	O
her	O
private	O
parts	O
with	O
his	O
fingers	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
himself	O
on	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
former	O
usage	O
hurt	O
her	O
extreamly	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
followed	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
near	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
a	O
mischief	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
promise	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
parents	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
discover	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
fear	O
till	O
her	O
Mother	O
discovered	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
viewing	O
her	O
,	O
discovered	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
imparted	O
the	O
Disaster	O
to	O
the	O
Girls	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
also	O
ignorant	O
of	O
its	O
cause	O
or	O
effects	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
:	O
The	O
former	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
violence	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Lacerated	O
and	O
Torn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
an	O
issuing	O
of	O
a	O
Virulent	O
matter	O
proceeding	O
from	O
a	O
Gonorrhea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
otherwise	O
contracted	O
than	O
by	O
the	O
Carnal	O
Knowledgeof	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
press	O
'd	O
to	O
confess	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
two	O
several	O
attempts	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Girl	O
with	O
his	O
fingers	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
formerly	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
infected	O
with	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Alhollows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dounks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
60	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
some	O
Iron	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
yard	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
observing	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
supposing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
empty	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Palmer	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eusepy	B-pers
Medows	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
silver	O
Taster	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
doors	O
being	O
all	O
shut	O
the	O
Cellar	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
his	O
Counter	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
an	O
accidental	O
Search	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
part	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Guntam	I-pers
and	O
Elenor	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
5	O
holland	O
Coins	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
either	O
the	O
Felony	O
or	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnus	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
35	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Robins	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
Roberts	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Harbert	B-pers
Herrin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
watched	O
an	O
opportunity	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
the	O
Poker	O
from	O
the	O
fire-side	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
forced	O
also	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Exchequer	O
Notes	O
;	O
and	O
placing	O
the	O
Poker	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Crown	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
compounded	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
having	O
his	O
Relations	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
Misdemeanors	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
carrying	O
away	O
4	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Veal	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
carrying	O
away	O
four	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Veal	O
from	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Basket	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
frequenting	O
the	O
Markets	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
they	O
delivered	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
before-hand	O
for	O
her	O
pains	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
mistook	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
it	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
Reward	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
73	O
yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Pewland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Bagnol	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Thistleworth	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Fant	O
le	O
Roy	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Cooper	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Fant	O
le	O
Roy	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
John	O
Waters	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
one	O
Cloth-coat	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
would	O
permit	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
see	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
shaloon	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Tenter-hooks	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Tenter-hooks	O
went	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
up	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
and	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Tenter-hooks	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
Felony	O
without	O
benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
single	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Augustine	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Beddely	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Red	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
whose	O
Possession	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
Information	O
of	O
it	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Horse	O
as	O
his	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Horse	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
green	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
aside	O
by	O
the	O
Owners	O
as	O
unserviceable	O
;	O
so	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
other	O
body	O
,	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
Carrion	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
knowingly	O
hiding	O
,	O
concealing	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
a	O
Press	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
3	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Utensils	O
belonging	O
to	O
that	O
bellish	O
Trade	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Authority	O
from	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
lord	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lent	O
them	O
Mony	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
supply	O
their	O
occasions	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
bad	O
Mony	O
,	O
allowing	O
upon	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
:	O
That	O
about	O
5	O
months	O
ago	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Garret	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
making	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
screw	O
to	O
a	O
Coining-mill	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
making	O
blanks	O
:	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Cellar	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turning	O
the	O
Fly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
putting	O
pieces	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
showed	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
besides	O
Pistoles	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
could	O
coin	O
money	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
no	O
Goldsmith	O
should	O
refuse	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
transmute	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
Metal	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
's	O
House	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
and	O
upper	O
Rooms	O
several	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Mill	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
from	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
's	O
House	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
hellish	O
Utensils	O
lookt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
bad	O
Mony	O
fromone	O
who	O
charged	O
it	O
upon	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
as	O
a	O
block	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
some	O
additional	O
works	O
were	O
made	O
to	O
it	O
since	O
they	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Utensils	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
their	O
Houses	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
remain	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
had	O
constantly	O
free	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
on	O
that	O
Trade	O
without	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
by	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
adjoyning	O
Neighbours	O
:	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Morgan	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
was	O
charged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
little	O
to	O
the	O
point	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
to	O
their	O
Knowledge	O
received	O
any	O
bad	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
honest	O
men	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whittchappel	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
either	O
the	O
Felony	O
or	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
some	O
presumptions	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
coat	O
off	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Coach-box	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
some	O
Goosberry-bushes	O
,	O
but	O
dropt	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
sheets	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
all	O
his	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
being	O
made	O
fast	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Chairmen	O
coming	O
home	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ally	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
noise	O
before	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
cause	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
no	O
good	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
escapt	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
seized	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Ally	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
goods	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roman	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Cecil	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
14	O
French	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
two	O
Doulas	O
Shirts	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Felonies	O
were	O
committed	O
at	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Clothes	O
being	O
hung	O
on	O
Hedges	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
watch	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
missing	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
the	O
others	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threatned	O
that	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
they	O
would	O
begin	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
Child	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
behaved	O
themselves	O
very	O
insolently	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
to	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
Numbered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
warehouse	O
Window	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
Confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
delivered	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Loo	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Patison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Pins	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
12	O
Knives	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Ginger	O
bread	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
But	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sage	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Hartwel	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Looking	O
glass	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
had	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
about	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Luke	B-pers
Hendon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
it	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Shoes	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
observed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Roman	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
upon	O
three	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
after	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
1688	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
without	O
license	O
from	O
his	O
Majesty	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
return	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
into	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
false	O
Traitors	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
did	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
obtained	O
Licenses	O
under	O
the	O
Privy	O
Seal	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
from	O
Rumner	O
to	O
Calais	O
in	O
France	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
December	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Calais	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Proclamation	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
not	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
or	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
fell	O
not	O
under	O
the	O
Statute	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	O
de	O
Gady	O
de	O
Bussy	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Statute	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
and	O
coming	O
from	O
France	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
in	O
England	O
without	O
License	O
under	O
the	O
Privy	O
Seal	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
was	O
not	O
voluntary	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
present	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
to	O
depart	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
in	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
served	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pass	O
obtained	O
thereupon	O
from	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Shrewsbury	O
,	O
by	O
either	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
prohibited	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
France	O
.	O
An	O
Abstract	O
of	O
the	O
Order	O
and	O
the	O
original	O
Pass	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
his	O
utmost	O
endeavour	O
for	O
liberty	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Lady	O
whom	O
he	O
married	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
whose	O
death	O
he	O
had	O
signified	O
to	O
his	O
Excellency	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Portland	O
at	O
Paris	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
coming	O
over	O
hither	O
,	O
desiring	O
his	O
Pass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
publickly	O
to	O
settle	O
his	O
Affairs	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
upon	O
any	O
private	O
Design	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Blanch	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Clark	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
:	O
But	O
Smith	O
putting	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
differ	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
immediately	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tomlens	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
perceived	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Glin	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Gen.	B-pers
Glen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
25	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bonny	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Sibly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Copper	O
Pots	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
24	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sibly	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
act	O
of	O
stealing	O
Glass-bottles	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
500	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Darnell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
stuff	O
Gowns	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
stuff	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
home	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
broke	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bolt	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
on	O
suspicion	O
in	O
a	O
Corn-field	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
clear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Humfrey	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
linnen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Family	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
the	O
Sash-window	O
being	O
open	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
Christmass	O
,	O
and	O
bespoke	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Coining-press	O
,	O
and	O
ibly	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
April	O
after	O
bespoke	O
some	O
shilling	O
Dies	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
Amongst	O
which	O
Sum	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
:	O
The	O
Guinea	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
also	O
the	O
Stamps	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
cut	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
coined	O
with	O
the	O
Dies	O
he	O
made	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coin	O
Guineas	O
file	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
edg	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Rooms	O
with	O
the	O
Press	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
Edges	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
filings	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
May	O
was	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Coining	O
Tools	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Rooms	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
seized	O
at	O
Dublin	O
and	O
brought	O
over	O
hither	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Landladies	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Boutcher	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edmond	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Boutcher	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
melted	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
Boutcher	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
his	O
Arms	O
being	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
cut	O
with	O
the	O
Arms	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
before	O
she	O
melted	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
which	O
Boutcher	O
disswaded	O
her	O
from	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
melt	O
it	O
down	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
flaxen	O
shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbered	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lidel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mees	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Lute-string	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Oliver	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Staines	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
gray-coloured	O
Gelding	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
Stains	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
3d	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
possession	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Reading	O
Fair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Randel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
Pearls	O
,	O
Jewels	O
and	O
Gold	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stanwel	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Sheep	O
,	O
made	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
skin	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
quarters	O
,	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
lights	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
under	O
a	O
hedg	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seized	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lympany	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
knit	O
Stockings	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Dingly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dingly	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Strutt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Glass	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Wash-balls	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Picture	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Douning	I-pers
Bar	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loxly	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
procuring	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
mixt	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
utter	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
paiment	O
as	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
of	O
Sepulchers	B-place
as	O
accessory	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
11	O
yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Fringe	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
Townsend	O
for	O
harbouring	O
,	O
assisting	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Moody	O
being	O
abroad	O
after	O
purchase	O
,	O
waited	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coach-house	O
joining	O
to	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
Moody	O
entring	O
it	O
,	O
delivered	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Townsend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
reset	O
and	O
offered	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Brown	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jewel	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Philip	B-pers
Hokly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
throughthe	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
;	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
jumpt	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
where	O
he	O
hid	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
sink	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Wig	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Sydell	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Rest	I-pers
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth-Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
had	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
cried	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
three	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
3	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
steal	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Doulas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cicil	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
Widow	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
hung	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Hedges	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
dropt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
sweep	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
murder	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
him	O
in	O
Goal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Blunt	O
's	O
and	O
Ellis	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
Marshals	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
alias	O
Ugly	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Muslen	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
Door	O
being	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
Fox	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Clothes	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grumbal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blacket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Blacket	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Copper	O
was	O
fixed	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
over	O
a	O
Field	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Copper	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
followed	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
seized	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carrid	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Copper	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Copper	O
at	O
Barkin	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
observed	O
to	O
tye	O
up	O
a	O
Bundle	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Cellar-door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
in	O
Whitsons-Park	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
close	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Helenor	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
laced	O
muslen	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ingrum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dormet	I-pers
alias	O
Bennet	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
some	O
Iron-bars	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tradway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Luellen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbred	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Markany	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbred	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Argent	I-pers
alias	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
made	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
swears	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Kings	O
Service	O
,	O
under	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dubart	O
,	O
in	O
1691.	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
several	O
Ships	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
being	O
tried	O
and	O
acquitted	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Admiralty-Sessions	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
end	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
in	O
England	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
late	O
Statute	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Licence	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
a	O
meeting	O
with	O
one	O
Lewis	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Lewis	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
the	O
Captain	O
;	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
Jealousy	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
100	O
l.	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Captains	O
Business	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
other	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
them	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
1689	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
long	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
himself	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
served	O
under	O
Dubart	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
served	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	O
Argent	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Name	O
was	O
Warner	O
,	O
as	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
on	O
board	O
other	O
Ships	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Perjury	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Frogget	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
carrying	O
away	O
Letters	O
directed	O
to	O
Parliament-men	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
Bills	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
contain	O
'd	O
therein	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
Houses	O
,	O
was	O
Arrested	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
entring	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
,	O
great	O
many	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Letters	O
directed	O
to	O
Members	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
all	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
one	O
Post	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
60	O
Letters	O
taken	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
directed	O
to	O
Members	O
of	O
Parliament	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Members	O
themselves	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Letters	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
they	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Commons	O
Lobby	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watched	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
Committee	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
to	O
receive	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfiting	O
Bills	O
of	O
Sale	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Oxly	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratling	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Elis	O
,	O
Robert	O
Ingrum	O
,	O
Edmund	O
Audley	O
,	O
Edward	O
Beddtly	O
,	O
Nathaniel	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
,	O
William	O
Cook	O
,	O
Oliver	O
Bright	O
,	O
Robert	O
Brown	O
,	O
Awby	O
Price	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
32	O
.	O
Charles	O
Lestal	O
,	O
Robert	O
Barnet	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Palmer	O
,	O
William	O
Sompson	O
,	O
Roman	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hickson	O
,	O
Edward	O
Cross	O
,	O
John	O
Bek	O
John	O
Tomlens	O
,	O
Arthur	O
Chambers	O
,	O
Robert	O
Jury	O
,	O
Ann	O
Clerk	O
,	O
Jane	O
Robins	O
,	O
Mary	O
Gremes	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Poland	O
,	O
Sage	O
Edmond	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Evans	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Mikany	O
,	O
Ann	O
Oxly	O
.	O
Jane	O
comb	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lia	O
Mary	O
Price	O
,	O
Thomasin	O
Barton	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Mason	O
,	O
Joan	O
Fox	O
,	O
Joan	O
Lart	O
,	O
Mary	O
Clerks	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hades	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bares	O
,	O
Helenor	O
Boucher	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ulix	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
,	O
George	O
Bostock	O
,	O
John	O
Bonny	O
,	O
John	O
Sibly	O
,	O
Hugh	O
G	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Thomas	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
one	O
.	O
John	O
Waters	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Smallwood	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Navy	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
Pay	O
Office	O
;	O
fined	O
6	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Surety	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Richard	O
Froggtt	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
fined	O
13	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Surety	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
William	O
Argent	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
fined	O
6	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Surety	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Stevens	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Grumbal	O
were	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Mander	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridwel	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
at	O
hard	O
Labour	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Trial	O
of	O
Edmund	O
Audley	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	O
Bullevant	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
Aubry	O
Price	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
Note	O
,	O
being	O
both	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
tomorrow	O
in	O
one	O
half	O
Sheet	O
.	O
WHereas	O
of	O
Late	O
some	O
Persons	O
have	O
published	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Confessions	O
of	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Criminals	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
die	O
;	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
thinks	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
imposed	O
upon	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
utterly	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
true	O
Account	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Prisoners	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
Attested	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
;	O
his	O
Account	O
being	O
constantly	O
printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Mallet	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
A	O
Detection	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
during	O
the	O
4	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interregnum	O
;	O
consisting	O
of	O
private	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
many	O
Secrets	O
never	O
before	O
publick	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
more	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Civil	O
Wars	O
in	O
England	O
than	O
has	O
yet	O
been	O
given	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
Coke	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
3	O
d	O
Edition	O
;	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
thereof	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
1676	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Reswick	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Mankind	O
in	O
Matters	O
of	O
Religion	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reasons	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
Diffenters	O
not	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Churches	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
General	O
Naturalization	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Postscript	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Convocation-man	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
attaining	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
containing	O
such	O
Precepts	O
as	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
Languages	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
what	O
is	O
more	O
peculiar	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
those	O
of	O
riper	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
Child	O
that	O
can	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
Method	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
arrive	O
at	O
a	O
greater	O
degree	O
of	O
Knowledg	O
than	O
is	O
usually	O
attain	O
'd	O
after	O
several	O
years	O
Drudgery	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
Road	O
.	O
Most	O
logical	O
Terms	O
being	O
in	O
this	O
Treatise	O
also	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Reasoning	O
may	O
be	O
perfectly	O
learn	O
'd	O
without	O
much	O
farther	O
trouble	O
.	O
By	O
A	O
.	O
Line	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
;	O
A	O
Treatise	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
By	O
Marius	O
D	O
'	O
Assigny	O
B.	O
D.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Short-hand	O
yet	O
shorter	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-writing	O
advanced	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
swise	O
,	O
easy	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Method	O
than	O
bitherto	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Ridpath	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Diseases	O
of	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Child-bed	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
best	O
means	O
of	O
helping	O
them	O
in	O
natural	O
and	O
unnatural	O
Labors	O
.	O
With	O
fit	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
several	O
Indispositions	O
of	O
new-born	O
Babes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefixed	O
an	O
Anatomical	O
Treatise	O
.	O
All	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divers	O
fair	O
Figures	O
correctly	O
engraven	O
in	O
Copper	O
.	O
A	O
Work	O
much	O
more	O
perfect	O
than	O
any	O
now	O
extant	O
in	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
necessary	O
for	O
Chirurgeons	O
and	O
Midwives	O
practising	O
this	O
Art	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
Rutherford	O
's	O
Letters	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Fulfilling	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Providences	O
of	O
God	O
towards	O
this	O
Nation	O
in	O
introducing	O
the	O
True	O
Religion	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Slingsby	O
Bethel	O
Esq	O
;	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
a	O
Vacuum	O
;	O
wherein	O
is	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
demonstrated	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Vaccum	O
Intersperfum	O
runs	O
through	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
in	O
all	O
Bodies	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Lover	O
of	O
the	O
Corpuscular	O
Philosophy	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Immorality	O
and	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
Reproof	O
of	O
Scripture	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Censure	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
.	O
Containing	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
Penal	O
Laws	O
in	O
force	O
against	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Drunkenness	O
,	O
Houses	O
of	O
unlawful	O
Games	O
,	O
prosane	O
Swearing	O
and	O
Cursing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Militia	O
Reform	O
'd	O
;	O
or	O
an	O
easy	O
Scheme	O
of	O
Furnishing	O
England	O
with	O
a	O
constant	O
Land-force	O
,	O
capable	O
to	O
prevent	O
or	O
to	O
subdue	O
any	O
Foreign	O
Power	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
maintain	O
perpetual	O
Quiet	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
without	O
endangering	O
the	O
Publick	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
shewing	O
that	O
a	O
Restraint	O
on	O
the	O
Press	O
is	O
absolutely	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
The	O
Anatomy	O
of	O
a	O
Project	O
for	O
raising	O
two	O
Millions	O
.	O
The	O
Grounds	O
and	O
Occasions	O
of	O
the	O
Controversy	O
touching	O
the	O
Unity	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Methods	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
manag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
to	O
compose	O
it	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	O
FIRMIN	O
and	O
other	O
Unitarians	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Whitlock	O
near	O
Stationers-hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
Physick	O
truly	O
Practised	O
,	O
BY	O
Dr.	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
ordinary	O
to	O
K.	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
many	O
Years	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
first	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
hindring	O
no	O
business	O
,	O
undertakes	O
to	O
cure	O
all	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
bodies	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
he	O
cures	O
not	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
hath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundreds	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
raiseth	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
fixing	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
Take	O
heed	O
whom	O
you	O
trust	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
's	O
become	O
a	O
common	O
Cheat	O
to	O
prosess	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
write	O
or	O
come	O
,	O
for	O
Nothing	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
truly	O
write	O
their	O
Distemper	O
and	O
Age	O
,	O
he	O
fits	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Medicine	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
if	O
present	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
plough-Yard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
Lanthorn	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
integrity	O
;	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditionsly	O
was	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
;	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
is	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
Prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worst	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
hundred	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
cured	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
Famous	O
City	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
;	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
way	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
insallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Act	O
to	O
Admiration	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
:	O
Takes	O
away	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Govt	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
103	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
also	O
an	O
Expeditions	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
