TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
21th	O
,	O
22th	O
,	O
23th	O
and	O
25th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1698	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
21th	O
,	O
22th	O
,	O
23th	O
,	O
and	O
25th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
1698	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Unet	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rodgers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Partherick	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Uncles	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hannet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Berken	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
one	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Office	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sara	B-pers
de	I-pers
Lany	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Dukes	I-place
place	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Antony	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Cup	O
lay	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
followed	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
fled	O
from	O
the	O
Bailies	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
Arrested	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
silver	O
Porenger	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Dogs	O
barking	O
,	O
it	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
jealous	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbors	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
plate	O
amongst	O
some	O
ashes	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
hotly	O
pursued	O
was	O
seized	O
there	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barken	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
4	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Wading	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
37	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
3	O
Pocket-Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
Widow	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Wa	B-pers
Yarbery	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
And	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
taking	O
another	O
of	O
like	O
value	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Temple	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bar	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Yarberys	O
window	O
,	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Temple	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Laurence	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
4	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
having	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seized	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
recovered	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Midsham	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bonlace	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Barnet	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
Picklock	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
latter	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
on	O
their	O
coming	O
out	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bonlace	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Barnet	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
their	O
ever	O
having	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
;	O
that	O
what	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
E.	O
Barnet	O
she	O
bought	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
many	O
Storys	O
,	O
so	O
lessened	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pageter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
Paper	O
Book	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Salisbury-Court	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
Women	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
came	O
before	O
and	O
some	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
coming	O
close	O
about	O
him	O
pickt	O
the	O
Book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
suddenly	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
instead	O
of	O
giving	O
it	O
back	O
pickt	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Crown-piece	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
acquainting	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Book	O
and	O
Papers	O
were	O
thrown	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
was	O
sent	O
thither	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
either	O
the	O
Book	O
or	O
Mony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
9	O
Womens	O
Shifts	O
,	O
40	O
shillings	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sister	O
bringing	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
wanted	O
to	O
case	O
her	O
head	O
by	O
resting	O
the	O
Box	O
on	O
a	O
Shop-window	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
,	O
offered	O
his	O
assistance	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accepted	O
:	O
And	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
box	O
rested	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
gang	O
with	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
the	O
mony	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
sunk	O
,	O
and	O
deprived	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
their	O
shares	O
.	O
The	O
Clothes	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
orders	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
thence	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Left-breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
Sutler	O
's	O
near	O
the	O
Horse-Guards	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
intruded	O
himself	O
into	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
till	O
each	O
Man	O
had	O
spent	O
his	O
Six	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
supposing	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
engaged	O
in	O
a	O
fresh	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
double	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
placed	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Tankard	O
up	O
,	O
emptied	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
committed	O
several	O
Insolencies	O
;	O
and	O
damning	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
by	O
no	O
such	O
Pimp	O
as	O
he	O
:	O
On	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Sword	O
betwixt	O
his	O
leggs	O
,	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
(	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
)	O
without	O
other	O
provocation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Company	O
being	O
so	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
looking	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
gave	O
time	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
bringing	O
over	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
he	O
inquired	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
agreed	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
hand	O
lifted	O
,	O
or	O
Stroak	O
struck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
threw	O
a	O
Tobacco-pipe	O
at	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clave	I-pers
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
on	O
3	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Partmaner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hampshire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Lac	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
former	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shift	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
latter	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Leonards	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Friar	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Anthony	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
travelling	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
near	O
Mims	B-place
he	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
riding	O
some	O
space	O
before	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
askt	O
how	O
far	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
resolved	O
him	O
and	O
past	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Horse	O
tail	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Wood	O
,	O
two	O
more	O
engaged	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
surrounded	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
commanding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
alight	O
from	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
obstinate	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
were	O
knockt	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
lying	O
bound	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
obliged	O
'em	O
to	O
deliver	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
treatned	O
to	O
bind	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
persisted	O
to	O
long	O
in	O
that	O
obstinacy	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
left	O
'em	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
'em	O
have	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
'em	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
Albans	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
free	O
Gentlemen	O
however	O
delivered	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistole	O
.	O
And	O
next	O
morning	O
on	O
pursuit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
at	O
Must	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
dgwar	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
abroad	O
about	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entered	O
the	O
Barn	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Adshed	I-pers
alias	O
Davenport	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenchly	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Freeze	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Parlor	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
somewhat	O
dark	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
for	O
light	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
below	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
lookt	O
over	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
persons	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
clothes	O
in	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adshed	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
both	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
gold	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gaden	I-pers
)	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
,	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
with	O
Adshed	O
and	O
Philips	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Adshed	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Philips	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Eaton	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deposed	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
were	O
stopt	O
as	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
Adshed	O
and	O
Philips	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
affect	O
Howard	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Philips	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Daniel	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Canteril	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
17	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
17	O
silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
one	O
Point	O
Cravat	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Hays	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
some	O
faults	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
treatned	O
to	O
be	O
turned	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
placed	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
occasion	O
before	O
morning	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
confess	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
;	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
one	O
Gray	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Confederates	O
,	O
upon	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Table-Basket	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Hays	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
bruised	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Pawnbrokers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Gray	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
knockt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
Gray	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Mackdonald	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Mackdonald	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hays	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judeth	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Tingsly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Linen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
,	O
Smith	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hans	B-pers
Resnar	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
as	O
Accessarys	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Davenant	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
held	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Locker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
19th	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
occasionally	O
late	O
abroad	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Garden	O
door	O
shut	O
it	O
again	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
mist	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
always	O
plac	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
window	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
knockt	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
heard	O
,	O
coming	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
Entry	O
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
came	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
speaking	O
one	O
word	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
Murderer	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
5	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
only	O
some	O
circumstances	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
their	O
Shoes	O
being	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
impressions	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
mouldy	O
Earth	O
,	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
seen	O
together	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Locker	O
's	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
sure	O
the	O
Man	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
as	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
only	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Trimer	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Jewels	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mordent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
getting	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
14	O
l.	O
of	O
false	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
at	O
a	O
lesser	O
value	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dowey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
But	O
he	O
bringing	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
thro	O
several	O
hands	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Cicily	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
10	O
French	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adshed	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davenport	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pines	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
;	O
another	O
Woman	O
prevailed	O
with	O
his	O
Maid	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
falling	O
into	O
a	O
Musick-house	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
pretended	O
Fortune-teller	O
,	O
they	O
hearkned	O
to	O
her	O
Prophecy	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
should	O
enter	O
the	O
room	O
would	O
be	O
Husband	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
either	O
by	O
accident	O
or	O
contrivance	O
,	O
that	O
Adshed	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
who	O
pretending	O
much	O
Love	O
and	O
Courtship	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
would	O
needs	O
see	O
her	O
home	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
admitted	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
coming	O
again	O
to	O
renew	O
his	O
feigned	O
Courtship	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Folly	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
Holiday	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
seemingly	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Parlor	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
probable	O
the	O
new	O
Lover	O
staid	O
behind	O
for	O
Lucre	O
;	O
for	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Holiday	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
yet	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
stoln	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
Davenport	O
confest	O
the	O
pieces	O
were	O
sold	O
at	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
price	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Pines	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rutton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jaspar	B-pers
Bars	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
suddenly	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
some	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
so	O
much	O
resented	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
great	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
the	O
point	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
obliged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
and	O
pushing	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
several	O
times	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
again	O
renew	O
their	O
engagement	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
closing	O
cry	O
Ho	O
t	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
wound	O
:	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
,	O
particularly	O
on	O
the	O
deceaseds	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Everets	I-pers
and	O
Helenor	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Everets	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
Roberts	O
were	O
seen	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Entry	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Everets	O
entered	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
hand	O
them	O
to	O
Roberts	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Tinker	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
2	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Coral	O
Necklace	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
Locket	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
a	O
common	O
foot	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
2	O
silver	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chance	I-pers
and	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
rooms	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Confederates	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Bedford-Row	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
can	O
be	O
had	O
for	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Croutson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
5	O
Shillings	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
mony	O
to	O
buy	O
Flasks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
send	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Sand	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Tin-Glass	O
from	O
a	O
Pewterers	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
design	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
24	O
false	O
Shillings	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gild	O
a	O
silver	O
Guinea	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
designed	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
that	O
what	O
mony	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
would	O
serve	O
to	O
pass	O
there	O
.	O
And	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
gild	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
several	O
false	O
Stamps	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
seized	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Mony	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
many	O
Tools	O
for	O
Coining	O
at	O
Chester	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
seized	O
him	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
mony	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
coin	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
anotherplace	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
confronted	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
varied	O
in	O
their	O
testimonies	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
hereupon	O
strictly	O
examined	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
hard	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
declare	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
20	O
Guineas	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
Newington	O
for	O
some	O
Weeks	O
,	O
which	O
included	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
declaration	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
being	O
under	O
an	O
ill	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Highway	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sampson	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
300	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hops	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
or	O
Warehouse	O
under	O
ground	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gang	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
:	O
another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
lodging	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
seized	O
they	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
of	O
Padington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huksly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
persons	O
on	O
foot	O
near	O
Tyburn	B-place
,	O
who	O
knockt	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
only	O
suspected	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
proportion	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
:	O
And	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
swore	O
they	O
met	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
several	O
;	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
at	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
in	O
Maribone-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
30	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2	O
d.	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Widen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
5	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
either	O
the	O
Felony	O
or	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
2	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lodowick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
at	O
him	O
a	O
2	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
which	O
hitting	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
reflected	O
upon	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
much	O
undervaluing	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
squitted	O
some	O
Beer	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
enraged	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Paring-shovel	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
averted	O
the	O
blow	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
he	O
designed	O
another	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
weight	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
taking	O
up	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
again	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
temper	O
,	O
being	O
somewhat	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
avoided	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
And	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
dressed	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
twice	O
Blooded	O
:	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
into	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
pain	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
addicted	O
to	O
Quarelling	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
mild	O
disposition	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Eaton	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
worth	O
above	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Lustring	O
Gown	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Eaton	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
Eaton	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
'em	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
Howard	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
36	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
Palmer	O
had	O
12	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Howard	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Bewick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Gown	O
Embroidered	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
5	O
flaxen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Jacob	B-pers
de	I-pers
Lass	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
House	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
from	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
in	O
Bunhill-fields	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
of	O
Fullham	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Ring	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ingrum	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Anchor	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
Cable	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
the	O
Anchor	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
from	O
Dickshort	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Anchor	O
being	O
afterwards	O
cried	O
,	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Midsham	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Treat	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
locks	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tho	O
.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blathwet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
52	O
yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Duttonfield	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cod	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
,	O
wanted	O
one	O
Gwyn	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
House	O
refusing	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Pot	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
rebounded	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
murdered	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
voided	O
near	O
3	O
quarts	O
of	O
Blood	O
at	O
her	O
mouth	O
and	O
nose	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
opening	O
her	O
head	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Imposthumation	O
,	O
which	O
breaking	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
perceive	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
outward	O
Violence	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
And	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Blood	O
issued	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
occasioned	O
such	O
a	O
stench	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
scarcely	O
endure	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
of	O
Padington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
6	O
Chickens	O
,	O
3	O
Pullets	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Felps	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Singar	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
9	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloths	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
into	O
theWood-Garret	O
watched	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Andersons	O
house	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
her	O
Lodger	O
;	O
and	O
receiving	O
an	O
answer	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
some	O
what	O
suspicious	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Nightrail	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
run	O
by	O
her	O
and	O
escaped	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
was	O
discovered	O
and	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Burglary	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Butts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smacks	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Nightrail	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bedely	I-pers
of	O
Hillingdon	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dan	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Band	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
mony	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
immediately	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
goods	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
Stoln	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
but	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
the	O
Norwich	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
worth	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
except	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harden	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Tankard	O
stoln	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
gilt	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
for	O
change	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
John	O
Marshal	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
inspecting	O
narrowly	O
,	O
perceived	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
questioned	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
at	O
Greengoose-fair	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
confest	O
her	O
Husband	O
made	O
such	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Chelmsford	O
Goal	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
account	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bentiman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Doulas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Aubridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
20	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Butter	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
also	O
many	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Latly	I-pers
10	O
Chickens	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeffry	B-pers
Sall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Brass	O
Mortar	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Paulen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
5	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat-flower	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Maidenhead	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
and	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
stole	O
the	O
flower	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
seized	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
only	O
to	O
try	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Falkland	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Laced	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fenny	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharen	B-pers
Beven	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bonnet	I-pers
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Lee	O
,	O
Leonard	O
Leonards	O
,	O
and	O
Ferdinando	O
Croutson	O
.	O
Mary	O
Potter	O
,	O
Mary	O
Seager	O
;	O
and	O
Joan	O
Brown	O
,	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
30	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Price	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Castle	O
,	O
Robert	O
Winder	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Boyn	O
,	O
Richard	O
Atkison	O
,	O
James	O
Philips	O
,	O
Charles	O
Rutton	O
,	O
William	O
Marvell	O
,	O
William	O
Felps	O
,	O
William	O
Dunn	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
John	O
Bedle	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Cook	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
William	O
Paulen	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Howard	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
James	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Sara	O
de	O
Lane	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Anne	O
Lee	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Campbell	O
,	O
Sara	O
Bailly	O
,	O
Mary	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Judeth	O
Wallis	O
,	O
Helen	O
.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Jane	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
Mary	O
Everets	O
,	O
Katharine	O
Parker	O
,	O
Katharine	O
Beven	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
3	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Highway	O
,	O
John	O
Anderson	O
,	O
Geo	O
.	O
Sparks	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
5	O
.	O
John	O
Davenport	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
Ford	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Hays	O
,	O
Charles	O
Gibson	O
,	O
John	O
Holiday	O
Francis	O
Ward	O
was	O
Fin	O
'd	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behavior	O
for	O
6	O
months	O
:	O
Elizabeth	O
Howard	O
,	O
John	O
Marshal	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Steward	O
,	O
were	O
Fin	O
'd	O
40	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behavior	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
A	O
Detection	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
during	O
the	O
4	O
last	O
Reigns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interregnum	O
;	O
consisting	O
of	O
private	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
Observations	O
and	O
Reflections	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Appendix	O
discovering	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
many	O
Secrets	O
never	O
before	O
publick	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
more	O
impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Civil	O
Wars	O
in	O
England	O
than	O
has	O
yet	O
been	O
given	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
Coke	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
very	O
much	O
corrected	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
.	O
Price	O
7	O
s.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
Europe	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
thereof	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
1676	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Reswich	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
included	O
the	O
Preliminaries	O
and	O
Articles	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
the	O
Infringements	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Revolutions	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Actions	O
by	O
Sea	O
and	O
Land	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Steps	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
this	O
General	O
Peace	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
Offers	O
thereof	O
after	O
the	O
Battel	O
of	O
La	O
Hoeue	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
happy	O
Conclusion	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
divers	O
Original	O
Papers	O
and	O
Memoirs	O
never	O
before	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
concern	O
'd	O
therein	O
;	O
and	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
exact	O
Journal	O
of	O
Affairs	O
for	O
above	O
these	O
20	O
years	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
introduction	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
of	O
the	O
Treaty	O
of	O
Nimeguen	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Advances	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
obtaining	O
an	O
Universal	O
Monarchy	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Mankind	O
in	O
Matters	O
of	O
Religion	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reasons	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
not	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
but	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Churches	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
General	O
Naturalization	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
Postscript	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Convocation	O
man	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Joannis	O
Clerici	O
Ars	O
Critica	O
,	O
in	O
qua	O
ad	O
Studia	O
Linguarum	O
Latinae	O
,	O
Giaeeae	O
,	O
&	O
Hebraicae	O
via	O
munitur	O
;	O
Veterumque	O
emendandorum	O
,	O
&	O
Spuriorum	O
Scriptorum	O
a	O
Genuinis	O
dignoscendorum	O
ratio	O
traditur	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
attaining	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
containing	O
such	O
Precepts	O
as	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
all	O
Languages	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
what	O
is	O
more	O
peculiar	O
to	O
the	O
Latin	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
those	O
of	O
riper	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
Child	O
that	O
can	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
Method	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
arrive	O
at	O
a	O
greater	O
degree	O
of	O
Knowledg	O
then	O
is	O
usually	O
attain	O
'd	O
after	O
several	O
years	O
Drudgery	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
Road	O
.	O
Most	O
Logical	O
Terms	O
being	O
in	O
this	O
Treatise	O
also	O
explain	O
'd	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Reasoning	O
may	O
be	O
perfectly	O
learn	O
'd	O
without	O
much	O
farther	O
trouble	O
.	O
By	O
A	O
.	O
Lane	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
:	O
A	O
Treatise	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
especially	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
By	O
Marius	O
D	O
'	O
Assigny	O
B.	O
D.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Scotland	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
asserted	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Dispute	O
concerning	O
Homage	O
,	O
against	O
those	O
who	O
maintain	O
that	O
Scotland	O
is	O
a	O
Fee	O
Liege	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Scots	O
owes	O
Homage	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Tho	O
.	O
Craig	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
Manuscript	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
containing	O
a	O
Confuration	O
of	O
that	O
Homage	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
performed	O
by	O
Malcolm	O
III	O
.	O
to	O
Edward	O
the	O
Confessor	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Short-hand	O
yet	O
shorter	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-writing	O
advanced	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
swist	O
,	O
casy	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Method	O
than	O
hitherto	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Ridpath	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Diseases	O
of	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Child-bed	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
best	O
means	O
of	O
helping	O
them	O
in	O
natural	O
and	O
unnatural	O
Labors	O
.	O
With	O
fit	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
several	O
Indispositions	O
of	O
new-born	O
Babes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefixed	O
an	O
Anatomical	O
Treatise	O
.	O
All	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divers	O
fair	O
Figures	O
,	O
correctly	O
engraven	O
in	O
Copper	O
.	O
A	O
Work	O
much	O
more	O
perfect	O
than	O
any	O
now	O
extant	O
in	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
necessary	O
for	O
Chirurgeons	O
and	O
Midwives	O
practising	O
this	O
Art	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Edition	O
corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
Immorality	O
and	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
Reproof	O
of	O
Scripture	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Censure	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
Containing	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
Penal	O
Laws	O
in	O
force	O
against	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Drunkenness	O
,	O
Houses	O
of	O
unlawful	O
Games	O
,	O
profane	O
Swearing	O
and	O
Cursins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
An	O
Argument	O
shewing	O
that	O
a	O
Standing	O
Army	O
is	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
a	O
Free	O
Government	O
,	O
In	O
two	O
Parts	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Author	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Balancing	O
Letter	O
.	O
The	O
Militia	O
Reform	O
'd	O
;	O
or	O
an	O
easy	O
Scheme	O
of	O
Furnishing	O
England	O
with	O
a	O
constant	O
Land-force	O
,	O
capable	O
to	O
prevent	O
or	O
to	O
subdue	O
any	O
Foreign	O
Power	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
maintain	O
perpetual	O
Quiet	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
without	O
endangering	O
the	O
Publick	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Sadducisunis	O
Debellatus	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
true	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Sorceries	O
and	O
Witch	O
erases	O
exercis	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
and	O
his	O
Instruments	O
,	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Christian	O
Shaw	O
,	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Shaw	O
,	O
of	O
Bargarran	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Renfrew	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
from	O
Aug.	O
1696.	O
to	O
Apr	O
.	O
1697	O
.	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
shewing	O
that	O
a	O
Restraint	O
on	O
the	O
Press	O
is	O
absolutely	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
The	O
Ground	O
and	O
Occasions	O
of	O
the	O
Controversy	O
touching	O
the	O
Unity	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Method	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
manag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
to	O
compose	O
it	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	O
FIRMIN	O
and	O
other	O
U	O
tariant	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Divine	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Whillock	O
near	O
Stationers-hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
+++	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Father	O
of	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
concerning	O
the	O
Expedients	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Predecessors	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Monarchy	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
Physick	O
truly	O
Practised	O
,	O
BY	O
Dr.	O
Kirlcus	O
,	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
ordinary	O
to	O
K.	O
Charles	O
II	O
many	O
Years	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
first	O
a	O
Collegiare	O
,	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
hindring	O
no	O
business	O
,	O
undertakes	O
to	O
cure	O
all	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Irch	O
,	O
Scurss	O
,	O
Leprofies	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
bodies	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
he	O
cures	O
not	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
hath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundred	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
raiseth	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
;	O
and	O
fixing	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quarr	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
,	O
Take	O
heed	O
whom	O
you	O
trust	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
's	O
become	O
a	O
common	O
Cheat	O
to	O
profess	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
write	O
or	O
come	O
,	O
for	O
Nothing	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
truly	O
,	O
write	O
their	O
Distemper	O
and	O
Age	O
,	O
he	O
fits	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Medicine	O
as	O
,	O
well	O
as	O
if	O
present	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plough-Yard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
Lanthorn	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
is	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
Prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrare	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improved	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
hundreds	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
cured	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
Famous	O
City	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
was	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
:	O
Takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessary	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
also	O
an	O
Expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
4	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certaines	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Whereas	O
of	O
late	O
some	O
Persons	O
have	O
published	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Confessions	O
of	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Criminals	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
die	O
;	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
thinks	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
acquaint	O
The	O
World	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
imposed	O
upon	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
utterly	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
true	O
Account	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Condenmed	O
Prisoners	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
Attested	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Hind	O
,	O
his	O
Account	O
being	O
constantly	O
printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Maller	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridg	O
.	O
