TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
,	O
13	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1699	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1699	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Kimble	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ludlam	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wickham	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kidgell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Perrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
thence	O
83	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
Drink	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tarry	O
till	O
he	O
fetcht	O
some	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
askt	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Twelve	O
being	O
come	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
went	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
climbed	O
up	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
got	O
upon	O
a	O
Pent-house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
a	O
Sack	O
to	O
a	O
Window	O
by	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
putting	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
slipt	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Rope	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
between	O
two	O
Gates	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
found	O
blistered	O
by	O
the	O
Rope	O
,	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
New	O
England	O
Man	O
born	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
Gates	O
were	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
Watchman	O
before	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
Creechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Womans	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sampson	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Thief	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
searching	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
his	O
ways	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
he	O
upon	O
some	O
Loggs	O
,	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magdalen	I-place
Milk-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
staling	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Grazett	O
Stuff	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Buccoe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
again	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
pursued	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
conveyedt	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Blair	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithens	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
three	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
six	O
Castors	O
,	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
six	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
heard	O
,	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
her	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
,	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
false	O
Key	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Hackney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloath	O
,	O
two	O
black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
eight	O
laced	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Sham-Letter	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Relations	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Hartshorn-Lane	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
her	O
Cloggs	O
upon	O
her	O
Feet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Cloggs	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dirty	O
Weather	O
,	O
she	O
borrowed	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Perry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ford	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Alice	B-pers
Row	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
sad-coloured	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Atlas	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Fringes	O
,	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
four	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
an	O
Ear-ring	O
with	O
an	O
Emerald	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monies	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Alice	O
Row	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Callico	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Church	O
with	O
her	O
Family	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
saw	O
they	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
break	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
window	O
:	O
But	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
through	O
an	O
old	O
empty	O
House	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Man	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Lady	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Shirt	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Shirt	O
of	O
an	O
Old	O
Man	O
in	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sysom	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
laced	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monies	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
Clarke	O
was	O
for	O
making	O
her	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Back-door	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
restored	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Sysom	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Nests	O
of	O
Cyprus	O
and	O
Wallnut-Tree	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
Wallnut-Tree	O
Table	O
,	O
three	O
Drugget	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Vallens	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Clouts	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
a	O
Removing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Windrum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
four	O
Muslin	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
blew	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
Dine	O
abroad	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
admittance	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
borrowed	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dewty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
Apostles	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
from	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke's-Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
Musling	O
Head-dresses	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lopez	I-pers
de	I-pers
Cordova	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
plainly	O
proving	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Coifs	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Hole	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
creep	O
in	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
Pin	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
SilkScarfs	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pillows	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Acon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Harlow-street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gause	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hesley	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	O
Rand	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Idle	O
Body	O
;	O
upon	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Relations	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
seized	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
freely	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
behind	O
some	O
Brushes	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yarron	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Little	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Iron	O
Locks	O
from	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
same	O
under	O
her	O
Scarf	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
presently	O
mist	O
,	O
they	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Bond	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
Alderman	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
for	O
40000	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Condition	O
to	O
pay	O
1200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
with	O
Interest	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Decease	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
,	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
20000	O
l.	O
paid	O
her	O
within	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
which	O
Bond	O
had	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
witnessed	O
by	O
four	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
,	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Attorney	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Client	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
that	O
another	O
should	O
be	O
drawn	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Bond	O
was	O
signed	O
Robert	O
Clayton	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Seal	O
affixed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
four	O
Witnesses	O
subscribed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
40000	O
l.	O
and	O
dated	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1687.	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
1200	O
l.	O
yearly	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
should	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
Decease	O
,	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
20000	O
l.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
kept	O
a	O
great	O
Secret	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Servants	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
disclaim	O
her	O
Interest	O
by	O
a	O
Bill	O
in	O
Chancery	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
deny	O
him	O
to	O
cast	O
up	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
Arrear	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
special	O
Condition	O
(	O
which	O
Copy	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
54000	O
l.	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
27000	O
l.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
require	O
People	O
of	O
some	O
Credit	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
done	O
himself	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
:	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Bond	O
and	O
the	O
Draught	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
then	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
cause	O
the	O
Bond	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
Lucar	O
,	O
a	O
Scrivener	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
Order	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
altogether	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
wrong	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
N.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cornelius	I-pers
Losvelt	I-pers
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
aforesaid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1692.	O
about	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
200	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1692.	O
he	O
returned	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sooner	O
than	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
N.	O
S.	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
J	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
several	O
Spirits	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
said	O
N.	O
S.	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Whereas	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Losvelt	O
being	O
indebted	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
J	O
.	O
B.	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Stills	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
Malt	O
,	O
Molossoes	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Stilling	O
Trade	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
N.	O
S.	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
J	O
.	O
B.	O
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
Possession	O
for	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Losvelt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Possession	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Partner	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Name	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
owning	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
N.	O
S.	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
villanous	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Sollicitor	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
Court	O
till	O
the	O
Court	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
being	O
severely	O
reprimanded	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Losvelt	O
's	O
Sollicitor	O
should	O
never	O
more	O
come	O
into	O
that	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
J	O
.	O
B.	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
the	O
said	O
Losvelt	O
for	O
his	O
Damages	O
.	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Blissett	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
Joe	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
by	O
the	O
Play-House	O
in	O
Little	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Gaming	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
words	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Great	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leapt	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
Blissett	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Rails	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
to	O
prevent	O
mischief	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
between	O
two	O
Posts	O
to	O
get	O
through	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
Evening	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ignatius	I-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Assaultingone	O
Ann	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
22	O
dozen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
Golden-Square	O
in	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Arrest	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
House	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
Tape	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
her	O
Ring	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Warrant	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
he	O
any	O
Officer	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pembleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sows	O
and	O
four	O
Barrow	O
Hogs	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Sow	O
and	O
one	O
Barrow	O
Hog	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
Paget	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
seven	O
Hogs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
driving	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Sow	O
and	O
Hog	O
of	O
Edmunds	O
:	O
So	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Swan	O
skin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
six	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
after	O
wards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
lower-end	O
of	O
Milford	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
bargain	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
down	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
more	O
if	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
not	O
owned	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nurden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
her	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
Pawned	O
it	O
for	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
76	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
26	O
l.	O
eight	O
Five	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
two	O
Medals	O
,	O
nineteen	O
Pistols	O
,	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
her	O
innocence	O
,	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Charity	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
Nature	O
,	O
had	O
Venery	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
did	O
commit	O
and	O
perpetrate	O
the	O
abominable	O
Sin	O
called	O
Buggery	O
,	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Adam	B-pers
Lyn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Two	O
and	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
two	O
stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Perkins	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
let	O
in	O
a	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
suppose	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bristol	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Lyn	O
,	O
he	O
proved	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bellingham	I-pers
excepted	O
against	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
so	O
many	O
fresh	O
Men	O
were	O
empanelled	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Brian	B-pers
Turbervill	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunk	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Bellingham	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
altering	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
Bill	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Farthing	O
a	O
Day	O
Interest	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
with	O
2d	O
a	O
Day	O
Interest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
altered	O
the	O
Endorsement	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
did	O
offer	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
payment	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
deceive	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
altering	O
the	O
Endorsement	O
of	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Elwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
this	O
last	O
Indictment	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
the	O
18th	O
or	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Lincolns-Inn-Walks	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
business	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
kindness	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fairly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Arthur	O
's	O
Bills	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
Exchequer	O
Bills	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Bill	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
communicated	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
the	O
Trustees	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
Exchequer	O
Bill	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Easton	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
Bill	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
Linnen	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
Bill	O
in	O
payment	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
40	O
l.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
advise	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Bill	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Bill	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
them	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
being	O
disatisfied	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
come	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Bill	O
altered	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
Secretary	O
Vernon	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
an	O
hours	O
hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Mercy	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
replied	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
freely	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
body	O
did	O
it	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
by	O
what	O
way	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
one	O
Arthur	O
,	O
who	O
robbed	O
the	O
Mail	O
sometime	O
since	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Bank	O
Bills	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
believed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
for	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Maxim	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
a	O
Person	O
should	O
confess	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
replied	O
,	O
If	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Maxim	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
old	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
forgotten	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
any	O
such	O
Record	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Tin	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Ells	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
Hedge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
80	O
Ells	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Chatterton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Malsfret	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
Lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Chatterton	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Confederates	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gunford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
Thirteen	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Dornell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
d.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Suborn	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
to	O
commit	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Case	O
with	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Instruments	O
,	O
Twelve	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Tin	O
Boxes	O
,	O
Six	O
Gally-pots	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pincent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
112	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dammaree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Nests	O
of	O
Cyprus	O
and	O
Walnut-Tree	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Malcher	I-pers
alias	O
Pepperill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
four	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Quilt	O
Embroidered	O
,	O
five	O
laced	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Window	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Houseman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
an	O
Olive-Tree	O
Dressing-Box	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Cap	O
Embroidered	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Gilding	O
a	O
French	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistol	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Crookshanck	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
bit	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
struggling	O
an	O
Iron	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
supposed	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
lying	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Danford	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Catharine	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Barrow	O
Hogs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sow	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haden	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledged	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Rawson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bransey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kingsbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leading	O
the	O
Gelding	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
How	I-pers
s	O
Grounds	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
hovering	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Gelding	O
straying	O
with	O
a	O
Halter	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
Cried	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Market	O
Town	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Six	O
and	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
stuff	O
Manteau	O
Gown	O
,	O
ten	O
Laced	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Caliico	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
Apron	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
openly	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
advantage	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sarsenet	O
Head	O
piece	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bancks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Iveson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
Arthur	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Seamens	O
Tickets	O
,	O
pretending	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Plimouth	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Ship	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
made	O
his	O
claim	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
saying	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
Nails	O
,	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
a	O
Fender	O
,	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Alesbury	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Ludor	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
divers	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Indicted	O
this	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Houseman	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wastinnees	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10	O
Jane	O
Blair	O
,	O
John	O
Bellingham	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Browne	O
,	O
John	O
Bransey	O
,	O
Henry	O
Chapman	O
,	O
Frances	O
Fox	O
,	O
Richard	O
Holden	O
,	O
alias	O
Browne	O
,	O
Henry	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Malcher	O
,	O
Susan	O
Ralph	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Cheek	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Francis	O
Child	O
,	O
Ann	O
Edmunds	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Harrison	O
,	O
John	O
Harding	O
,	O
Henry	O
Marshal	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Palmer	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
George	O
Hart	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Perkins	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Jane	O
Chatterton	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Dewly	O
,	O
Jane	O
Metcalse	O
,	O
Mary	O
Pemberton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Winder	O
,	O
alias	O
Windrum	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Walter	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Watson	O
.	O
Jane	O
Blair	O
,	O
Susan	O
Ralph	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Malcher	O
,	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Elizabeth	O
Malcher	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Mary	O
Butler	O
was	O
Fined	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
she	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Iveson	O
Fined	O
Twenty	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
WHereas	O
the	O
last	O
Dying	O
Speech	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Criminals	O
,	O
Executed	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
was	O
published	O
by	O
E.	O
Mallet	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
will	O
now	O
be	O
published	O
as	O
formerly	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
Jer	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
in	O
Whitefriers	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
Attested	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Jo	O
.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Ordinary	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
:	O
Liveth	O
in	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
if	O
cureable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
fight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Cureable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
in	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
Cured	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
famous	O
City	O
is	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
way	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
PILL	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
;	O
Infallibly	O
Curing	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Likewise	O
he	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Clap	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numerous	O
Attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
products	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
ruine	O
of	O
many	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
Death	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Irregular	O
and	O
Base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
of	O
foolish	O
and	O
unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
*	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arecanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
,	O
where	O
purging	O
is	O
requisite	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
of	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
of	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
a	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
make	O
no	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
Sign	O
in	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
.	O
The	O
above	O
said	O
Pills	O
and	O
Gargarism	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
J	O
.	O
Mayor	O
Printer	O
and	O
Stationer	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Castic-Tavern	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
