TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1700	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1700	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LEVET	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
Dyer	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Foxcroft	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowsewell	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Heyrick	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wybird	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Norford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Kidleather	O
Gloves	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alleadged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
to	O
fetch	O
such	O
Goods	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
lack	O
Silk	O
Fur	O
Cap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gilford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
comitted	O
another	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
the	O
Cap	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Terrey	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Guilford	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Stall	O
;	O
but	O
Terrey	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
Ends	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Man	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
Fink	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plates	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
up	O
his	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
searching	O
,	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
only	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Gash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
was	O
turning	O
her	O
Back	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
clapt	O
them	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
do	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
who	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petti-coat	O
,	O
6	O
suits	O
of	O
Head	O
cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Rateen	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Deyrick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bays	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Deyrick	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Brokerwoman	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnett	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
Orgars	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Candlewick	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barnsly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petti-coat	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
Graham	O
took	O
the	O
Stuff	O
and	O
conveyed	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
cheapning	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
an	O
under	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
perceived	O
that	O
Graham	O
took	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
when	O
her	O
Mitimus	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
putting	O
her	O
Head	O
into	O
a	O
new	O
fashion	O
Engine	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Munns	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereuponfound	O
her	O
Guilty	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Barnet	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ellis	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	O
Tanner	O
,	O
his	O
true	O
name	O
being	O
Lingfeild	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Holland	O
Night	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
from	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Henser	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Lingfeild	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
accused	O
them	O
.	O
Morris	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
being	O
dissatisfied	O
,	O
they	O
searcht	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
Lingfeild	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hemsford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Codling	O
Fish	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Chamberlane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
.	O
There	O
bring	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
friars	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
l	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
granted	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
they	O
cut	O
open	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Feathers	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Grass	O
and	O
Dirt	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
Ways	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
doing	O
it	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
her	O
Husbands	O
Commands	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Sirloins	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Shoulders	O
of	O
Mutton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Brittaile	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
54	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Lodger	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
Hall	O
being	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
but	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
Clark	O
likewise	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Bess	B-pers
Knightly	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
had	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
share	O
in	O
Money	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
worth	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
ever	O
confest	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Hall	O
,	O
Clarke	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jones	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lattingbell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
pretending	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Captain	O
Browne	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
mistrusted	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
anything	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
a	O
Chair-man	O
to	O
pursue	O
after	O
him	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
whilst	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
overtaking	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Fort	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
Drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Wives	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
Forts	O
Wife	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pumel	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
a	O
Reason	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
which	O
struck	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
being	O
both	O
Wounded	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bled	O
inwardly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Fray	O
received	O
his	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
good	O
Friends	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Mallum	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
Fist	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
striking	O
and	O
bruising	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Blow	O
but	O
by	O
an	O
Imposthume	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Buckler	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborne	I-place
,	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
committed	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Principal	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edmond	O
Tooll	O
,	O
alis	O
Toolley	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Finchley	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
Belt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Robert	O
Leaver	O
of	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
watch	O
,	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath-coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Leaver	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
Gun-powder	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Fundament	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Leavers	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
travelling	O
into	O
Lancashire	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Finchly-Common	B-place
,	O
by	O
some	O
High-way	O
Men	O
who	O
wounded	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
Horses	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
and	O
Person	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Leavers	O
Cloaths	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Man	O
was	O
askt	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
wore	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
them	O
very	O
cruelly	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
stabbed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
stript	O
them	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
and	O
a	O
Beltfrom	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
with	O
a	O
Port	O
.	O
Manteau	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
or	O
3	O
l.	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
being	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Leaver	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Button	O
and	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
the	O
Stuff	O
that	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Leavers	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
by	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
hard	O
by	O
Hampton-Court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
bring	O
two	O
Horses	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Grass	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
agreeing	O
upon	O
the	O
Price	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
back	O
the	O
Horses	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Horses	O
was	O
shewed	O
Mr.	O
Leavers	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Masters	O
Horse	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
firing	O
through	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
some	O
Men	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
he	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
forced	O
him	O
with	O
threats	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
hold	O
their	O
Horses	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
pulled	O
of	O
the	O
Genmans	O
Coat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
stampt	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
Stomack	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lye	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
downward	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
spare	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Leavers	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
saw	O
Wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
untying	O
them	O
,	O
Shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
went	O
through	O
High-gate	O
about	O
duskish	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
a	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
in	O
a	O
Thicket	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Hand	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
heard	O
some	O
Horsemen	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
road	O
up	O
to	O
Mr	O
Leaver	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Leaver	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
died	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
Robbed	O
and	O
bound	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
over	O
to	O
Whetstone	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Enfield	O
Chace	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
Epping	O
Forest	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Green-man	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
dined	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
German-street	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
resistance	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
Pistols	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
Leavers	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
shorten	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depose	O
this	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stab	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
.	O
The	O
Chirurgeon	O
likewise	O
declared	O
he	O
Probed	O
Mr.	O
Leavers	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Bullet	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
Guts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
such	O
Wounds	O
were	O
always	O
Mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Indictments	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
with	O
one	O
Brian	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Swillivan	B-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Hugh	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Rope	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
cross	O
the	O
Rode	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
doings	O
they	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
stept	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Tooll	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Sullivan	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lyddall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Cavendish	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petti-coat	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
lace	O
a	O
Callico	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petti-coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petti-coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Fringes	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
;	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
reward	O
of	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
out	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Ship	O
Carver	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
20	O
l.	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
left	O
that	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Stroling	O
Player	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
failing	O
in	O
that	O
also	O
,	O
applied	O
himself	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
Cloathed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
requital	O
thereof	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
Confest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Impey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Urlin	I-pers
Widow	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Table	O
cloath	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Southampton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
of	O
his	O
Graces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Grave	O
in	O
Kensington	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoredich	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Labree	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bayley	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jackson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Deverall	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Attkinson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Dukes-Place	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Convicted	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Labree	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Biggs	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrewi	I-place
Holborne	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
,	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
Head	I-place
Tavern	I-place
by	O
Holborn-bridge	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Companions	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
Kidnapping	O
and	O
Trepaning	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Portall	I-pers
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
conveyed	O
to	O
Mary-land	O
,	O
in	O
parts	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
into	O
Slavery	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Spiritting	O
and	O
Treppaning	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
a	O
Christian	O
Youth	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
also	O
sent	O
into	O
Slavery	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
Indictment	O
,	O
proved	O
very	O
fully	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Portall	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
Ceuta	O
in	O
Africa	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
but	O
Two	O
Days	O
,	O
was	O
enticed	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Exchange	O
to	O
an	O
Office	O
by	O
St.	O
Mary-hill	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
bound	O
to	O
serve	O
Smith	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
in	O
England	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
Coopers	O
Parents	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
their	O
Child	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
more	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
they	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Office	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
Smith	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Jew	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
affirmed	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Smith	O
had	O
lately	O
bound	O
several	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
young	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Office	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
all	O
sent	O
for	O
Slaves	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Council	O
learned	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
allowed	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Facts	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
they	O
owned	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
justify	O
the	O
Action	O
by	O
a	O
Patent	O
for	O
binding	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
Plantations	O
;	O
which	O
Patent	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
the	O
intent	O
and	O
meaning	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Patent	O
and	O
Office	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
unfair	O
practices	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
hinderany	O
Person	O
being	O
sent	O
away	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Freewill	O
and	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
his	O
Parents	O
or	O
Friends	O
,	O
which	O
Consent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
Prove	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Friends	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
did	O
Affirm	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Spoke	O
to	O
Samuel	O
Cooper	O
in	O
Irish	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
Bound	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
himself	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Examination	O
of	O
that	O
matter	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Cooper	O
had	O
alwayes	O
Lived	O
with	O
his	O
Parents	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
could	O
Speak	O
Irish	O
;	O
which	O
Witness	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
Secured	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
10	O
s.	O
per	O
.	O
Week	O
allowed	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
shifted	O
the	O
Fact	O
from	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
several	O
bad	O
things	O
were	O
fixed	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
particularly	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
vallued	O
not	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
do	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
was	O
but	O
to	O
look	O
through	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Nutcracks	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
enraged	O
against	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kysor	I-pers
who	O
had	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Apprehended	O
and	O
Prosecuted	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wisht	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Heart	O
Broyled	O
on	O
Coals	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
Eat	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Drink	O
his	O
Blood	O
after	O
it	O
:	O
After	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Summed	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
brought	O
Smith	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
,	O
for	O
Speaking	O
Seditious	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
Words	O
against	O
our	O
Dread	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
King	O
William	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
good	O
Affection	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Bond	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
for	O
300	O
l.	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Littlehales	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Extorting	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
a	O
Carrier	O
5	O
l.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Drawing	O
with	O
Six	O
Horses	O
at	O
Length	O
,	O
whereas	O
in	O
truth	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Warrant	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
Extorting	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Southgate	I-pers
5	O
l.	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
pretence	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
Extorting	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
likewise	O
5	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
pretence	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
paid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
Quarter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
pretend	O
to	O
License	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
Six	O
Horses	O
in	O
Length	O
,	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
from	O
August	O
1698.	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
near	O
50	O
l.	O
besides	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
Quarter	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Inn	O
in	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Gate-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Deputy	O
Surveyor	O
of	O
the	O
High-Wayes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Licence	O
from	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
whereas	O
in	O
truth	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
to	O
produce	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
Deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Inn	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
first	O
5	O
l.	O
was	O
paid	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
several	O
considerable	O
Summs	O
at	O
times	O
besides	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
which	O
they	O
paid	O
when	O
Cook	O
paid	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
only	O
Borrow	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidences	O
all	O
alleadged	O
the	O
Contrary	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
such	O
means	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
had	O
Enriched	O
himself	O
,	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
said	O
Indictments	O
,	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Newey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Goodrich	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
at	O
Southlin	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	I-place
of	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Barbara	B-pers
Farrour	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
Alive	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
together	O
from	O
France	O
sometime	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
Condition	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
Relieved	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
suddain	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
wondered	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
gotten	O
by	O
a	O
Stratagem	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
refund	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
low	O
Ebb	O
,	O
he	O
applyed	O
himself	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
unfortunate	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
sham	O
Marriage	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
Hannah	O
Goodrich	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
replyed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
by	O
his	O
often	O
Importunities	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
Hannah	O
Goodrich	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Somerset-house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
there	O
he	O
Married	O
them	O
in	O
English	O
;	O
but	O
read	O
the	O
Prayers	O
in	O
Latin	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Latin	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
Pronounce	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
Northampton	O
shire	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Goodrich	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Lived	O
there	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
gave	O
them	O
several	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
Sold	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Goodrich	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Crown-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Anns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Search	O
the	O
Register	O
at	O
Southlin	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
which	O
testified	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Barbara	O
Ferrour	O
was	O
Married	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
divers	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
Barbara	O
Ferrour	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
Co	O
habit	O
together	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
own	O
'd	O
Hannah	O
Goodrich	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Marshal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
Poysoned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
using	O
a	O
multitude	O
of	O
Words	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
effect	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Greenway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petti	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
dress	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
lasts	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Hatch	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
took	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
Trespass	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Felony	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
,	O
Kettles	O
,	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mooring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Dimrel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
,	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Pleasant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
lawfully	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
2	O
false	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
other	O
Counterfeit	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
deceive	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Subject	O
,	O
therewith	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Clary	I-pers
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thencea	O
Lute	O
String	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
Petti-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Nethermood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pikes	O
,	O
8	O
Carps	O
,	O
11	O
Tench	O
,	O
3	O
Trouts	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Eeles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Well	O
boat	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
the	O
Fish	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
alias	O
Rose	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
granted	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Contract	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Rug	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
an	O
Amathyst	O
Locket	O
,	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Crosier	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
Rubies	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spellman	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
9	O
Laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
Callico	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Linnen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Spellmen	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
,	O
7	O
Iron	O
Hearth-plates	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nicols	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
black	O
Carolina	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Perruque	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
alledging	O
their	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Rumps	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
2	O
Sirloyns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Meat	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Stone-horse	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Pleasant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
Sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
one	O
Mold	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Chelmsford	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
Steal	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Ta	O
-Cloath	O
,	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
er	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
Stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Littlehales	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
extorting	O
Money	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
It	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
of	O
3	O
former	O
Indictments	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
100	O
l.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
Stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloath-coat	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
150	O
Spanish	O
Dollars	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sows	O
,	O
value	O
47	O
s	O
.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Bullion	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Charriot	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sise	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Usquin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Mark	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Cover	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Porringer	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felonously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petti	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Petti-coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Willful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Recieved	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11	O
.	O
Jane	O
Biggs	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Philip	O
Clark	O
,	O
Richard	O
Gash	O
,	O
Anne	O
Graham	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Greene	O
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	O
Jones	O
,	O
Cecilia	O
Labree	O
,	O
Brian	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
Edmond	O
Tooll	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheeck	O
12	O
.	O
Andrew	O
Andrews	O
,	O
John	O
Adams	O
,	O
Peter	O
Browne	O
,	O
Francis	O
Coleman	O
,	O
Robert	O
Collins	O
,	O
John	O
Handly	O
,	O
William	O
Lyddalt	O
Catherine	O
Lewis	O
,	O
George	O
Oxford	O
,	O
Walter	O
Terrey	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
Wood	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Walker	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3	O
.	O
Cornelius	O
Fort	O
,	O
James	O
Hewit	O
and	O
Charles	O
Newey	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
8	O
.	O
John	O
Browne	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Lee	O
,	O
James	O
Morris	O
,	O
Henry	O
Merchant	O
,	O
William	O
Netherwood	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Richmond	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Spellman	O
and	O
John	O
Willis	O
.	O
Edmond	O
Tool	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
and	O
Hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Chains	O
a	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
conveniently	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
.	O
Reprieved	O
after	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Nicholas	O
Bennet	O
and	O
John	O
Jones	O
.	O
Ann	O
Graham	O
,	O
Jane	O
Biggs	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Anne	O
Graham	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Biggs	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
John	O
Littlehales	O
Fined	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
his	O
5	O
Misdedmeanors	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Surties	O
for	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Henry	O
Waldron	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
Fined	O
80	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower-end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
in	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
menton	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Patients	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
Cured	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
famous	O
City	O
is	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Ability	O
and	O
Care	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
.	O
Likewise	O
he	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Diseale	O
and	O
Clap	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numorous	O
Attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
products	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
ruin	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
Death	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Irregular	O
and	O
Base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicinee	O
of	O
Foolish	O
and	O
Unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
Smith	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
any	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
requisite	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
Sign	O
is	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
.	O
The	O
above	O
said	O
Pills	O
and	O
Gargarism	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
J	O
:	O
Mayes	O
,	O
Printer	O
and	O
Stationer	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
A	O
New	O
way	O
of	O
Glass-Clipping	O
,	O
performed	O
without	O
Fire	O
,	O
Lamp	O
,	O
or	O
Mouth	O
Suction	O
,	O
invented	O
by	O
F	O
,	O
HAWKSBEE	O
'	O
only	O
,	O
in	O
Giltspur-street	O
,	O
just	O
without	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
Publick	O
Good	O
selleth	O
the	O
Engine	O
,	O
Glasses	O
,	O
Scarrifying	O
Flems	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Appurtenances	O
that	O
compleat	O
its	O
Practice	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
so	O
easie	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Operation	O
,	O
any	O
Person	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
performing	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Glasses	O
that	O
will	O
Cup	O
a	O
whole	O
Finger	O
or	O
Toe	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
besides	O
others	O
larger	O
and	O
smaller	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
useful	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
several	O
Glasses	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
applied	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
one	O
small	O
Engine	O
required	O
in	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
Suction	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
to	O
any	O
degree	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Operator	O
shall	O
find	O
necessary	O
.	O
Attendance	O
is	O
daily	O
given	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Operation	O
to	O
any	O
Phisitian	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
that	O
shall	O
desire	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
now	O
practised	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
eminent	O
Surgeons	O
both	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
Any	O
Surgeon	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Engine	O
,	O
and	O
sett	O
of	O
Glasses	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Directions	O
in	O
Writing	O
how	O
to	O
order	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
whatsoever	O
else	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Practise	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
farthest	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
,	O
in	O
Blew-Ball	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Court	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Saisbury-Square	O
,	O
Persons	O
may	O
have	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Business	O
depending	O
before	O
the	O
Council	O
.	O
Lords	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
his	O
Majestys	O
Treasury	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
and	O
Navy	O
Office	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Out	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
Causes	O
depending	O
in	O
the	O
High-Court	O
of	O
Chancery	O
,	O
Courts	O
of	O
Kings-Bench	O
Common-Pleas	O
,	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Speedily	O
and	O
Faithfully	O
Sollicited	O
.	O
Persons	O
may	O
here	O
be	O
Furnished	O
with	O
what	O
Sums	O
they	O
please	O
on	O
good	O
Mortgages	O
.	O
Any	O
who	O
have	O
Estates	O
Houses	O
.	O
Grounds	O
.	O
Rents	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
Sell	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Titles	O
are	O
indisputable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
will	O
deal	O
on	O
reasonable	O
Terms	O
,	O
may	O
here	O
be	O
recommended	O
to	O
able	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
make	O
an	O
Interest	O
to	O
invest	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
Employments	O
suitable	O
to	O
their	O
several	O
Qualities	O
and	O
Capacities	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
Places	O
both	O
in	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
from	O
1200	O
to	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
Many	O
for	O
Life	O
;	O
Qualifications	O
for	O
most	O
,	O
required	O
only	O
to	O
Write	O
a	O
legible	O
Hand	O
:	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
ones	O
,	O
but	O
small	O
Attendance	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
manag	O
'd	O
by	O
Deputies	O
:	O
For	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
I	O
refer	O
to	O
my	O
Bills	O
,	O
published	O
in	O
most	O
Coffee-houses	O
:	O
Or	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
Gratis	O
.	O
WHereas	O
Mr.	O
Edmond	O
Searle	O
,	O
lately	O
deceased	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
famous	O
at	O
curing	O
all	O
forts	O
of	O
Deasness	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
therefore	O
to	O
Adverise	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Graves	O
Overton	O
,	O
his	O
only	O
Servant	O
,	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Ear	O
in	O
Pye	O
Corner	O
,	O
alias	O
Gilt-spur-street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
performs	O
the	O
same	O
Cures	O
by	O
his	O
Masters	O
secret	O
Method	O
There	O
being	O
now	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Family	O
living	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
performs	O
the	O
said	O
Cure	O
.	O
THe	O
Famous	O
Issue-Plaister	O
prepared	O
by	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Fragrant	O
and	O
Pleasant	O
Scent	O
,	O
sticking	O
without	O
Rolling	O
or	O
Binding	O
,	O
spread	O
upon	O
Issue-Paper	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
sold	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
as	O
will	O
make	O
11	O
dozen	O
of	O
Plaisters	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
dress	O
your	O
Issue	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Billingsly	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Printing-Press	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dancer	O
's	O
Bookseller	O
next	O
St.	O
Difnstan	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hannam	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Toy-Shop	O
on	O
the	O
North	O
side	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
Mr	O
,	O
Smeaton	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Pen	O
against	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Thornton	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
Toy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
Connterfiets	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
is	O
upon	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Plaister	O
Roll	O
'd	O
up	O
viz	O
.	O
A	O
Lyon	O
Passant	O
between	O
three	O
Starrs	O
Index	O
.	O
beware	O
of	O
the	O
Garways	O
Fruiterer	O
who	O
Counterfiets	O
,	O
