TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1701	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1701	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elborow	I-pers
,	O
Dier	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Mathew	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Turbervil	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Arguis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Fustian	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Shop-lifter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
dirty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
buy	O
some	O
Fustian	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
medle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
)	O
for	O
Stealing	O
1000	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Braines	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
by	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
Padlockt	O
up	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
with	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Padlock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
Williams	O
lent	O
them	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
some	O
Matches	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
they	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
gave	O
them	O
28	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Williams	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Williams	O
also	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
calling	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Man	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
Mug	O
tipt	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servent	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mathia	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland-apron	O
,	O
a	O
Holland-smock	O
,	O
2	O
Coiss	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothingof	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Bread-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Knot	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
:	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
calling	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
black	O
Silk	O
;	O
they	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
pulled	O
a	O
Squirrel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Closet	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prentice	O
went	O
to	O
catch	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
catcht	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
Belcher	O
take	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
He	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Shop-lifters	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
thinking	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
betray	O
'd	O
,	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
They	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
the	O
same	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Fast-day	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Kitchen-fire	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Mistress	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
for	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
better	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
work	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
she	O
did	O
mistrust	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
No	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Arm	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Chare-woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Brickbats	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
likely	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
alive	O
Born	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
Arm	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Things	O
for	O
a	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
Sisters	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
:	O
She	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Fall	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
hurt	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
felt	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
stir	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
one	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
Condition	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neck-cloth	O
2	O
Necks	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
catcht	O
her	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Winsor-Court	B-place
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
making	O
an	O
idle	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Tortoise	O
shell	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jefferies	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Stephens	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Huffam	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
11	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
but	O
done	O
by	O
consent	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Hellens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Pooler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
was	O
seen	O
hovering	O
about	O
an	O
Apple	O
stall	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
left	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
He	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Stall-door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
them	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hubart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Diamond-ring	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Alkorne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
washing	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
Ring	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
presently	O
mist	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
till	O
sometime	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
found	O
sewed	O
into	O
her	O
Stomacher	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
soplainly	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Restitution	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
divers	O
Goods	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
feloniously	O
stolen	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Luke	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Feme	O
Covert	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
quasht	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Tite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
Steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Tite	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
holding	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
smoaking	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
saw	O
Flower	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
Master	O
:	O
She	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Flower	O
,	O
and	O
Ellis	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
,	O
she	O
shut	O
but	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
their	O
Feet	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Piazza	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Tite	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
rescued	O
him	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
nor	O
were	O
never	O
near	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Castor	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Blackwel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
he	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Istleworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Higby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Spade	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Flock-bolster	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
She	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Spade	O
sold	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Twittenham	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sallitay	I-pers
,	O
and	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
10	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Sallitay	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
sometimes	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
G	O
-	O
who	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
G	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Sallitay	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Black-woman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland-sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sealey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Alamode-scarf	O
and	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blevey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Broome	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
6	O
silk	O
Scarfs	O
embroidered	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
quilted	O
Wastcoats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Atkins	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
dropt	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
tenderness	O
of	O
Atkin	O
's	O
Age	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
2	O
others	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Pridow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Callico-gown	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
who	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Wastcoat	O
embroidered	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Claude	O
du	O
Parrel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
bruising	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
Arms	O
,	O
Thighs	O
,	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
4	O
Holland-shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lite	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
alleging	O
their	O
Innocence	O
,	O
calling	O
People	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Burdock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Mark	B-place
stay	I-place
,	O
near	O
Colchester	B-place
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
near	O
Colchester	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
2	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
upon	O
one	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
Rumford	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
ride	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
overtake	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Picadilly	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Alamode	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
an	O
embroidered	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
unwasht	O
Linnen	O
to	O
Kent-street	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
mistrusting	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
Owner	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
some	O
Water-men	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
inquiry	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
Bulk	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Laddin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whip	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
only	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
Pepper-Alley	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hollingsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
several	O
Sails	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
second	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
third	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
3	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bailis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Spiggot	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mackrary	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Surry	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Farrel	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
certain	O
Kicks	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
Foot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
private	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
Cods	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	O
Peters	O
in	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Turnley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wagstaffe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
4	O
firsts	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
as	O
Accessarys	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Susan	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
did	O
put	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Beril	I-pers
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Foot-man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
3	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
their	O
Faces	O
were	O
blackt	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
strugled	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Napkin	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Rogues	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
strugled	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
thrust	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
to	O
strangle	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
who	O
found	O
Jones	O
and	O
Turnley	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
under	O
ground	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
Vizards	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
Lantern	O
,	O
Gaggs	O
,	O
Chissels	O
,	O
Cords	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
But	O
Morris	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Shoes	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Morris	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
by	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Foot-man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
him	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
divulg	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
his	O
secret	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3000	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
time	O
was	O
prefixt	O
when	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sawed	O
a	O
Bar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
provided	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Derby-Ale	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
pulled	O
off	O
their	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
Ladies	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
placed	O
Clay	O
upon	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
toucht	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
meeting	O
at	O
the	O
Goat-Tavern	O
by	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
where	O
Wagstaffe	O
,	O
Hodges	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Hare	O
were	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
too	O
many	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
trusty	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
never	O
betray	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
another	O
Appointment	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
where	O
Hare	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
Wagstaff	O
,	O
and	O
Hodges	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Turnley	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
Morris	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
Butler	O
would	O
giv'em	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
no	O
further	O
when	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Foot	O
man	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
up	O
when	O
hewent	O
to	O
Bed	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
down	O
when	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Morris	O
,	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
Turnley	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Alamode-hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Pendants	O
,	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Revel	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Ribbon	O
with	O
a	O
Cherry-colour	O
'd	O
Edging	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Limon-colour	O
'd	O
and	O
white	O
Ribon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Goodacre	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Goods	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
Fringe	O
,	O
and	O
gold	O
Spangle'd-lace	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
for	O
28	O
s.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shew-glass	O
Case	O
,	O
9	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Bottles	O
,	O
4	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
His	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Ballard	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Perruque	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
alleging	O
their	O
Innocence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Intention	O
proved	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
Bunhil-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
:	O
It	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Tisard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
alleging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
TRIALS	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
Charles	O
Alexander	O
,	O
Ambrose	O
Adams	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Ellis	O
,	O
Peter	O
Flower	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
Jones	O
,	O
Richard	O
Morru	O
,	O
Christian	O
Russel	O
,	O
William	O
Tite	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	O
Turnley	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheek	O
8	O
.	O
Edward	O
Ayres	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hubart	O
,	O
William	O
Hollingsby	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Man	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Frances	O
Spencer	O
,	O
and	O
Ellinor	O
Walker	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
16	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Atkins	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Belcher	O
,	O
James	O
Blackwel	O
,	O
Ann	O
Bromely	O
,	O
Mary	O
Dickson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
,	O
Catherine	O
Hetherington	O
,	O
Mathia	O
Lines	O
,	O
John	O
Laddin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Parr	O
,	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Sallitay	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Sealey	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
Into	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
at	O
Land	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
Edward	O
Ayres	O
.	O
For	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Hollingsby	O
.	O
WHeras	O
some	O
Persons	O
have	O
hitherto	O
assumed	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
imposing	O
upon	O
the	O
World	O
with	O
Sham-papers	O
,	O
conconcerning	O
the	O
Dying	O
Criminals	O
:	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
only	O
true	O
Accounts	O
that	O
is	O
given	O
of	O
them	O
every	O
Sessions	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
comes	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
their	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
attested	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
printed	O
for	O
Elizabeth	O
Mallet	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Title	O
of	O
which	O
Account	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
false	O
ones	O
)	O
shall	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
constantly	O
begin	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
ORDINARY	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
his	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
THE	O
New	O
State	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
true	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
Transactions	O
and	O
Learning	O
,	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
every	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Morning	O
;	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Mallet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Books	O
Printed	O
in	O
Europe	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
constantly	O
expected	O
in	O
that	O
Paper	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
encouragement	O
of	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
when	O
ever	O
they	O
publish	O
a	O
new	O
Book	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
Advertis	O
'd	O
grain	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
please	O
to	O
send	O
in	O
their	O
Advertisements	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Mailer	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
J.	O
Mathews	O
in	O
Pilkington	O
Court	O
in	O
Little	O
Brittain	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Rates	O
.	O
THE	O
Mouse-grown	O
a	O
Rat	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Story	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
Mouse	O
newly	O
Transpor	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Discourse	O
betwixt	O
Bars	O
,	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Brittish	O
Muse	O
,	O
or	O
Tyranny	O
expos	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
all	O
Poems	O
and	O
Elegies	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
Each	O
price	O
6	O
d.	O
HARMAN	O
STRODTMAN	O
's	O
last	O
Legacy	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
:	O
Containing	O
most	O
excellent	O
Meditations	O
and	O
Prayers	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Exercise	O
both	O
of	O
Devont	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Sinners	O
;	O
are	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
design	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
perusal	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Persons	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
THE	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Groans	O
or	O
a	O
short	O
,	O
but	O
faithful	O
Relation	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Abuses	O
and	O
Oppressions	O
our	O
English	O
Seamen	O
lay	O
under	O
during	O
the	O
late	O
War	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
them	O
ever	O
before	O
made	O
publick	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
Proposals	O
for	O
increasing	O
their	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
incouraging	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
our	O
Fleet	O
may	O
be	O
always	O
well	O
Man	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Readiness	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Seamen	O
well	O
used	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Country	O
may	O
be	O
well	O
Served	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
a	O
Sailor	O
.	O
Humbly	O
Recommended	O
to	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
both	O
Houses	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
sold	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Mallet	O
,	O
near	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms-Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
THE	O
Dying	O
Man	O
's	O
Asistant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
SHORT	O
INSTRUCTIONS	O
how	O
to	O
prepare	O
Sick	O
Perons	O
for	O
Death	O
:	O
Which	O
are	O
no	O
less	O
worthy	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
all	O
good	O
Christians	O
in	O
time	O
of	O
Health	O
;	O
as	O
shewing	O
the	O
Importance	O
of	O
an	O
early	O
Preparation	O
for	O
their	O
Latter-End	O
.	O
Set	O
forth	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
and	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honouraable	O
the	O
late	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
by	O
Paul	O
Lorrain	O
,	O
Ordinary	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Lawrence-at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Bible	O
in	O
large	O
Folio	O
for	O
Churches	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Thousand	O
References	O
more	O
than	O
Dr.	O
Scatergood	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Years	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
Christ	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Primate	O
Usher	O
's	O
Annals	O
,	O
Revised	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Worcester	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chronological	O
Table	O
and	O
Index	O
:	O
Also	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
Scripture	O
Measures	O
,	O
Weights	O
and	O
Coins	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Appendix	O
containing	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
Calculating	O
its	O
Measures	O
of	O
Surface	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Peterborough	O
.	O
Published	O
at	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing-Office	O
in	O
Black-friars	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
ready	O
Bound	O
of	O
Rob	O
.	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate-street	O
.	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
now	O
living	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
within	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
large	O
and	O
small	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
Bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
,	O
extraordinary	O
or	O
plain	O
,	O
or	O
unbound	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
Statuces	O
at	O
large	O
and	O
Articles	O
and	O
Canons	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
all	O
Books	O
nearly	O
Bound	O
,	O
at	O
Reasonable	O
Rates	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
WElmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
famous	O
for	O
Relieving	O
and	O
Curing	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
hath	O
Practised	O
almost	O
40	O
Years	O
,	O
still	O
is	O
veth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
ready	O
upon	O
any	O
occasion	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
such	O
at	O
apply	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
cloth	O
challenge	O
the	O
whole	O
World	O
in	O
perform	O
the	O
like	O
Cures	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
in	O
Deafness	O
.	O
Beware	O
of	O
some	O
who	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
,	O
as	O
white	O
at	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Curs	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Gargarism	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
at	O
J.	O
Mayoes	O
's	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
a	O
Stationer	O
.	O
BLilburn	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
now	O
Lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
,	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
.	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
selleth	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
near	O
20	O
Years	O
)	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
,	O
Pimple	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitae	O
,	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Etsences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
all	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Female	O
Sex	O
,	O
likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Anti	O
scorbutick	O
Pills	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scabe	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
Titters	O
,	O
Itch	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
where	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Aches	O
,	O
and	O
Strains	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
Past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
who	O
now	O
doth	O
understand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effect-answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
nor	O
tice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s	O
.	O
