TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
House	O
ye	O
23	O
d	O
May	O
The	O
Letter	O
which	O
you	O
wrote	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
till	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
London	B-place
last	O
Wedy	O
you	O
will	O
my	O
dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
easily	O
imagine	O
my	O
Mind	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
agitated	O
upon	O
the	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
that	O
Bleſsed	O
Angel	O
five	O
Weeks	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
fullest	O
Bloom	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
fulfill	O
yr̅	O
Comiſsion	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
lives	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
seize	O
the	O
first	O
oportunity	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
&	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
--	O
This	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
wrote	O
yesterdy	O
since	O
wc̅h	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
23	O
d	O
May	O
1783	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
the	O
melancholy	O
account	O
you	O
had	O
red	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
,	O
believe	O
me	O
sincere	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
exceedingly	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
true	O
a	O
Friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Loſs	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
still	O
hope	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
your	O
alarm	O
has	O
been	O
great	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
witneſs	O
of	O
her	O
Recovery	O
,	O
believe	O
these	O
wishes	O
flow	O
from	O
real	O
feeling	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
R	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northampton	B-place
