TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Juliana	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
day	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
Ld	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
had	O
some	O
good	O
Sleep	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
thō	O
deeply	O
afflicted	O
.	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
Coming	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
I	O
propose	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
by	O
Ten	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
C.F	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wednesday	O
Night	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
