TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
when	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Heritable	O
Bond	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
your	O
letter	O
;	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
Assignment	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Trust	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
apply	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
when	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
proper	O
Instructions	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
I	O
propose	O
it	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
my	O
Friend	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Cunynghame	I-pers
.	O
If	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
send	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
his	O
Banker	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Receipt	O
upon	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Stamp	O
signed	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
authority	O
sufficient	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
The	B-pers
Revd	I-pers
.	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
Sterlg	O
.	O
due	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
upon	O
an	O
Heritable	O
Bond	O
of	O
Provision	O
granted	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Father	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Twenty	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
being	O
half	O
a	O
years	O
Interest	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
due	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
1786	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
Demands	O
whatever	O
--	O
.	O
We	O
receiv	O
'd	O
yesterday	O
the	O
afflicting	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
poor	O
Lord	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
at	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
Winchester	B-place
&	O
died	O
in	O
six	O
hours	O
after	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
particulars	O
I	O
have	O
yet	O
heard	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
are	O
in	O
the	O
utmost	O
affliction	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
we	O
hear	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
by	O
chance	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
lately	O
Adieu	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
remain	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
May	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
.	O
P.	O
S	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
order	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
his	O
Banker	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
or	O
certainly	O
the	O
next	O
