TOKEN	NE
Worcester	B-place
7	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1782	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
your	O
departure	O
from	O
this	O
Life	O
announced	O
in	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
venture	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
doing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
this	O
enquiry	O
in	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Jilt	O
Fortune	O
(	O
who	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
has	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Trip	O
to	O
London	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
All	O
my	O
hopes	O
in	O
the	O
Lottery	O
were	O
blasted	O
;	O
the	O
Tickets	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
drawn	O
Blanks	O
.	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
rich	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Birthday	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
collected	O
£100	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
spent	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
My	O
attempts	O
in	O
Recruiting	O
have	O
not	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Succeſs	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
Should	O
this	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
be	O
removed	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
Chelmsford	B-place
will	O
then	O
be	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
should	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
.	O
Worcester	B-place
proves	O
a	O
very	O
agreable	O
Winter	O
Quarter	O
.	O
Many	O
of	O
the	O
Prebendary	O
's	O
are	O
now	O
arrived	O
,	O
who	O
give	O
good	O
Dinners	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
civil	O
as	O
to	O
require	O
my	O
aſsistance	O
at	O
several	O
of	O
their	O
Feeds	O
.	O
In	O
summer	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
collect	O
at	O
Malvern	B-place
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Air	O
&	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
you	O
mention	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Wor——shire	B-place
or	O
not	O
?	O
The	O
view	O
into	O
Herefordshire	B-place
from	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Malvern	B-place
Hill	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
pleasing	O
prospects	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
seen	O
The	O
Ground	O
is	O
prettily	O
broke	O
into	O
little	O
Hills	O
covered	O
with	O
Apple	O
Trees	O
.	O
In	O
spring	O
the	O
beauty	O
&	O
richneſs	O
of	O
the	O
bloſsoms	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
described	O
.	O
Wor——shire	B-place
is	O
well	O
wooded	O
and	O
watered	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
accustomed	O
to	O
Hertfordshire	B-place
,	O
looks	O
rather	O
bare	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
after	O
Natural	O
Curiosities	O
for	O
You	O
but	O
without	O
Succeſs	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Genius	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintances	O
here	O
to	O
make	O
those	O
collections	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
You	O
.	O
Politics	O
have	O
lately	O
become	O
the	O
darling	O
topic	O
of	O
conversation	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
easily	O
beleive	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
particularly	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Cornwallis	I-pers
's	O
misfortunes	O
.	O
The	O
Newspapers	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
mentioned	O
his	O
arrival	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
Our	O
Politicians	O
are	O
impatient	O
to	O
hear	O
his	O
opinion	O
of	O
American	O
Affairs	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
very	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
