TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
,	O
it	O
rains	O
so	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
as	O
company	O
dines	O
here	O
I	O
must	O
dreſs	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
you	O
soon	O
in	O
Town	O
or	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
,	O
for	O
I	O
intend	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
next	O
week	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Binning	I-pers
s	O
&	O
shall	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
thence	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
affectionatly	O
--	O
Honble	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
June	O
1788	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
