TOKEN	NE
4	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
,	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1802	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
forwarded	O
your	O
enormous	O
Packet	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
,	O
this	O
forenoon	O
,	O
without	O
reading	O
one	O
single	O
Syllable	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
poſseſsing	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
Curiosity	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
a	O
certain	O
Sex	O
is	O
so	O
renowned	O
,	O
nor	O
feeling	O
any	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Melancholy	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
formerly	O
heard	O
from	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Halifax	I-pers
.	O
Your	O
accusation	O
against	O
Me	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
unjust	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
You	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
am	O
so	O
kept	O
myself	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
received	O
me	O
most	O
graciously	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
enlighten	O
their	O
Understandings	O
,	O
and	O
They	O
promised	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
early	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
who	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
might	O
comprehend	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Busineſs	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
for	O
the	O
Home	O
Department	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
is	O
arrived	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Interview	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
settle	O
my	O
affair	O
,	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
,	O
thirty	O
three	O
Minutes	O
past	O
Nine	O
O'Clock	O
exactly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
written	O
or	O
verbal	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
,	O
from	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Great	O
Men	O
,	O
is	O
an	O
Invitation	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
,	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
instant	O
,	O
at	O
Six	O
O'Clock	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
1784	O
,	O
at	O
Eight	O
O'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
resigned	O
my	O
Liberty	O
,	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
George	O
Street	O
,	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
nothing	O
more	O
calamitous	O
may	O
happen	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Anniversary	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
's	O
.	O
As	O
proof	O
of	O
your	O
consistency	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
compare	O
the	O
enclosed	O
scraps	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
Letter	O
.	O
You	O
first	O
bid	O
me	O
read	O
Mrs.	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
threaten	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
a	O
Wafer	O
,	O
&	O
spit	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
You	O
manage	O
at	O
Buzzard	O
Hall	O
,	O
to	O
read	O
sealed	O
up	O
Letters	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
known	O
to	O
Yourself	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
above	O
my	O
capacity	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Girl	O
will	O
remain	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
All	O
chance	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
of	O
our	O
Meeting	O
is	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
leave	O
London	B-place
before	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
,	O
but	O
probably	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
unleſs	O
I	O
am	O
packed	O
off	O
by	O
Royal	O
Command	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
time	O
for	O
Visiting	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
civil	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Yourself	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
to	O
spare	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
remain	O
ever	O
Your	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Sunday	O
,	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
this	O
letter	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
forenoon	O
.	O
My	O
business	O
is	O
settled	O
with	O
Ministers	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
provide	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leven	I-pers
with	O
an	O
Equivalent	O
on	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Establishment	O
.	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Ratification	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
wanted	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
refused	O
--	O
London	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
April	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
