TOKEN	NE
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
from	O
Northampton	B-place
;	O
and	O
this	O
morning	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
desire	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
one	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
to	O
your	O
Bankers	O
Meſsrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
&	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
called	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
paid	O
her	O
Twenty	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
for	O
both	O
which	O
Sums	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
your	O
Receipts	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
May	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
