TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
July	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
——	I-pers
,	O
My	O
last	O
Letter	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
of	O
our	O
Diſsappointment	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
having	O
left	O
us	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
arrived	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
much	O
more	O
distreſsing	O
Event	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
last	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
shock't	O
with	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
dated	O
Vigo	B-place
in	O
Spain	B-place
June	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
She	O
sail	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Mercury	O
Packet	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
they	O
were	O
chased	O
for	O
12	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
taken	O
by	O
an	O
American	O
Privateer	O
the	O
horror	O
of	O
finding	O
what	O
hands	O
they	O
wase	O
fallen	O
into	O
was	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
they	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
humane	O
Treatment	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
landed	O
them	O
at	O
Vigo	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
writes	O
,	O
having	O
by	O
great	O
good	O
fortune	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
a	O
Letter	O
hither	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
and	O
herself	O
are	O
all	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
House	O
like	O
a	O
Barn	O
,	O
but	O
thankful	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
escaped	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
Paſs-ports	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
determine	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Oporto	B-place
which	O
is	O
but	O
two	O
Days	O
Journey	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
well	O
off	O
,	O
both	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
itself	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
of	O
Oporto	B-place
,	O
who	O
fortunately	O
we	O
had	O
made	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Credit	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
every	O
Aſsistance	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
till	O
they	O
can	O
determine	O
what	O
farther	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
This	O
Letter	O
we	O
sent	O
there	O
by	O
Expreſs	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Distance	O
is	O
very	O
great	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
finding	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
hope	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
they	O
can	O
have	O
taken	O
any	O
steps	O
yet	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
have	O
determin	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
.	O
we	O
also	O
sent	O
another	O
Expreſs	O
to	O
Lisbon	B-place
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
bring	O
him	O
here	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
propose	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Oporto	B-place
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
back	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
God	O
this	O
Project	O
will	O
succeed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
and	O
unhappy	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
her	O
again	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
that	O
comfort	O
this	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
country	O
for	O
Travelling	O
in	O
,	O
no	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
change	O
of	O
Horses	O
or	O
Mules	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
pair	O
goes	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
an	O
open	O
chaise	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
sent	O
ōn	O
purpose	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
none	O
at	O
Oporto	B-place
,	O
and	O
bett	O
between	O
Vigo	B-place
and	O
Oporto	B-place
none	O
can	O
go	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
tillers	O
.	O
indeed	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
am	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
and	O
vext	O
beyond	O
measure	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
feel	O
happy	O
and	O
thankful	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
carried	O
to	O
America	B-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
pleas	O
'd	O
myself	O
with	O
thinking	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
arriv	O
'd	O
in	O
England	B-place
long	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
&	O
happineſs	O
of	O
Seeing	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
and	O
they	O
dear	O
Royal	O
Children	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
charged	O
with	O
my	O
most	O
Dutiful	O
Thanks	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
for	O
all	O
their	O
goodneſs	O
&	O
indulgence	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
long	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
expreſsing	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
particular	O
Manner	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
with	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
pray	O
my	O
Dear	O
mention	O
this	O
with	O
my	O
humble	O
Duty	O
.	O
the	O
hurry	O
I	O
now	O
write	O
in	O
does	O
not	O
permit	O
of	O
my	O
having	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
writing	O
my	O
Letters	O
to	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
was	O
also	O
to	O
have	O
represented	O
my	O
situation	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
requested	O
their	O
Leave	O
to	O
prolong	O
my	O
stay	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
leave	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
easy	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
he	O
continues	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
so	O
much	O
hopes	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
set	O
at	O
Liberty	O
Dr.	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
his	O
Physician	O
who	O
was	O
Originally	O
going	O
to	O
England	B-place
on	O
his	O
own	O
private	O
Affairs	O
And	O
whose	O
situation	O
then	O
,	O
calls	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
America	B-place
,	O
Ld-	B-pers
Wina	I-pers
.	I-pers
thought	O
,	O
whatever	O
satisfaction	O
he	O
or	O
I	O
might	O
derive	O
from	O
keeping	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fair	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
poſsible	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
flatter	O
myself	O
from	O
what	O
Dr.	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
says	O
,	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Winchelsea	I-pers
is	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
free	O
from	O
the	O
illneſs	O
itself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
it	O
still	O
remain	O
and	O
will	O
sometime	O
,	O
which	O
shew	O
themselves	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
swelling	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
&	O
weakneſs	O
in	O
walking	O
,	O
or	O
standing	O
,	O
attended	O
with	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
joints	O
,	O
some	O
fix't	O
and	O
some	O
flying	O
ones	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
says	O
,	O
with	O
Care	O
,	O
Gentle	O
Exercise	O
,	O
&	O
great	O
attention	O
to	O
Diet	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
pursuing	O
of	O
these	O
waters	O
,	O
&	O
some	O
physical	O
Method	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
greatest	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
perfectly	O
recover	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
(	O
tho	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
oppose	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
rather	O
distreſsful	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
really	O
knows	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
his	O
Case	O
,	O
And	O
as	O
(	O
Under	O
God	O
)	O
we	O
must	O
impute	O
his	O
Recovery	O
to	O
his	O
Skill	O
and	O
Care	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
both	O
anxious	O
on	O
every	O
Account	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
recovery	O
advance	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
admit	O
of	O
my	O
Return	O
,	O
being	O
fully	O
and	O
gratefully	O
sensible	O
of	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
great	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
indulgence	O
about	O
my	O
Absence	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
prolong	O
'd	O
a	O
Moment	O
beyond	O
what	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
my	O
dear	O
Miss	B-pers
——	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
with	O
safety	O
,	O
now	O
the	O
Seas	O
are	O
so	O
infested	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
A	O
Land	O
Journey	O
would	O
ruin	O
my	O
finances	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
difficulties	O
of	O
travelling	O
thro	O
Spain	B-place
&	O
Portugal	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
tedious	O
time	O
it	O
would	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Packet	O
I	O
certainly	O
now	O
can	O
never	O
Venture	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Neutral	O
Ship	O
must	O
be	O
our	O
resource	O
,	O
whenever	O
the	O
happy	O
time	O
comes	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
my	O
son	O
so	O
restor	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
with	O
ease	O
&	O
Hope	O
.	O
His	O
paſsing	O
the	O
Winter	O
abroad	O
seems	O
so	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
an	O
Idea	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
England	B-place
himself	O
.	O
I	O
Hope	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
&	O
continued	O
good	O
Accounts	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
,	O
And	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
h	O
er	O
e	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
more	O
about	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
will	O
at	O
best	O
have	O
a	O
long	O
&	O
very	O
Uncomfortable	O
Journey	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
come	O
hither	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
Most	O
Affly	O
..	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
