TOKEN	NE
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
3	O
d	O
of	O
Janr	O
.	O
1775	O
Madam	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
m	O
y	O
Father	O
died	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
severe	O
&	O
tedious	O
Illneſs	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
suffered	O
much	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
easily	O
judge	O
of	O
our	O
affliction	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
so	O
affectionate	O
a	O
Parent	O
,	O
may	O
the	O
Almighty	O
God	O
support	O
us	O
on	O
this	O
severe	O
tri	O
al	O
My	O
Sisters	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
yourself	O
&	O
Family	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
Affecate	O
.	O
Cousin	O
&	O
humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frans	B-pers
:	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
