TOKEN	NE
2	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
--	O
1789	O
--	O
This	O
day	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
prognosticated	O
--	O
Ingles	B-pers
&	O
I	O
rode	O
to	O
old	B-place
Down	I-place
14	O
Miles	O
from	O
hence	O
on	O
the	O
Exeter	B-place
Road	O
where	O
we	O
stopt	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
on	O
to	O
Stone	B-place
easton	I-place
the	O
seat	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Member	O
for	O
this	O
County	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hipsley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
married	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
's	O
sister	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
us	O
an	O
Invitation	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
doubts	O
about	O
this	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
appetites	O
not	O
brooking	O
any	O
delay	O
,	O
we	O
ransacked	O
the	O
Larder	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
for	O
Cold	O
Meat	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
were	O
agreeably	O
amusing	O
ourselves	O
when	O
the	O
servant	O
arrived	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
all	O
reasonable	O
people	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
,	O
yet	O
an	O
order	O
was	O
immediately	O
given	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Cavalry	O
in	O
motion	O
&	O
to	O
storm	O
the	O
Castle	O
Sword	O
in	O
hand	O
--	O
the	O
gates	O
were	O
opened	O
and	O
we	O
received	O
with	O
great	O
courtesy	O
by	O
the	O
Deputy	O
Governor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hipsley	I-pers
,	O
also	O
by	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
Traveller	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
perfect	O
Goddeſs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
clergyman	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
well-bred	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
manners	O
are	O
very	O
engaging	O
--	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
(	O
member	O
for	O
some	O
place	O
)	O
&	O
his	O
chubfaced	O
wife	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
young	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Cockade	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
--	O
also	O
a	O
country	O
justice	O
arrived	O
soon	O
after	O
us	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
did	O
not	O
make	O
his	O
appearance	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
weighs	O
22	O
Stone	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
seems	O
active	O
,	O
his	O
countenance	O
is	O
sensible	O
&	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
handsome	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
his	O
under	O
Lip	O
which	O
is	O
thick	O
&	O
has	O
in	O
no	O
play	O
in	O
its	O
muscles	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
the	O
dinner	O
and	O
Wines	O
were	O
suitable	O
to	O
his	O
fortune	O
which	O
is	O
16000	O
£	O
a	O
year	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
turned	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
politicks	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
chiefly	O
to	O
justice	O
businiſs	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
is	O
a	O
delightful	O
Subject	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
enquiring	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
rather	O
better	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
this	O
Seat	O
of	O
plenty	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
cheerful	O
ride	O
thrō	O
the	O
pleasantest	O
Country	O
I	O
have	O
hitherto	O
seen	O
--	O
which	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
equally	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
how	O
often	O
did	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
exclaim	O
“	O
Mr.	B-pers
D.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
look	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
;	O
how	O
beautiful	O
that	O
Scenery	O
!	O
”	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
greatly	O
this	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
added	O
to	O
my	O
pleasure	O
--	O
3	O
d	O
/	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Ingles	B-pers
at	O
8	O
--	O
we	O
walked	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
2	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
them	O
&	O
went	O
a	O
shopping	O
with	O
her	O
which	O
(	O
entre	O
nous	O
)	O
She	O
receives	O
greater	O
pleasure	O
from	O
than	O
her	O
Husband	O
wishes	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
with	O
Ingles	B-pers
&	O
took	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
this	O
afternoon	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
s	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
sent	O
Compts-	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
felicity	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
yr-	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
28	O
June	O
--	O
&	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
pump	O
room	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
list	O
of	O
arrivals	O
--	O
the	O
Pump	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
Names	O
were	O
invented	O
merely	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
list	O
of	O
arrivals	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Kinder	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Dickenson	O
,	O
not	O
my	O
sweet	O
Cozn	O
..	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
prejudicial	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
or	O
write	O
or	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
occupied	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
drinkg	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
She	O
soon	O
changed	O
her	O
opinon	O
when	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
book	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
mother	O
wch	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
on	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
revolution	O
in	O
Holland	B-place
--	O
with	O
which	O
She	O
seemed	O
much	O
pleased	O
&	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
--	O
we	O
began	O
--	O
but	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
proceed	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
inceſsant	O
gabbling	O
of	O
a	O
whist	O
party	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
two	O
hours	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
charged	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
1000	O
civil	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
Hair	O
for	O
which	O
She	O
was	O
more	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
than	O
she	O
cd	O
.	O
expreſs	O
--	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
design	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
not	O
that	O
precious	O
relick	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
its	O
reception	O
/	O
4	O
/	O
I	O
bathed	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
morning	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
&	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
engaged	O
in	O
her	O
attendance	O
upon	O
an	O
old	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
anxious	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
constant	O
expectation	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
does	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Lady	O
is	O
dead	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
means	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
amongst	O
her	O
own	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
agreeable	O
freinds	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
principal	O
weakneſs	O
arises	O
from	O
family	O
pride	O
&	O
the	O
recent	O
Nobility	O
of	O
their	O
blood	O
has	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
diminished	O
her	O
self	O
satisfaction	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
exceſsively	O
laughed	O
at	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
by	O
a	O
party	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Merit	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
had	O
thanked	O
her	O
for	O
introducing	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
flattering	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Vanbrugh	B-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
yesterday	O
was	O
the	O
hottest	O
day	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
day	O
again	O
is	O
cloudy	O
&	O
will	O
rain	O
--	O
5	O
/	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	I-pers
last	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
rain	O
that	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
made	O
the	O
air	O
so	O
damp	O
that	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
venture	O
out	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
Chair	O
Hire	O
--	O
The	O
Wetneſs	O
of	O
this	O
morning	O
prevented	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sermon	O
of	O
Tillotson	B-pers
s	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughters	O
The	O
weather	O
cleared	O
up	O
at	O
one	O
&	O
at	O
2	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
their	O
two	O
eldest	O
Daughters	O
&	O
I	O
marched	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Cottage	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
where	O
we	O
dined	O
with	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
--	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
of	O
good	O
fortune	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
here	O
&	O
has	O
taken	O
this	O
place	O
as	O
a	O
home	O
in	O
this	O
neighborhood	O
--	O
he	O
gives	O
Claret	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
for	O
every	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
or	O
without	O
a	O
fortune	O
now	O
can	O
bear	O
nothing	O
but	O
Claret	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Wine	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
drink	O
but	O
that	O
precious	O
Liquor	O
--	O
the	O
more	O
this	O
country	O
is	O
taxed	O
&	O
the	O
more	O
extravagant	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
of	O
this	O
country	O
become	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
an	O
agreeable	O
circumstance	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
pump	O
room	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
who	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
was	O
in	O
town	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
from	O
Exeter	B-place
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
as	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
man	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
higher	O
esteem	O
&	O
he	O
seemed	O
equally	O
pleased	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
means	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
water	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
has	O
wrote	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
lovely	O
sister	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
She	O
bears	O
up	O
under	O
this	O
affliction	O
wonderfully	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
Teignmouth	B-place
till	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
can	O
return	O
&	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
--	O
this	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
he	O
added	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
excuse	O
for	O
S.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
ride	O
his	O
Hobby	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
those	O
frequent	O
journeys	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
lucky	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
could	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
Sister	O
for	O
being	O
convinced	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
poor	O
Soul	O
could	O
live	O
,	O
She	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
miserable	O
Criple	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
--	O
would	O
induce	O
the	O
most	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
to	O
wish	O
for	O
her	O
release	O
--	O
Nina	B-pers
is	O
tolerable	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
supposes	O
that	O
She	O
may	O
be	O
kept	O
nearly	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
--	O
/	O
6	O
/	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
at	O
9	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
whilst	O
I	O
stayed	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
breakfast	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
mine	O
--	O
at	O
2	O
I	O
met	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
Milsom	O
Street	O
,	O
we	O
talked	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
s	O
irresolution	O
in	O
not	O
consulting	O
a	O
Physician	O
--	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
only	O
one	O
small	O
glaſs	O
of	O
water	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
disordered	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
concluded	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
send	O
one	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
Dr.	B-pers
Harington	I-pers
we	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
I	O
called	O
&	O
found	O
them	O
playing	O
at	O
Backgammon	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
in	O
his	O
good	O
humored	O
way	O
--	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
determine	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
throw	O
away	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
or	O
not	O
--	O
I	O
played	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
game	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
whistled	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
bad	O
throw	O
which	O
reduced	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
dilemma	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thing	O
for	O
an	O
Englishman	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
us	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
whistle	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
Occasion	O
in	O
France	B-place
that	O
we	O
shd	O
.	O
undoubtedly	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
this	O
instance	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
aſsertion	O
--	O
L.	B-pers
Eglintown	I-pers
was	O
at	O
play	O
in	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
in	O
a	O
similar	O
situation	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
whistled	O
--	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
tapped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
&	O
walked	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
whither	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
his	O
great	O
astonishment	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
sword	O
drawn	O
&	O
in	O
an	O
attitude	O
for	O
fighting	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
this	O
&	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
insulted	O
him	O
&	O
must	O
fight	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
deemed	O
an	O
insult	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
that	O
in	O
France	B-place
they	O
whistled	O
to	O
Horses	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
gentlemen	O
--	O
luckily	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
not	O
his	O
sword	O
or	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
fallen	O
a	O
victim	O
to	O
French	O
Punctilio	O
,	O
&	O
before	O
he	O
cd	O
.	O
procure	O
one	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
made	O
known	O
&	O
some	O
sensible	O
people	O
explained	O
to	O
the	O
hot	O
Frenchman	O
the	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
's	O
having	O
meant	O
any	O
affront	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
what	O
might	O
have	O
escaped	O
him	O
involuntarily	O
--	O
Sacville	B-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
he	O
certainly	O
should	O
have	O
whistled	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
then	O
in	O
France	B-place
--	O
I	O
beat	O
this	O
good	O
Creature	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
reception	O
&	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
9	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
send	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
lamented	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
two	O
friends	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Rubber	O
at	O
Backgammon	O
which	O
I	O
won	O
&	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
ten	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
overjoyed	O
to	O
find	O
our	O
West	O
Indians	O
returned	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Capn	B-pers
.	I-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
punishments	O
that	O
are	O
inflicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Blacks	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
for	O
capital	O
Crime	O
ye-	O
Convict	O
is	O
always	O
burnt	O
--	O
for	O
a	O
Black	O
man	O
or	O
woman	O
will	O
see	O
their	O
dearest	O
relatives	O
put	O
to	O
death	O
with	O
the	O
greatt	O
.	O
composure	O
&	O
will	O
rather	O
rejoice	O
if	O
they	O
can	O
have	O
the	O
body	O
to	O
bury	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
a	O
Black	O
is	O
buried	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
home	O
&	O
are	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
happy	O
whatever	O
crimes	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
Burning	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
punishment	O
that	O
strikes	O
their	O
minds	O
with	O
any	O
degree	O
of	O
horror	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
who	O
complemented	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
improvement	O
of	O
my	O
looks	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
who	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
for	O
today	O
,	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
--	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
another	O
dose	O
of	O
Castor	O
oil	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
do	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
he	O
thinks	O
it	O
will	O
aſsist	O
the	O
Waters	O
very	O
effectually	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
parades	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
aſsisting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beavoir	I-pers
whose	O
Husband	O
is	O
dead	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
giving	O
orders	O
for	O
the	O
funeral	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
got	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
have	O
them	O
soon	O
--	O
/	O
7	O
/	O
I	O
am	O
lying	O
in	O
today	O
and	O
am	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
expected	O
--	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
great	O
grief	O
&	O
concern	O
which	O
has	O
mightily	O
affected	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
havg	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
Shoes	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
however	O
we	O
can	O
ease	O
my	O
conscience	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
order	O
Morrison	B-pers
,	O
(	O
dear	O
Soul	O
!	O
what	O
pleasing	O
expectations	O
may	O
she	O
not	O
form	O
in	O
her	O
mind	O
from	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
every	O
day	O
reminded	O
of	O
her	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
gratitude	O
)	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
exact	O
measure	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
your	O
shoe	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
remeasured	O
by	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
thread	O
&	O
a	O
knot	O
upon	O
it	O
(	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
knot	O
as	O
She	O
dreams	O
of	O
every	O
night	O
)	O
will	O
ascertain	O
that	O
important	O
point	O
--	O
then	O
a	O
string	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
round	O
the	O
instep	O
will	O
clear	O
that	O
difficulty	O
,	O
&	O
also	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
miles	O
&	O
exact	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
the	O
foot	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
point	O
that	O
covers	O
yr	O
well	O
turned	O
instep	O
will	O
set	O
this	O
matter	O
in	O
so	O
clear	O
a	O
light	O
that	O
any	O
number	O
of	O
Shoes	O
may	O
be	O
produced	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
yr	O
commands	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
best	O
friend	O
--	O
write	O
me	O
another	O
charming	O
Letter	O
&	O
believe	O
that	O
your	O
D	B-pers
is	O
the	O
happiest	O
Husband	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Herschell	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
learn	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
my	O
eyes	O
are	O
sufficiently	O
employed	O
already	O
--	O
Rauzzini	B-pers
is	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbor	O
--	O
but	O
his	O
terms	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
will	O
keep	O
us	O
at	O
a	O
respectable	O
distance	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
throw	O
away	O
upon	O
my	O
voice	O
--	O
once	O
more	O
Adieu	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
most	O
Affly	O
to	O
every	O
Body	O
--	O
&	O
embrace	O
our	O
dear	O
Child	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
perfectly	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
dined/	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
post	O
