TOKEN	NE
Wensday	O
I	O
am	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lonn	B-place
this	O
Morning	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
wait	O
on	O
You	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
ſhou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
seeing	O
You	O
Here	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
hope	O
for	O
(	O
I	O
doubt	O
)	O
but	O
to	O
Morrow	O
I	O
depend	O
on	O
seeing	O
You	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
4	O
o	O
clock	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
tell	O
yr	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
W——	I-pers
who	O
He	O
wou	O
'd	O
find	O
if	O
He	O
were	O
graciously	O
dispos	O
'd	O
towards	O
our	O
petit	O
Couvert	O
Bon	O
Jour	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
1	O
st	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1788	O
