TOKEN	NE
Monday	O
My	O
dear	O
Sister	O
/	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
pleasing	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
quieted	O
my	O
conscience	O
&	O
allow	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
without	O
remorse	O
of	O
the	O
days	O
that	O
paſsed	O
by	O
without	O
one	O
single	O
line	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
me	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
this	O
morning	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
My	O
B	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
you	O
meant	O
to	O
spend	O
another	O
week	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
allow	O
this	O
evening	O
to	O
escape	O
me	O
without	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
for	O
their	O
very	O
charming	O
and	O
interesting	O
notes	O
in	O
your	O
letter	O
.	O
--	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
My	O
Father	O
was	O
extremely	O
flatterd	O
,	O
and	O
few	O
people	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
Birch	B-place
that	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
honord	O
with	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
those	O
agreeable	O
testimonies	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
his	O
darling	O
granddaughter	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
also	O
give	O
my	O
Respects	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
aſsure	O
her	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
honor	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
obliging	O
remembrance	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
write	O
this	O
letter	O
very	O
expeditiously	O
for	O
my	O
F	O
has	O
been	O
giving	O
so	O
many	O
prudent	O
reasons	O
why	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
written	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
even	O
a	O
melancholy	O
rainy	O
morning	O
with	O
all	O
it	O
's	O
attendant	O
horrors	O
coud	O
have	O
no	O
effect	O
to	O
prevail	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
respite	O
me	O
but	O
for	O
one	O
single	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
woud	O
give	O
me	O
credit	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
partly	O
for	O
your	O
sake	O
I	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
postpone	O
writing	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
an	O
unaccountable	O
effect	O
upon	O
my	O
variable	O
mind	O
&	O
you	O
could	O
expect	O
neither	O
energy	O
nor	O
entertainment	O
were	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
clouds	O
&	O
hear	O
the	O
wind	O
that	O
that	O
my	O
miserable	O
senses	O
are	O
aſsaild	O
with	O
.	O
Truly	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
england	O
hang	O
&	O
drown	O
themselves	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
canal	O
is	O
empty	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
insurmountable	O
objection	O
to	O
being	O
suspended	O
,	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
consequence	O
woud	O
be	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
gay	O
while	O
the	O
sun	O
shone	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
&	O
have	O
seized	O
every	O
paſsing	O
minute	O
that	O
coud	O
bestow	O
the	O
least	O
delight	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
I	O
think	O
I	O
perform	O
the	O
evil	O
of	O
morning	O
visiting	O
with	O
a	O
dispatch	O
worthy	O
of	O
myself	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Place	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
returned	O
with	O
us	O
:	O
Yesterday	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Highgrove	B-place
to	O
dine	O
but	O
unfortunately	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
not	O
favourable	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
Bachelors	O
wishes	O
so	O
there	O
perhaps	O
was	O
a	O
conquest	O
lost	O
--	O
To	O
day	O
Thursday	O
we	O
dine	O
by	O
an	O
invitation	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
standing	O
at	O
Townsend	B-place
how	O
we	O
shall	O
get	O
there	O
remains	O
for	O
time	O
to	O
unfold	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
dry	O
thread	O
left	O
on	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
fully	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
expect	O
,	O
to	O
morrow	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
am	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
party	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
If	O
nothing	O
unforseed	O
prevents	O
all	O
this	O
taking	O
place	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
I	O
entering	O
into	O
what	O
I	O
shoud	O
once	O
have	O
calld	O
a	O
diſsipated	O
life	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
is	O
very	O
indifferent	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
if	O
their	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
alteration	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
in	O
tolerable	O
spirits	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
heartbroken	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
soon	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
medical	O
men	O
attending	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
enough	O
to	O
wear	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
shadow	O
to	O
see	O
those	O
harbingers	O
of	O
death	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
without	O
intermiſsion	O
.	O
I	O
shan	O
t	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
nerves	O
being	O
uneaqual	O
to	O
the	O
fatigue	O
&	O
anxiety	O
she	O
must	O
of	O
course	O
undergo	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
&	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
you	O
they	O
are	O
arrived	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
she	O
mentions	O
with	O
pleasure	O
Sir	B-pers
W	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
great	O
attentions	O
to	O
them	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
alarm	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
babies	O
being	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
Pox	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
that	O
hot	O
Climate	O
is	O
very	O
alarming	O
at	O
this	O
season	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
--	O
John	B-pers
Mellor	I-pers
s	O
son	O
at	O
Mhy	B-place
fold	I-place
has	O
got	O
the	O
Measles	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
today	O
&	O
find	O
he	O
is	O
doing	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
this	O
disease	O
prevails	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
&	O
indeed	O
in	O
so	O
populous	O
a	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
to	O
escape	O
infectious	O
diseases	O
among	O
children	O
.	O
My	O
F	O
desires	O
Louisa	B-pers
may	O
have	O
some	O
medicine	O
before	O
she	O
comes	O
down	O
to	O
purify	O
her	O
blood	O
before	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
young	O
Lady	O
still	O
continues	O
to	O
deserve	O
so	O
well	O
the	O
approbation	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
interested	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
hear	O
her	O
praised	O
is	O
a	O
cordial	O
to	O
ones	O
spirits	O
&	O
makes	O
us	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
her	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Patty	I-pers
has	O
produced	O
two	O
kittens	O
&	O
had	O
so	O
artfully	O
conceald	O
them	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
trace	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
little	O
family	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
plaintive	O
&	O
very	O
hungry	O
.	O
Parker	B-pers
enjoys	O
good	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
since	O
corn	O
became	O
so	O
scarce	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
mad	O
an	O
order	O
that	O
the	O
dogs	O
shall	O
not	O
live	O
so	O
luxuriously	O
as	O
usual	O
he	O
has	O
found	O
the	O
benefits	O
of	O
this	O
regulation	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
lively	O
&	O
youthful	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
Thrush	O
in	O
Birch	O
Garden	O
that	O
will	O
vie	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Nightingales	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
ears	O
feasted	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
The	O
Barberries	O
lament	O
my	O
Nieces	O
absence	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
find	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
delay	O
coming	O
to	O
perfection	O
before	O
her	O
arrival	O
to	O
taste	O
their	O
sweetneſs	O
The	O
gooseberrys	O
&	O
currants	O
tho	O
'	O
vulgar	O
fruits	O
,	O
bear	O
a	O
very	O
promising	O
appearance	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
kinds	O
the	O
inexorable	O
winds	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
have	O
prevented	O
us	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
our	O
power	O
to	O
boast	O
of	O
either	O
quantity	O
or	O
delicacy	O
of	O
taste	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Place	I-pers
is	O
besieging	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
loquacity	O
;	O
she	O
sings	O
,	O
she	O
talks	O
,	O
&	O
laughs	O
so	O
intolerably	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
arrange	O
one	O
's	O
thought	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
therefore	O
conclude	O
in	O
haste	O
and	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
intense	O
affection	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
her	O
we	O
shall	O
rejoice	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
has	O
contri	O
ved	O
to	O
tumble	O
of	O
a	O
haymow	O
&	O
has	O
hurt	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
him	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Thilles	I-pers
but	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
nother	O
person	O
.	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
better	O
today	O
--	O
I	O
woud	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
some	O
hi	O
gh	O
mountain	O
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
before	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
reconcile	O
your	O
eye	O
to	O
Birch	B-place
after	O
having	O
dwelt	O
so	O
long	O
on	O
the	O
luxurious	O
beauties	O
of	O
Hampton	B-place
&	O
Pheasant	O
Grove	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
few	O
charms	O
to	O
boast	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
lament	O
daily	O
the	O
ravages	O
the	O
severity	O
of	O
last	O
winter	O
made	O
among	O
my	O
plants	O
.	O
My	O
Raspberry	O
trees	O
look	O
very	O
sickly	O
indeed	O
&	O
poor	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Garden	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
grandpapa	O
s	O
good	O
wishes	O
is	O
rather	O
in	O
a	O
forlorn	O
state	O
.	O
I	O
gr	O
udge	O
every	O
rose	O
that	O
appears	O
&	O
had	O
I	O
the	O
power	O
woud	O
persuade	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
look	O
as	O
agreeable	O
as	O
poſsible	O
but	O
as	O
persuasion	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
forte	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
accept	O
my	O
good	O
intentions	O
instead	O
of	O
actual	O
service	O
--	O
Milly	B-pers
is	O
here	O
still	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
peremptory	O
indeed	O
to	O
convince	O
her	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
us	O
--	O
Poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
has	O
again	O
been	O
unfortunate	O
.	O
My	O
F	O
who	O
is	O
Master	O
of	O
that	O
subject	O
recommends	O
strongly	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
bathe	O
in	O
Rosew	O
.	O
in	O
short	O
he	O
agrees	O
with	O
her	O
medical	O
advisers	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
scarcely	O
anything	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
Potter	I-pers
I	O
hear	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
&	O
I	O
saw	O
the	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
's	I-pers
one	O
day	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
invitation	O
--	O
flour	O
is	O
£9:10:0	O
a	O
load	O
but	O
trade	O
goes	O
delightfully	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
poor	O
are	O
all	O
imployed	O
&	O
busy	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
mischief	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
to	O
London	B-place
at	O
a	O
moments	O
notice	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
fleet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
eating	O
bread	O
at	O
dinner	O
&	O
supper	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
pastry	O
or	O
puddings	O
in	O
which	O
flour	O
enters	O
the	O
composition	O
.	O
if	O
every	O
family	O
woud	O
relinquish	O
their	O
superfluities	O
plenty	O
woud	O
soon	O
return	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
The	O
fear	O
of	O
famine	O
never	O
presented	O
itself	O
to	O
my	O
Imagination	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
active	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
what	O
woud	O
become	O
of	O
us	O
if	O
the	O
people	O
have	O
more	O
to	O
view	O
?	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
harvest	O
has	O
is	O
in	O
so	O
forward	O
a	O
state	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
real	O
ground	O
for	O
that	O
fear	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
provisions	O
are	O
more	O
plentiful	O
with	O
us	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
so	O
do	O
not	O
fear	O
being	O
quite	O
famishd	O
amongst	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
garden	O
is	O
very	O
productive	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
shall	O
have	O
Barley	O
Soup	O
in	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
times	O
I	O
really	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
dreſs	O
for	O
this	O
adventurous	O
expedition	O
of	O
ours	O
it	O
still	O
rains	O
&	O
is	O
gloomy	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
sister	O
--	O
Love	O
to	O
my	O
B	O
.	O
--	O
Kiss	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
me	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
cold	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
to	O
warm	O
myself	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
1795	O
June	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
Pheasant	O
Grove	O
Chislehurst	B-place
Kent	B-place
