TOKEN	NE
Babel	B-place
--	O
1781	O
--	O
8	O
th	O
August	O
1781	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
&	O
Your	O
two	O
dear	O
letters	O
of	O
July	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
&	O
28	O
th	O
remain	O
unanswer	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
good	O
reasons	O
to	O
give	O
for	O
my	O
silence	O
--	O
the	O
Illneſs	O
of	O
Elise	B-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
obliges	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
constant	O
attendance	O
--	O
Journeys	O
to	O
Leuctra	B-place
,	O
&	O
Accapulco	B-place
--	O
thinking	O
feeling	O
quite	O
exhausted	O
wth-	O
wth-	O
fatigue	O
at	O
night	O
(	O
otherwise	O
I	O
might	O
sometimes	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
ye	O
.	O
busineſs	O
of	O
ye	O
..	O
day	O
does	O
not	O
close	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
&	O
begins	O
at	O
6	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
get	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
12	O
for	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
s	O
room	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
I	O
waited	O
likewise	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
for	O
You	O
,	O
where	O
Mercury	B-pers
's	O
day	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
;	O
&	O
after	O
every	O
enquiry	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
inform	O
You	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
kept	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
absent	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Synod	O
held	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
of	O
course	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
invited	O
to	O
the	O
Fête	O
on	O
P.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
day	O
will	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
conduct	O
of	O
Helen	B-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
is	O
become	O
the	O
common	O
topic	O
of	O
conversation	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
particulars	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
greatly	O
rejoice	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
&	O
not	O
of	O
their	O
parties	O
to	O
Babel	B-place
--	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
miſs	O
'd	O
one	O
afternoon	O
coming	O
over	O
--	O
Helen	B-pers
is	O
highly	O
blam	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
though	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
judge	O
of	O
her	O
actions	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
her	O
both	O
imprudent	O
&	O
weak	O
.	O
The	O
Germans	O
are	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
England	B-place
w	O
h	O
ether	O
she	O
deserves	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
character	O
is	O
ruined	O
--	O
in	O
this	O
family	O
her	O
name	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
mention	O
'd	O
since	O
their	O
abrupt	O
departure	O
.	O
Ah	O
!	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
Friend	O
what	O
profit	O
&	O
instruction	O
one	O
gains	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
has	O
any	O
turn	O
for	O
reflection	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
school	O
as	O
this	O
--	O
&	O
what	O
comfort	O
to	O
poſseſs	O
a	O
clear	O
conscience	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
presumptuously	O
however	O
imagine	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
perfect	O
than	O
others	O
&	O
therefore	O
leſs	O
liable	O
to	O
err	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
too	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
weakneſs	O
&	O
imperfection	O
of	O
human	O
Nature	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
constantly	O
implore	O
the	O
protection	O
of	O
our	O
almighty	O
Father	O
,	O
(	O
&	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
)	O
friend	O
&	O
protector	O
,	O
to	O
guard	O
my	O
erring	O
Soul	O
.	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
some	O
sweet	O
lines	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
Poems	O
?	O
“	O
If	O
by	O
the	O
days	O
illusive	O
Scenes	O
misled	O
,	O
“	O
My	O
Erring	O
Soul	O
from	O
Virtues	O
path	O
has	O
stray	O
'd	O
:	O
“	O
If	O
by	O
example	O
snar	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
Paſsion	O
warm	O
'd	O
,	O
“	O
Some	O
false	O
delight	O
my	O
Giddy	O
sense	O
has	O
charm	O
'd	O
“	O
My	O
calmer	O
thoughts	O
the	O
wretched	O
choice	O
reprove	O
,	O
“	O
And	O
my	O
best	O
hopes	O
are	O
center	O
'd	O
in	O
thy	O
love	O
.	O
“	O
Deprived	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
can	O
life	O
one	O
joy	O
afford	O
?	O
!	O
“	O
It	O
's	O
utmost	O
boast	O
,	O
a	O
vain	O
unmeaning	O
word	O
,	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
All	O
powerful	O
Grace	O
,	O
exert	O
thy	O
gentle	O
sway	O
,	O
“	O
And	O
teach	O
my	O
rebel	O
Paſsions	O
to	O
obey	O
,	O
“	O
Lest	O
lurking	O
folly	O
wth	O
.	O
insidious	O
Art	O
“	O
Regain	O
my	O
volatile	O
inconstant	O
Heart	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
Sections	O
from	O
A	O
Night	O
Piece	O
(	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
Thoughts	O
at	O
Midnight	O
)	O
,	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Carter	O
(	O
16	O
December	O
1717	O
–	O
19	O
February	O
1806	O
)	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
You	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
in	O
Health	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
your	O
old	O
complaint	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
apprehensions	O
that	O
you	O
secretly	O
cherish	O
a	O
recollections	O
that	O
depreſs	O
yor	O
.	O
Spirits	O
.	O
to	O
what	O
else	O
can	O
I	O
impute	O
the	O
melancholy	O
that	O
hangs	O
over	O
You	O
--	O
surrounded	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
dear	O
to	O
you	O
except	O
Your	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
&	O
though	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
being	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
You	O
,	O
aſsured	O
of	O
her	O
affection	O
&	O
the	O
sincerity	O
of	O
her	O
friendship	O
--	O
open	O
you	O
heart	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
ease	O
my	O
anxiety	O
--	O
or	O
let	O
me	O
share	O
your	O
sorrows	O
.	O
Hero	B-pers
is	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
meſsage	O
from	O
her	O
--	O
a	O
verbal	O
enquiry	O
--	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
her	O
apartments	O
are	O
open	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
making	O
preparations	O
for	O
her	O
coming	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
does	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
saying	O
every	O
thing	O
proper	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Louise	B-pers
has	O
sent	O
You	O
Klopstock	O
from	O
Hanover	B-place
,	O
ye	O
.	O
German	O
General	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Drst	O
.	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
write	O
in	O
haste	O
--	O
give	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
B	B-pers
&	O
Is	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
enclose	O
the	O
list	O
of	O
those	O
invited	O
to	O
Orion	B-pers
s	O
Fête	O
.	O
Perfecta	B-pers
has	O
written	O
me	O
two	O
letters	O
--	O
her	O
Son	O
s	O
health	O
gains	O
ground	O
but	O
slowly	O
--	O
her	O
married	O
daughter	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
Cousins	O
were	O
taken	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
&	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
Spain	B-place
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
