TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
inadvertently	O
deferr	O
'd	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
much	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
shall	O
not	O
offer	O
any	O
further	O
apology	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
treating	O
you	O
with	O
too	O
much	O
formality	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
borne	O
your	O
late	O
loſs	O
with	O
such	O
proper	O
resignation	O
;	O
your	O
dutiful	O
affection	O
to	O
your	O
Parent	O
was	O
too	O
evident	O
to	O
leave	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
distreſs	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
felt	O
in	O
being	O
deprived	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
crisis	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
your	O
conduct	O
had	O
created	O
you	O
so	O
many	O
Friends	O
,	O
which	O
without	O
flattery	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
retain	O
.	O
The	O
Papers	O
you	O
mention	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
destroy	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
an	O
incumbrance	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fetherston	I-pers
to	O
remit	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
half	O
a	O
years	O
Jointure	O
due	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
expect	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
poverty	O
and	O
distreſs	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
conceiv	O
'd	O
&	O
Rents	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
got	O
in	O
as	O
formerly	O
;	O
if	O
Ireland	B-place
does	O
not	O
get	O
some	O
relief	O
soon	O
as	O
its	O
trade	O
and	O
manufactures	O
are	O
totally	O
at	O
a	O
stand	O
all	O
ranks	O
of	O
people	O
must	O
suffer	O
in	O
proportion	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
calamity	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
also	O
receive	O
an	O
Arrear	O
of	O
Jointure	O
money	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
in	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
will	O
be	O
punctual	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
also	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
great	O
complaints	O
of	O
the	O
scarcity	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
Quarter	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fetherston	I-pers
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
no	O
acknowledgement	O
for	O
his	O
last	O
remittance	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
himself	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
advice	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
Affairs	O
you	O
may	O
command	O
it	O
and	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
given	O
with	O
perfect	O
sincerity	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Winter	O
here	O
in	O
great	O
solitude	O
not	O
by	O
choice	O
for	O
after	O
my	O
great	O
expences	O
upon	O
this	O
Place	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
keep	O
two	O
Houses	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
my	O
two	O
Children	O
are	O
also	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
and	O
are	O
indeed	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
as	O
promising	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
Jane	B-pers
so	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
between	O
10	O
&	O
11	O
years	O
old	O
is	O
very	O
handsome	O
&	O
has	O
uncommon	O
abilities	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
between	O
7	O
&	O
8	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
thoroughly	O
recover	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
go	O
od	O
school	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affect	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Latour	O
,	O
near	O
Dublin	B-place
Feby	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
1779	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
London	B-place
