TOKEN	NE
1783	O
4	O
th	O
to	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
..	O
November	O
.	O
Your	O
M	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
answer	O
a	O
l	O
etter	O
from	O
in	O
Dſs	B-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
Poſseſsion	O
&	O
hers	O
now	O
For	O
Man	O
sha	O
n't	O
stand	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
frown	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
a	O
King	O
--	O
oppreſs	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
Usurper	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
be	O
Hector	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Subject	O
Anne	O
D	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
November	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
1803	O
B	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
a	O
most	O
heavenly	O
day	O
as	O
warm	O
as	O
in	O
July	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Spencer	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
--	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
&	O
at	O
Bulst	O
rode	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
left	O
me	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
1.	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
come	O
.	O
heard	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
last	O
night	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mathias	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveng	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
s.	O
met	O
there	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
.	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
the	O
Col	O
.	O
was	O
better	O
but	O
had	O
his	O
leg	O
upon	O
a	O
stool	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
below	O
work	O
&	O
conversation	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
was	O
come	O
&	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
meſsage	O
.	O
we	O
workd	O
&	O
convers	O
'd	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	O
AM	B-pers
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
Novbr-	O
1783	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Had	O
a	O
Cold	O
in	O
my	O
Limbs	O
--	O
had	O
hartshorn	O
&	O
tea	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
11	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Fredrick	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
.	O
sent	O
AM	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
after	O
sitting	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
him	O
we	O
nt	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
to	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s.	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
saw	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
who	O
was	O
vastly	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
Coach	O
&	O
took	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
tho	O
still	O
lame	O
&	O
weak	O
from	O
her	O
fall	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
a	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
Stay	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
neither	O
she	O
nor	O
my	O
Uncle	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brigham	I-pers
came	O
from	O
Dr	B-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
for	O
ye	O
.	O
rent	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Phillips	O
--	O
but	O
should	O
return	O
to	O
Town	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
&	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
after	O
wrote	O
a	O
joint	O
letter	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
went	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
Sup	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
Thursday	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Monsieur	B-pers
Tremblay	I-pers
(	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentl	O
.	O
who	O
brought	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
Geneva	B-place
)	O
call	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chiswick	B-place
where	O
Master	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
at	O
school	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Clear	O
day	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
drive	O
.	O
Monr	B-pers
Tremblay	I-pers
seems	O
a	O
lively	O
sensible	O
Young	O
Man	O
good	O
humourd	O
&	O
full	O
of	O
observation	O
.	O
we	O
found	O
Master	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Grown	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
improved	O
.	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Master	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
School	O
--	O
an	O
original	O
in	O
person	O
&	O
Manner	O
--	O
his	O
2	O
daughters	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
sensible	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
original	O
Old	O
Maiden	O
figure	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
yellow	O
face	O
&	O
Yellow	O
ribbons	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
Contrast	O
her	O
thin	O
scrggy	O
figure	O
to	O
the	O
Corpulent	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
a	O
Mr.Dr	B-pers
Coombes	I-pers
who	O
came	O
from	O
America	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
sensible	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
talkd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Nurse	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
a	O
Neice	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Husband	O
.	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Town	B-place
abt	O
.	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye-	O
Coach	O
wth	O
her	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
were	O
with	O
her	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
Saturday	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
she	O
wld	O
.	O
take	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
sat	O
below	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
letters	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
we	O
read	O
,	O
Abbé	O
du	O
Bois	O
Man	O
of	O
feeling	O
.	O
work	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
past	O
11	O
little	O
Henry	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
us	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
Friday	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Groom	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Change	O
in	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
s	O
establishmt	O
that	O
P.	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
had	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
wth-	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
place	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
was	O
to	O
allow	O
him	O
½	O
his	O
Salary	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
ys	O
.	O
before	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
Netting	O
box	O
from	O
Tunbridge	B-place
.	O
dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Aunt	O
we	O
took	O
an	O
Airing	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
5	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Backgammon	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
had	O
my	O
Aunt	O
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Cs	I-pers
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
wrote	O
my	O
Journal	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
An	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Novbr	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Saturday	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
Habit	O
--	O
breakfast	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
settled	O
wth	O
..	O
Maria	B-pers
about	O
our	O
accounts	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
Met	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
she	O
was	O
engaged	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
staid	O
there	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Weldren	I-pers
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
kindly	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
had	O
spoke	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
ye	B-pers
P	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walked	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
did	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
'd	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
invitation	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
come	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
quiet	O
party	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
day	O
sent	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
ym	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
house	O
,	O
heard	O
Coll	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
was	O
at	O
Chichester	B-place
her	O
Children	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
there	O
also	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
expected	O
in	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
left	O
my	O
letter	O
for	O
him	O
there	O
Stopd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
as	O
she	O
paſsd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
walk	O
'd	O
down	O
ye	O
street	O
.	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
Novbr	O
.	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Sunday	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
dres	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
church	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Johnsons	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
&	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
they	O
came	O
yesterday	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
,	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
Dover	O
Street	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
..	O
Eveg	O
wth	O
.	O
Dowr	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
rather	O
uneasy	O
abt	O
.	O
dear	O
little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
was	O
much	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Fanny	B-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Novbr	O
.	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Monday	O
1783	O
.	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
.	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
with	O
AM	B-pers
till	O
past	O
12.	O
when	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Isabella	B-pers
came	O
he	O
sat	O
near	O
2	O
hours	O
with	O
me	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
an	O
airing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
as	O
my	O
Uncle	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
recd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
uncomfortable	O
accounts	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
&	O
no	O
certainty	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
6.	O
went	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Play	O
House	O
.	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
of	O
Harry	O
ye	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
farce	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
just	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Hall	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Cambridge	B-place
tomorrow	O
but	O
would	O
if	O
Poſsible	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
excused	O
himself	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
alone	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Bell	B-pers
where	O
she	O
sup	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
¼	O
past	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Novbr	O
.	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Went	O
down	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
at	O
10	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
of	O
his	O
disagreement	O
wth	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
.	O
quitting	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Family	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
who	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
playd	O
at	O
Cheſs	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
came	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
.	O
just	O
as	O
as	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufrers	I-pers
came	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
¼	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Servt	O
.	O
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
&	O
a	O
Hare	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
not	O
better	O
.	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
come	O
for	O
ye-	O
meeting	O
of	O
Parliament	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
wrote	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Wake	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
StormontWake	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sat	O
below	O
wth	O
.	O
AMaria	B-pers
till	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
together	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
letter	O
frm	O
.	O
a	O
Lady	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
chearful	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
--	O
came	O
away	O
we	O
set	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
down	O
in	O
Albermarle	O
Street	O
.	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
was	O
alone	O
Col	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
out	O
at	O
Isabella	B-pers
,	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
..	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
oClock	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
12	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
&	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
glover	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Thimble	O
Earings	O
&	O
c.	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
engravings	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
D'agincourt	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Miniature	O
Painter	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Enamels	O
&	O
another	O
Man	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
fine	O
Sketch	O
of	O
Vandykes	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
aſsension	O
.	O
they	O
soon	O
went	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
staid	O
sometime	O
after	O
they	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Man	O
wth	O
.	O
Linnen	O
&	O
bespoke	O
my	O
Uncle	O
some	O
shirts	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
.	O
Hurter	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
After	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
came	O
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
staid	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
paid	O
me	O
my	O
interest	O
Money	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
staid	O
sometime	O
after	O
my	O
Uncle	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
&	O
sat	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Fredk	I-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
read	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sorrel	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
we	O
began	O
,	O
&	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
French	O
Novel	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
.	O
rcd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
who	O
wrote	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Albans	I-place
,	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
school	O
&	O
c	O
Thursday	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr-	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Locke	B-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Carriage	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
oClock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
s	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
staid	O
there	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
sometime	O
whilst	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
my	O
Uncle	O
his	O
Pictures	O
,	O
my	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Master	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
corrected	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
copy	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Poem	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bas-bleu	O
&	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
staid	O
wth	O
her	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
came	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
for	O
dinner	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
disappointed	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
been	O
at	O
not	O
meeting	O
me	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
before	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
invite	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
c	O
...	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Bell	B-pers
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
Mother	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
ye	O
Man	O
lived	O
yt	O
.	O
made	O
ye	O
.	O
V	O
v	O
ide	O
Poche	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
last	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
home	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
where	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
because	O
I	O
expected	O
Maria	B-pers
--	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
&	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
Morg	O
to	O
desire	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
Letters	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
found	O
after	O
her	O
death	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
½	O
after	O
.	O
Friday	O
14	O
Novbr	O
..	O
1783	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
early	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
immediately	O
after	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
--	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
sent	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
&	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
Money	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
should	O
borrow	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
even	O
to	O
ye-	O
Sum	O
of	O
200	O
L	O
I	O
thankd	O
him	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
debt	O
neither	O
was	O
I	O
diſstreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
money	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
&	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
gone	O
wth	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
were	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
I	O
went	O
there	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
went	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
they	O
'd	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
a	O
needle	O
Book	O
&	O
workbag	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
staid	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
wth	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
out	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
supper	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	I-pers
I	O
thought	O
better	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Marianne	B-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Catton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
Antrobus	B-pers
ran	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
..	O
Anna	B-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
left	O
word	O
he	O
wld	O
..	O
come	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
recd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
answerd	O
it	O
Saturday	O
15	O
th	O
..	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
sent	O
up	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Hair	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ye-	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s.	O
then	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
found	O
after	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
left	O
ym-	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
promised	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
at	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s.	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
had	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
gave	O
her	O
work	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
(	O
again	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
read	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
Letters	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
.	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
gown	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
H	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
Marianne	B-pers
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
came	O
(	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
went	O
out	O
)	O
we	O
sent	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
read	O
to	O
Marianne	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
&	O
they	O
wept	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye-	O
next	O
room	O
&	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
came	O
in	O
(	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
after	O
7	O
--	O
had	O
Mr	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
had	O
powder	O
in	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
walkd	O
acroſs	O
to	O
Antrobus	B-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Howe	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baller	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
,	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
engagement	O
with	O
me	O
though	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sunday	O
16	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
ten	O
--	O
had	O
B	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
then	O
dreſsd	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
William	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
wth.——	O
me	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
affection	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
sometime	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
copying	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
she	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
went	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
past	O
4	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
&	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Daughters	O
&	O
Cousin	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
.	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
that	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
respects	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
harpsicord	O
.	O
her	O
execution	O
was	O
good	O
but	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
without	O
taste	O
or	O
feeling	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
we	O
conversed	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
in	O
sin	O
cerity	O
of	O
Princes	O
in	O
General	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
again	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
.	O
he	O
accompanied	O
me	O
to	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
s	O
where	O
he	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
there	O
who	O
soon	O
went	O
away	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
left	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Carriage	O
back	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
Ailsbury	I-pers
--	O
a	O
most	O
original	O
figure	O
--	O
short	O
,	O
square	O
,	O
fat	O
old	O
,	O
ugly	O
but	O
a	O
good	O
humourd	O
countenance	O
came	O
,	O
in	O
,	O
dreſsd	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
outrée	O
Manner	O
--	O
&	O
decorated	O
wth——	O
a	O
profusion	O
of	O
diamond	O
stars	O
in	O
her	O
hair	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
treble	O
drop	O
Diamond	O
earings	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sensible	O
Woman	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Saturday	O
continued	O
conversed	O
on	O
different	O
Subjects	O
Natural	O
Hist	O
:	O
of	O
some	O
curious	O
insects	O
&	O
c.	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garnett	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
acroſs	O
but	O
made	O
me	O
get	O
in	O
his	O
Carriage	O
&	O
turn	O
round	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
.	O
sent	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
Verses	O
of	O
Bas-bleu	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
1	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
(	O
we	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
bed	O
)	O
she	O
read	O
whilst	O
I	O
transcribed	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
.	O
Sunday	O
continued	O
ye	O
.	O
celebrated	O
good	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s.	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
read	O
Dr	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
affecting	O
letters	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Lyttelton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Kings	O
--	O
they	O
wept	O
&	O
were	O
much	O
moved	O
by	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
were	O
I	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
oClock	O
,	O
I	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
undreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
happy	O
by	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
enquired	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
her	O
old	O
friend	O
the	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
esteem	O
'd	O
&	O
greatly	O
beloved	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
all	O
this	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Chevalier	B-pers
Sagramoso	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
us	O
in	O
ye-	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Monday	O
17	O
th	O
..	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
London	B-place
.	O
Got	O
up	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
conversed	O
about	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
too	O
--	O
her	O
health	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
off	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
Marianne	B-pers
came	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
--	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bedgown	O
--	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
Note	O
--	O
he	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
mutually	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
see	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
Yesterday	O
--	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
till	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
c	O
come	O
up	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
next	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cast	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
sat	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
new	O
silk	O
case	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
case	O
wch	O
.	O
conta	O
ins	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
letters	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
calld	O
at	O
ye	O
door	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
not	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
4	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
where	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
.	O
at	O
Coffee	O
time	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cheſs	O
wth	O
.	O
Antrobus	B-pers
.	O
abt	O
7	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
)	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
sit	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
recommended	O
ye	O
.	O
Story	O
of	O
La	O
Roche	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
read	O
from	O
ye	O
Mirror	O
.	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
tea	O
.	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
them	O
&	O
sat	O
below	O
after	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Marianne	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
c	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
bind	O
my	O
work	O
'd	O
apron	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
12.	O
we	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Chèvalier	B-pers
Scagramoso	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Bell	B-pers
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
&	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
up	O
.	O
she	O
staid	O
to	O
finish	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chevalier	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
got	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
8	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wk	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
she	O
had	O
already	O
got	O
her	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
.	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
breakfast	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'	O
d	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
&	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
my	O
things	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
received	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
town	B-place
some	O
days	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
confin	O
'd	O
since	O
Sunday	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
hurried	O
&	O
expected	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Chaise	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
besides	O
was	O
rain	O
'd	O
all	O
night	O
&	O
then	O
rain	O
'd	O
&	O
blew	O
hard	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
ye	O
Ducheſs	O
's	O
Chaise	O
&	O
a	O
Servt	O
.	O
on	O
horseback	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
the	O
roads	O
were	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
clear	O
'd	O
up	O
--	O
ye	O
air	O
was	O
uncommonly	O
warm	O
&	O
ye	O
Sun	O
came	O
out	O
--	O
came	O
through	O
Tyburn	B-place
Turnpike	O
--	O
&	O
Uxbridge	B-place
the	O
country	O
not	O
pretty	O
--	O
&	O
flat	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Way	O
--	O
Uxbridge	B-place
is	O
5	O
Miles	O
from	O
Bullstrode	O
.	O
arrived	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
in	O
2	O
hours	O
&	O
¾	O
's	O
--	O
was	O
most	O
kindly	O
welcom	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
..	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
whom	O
I	O
found	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
arrived	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
suffer	O
us	O
to	O
change	O
our	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
4.	O
before	O
dinner	O
ye	O
:	O
Dſs	O
.	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
apartment	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
knotted	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
tea	O
wrote	O
to	O
invite	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
Bullstrode	O
.	O
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
ten	O
very	O
lively	O
chearful	O
conversation	O
separated	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
Wedn	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Bulstrode	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
library	O
before	O
B——	O
Chas	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm-	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
pretty	O
for	O
fringe	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
had	O
given	O
her	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Gold	O
Netting	O
Shuttle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
had	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
parted	O
I	O
came	O
int	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
went	O
up	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
AMClarke	I-pers
came	O
from	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Chapel	O
&	O
had	O
Morning	O
Prayers	O
.	O
after	O
P	O
.	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Knotting	O
ye	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
fringe	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
spent	O
W	O
.	O
afternoon	O
in	O
an	O
agreeable	O
lively	O
Manner	O
--	O
had	O
our	O
work	O
tables	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
was	O
writing	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
..	O
s	O
shells	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
over	O
prints	O
&	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
:	O
Dſs	O
:	O
explain	O
'd	O
&	O
talk	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
historical	O
Portraits	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
supper	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
particularly	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
&	O
I	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
friendly	O
disagreements	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
I	O
like	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
very	O
much	O
.	O
unaffected	O
easy	O
,	O
chearful	O
sensible	O
--	O
we	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
Thursday	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
Bullstrode	O
1783	O
Went	O
upstairs	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
ask	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
Chambers	O
for	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B——	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
all	O
met	O
to	O
B	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
came	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
her	O
situation	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Chaise	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
Park	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
&	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
wch	O
.	O
did	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
birds	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
when	O
she	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Greenhouse	O
,	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Peacock	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
some	O
Fungus	O
&	O
a	O
Caterpillar	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
..	O
's	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
my	O
Fungus	O
's	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
left	O
us	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
dreſs	O
at	O
3	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
spent	O
ye-	O
Eveg	O
pleasantly	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
the	O
Bas	O
bleu	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
.	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Ton	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
MountEdgecome	I-pers
.	O
some	O
of	O
Evelina	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
before	O
tea	O
&	O
wrote	O
letter	O
to	O
Mde	B-pers
.	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
parted	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Novbr	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
1783	O
Friday	O
Bullstrode	O
Before	O
breakfast	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
write	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
letters	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Boscowan	B-pers
a	O
little	O
after	O
10	O
oClock	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr-	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
we	O
drove	O
only	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Mouflons	O
wch	O
.	O
came	O
from	O
Corsica	B-place
--	O
at	O
least	O
ye	O
.	O
parents	O
of	O
those	O
we	O
saw	O
--	O
something	O
between	O
ye	O
.	O
Goat	O
&	O
Dear	O
species	O
--	O
ye	O
Male	O
having	O
Strong	O
Horns	O
like	O
ye	O
Ram	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Paoli	I-pers
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
&	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
alarm	O
'd	O
as	O
we	O
apprehended	O
ye	O
Moufflon	O
wd	O
.	O
run	O
at	O
us	O
or	O
jump	O
over	O
our	O
heads	O
.	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
these	O
animals	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Hot	O
Houses	O
&	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Garderner	O
s	O
House	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
got	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
Coach	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Hot	O
House	O
with	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
Gardiner	O
is	O
a	O
Scotch	O
man	O
.	O
Young	O
he	O
lived	O
4	O
Years	O
head	O
Gardiner	O
under	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
at	O
ye-	O
botanical	O
Garden	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
we	O
saw	O
many	O
curious	O
things	O
(	O
belonging	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
's	O
)	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
looking	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
they	O
usd	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
drink	O
tea	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
Foſsils	O
--	O
(	O
Plants	O
cut	O
out	O
upon	O
Paper	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
done	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
)	O
a	O
Hornets	O
nest	O
in	O
a	O
Glaſs	O
Case	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
we	O
returnd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Duſs	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
from	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Eaden	I-pers
came	O
we	O
had	O
prayers	O
in	O
ye	O
Chapel	O
After	O
Prayers	O
,	O
aſsisted	O
ye	O
Ducheſs	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
Birds	O
Eggs	O
,	O
saw	O
some	O
curious	O
Nests	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
Fungus	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
ye	O
Gardiner	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3.	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscript	O
viz	O
copying	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
s	O
little	O
Papers	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
prints	O
till	O
dinner	O
abt	O
..	O
½	O
past	O
4.	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
in	O
an	O
agreeable	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
Character	O
written	O
I	O
again	O
wrote	O
it	O
out	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Separated	O
after	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
as	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Solander	I-pers
Novbr	O
.	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Bullstrode	O
Satry	O
.	O
1783	O
Went	O
upstairs	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
was	O
soon	O
joind	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
.	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
--	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
left	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
for	O
a	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
talkd	O
,	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
Pictures	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
room	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
wrote	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
we	O
sat	O
together	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
look	O
over	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
oClock	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
,	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
sent	O
for	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
who	O
went	O
up	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
hours	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
c	O
staid	O
.	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
,	O
first	O
by	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
large	O
Book	O
of	O
Drawings	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
Room	O
.	O
of	O
Views	O
&	O
c	O
taken	O
by	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
Derbyshire	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
her	O
Maid	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
sensible	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
sensible	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
worthy	O
Woman	O
)	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Clergymans	O
Daughter	O
)	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Miniature	O
picture	O
of	O
herself	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
name	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
who	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
is	O
at	O
Astley	B-pers
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
.	O
3	O
Guineas	O
each	O
well	O
painted	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
likeneſs	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
Mavis	B-pers
&	O
c	O
went	O
away	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
after	O
4	O
oClock	O
.	O
Sr-	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
went	O
upstairs	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
our	O
dreſs	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
wch	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
s	O
footman	O
After	O
dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hours	O
sleep	O
as	O
usual	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
how	O
unhappy	O
she	O
was	O
abt	O
her	O
uneasineſs	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
she	O
shed	O
tears	O
of	O
pure	O
friendship	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
I	O
read	O
Evelina	O
,	O
pleasant	O
converse	O
work	O
&	O
c	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
supper	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
after	O
supper	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
Chearful	O
,	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
oClock	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
told	O
me	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
governeſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
2.3	O
d	O
.	O
Sunday	O
Novbr	O
.	O
Bullstrode	O
1783	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
téte	O
a	O
téte	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
sat	O
alone	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
this	O
dear	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
histry	O
.	O
of	O
her	O
Maid	O
s	O
Cousin	O
,	O
his	O
upbringing	O
at	O
Tobago	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
then	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
chapter	O
in	O
Partricks	O
Pilgrim	O
,	O
an	O
excellent	O
Parable	O
Relative	O
to	O
friendship	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
enquiry	O
as	O
usual	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chapel	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
met	O
her	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
went	O
to	O
Chapel	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
preach	O
a	O
good	O
Sermon	O
.	O
after	O
C——	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
aſsisted	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
in	O
looking	O
over	O
her	O
Books	O
of	O
flowers	O
.	O
putting	O
ye	O
Names	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
om̅itted	O
omitted	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
4.	O
at	O
½	O
after	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
she	O
again	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
wept	O
again	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
uneasineſs	O
she	O
had	O
undergone	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
read	O
many	O
charming	O
Letters	O
of	O
ye	O
late	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Year	O
39.	O
to	O
his	O
death	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
.	O
staid	O
from	O
near	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
told	O
me	O
many	O
interesting	O
stories	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
brought	O
an	O
unfinished	O
letter	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Young	I-pers
we	O
added	O
a	O
few	O
Meſsages	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
wrote	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
past	O
11.	O
did	O
not	O
part	O
till	O
near	O
12.	O
related	O
anecdotes	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Monday	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
room	O
to	O
breakfast	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
papers	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Chimney	O
board	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
repair	O
--	O
left	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
do	O
ye	O
.	O
:	O
C	O
.	O
Board	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
Wt	O
.	O
Sattin	O
Garter	O
Ribbons	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Dear	O
old	O
Woman	O
looke	O
'd	O
quite	O
elegant	O
.	O
I	O
continued	O
repairing	O
ye	O
.	O
Chimney	O
Board	O
.	O
cutting	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
Paper	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
1	O
oClock	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
saw	O
her	O
&	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Queen	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
busy	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
as	O
before	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3.	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawg	O
Room	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
returnd	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
not	O
till	O
near	O
5.	O
the	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chamber	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
fairly	O
scolded	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
.	O
as	O
did	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
were	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
abt	O
.	O
their	O
Visit	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
they	O
had	O
Music	O
,	O
saw	O
an	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
Cast	O
off	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gardens	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
one	O
I	O
sent	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
&	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
had	O
enquired	O
of	O
me	O
very	O
Kindly	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
After	O
Dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Room	O
as	O
usual	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
again	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
anxiety	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
apprehensions	O
of	O
her	O
hearing	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
affairs	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Dewes	O
who	O
come	O
tomorrow	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
Book	O
begun	O
ye	O
letters	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Lakes	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
Merry	O
&	O
chearful	O
,	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
Tuesday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Bullstrode	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lettice	I-pers
,	O
sat	O
sometime	O
after	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
her	O
friendship	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
other	O
interesting	O
Anecdotes	O
.	O
we	O
parted	O
I	O
dreſsd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
one	O
oClock	O
I	O
went	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
&	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
heard	O
her	O
Nephews	O
were	O
come	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Bernard	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
received	O
ym	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
politeneſs	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Dewes	O
.	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
fine	O
Antiques	O
.	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Books	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
cc	O
My	O
Uncle	O
entertain	O
'd	O
us	O
after	O
dinner	O
by	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
paſsion	O
for	O
shooting	O
his	O
library	O
of	O
Date	O
,	O
&	O
Nu	O
m	O
ber	O
of	O
game	O
killd	O
&	O
c	O
Wedn	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Bulstrode	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
before	O
9	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Copies	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
&	O
upon	O
leaving	O
Court	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
letters	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
highly	O
approved	O
of	O
my	O
Conduct	O
ye	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
came	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
went	O
away	O
before	O
breakfast	O
.	O
we	O
met	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
10	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
B	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
I	O
drew	O
upon	O
myself	O
much	O
Raillery	O
--	O
for	O
laughing	O
&	O
spilling	O
ye	O
.	O
tea	O
&	O
Coffee	O
I	O
made	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
found	O
her	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
went	O
up	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
better	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Chapel	O
.	O
After	O
Chapel	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
remain	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
in	O
ye	O
Gallery	O
,	O
looking	O
over	O
Minerals	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
,	O
till	O
near	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
acquaintance	O
wth	O
.	O
Dst	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
her	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
c.	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
in	O
ye	O
Gallery	O
saw	O
,	O
some	O
Jewels	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Minerals	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
dreſs	O
.	O
as	O
Delany	B-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
manageed	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
shd	O
dine	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
wthout	O
alarming	O
either	O
her	O
or	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Table	O
&	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
abt	O
..	O
½	O
past	O
4.	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
very	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
Volcano	O
's	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
.	O
Room	O
found	O
Dr	O
.	O
Swift	B-pers
there	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
most	O
agreeably	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
alter	O
my	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
went	O
away	O
abt	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
read	O
us	O
ye	O
Character	O
of	O
Mde	O
.	O
La	O
Valliere	O
wch	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
sent	O
--	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
work	O
abt	O
3	O
oClock	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
reposed	O
herself	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
the	O
Dſs	O
's	O
..	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
Gallery	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
renew	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
subject	O
nearest	O
her	O
heart	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
sleep	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dining	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
talked	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
he	O
agree	O
'd	O
how	O
wrong	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
might	O
agitate	O
her	O
Spirits	O
.	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
some	O
letters	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
's	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Portraits	O
of	O
French	O
People	O
of	O
Note	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
work	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
continued	O
putting	O
ye	O
.	O
names	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Books	O
of	O
flowers	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
waked	O
much	O
refreſsed	O
.	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
wheel	O
agreeable	O
interesting	O
converse	O
begun	O
after	O
tea	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
Bas	O
bleu	O
at	O
their	O
Desire	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
..	O
I	O
finished	O
my	O
task	O
&	O
ye	O
ton	O
Volume	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
took	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
again	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
&	O
he	O
again	O
promised	O
me	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
letters	O
.	O
before	O
supper	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
..	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
town	B-place
tomorrow	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
very	O
entertaining	O
chearful	O
converse	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
.	O
finished	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Leavers	I-pers
to	O
go	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
tomorrow	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
Friday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Novbr	O
..	O
Bullstrode	O
went	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Room	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Night	O
--	O
we	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
to	O
f	O
fou	O
nd	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
soon	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
I	O
made	O
Breakfast	O
soon	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
went	O
in	O
Coach	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
--	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
7	O
Miles	O
Round	O
)	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
12	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
an	O
humoursome	O
account	O
of	O
an	O
her	O
going	O
hunting	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
in	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
&	O
hoop	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
room	O
till	O
Prayer	O
Bell	O
rang	O
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
dear	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
--	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
.	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
i	O
n	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
went	O
to	O
Chapel	O
--	O
after	O
Prayers	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
immediately	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
not	O
at	O
Chapel	O
but	O
was	O
out	O
walking	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
fine	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
&	O
dreſsd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
wth	O
.	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
uneasy	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Duſs	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
Prayers	O
.	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
fretting	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
room	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
4	O
oClock	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
there	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
s	O
desire	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
organ	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
to	O
give	O
ye	O
.	O
signal	O
Lightfoot	B-pers
often	O
gives	O
for	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
notice	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
we	O
jok	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
:	O
account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Libr	O
ary	O
&	O
c	O
making	O
him	O
gueſs	O
ye	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
&	O
his	O
Museum	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
reposed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
s	O
Book	O
of	O
Plants	O
brought	O
for	O
me	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
Goose	O
tree	O
shells	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Gerrard	B-pers
came	O
in	O
soon	O
.	O
the	O
After	O
noon	O
&	O
Eveg	O
spent	O
agreeably	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Tea	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
..	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
our	O
table	O
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
her	O
work	O
&	O
Less	O
ons	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
transcribing	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
.	O
of	O
ye	O
Late	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
collection	O
of	O
shells	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
Spinning	O
.	O
I	O
knotting	O
her	O
fringe	O
&	O
writing	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
broken	O
Conversation	O
Dr.	B-pers
Solander	I-pers
looking	O
over	O
Portrait	O
Prints	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
explaining	O
&	O
shewing	O
a	O
thorough	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
antient	O
&	O
Modern	O
Histry	O
.	O
&	O
also	O
attending	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
or	O
near	O
11.	O
we	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
talkd	O
after	O
Supper	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
Spa	B-place
is	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
Ruſsia	B-place
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Daschov	I-pers
in	O
answer	O
to	O
hers	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
goes	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
Saty	O
:	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Bullstrode	O
went	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
soon	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
went	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
L——	I-pers
&	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Eaton	B-place
&	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
My	O
Notes	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
&	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
.	O
Ms.	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Chaise	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
Park	O
went	O
by	O
Queen	O
Elizabeths	O
(	O
at	O
Eaton	B-place
it	O
has	O
yt	O
.	O
name	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
straight	O
Avenues	O
of	O
trees	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
ye	O
taste	O
in	O
her	O
time	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
mild	O
as	O
in	O
June	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Sun	O
shone	O
bright	O
our	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
Courts	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
relation	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
his	O
arts	O
,	O
his	O
deceiving	O
her	O
her	O
friends	O
wanting	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
Bedchamber	O
Woman	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
how	O
well	O
satisfied	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
having	O
escaped	O
getting	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
.	O
Gave	O
me	O
much	O
information	O
respecting	O
Lord	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
folly	O
of	O
her	O
Conduct	O
--	O
Q	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
&	O
c	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
awkward	O
in	O
her	O
manner	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
a	O
weak	O
&	O
ambitious	O
Woman	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
from	O
airing	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Caracature	O
Prints	O
&	O
Borders	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
,	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Medley	O
screen	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
read	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscript	O
Book	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
sat	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
of	O
Prior	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
that	O
her	O
mind	O
was	O
relieved	O
,	O
we	O
cld	O
.	O
not	O
finish	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
was	O
waiting	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
&	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
set	O
out	O
an	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
read	O
in	O
Prior	O
.	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Stile	O
&	O
subject	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
3	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chamber	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
they	O
workd	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
of	O
ye	O
Lakes	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
change	O
my	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
from	O
W	B-place
.	I-place
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
an	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
being	O
rather	O
better	O
.	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
could	O
not	O
write	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
ye	O
Pſss	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eaton	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Rebellion	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Eaton	O
not	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
Scholars	O
but	O
of	O
ye	O
Masters	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
also	O
over	O
ye	O
Castle	O
at	O
W	B-place
.	I-place
it	O
was	O
after	O
4	O
before	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
Gown	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
just	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
as	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
staid	O
longer	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
than	O
we	O
thought	O
neceſsary	O
we	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
laugh	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
near	O
5	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
indeed	O
is	O
almost	O
always	O
ye	O
.	O
Case	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
reposed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Great	O
chair	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
Room	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
met	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
,	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
till	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
tea	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
in	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
past	O
7	O
oClock	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
at	O
our	O
different	O
Tables	O
&	O
Works	O
:	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
at	O
his	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Manscript	O
wch	O
she	O
had	O
coppied	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
original	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
poſseſsion	O
a	O
Diary	O
or	O
Journal	O
Thursday	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
sat	O
&	O
conversed	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
continued	O
persecution	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
who	O
really	O
is	O
paying	O
her	O
addreſs	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
my	O
persecutions	O
from	O
M	O
r	O
R	O
&	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
he	O
again	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
well	O
satisfied	O
he	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
conduct	O
.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
he	O
heard	O
every	O
one	O
give	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
B——	O
Dr.	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gore	I-pers
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
B	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
his	O
fine	O
antique	O
of	O
Jupiter	O
.	O
this	O
he	O
also	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
great	O
expreſsion	O
of	O
goodneſs	O
Majesty	O
ye	O
.	O
finest	O
&	O
most	O
perfect	O
thing	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
.	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
Baberini	O
Cabinet	O
--	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
Ran	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
scribbled	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
sent	O
a	O
Packet	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
my	O
uncle	O
.	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Anna	B-pers
soon	O
after	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
her	O
Book	O
of	O
flowers	O
.	O
put	O
ye	O
.	O
Names	O
's	O
this	O
employ	O
'd	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
looking	O
over	O
Minerals	O
--	O
and	O
ye	O
.	O
Volcanic	O
Prints	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
explained	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
did	O
not	O
sup	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
sat	O
&	O
had	O
pleasant	O
Conversation	O
--	O
natural	O
Histy	O
chiefly	O
.	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
.	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
I	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
her	O
goodnight	O
in	O
ye	O
Gallery	O
.	O
