TOKEN	NE
Dover	B-place
Sepr	O
:	O
4	O
th	O
1787	O
You	O
will	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
be	O
astonished	O
at	O
seeing	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Boy	O
finding	O
himself	O
grow	O
worse	O
instead	O
of	O
better	O
,	O
petitioned	O
his	O
poor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
moving	O
manner	O
poſsible	O
that	O
He	O
might	O
return	O
home	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
all	O
just	O
landed	O
again	O
on	O
this	O
Shore	O
--	O
for	O
many	O
reasons	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
thankful	O
.	O
I	O
send	O
away	O
this	O
hasty	O
Line	O
just	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
&	O
yr	O
:	O
kind	O
and	O
good	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
Dr	O
:	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
bore	O
the	O
Voyage	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
cd	O
:	O
have	O
expected	O
in	O
his	O
weak	O
State	O
&	O
that	O
poor	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
Ill	O
write	O
soon	O
again	O
--	O
Adieu	O
pray	O
for	O
me	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
Yrs	O
:	O
ever	O
Afft	O
PCremorne	B-pers
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
:	O
Dr	O
:	O
little	O
one	O
is	O
well	O
.	O
Kiſs	O
her	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Viscounteſs	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Sepr	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
