TOKEN	NE
Blackheath	B-place
May	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
Yours	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
came	O
ſafe	O
to	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
very	O
unreaſonable	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
deſire	O
lo	O
ng	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
absolutely	O
hurried	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
ſences	O
with	O
field	O
days	O
&	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
dont	O
leave	O
me	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
prepair	O
for	O
our	O
reviews	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
&	O
22	O
d	O
instant	O
the	O
first	O
by	O
Major	B-pers
General	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
by	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
on	O
ye	O
24	O
th	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Squ	O
are	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
but	O
I	O
shall	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
motions	O
&	O
the	O
exact	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
It	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pleaſure	O
that	O
Cloe	O
is	O
already	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
favorite	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
the	O
Lady	O
that	O
ſhe	O
belonged	O
too	O
otherwise	O
I	O
should	O
tell	O
her	O
all	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
you	O
are	O
fond	O
of	O
her	O
thats	O
quite	O
sufficient	O
for	O
my	O
purpose	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
good	O
natured	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
friends	O
among	O
the	O
Servants	O
which	O
will	O
likeways	O
show	O
her	O
good	O
sense	O
in	O
making	O
them	O
her	O
friends	O
as	O
a	O
dog	O
not	O
liked	O
by	O
them	O
always	O
paſses	O
but	O
a	O
miserable	O
life	O
tho	O
the	O
Miſstriſs	O
be	O
fond	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
they	O
dislike	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
contented	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
at	O
present	O
&	O
indeed	O
till	O
we	O
meet	O
as	O
this	O
most	O
certainly	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
longest	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
get	O
longer	O
ones	O
from	O
Buxton	B-place
if	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
do	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
convinced	O
off	O
as	O
yet	O
as	O
I	O
still	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
&	O
likewise	O
yourself	O
as	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
so	O
very	O
sedentary	O
a	O
Life	O
there	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
which	O
must	O
hurt	O
your	O
health	O
in	O
time	O
tho	O
at	O
present	O
not	O
visible	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
experience	O
as	O
I	O
owe	O
all	O
my	O
illneſs	O
's	O
to	O
that	O
way	O
of	O
Life	O
ſome	O
Years	O
ago	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
take	O
rather	O
more	O
exercise	O
now	O
tho	O
I	O
am	O
ſenſible	O
not	O
enough	O
yet	O
however	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
'll	O
mend	O
every	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
verrily	O
believe	O
its	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
to	O
preſerve	O
heath	O
,	O
exercise	O
of	O
the	O
mind	O
is	O
I	O
'll	O
allow	O
very	O
beneficial	O
but	O
the	O
body	O
must	O
likeways	O
be	O
exercised	O
otherwise	O
that	O
whimsical	O
frame	O
of	O
ours	O
would	O
ſoon	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
&	O
Doctors	O
are	O
the	O
dearest	O
Petts	O
I	O
know	O
off	O
made	O
use	O
off	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
this	O
Island	O
for	O
which	O
reason	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
ſome	O
years	O
past	O
Adieu	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
most	O
Affctly-	O
--	O
Napier	B-pers
remember	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
Manner	O
poſsible	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
