TOKEN	NE
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
ungrateful	O
were	O
I	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
acknowledgements	O
to	O
your	O
excellent	O
Father	O
&	O
Sister	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
let	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
know	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
his	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
this	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
your	O
discretion	O
to	O
keep	O
matters	O
as	O
fair	O
as	O
possible	O
between	O
all	O
parties	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
great	O
difficulty	O
in	O
procuring	O
what	O
money	O
be	O
may	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
my	O
Son	O
s	O
debts	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
conclude	O
you	O
will	O
permit	O
his	O
journey	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
c	O
an	O
be	O
well	O
&	O
conveniently	O
lodged	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
not	O
forgetting	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
aſsure	O
him	O
of	O
my	O
obligations	O
for	O
his	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
Portman	O
Square	O
August	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1792	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
--	O
Chapel	B-place
in	I-place
Frith	I-place
DerbyShire	B-place
