TOKEN	NE
Naples	B-place
1st	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
about	O
1770	O
A	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
truest	O
concern	O
as	O
it	O
gives	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
of	O
that	O
particular	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
as	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
or	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
writing	O
to	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
account	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
disorder	O
I	O
remember	O
you	O
once	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
making	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
you	O
both	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
Aſsure	O
you	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
so	O
English	O
a	O
Stile	O
that	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
fear	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Italian	O
ceremonys	O
&	O
nonsense	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
enter	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
poſsible	O
into	O
their	O
Stupid	O
Aſsemblys	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
are	O
almost	O
intirely	O
with	O
the	O
English	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
live	O
much	O
to	O
ourselves	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
all	O
comfortable	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
--	O
with	O
this	O
quiet	O
kind	O
of	O
Life	O
I	O
have	O
quite	O
recovered	O
my	O
health	O
&	O
am	O
now	O
rather	O
fat	O
than	O
lean	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
Climate	O
fine	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
is	O
certainly	O
not	O
good	O
for	O
the	O
Spirits	O
for	O
mine	O
were	O
never	O
so	O
bad	O
as	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
--	O
our	O
greatest	O
diversion	O
is	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
Sea	O
where	O
we	O
paſs	O
many	O
hours	O
fishing	O
,	O
we	O
take	O
our	O
dinner	O
&	O
eat	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Rock	O
:	O
&	O
try	O
to	O
forget	O
we	O
are	O
within	O
fifty	O
Miles	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
City	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
not	O
envy	O
us	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
him	O
Ld	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
next	O
Winter	O
here	O
;	O
however	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
upon	O
Election	O
Matters	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
Comfort	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
easy	O
,	O
as	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
agreeable	O
expences	O
--	O
Hamilton	B-pers
s	O
principal	O
friend	O
here	O
is	O
Count	B-pers
Lascaris	I-pers
the	O
Sardinian	O
Minister	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Sensible	O
Man	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
may	O
remember	O
him	O
in	O
England	B-place
where	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
Uncle	O
the	B-pers
Comte	I-pers
de	I-pers
Rubion	I-pers
--	O
pray	O
how	O
does	O
my	O
little	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
do	O
?	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
likewise	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
le	O
t	O
me	O
intreat	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
exactly	O
how	O
both	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
nobody	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
truly	O
interested	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
which	O
concerns	O
you	O
than	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yr	O
Most	O
Affecte-	O
Sister	O
&	O
Obliged	O
humble	O
Servant	O
CHamilton	B-pers
Naples	B-place
July	O
ye	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
Hamilton	B-pers
joins	O
in	O
Love	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Northampton	B-place
Northamptonshire	B-place
Inghilterra	B-place
by	O
way	O
of	O
London	B-place
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
