TOKEN	NE
Enfield	B-place
Febry	O
:	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1774	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
state	O
health	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
kind-neſses	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
your	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
mother	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
Papa	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Smellome	I-pers
has	O
heard	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
about	O
10	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Grandpapa	O
will	O
send	O
my	O
shirts	O
very	O
soon	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
all	O
friends	O
at	O
Forty-Hall	O
are	O
in	O
great	O
consternation	O
as	O
my	O
Youngest	O
Uncle	O
is	O
like	O
to	O
die	O
of	O
a	O
sore	O
throat	O
&	O
fever	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
greatly	O
oblige	O
.	O
Your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Chas	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
My	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
