TOKEN	NE
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
.	O
Dec	O
:	O
12	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
most	O
kind	O
and	O
friendly	O
letter	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
:	O
,	O
yesterday	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
lest	O
you	O
should	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
not	O
giving	O
due	O
consideration	O
to	O
the	O
advice	O
contained	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
begin	O
by	O
telling	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
vindication	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
engaged	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
in	O
Duke	O
Street	O
,	O
Manchester	O
Square	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
incur	O
merited	O
disapprobation	O
from	O
any	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
particularly	O
,	O
from	O
such	O
kind	O
and	O
anxious	O
friends	O
as	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
:	O
I	O
therefore	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
you	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
without	O
reserve	O
)	O
will	O
explain	O
the	O
motives	O
for	O
this	O
step	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
proceeded	O
by	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
's	O
expreſs	O
advice	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
mentioned	O
)	O
the	O
air	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
certainly	O
does	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
only	O
,	O
objection	O
to	O
a	O
constant	O
residence	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
spirits	O
are	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
injured	O
by	O
the	O
affliction	O
I	O
have	O
recently	O
experienced	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
require	O
more	O
diversion	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
by	O
mixing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
ever	O
cared	O
for	O
,	O
before	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
enter	O
into	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
termed	O
diſsipation	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
without	O
deranging	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
mode	O
of	O
living	O
,	O
accomplish	O
this	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
never	O
has	O
a	O
creature	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
except	O
morning	O
visitors	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
goes	O
to	O
any	O
party	O
of	O
an	O
Evening	O
.	O
My	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
too	O
,	O
(	O
admitting	O
that	O
I	O
sought	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
or	O
two	O
's	O
relaxation	O
,	O
out	O
)	O
must	O
disturb	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
hou	O
time	O
for	O
retiring	O
,	O
is	O
earlier	O
than	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
nothing	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
to	O
last	O
,	O
hoping	O
better	O
conduct	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
my	O
mind	O
to	O
accomodate	O
myself	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
prospect	O
changed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
fairly	O
discuſsed	O
the	O
point	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
that	O
the	O
modes	O
of	O
life	O
of	O
two	O
people	O
of	O
such	O
unequal	O
ages	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
supposed	O
to	O
accord	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
is	O
still	O
a	O
greater	O
reason	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
yet	O
adduced	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
confidence	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
fix	O
myself	O
permanently	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
think	O
himself	O
justified	O
in	O
supposing	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
probably	O
not	O
receive	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Father	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
want	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
justice	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
so	O
unwilling	O
was	O
I	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
least	O
semblance	O
of	O
want	O
of	O
affection	O
or	O
ingratitude	O
to	O
so	O
kind	O
and	O
generous	O
a	O
Father	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
consulted	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
whether	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
reside	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
finally	O
,	O
begged	O
his	O
decisive	O
advice	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
would	O
implicitly	O
abide	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
it	O
might	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
counselled	O
my	O
taking	O
a	O
residence	O
to	O
a	O
specified	O
amount	O
,	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
defraying	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
spe	O
nd	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
convenience	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
stowing	O
various	O
articles	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
collect	O
,	O
as	O
which	O
would	O
encumber	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
will	O
further	O
,	O
answer	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
removing	O
the	O
idea	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
party	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
no	O
expence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
to	O
visit	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
settled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
weather	O
becomes	O
tolerable	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
either	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
that	O
visit	O
,	O
I	O
purpose	O
availing	O
myself	O
of	O
your	O
so	O
often	O
repeated	O
cordial	O
invitation	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
acquit	O
me	O
of	O
blame	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
explanation	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
even	O
make	O
it	O
fuller	O
,	O
verbally	O
;	O
but	O
see	O
what	O
room	O
it	O
takes	O
on	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
add	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
purposed	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
upon	O
busineſs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
busineſs	O
was	O
retarded	O
till	O
the	O
weather	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
concluded	O
it	O
by	O
letter	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
desires	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
affecte	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remove	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
E.	I-pers
Best	I-pers
are	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
with	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aldborough	I-pers
:	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
before	O
March	O
,	O
as	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
to	O
lie-in	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
all	O
communication	O
;	O
but	O
write	O
this	O
line	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
extreme	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
say	O
with	O
what	O
pleasure	O
I	O
look	O
to	O
visiting	O
you	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
accomplish	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Sir	O
your	O
most	O
obliged	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
