TOKEN	NE
Dublin	B-place
Barracks	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Decr-	O
1784	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
This	O
letter	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
directed	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
as	O
neither	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
nor	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
yourself	O
have	O
announced	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
your	O
name	O
is	O
Dickenson	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
however	O
that	O
the	O
outside	O
is	O
mistaken	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
long	O
ago	O
followed	O
the	O
advice	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
when	O
we	O
last	O
parted	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
conceive	O
myself	O
still	O
entitled	O
to	O
scold	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
already	O
obeyed	O
my	O
commands	O
I	O
beg	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
pardon	O
for	O
the	O
familiar	O
style	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
addreſs	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
excuse	O
myself	O
by	O
calling	O
on	O
you	O
to	O
witneſs	O
that	O
you	O
ever	O
allowed	O
me	O
the	O
privilege	O
of	O
finding	O
fault	O
,	O
a	O
permiſsion	O
which	O
to	O
peevish	O
discontented	O
dispositions	O
like	O
mine	O
,	O
was	O
invaluable	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
likewise	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
declare	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
ready	O
to	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
the	O
slightest	O
opportunities	O
of	O
indulging	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
exercise	O
of	O
what	O
gives	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
apolog	O
ies	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
sooner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
conceive	O
in	O
strict	O
etiquette	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
the	O
inclination	O
I	O
felt	O
to	O
condole	O
with	O
You	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Indigo	O
Tribe	O
on	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
.	O
Alas	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
victim	O
to	O
Signora	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
's	O
marriage	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
insist	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
already	O
married	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
by	O
a	O
pretended	O
cruelty	O
run	O
the	O
risk	O
of	O
sacrificing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
would	O
certainly	O
make	O
a	O
fine	O
subject	O
for	O
a	O
Poem	O
for	O
the	O
blue	O
Stocking	O
tribe	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
had	O
murdered	O
a	O
deserving	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
who	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
your	O
real	O
disposition	O
can	O
not	O
suspect	O
you	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
cruelty	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
happily	O
my	O
dearest	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
every	O
inconvenience	O
she	O
experiences	O
,	O
is	O
ever	O
chearfull	O
and	O
desirous	O
of	O
making	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
natural	O
turn	O
for	O
Œconomy	O
we	O
contrive	O
to	O
have	O
every	O
comfort	O
without	O
the	O
folly	O
's	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
appears	O
so	O
comfortable	O
as	O
when	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
really	O
makes	O
me	O
(	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
obser	O
ve	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
compliment	O
I	O
ever	O
payed	O
You	O
)	O
a	O
most	O
rational	O
Companion	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
constantly	O
abused	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
now	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
her	O
most	O
affectionate	O
good	O
wishes	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
the	O
eve	O
of	O
purchasing	O
the	O
Majority	O
of	O
this	O
Regt-	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
Your	O
very	O
Affece	O
.	O
Brother	O
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
Napier	B-pers
If	O
you	O
should	O
condescend	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
direct	O
King	O
's	O
Own	O
Regt-	O
of	O
Foot	O
Dublin	B-place
Barracks	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Anr	O
Janry	O
1	O
st	O
85	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
IRELAND	B-place
