TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
16	O
th	O
.	O
October	O
1780	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
that	O
patience	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
Virtue	O
is	O
never	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
female	O
--	O
Your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
inst	O
:	O
is	O
a	O
strong	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
this	O
observation	O
--	O
You	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
not	O
chusing	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
right	O
to	O
abuse	O
you	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
Septr	O
as	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
intention	O
of	O
leaving	O
Quarters	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
Septr	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
fulfilled	O
that	O
intention	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
title	O
to	O
blame	O
me	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
ask	O
pardon	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
submiſsive	O
manner	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
gracious	O
mood	O
when	O
I	O
receive	O
your	O
apology	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
after	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
not	O
only	O
answered	O
it	O
but	O
likewise	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
your	O
commands	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Holyroodhouse	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
our	O
sixteen	O
representatives	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
opposition	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Earls	I-pers
of	I-pers
Breadalbane	I-pers
&	O
Bute	B-pers
retire	O
.	O
The	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
E.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Glencairn	I-pers
succeed	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
distinguishing	O
myself	O
as	O
a	O
Patriot	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Election	O
the	O
right	O
honorables	O
dine	O
together	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
those	O
who	O
do	O
n't	O
amuse	O
themselves	O
with	O
the	O
Battle	O
will	O
make	O
their	O
appearance	O
at	O
an	O
Aſsembly	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Aſsembly	O
&	O
take	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
with	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
adorable	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
aſsisting	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Lady	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Carnegy	I-pers
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
her	O
Nuptials	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
next	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
the	O
intended	O
Husband	O
of	O
L.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Cousin	O
German	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
.	O
I	O
congratulate	O
you	O
upon	O
Cornwallis	B-pers
's	O
succeſs	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
such	O
spirited	O
and	O
soldierlike	O
exertions	O
would	O
soon	O
give	O
a	O
turn	O
to	O
the	O
American	O
affairs	O
.	O
The	O
Parliament	O
will	O
probably	O
meet	O
the	B-pers
K——	I-pers
in	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
a	O
circumstance	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
expected	O
had	O
not	O
this	O
fortunate	O
peice	O
of	O
news	O
arrived	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
time	O
.	O
Adieu	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
you	O
tomorrow	O
&	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
anything	O
extraordinary	O
which	O
may	O
happen	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
:	O
October	O
1780	O
The	O
election	O
yesterday	O
was	O
conducted	O
with	O
leſs	O
confusion	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
The	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
appeared	O
perfectly	O
insensible	O
of	O
the	O
honor	O
conferred	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
however	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
are	O
expected	O
here	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
They	O
arrived	O
at	O
Cork	B-place
some	O
little	O
time	O
ago	O
&	O
wrote	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
instantly	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
very	O
Affect-	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
I	O
had	O
almost	O
forgot	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
Danced	O
all	O
last	O
Night	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Ld-	B-pers
Glencairn	I-pers
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
This	O
peice	O
of	O
intelligence	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
of	O
no	O
importance	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
astonishing	O
proof	O
of	O
my	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
I	O
detest	O
so	O
much	O
--	O
Walshingham	B-place
Walingham	B-place
Walsingham	B-place
