TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
I	O
forgot	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Leicester	O
House	O
today	O
--	O
instead	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
agreable	O
to	O
you	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
)	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
if	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
rain	O
Our	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
yrs	O
.	O
affectionately	O
WHamilton	B-pers
Mews	B-place
Tuesday	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Hampsted	B-place
