TOKEN	NE
Welwyn	B-place
,	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Decr-	O
1780	O
.	O
Your	O
disobedience	O
astonishes	O
me	O
--	O
Pray	O
Miſs	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
command	O
you	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Are	O
my	O
orders	O
to	O
be	O
treated	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
?	O
Am	O
I	O
to	O
write	O
Ten	O
letters	O
for	O
one	O
?	O
In	O
this	O
little	O
dirty	O
Village	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
than	O
read	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
forsooth	O
wo	O
n't	O
write	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
packet	O
to	O
transmit	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Hen	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
wanting	O
government	O
to	O
aſsist	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
distreſs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
forward	O
the	O
application	O
.	O
She	O
suggested	O
tell	O
send	O
ing	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
by	O
sending	O
it	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
desire	O
You	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
favour	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
may	O
make	O
the	O
request	O
effectual	O
.	O
Send	O
me	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
Yourself	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
inclose	O
the	O
Packet	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
yesterday	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
conversation	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
about	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
pleased	O
her	O
wonderfully	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
length	O
settled	O
in	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
My	O
Landlord	O
drives	O
a	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
Parlour	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
squalling	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Hog	O
stye	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
a	O
Blacksmiths	O
shop	O
in	O
front	O
.	O
My	O
only	O
amusements	O
are	O
Eating	O
Drinking	O
,	O
Sleeping	O
,	O
Drilling	O
Six	O
Men	O
,	O
Scolding	O
my	O
Serjeants	O
,	O
&	O
letter	O
scribbling	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
not	O
reading	O
,	O
for	O
alas	O
my	O
library	O
is	O
small	O
--	O
Adieu	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
Your	O
affect-	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
