TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
influenza	O
that	O
has	O
gone	O
about	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
am	O
still	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
but	O
few	O
words	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
express	O
my	O
constant	O
Affection	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
by	O
a	O
Baron	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Power	I-pers
a	O
packet	O
with	O
Six	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
muscle	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
the	O
production	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
reckon	O
'd	O
very	O
curious	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ruſsia	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
some	O
.	O
These	O
I	O
entreat	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
improper	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
.	O
one	O
I	O
dare	O
s	O
not	O
(	O
nor	O
am	O
I	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
)	O
to	O
present	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
to	O
any	O
Sovereign	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
being	O
curious	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
mere	O
trifle	O
I	O
hope	O
(	O
by	O
your	O
manner	O
of	O
presenting	O
them	O
)	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
offended	O
at	O
the	O
liberty	O
I	O
take	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
I	O
entreat	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
tell	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
family	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
stronger	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
by	O
my	O
hand	O
how	O
weak	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
gaining	O
gr	O
ound	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
desires	O
his	O
kind	O
love	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
yours	O
with	O
true	O
Affection	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Taranto	B-place
April	O
10	O
th	O
via	O
Naples	B-place
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
Ostende	B-place
London	B-place
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
to	O
their	O
neice	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
