TOKEN	NE
Weymouth	B-place
Febr	O
:	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Sir	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
this	O
Scrap	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
very	O
kind	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
delightful	O
Intellegence	O
it	O
contained	O
of	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
well	O
&	O
nursing	O
her	O
dr	O
:	O
precious	O
Infant	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
greatly	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
:	O
kind	O
Attention	O
in	O
writing	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
recd	O
.	O
my	O
Letter	O
of	O
Congratulations	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
again	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
scarcely	O
ask	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
pray	O
remember	O
to	O
seal	O
your	O
next	O
for	O
yr	O
:	O
last	O
came	O
unsealed	O
.	O
She	O
The	O
kindest	O
Wishes	O
attend	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
our	O
young	O
Folks	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
Yr	O
:	O
sincere	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obliged	O
PCremorne	B-pers
Dr	O
:	O
Julia	B-pers
's	O
Cough	O
has	O
ben	O
very	O
troublesome	O
;	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
fixed	O
upon	O
leaving	O
this	O
Place	O
next	O
wednesday	O
,	O
for	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
She	O
quite	O
longs	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
impatient	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
grieve	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
this	O
Fine	O
mild	O
Climate	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Tell	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
how	O
I	O
do	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Dr	O
:	O
Baby	O
.	O
--	O
pray	O
direct	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
Viscounteſs	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
recd	O
:	O
Janry	O
8	O
--	O
1787	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
:	I-pers
WEYMOUTH	B-place
