TOKEN	NE
16	O
th	O
Jan	O
:	O
1786	O
Why	O
do	O
I	O
not	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
?	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
received	O
my	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
yours	O
reached	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
immediatly	O
on	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
you	O
at	O
Courteen	B-place
hall	I-place
,	O
as	O
you	O
mentioned	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
immediatly	O
--	O
How	O
is	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
in	O
Health	O
and	O
spirits	O
?	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
yourself	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
?	O
this	O
severe	O
Weather	O
does	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
I	O
fear	O
--	O
yet	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
within	O
this	O
10	O
Days	O
some	O
very	O
mild	O
&	O
charming	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
for	O
hours	O
without	O
a	O
Hat	O
--	O
'you	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
expected	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
every	O
days	O
Post	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
'	O
or	O
you	O
would	O
before	O
now	O
have	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
convinced	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
concerns	O
you	O
,	O
interests	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
does	O
indeed	O
most	O
truly	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
then	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
ignorance	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
your	O
affairs	O
&	O
your	O
proceedings	O
--	O
Indeed	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
warmth	O
&	O
sincerity	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
,	O
never	O
will	O
these	O
sentiments	O
change	O
in	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
change	O
of	O
situation	O
&	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
circumstances	O
may	O
have	O
put	O
us	O
leſs	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
forget	O
me	O
--	O
They	O
write	O
from	O
France	B-place
so	O
seldom	O
&	O
then	O
so	O
uncomfortably	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
as	O
lief	O
not	O
hear	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
are	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Sister	O
likes	O
the	O
place	O
&	O
Society	O
extremely	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
,	O
uncomfortable	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
not	O
miserable	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
happy	O
--	O
ant	O
'	O
that	O
the	O
worst	O
disposition	O
one	O
can	O
be	O
in	O
?	O
I	O
feel	O
heavy	O
,	O
stupid	O
,	O
indiff	O
erent	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
never	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
room	O
or	O
open	O
my	O
lips	O
--	O
&	O
should	O
certainly	O
give	O
way	O
to	O
this	O
vis	O
inertia	O
(	O
this	O
word	O
is	O
only	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
)	O
if	O
my	O
Friends	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
certainly	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
Foley	O
House	O
is	O
my	O
home	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
asked	O
out	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
I	O
dine	O
there	O
--	O
sometimes	O
the	O
society	O
amuses	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
raised	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
are	O
only	O
false	O
ones	O
,	O
intoxication	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
wake	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
more	O
dejected	O
than	O
before	O
--	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
,	O
occupy	O
yourself	O
,	O
pursue	O
some	O
study	O
,	O
voila	O
le	O
mal	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
their	O
remedy	O
&	O
it	O
fails	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pursue	O
a	O
study	O
,	O
my	O
mind	O
&	O
pen	O
are	O
constantly	O
occupied	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
Busineſs	O
to	O
transact	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
write	O
leſs	O
than	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
letters	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
--	O
then	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
recreation	O
I	O
am	O
learning	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
Harpsicord	O
--	O
yet	O
all	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
do	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
few	O
People	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
I	O
see	O
sometimes	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
;	O
on	O
Lord	B-pers
Macartney	I-pers
s	O
return	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
honor	O
&	O
glory	O
of	O
having	O
spent	O
4	O
years	O
in	O
India	B-place
,	O
&	O
returning	O
home	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
servant	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
little	O
addition	O
to	O
his	O
income	O
&	O
that	O
only	O
from	O
having	O
saved	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
appointments	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
are	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
almost	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
comfort	O
from	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
like	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
&	O
melancholy	O
than	O
you	O
can	O
imagine	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Argylls	I-pers
are	O
at	O
Ealing	B-place
where	O
I	O
paſsed	O
some	O
Days	O
about	O
XmaſsChristmass	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
's	O
House	O
which	O
the	B-pers
D——	I-pers
has	O
bought	O
&	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pretty	O
place	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elisabeth	I-pers
is	O
recovering	O
very	O
fast	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
once	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
P.	B-pers
Augustus	I-pers
is	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
abroad	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
this	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
detained	O
above	O
3	O
Weeks	O
at	O
Dover	B-place
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wals	I-pers
:	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
dine	O
is	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nothin	O
g	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
summer	O
&	O
fear	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
favor	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
miſs	O
you	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
think	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
a	O
comfortable	O
letter	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
adieu	O
your	O
affec	O
:	O
CMG	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Courteen	B-place
hall	I-place
Northamton	B-place
