TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
June	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
——	I-pers
I	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
Letter	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
for	O
that	O
directed	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
which	O
came	O
too	O
Late	O
by	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
receive	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
Lisbon	B-place
just	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
Packet	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
miſs	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
really	O
was	O
so	O
mortifying	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
that	O
it	O
quite	O
disturbed	O
the	O
unexpected	O
Pleasure	O
his	O
Arrival	O
gave	O
us	O
;	O
She	O
saild	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Lisbon	B-place
the	O
very	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
had	O
they	O
but	O
deferr	O
'd	O
their	O
sailing	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Packet	O
informing	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
stopt	O
her	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
vext	O
I	O
feel	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
sad	O
Mortification	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
knows	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
one	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
Obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
us	O
above	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
ready	O
at	O
Lisbon	O
to	O
embark	O
when	O
the	O
Packet	O
saild	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
God	O
she	O
will	O
get	O
safe	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
feel	O
very	O
anxious	O
till	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
Arrival	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
packets	O
are	O
always	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
seeing	O
her	O
herself	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
satisfy	O
yourself	O
of	O
all	O
particulars	O
about	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
humble	O
request	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
for	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
prolong	O
my	O
stay	O
with	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
health	O
is	O
more	O
establish	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
an	O
Invalid	O
still	O
,	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
quit	O
him	O
without	O
great	O
anxiety	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
their	O
Goodneſs	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
Experience	O
)	O
will	O
consider	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
have	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
great	O
room	O
to	O
hope	O
hope	O
,	O
Time	O
and	O
Care	O
will	O
restore	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
strength	O
returns	O
slowly	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
of	O
late	O
made	O
so	O
much	O
Progreſs	O
as	O
when	O
first	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
recover	O
;	O
I	O
mean	O
particularly	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
Limbs	O
,	O
which	O
still	O
continue	O
to	O
Swell	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
can	O
take	O
Exercise	O
on	O
Horseback	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Circumstance	O
)	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
Equal	O
to	O
walking	O
,	O
without	O
uneasineſs	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
can	O
attempt	O
it	O
for	O
any	O
time	O
together	O
,	O
his	O
Pulse	O
is	O
rather	O
too	O
quick	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Disposition	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
bloated	O
and	O
heated	O
,	O
that	O
must	O
require	O
great	O
Attention	O
to	O
be	O
properly	O
managed	O
.	O
his	O
Appetite	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
rather	O
too	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sleeps	O
generally	O
well	O
,	O
his	O
Spirits	O
are	O
also	O
very	O
equal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
always	O
forming	O
hopes	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
compaſs	O
a	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
they	O
Physical	O
People	O
prescribe	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
be	O
well	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
or	O
Comfort	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
will	O
believe	O
,	O
nothing	O
should	O
detain	O
me	O
a	O
Moment	O
from	O
my	O
Duty	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
really	O
suffer	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
my	O
Absence	O
from	O
the	O
Happineſs	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
enjoy	O
in	O
performing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mind	O
Under	O
Anxiety	O
and	O
Uncertainty	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
Unfit	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
told	O
me	O
how	O
gracious	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
were	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
mention	O
of	O
our	O
situation	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Dear	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Duty	O
and	O
grateful	O
Thanks	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
dear	O
Princes	O
and	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
is	O
charged	O
with	O
Letters	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſses	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
delivering	O
before	O
this	O
reaches	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
write	O
by	O
this	O
same	O
Packet	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
charge	O
yourself	O
with	O
kind	O
remembrances	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
Every	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
some	O
fear	O
that	O
your	O
next	O
Letter	O
may	O
be	O
directed	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
I	O
of	O
course	O
shall	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
hers	O
are	O
all	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
stopt	O
at	O
Falmouth	B-place
now	O
She	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
meant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
repeat	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Health	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
so	O
kindly	O
enquire	O
after	O
,	O
is	O
vastly	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
fear	O
from	O
heat	O
,	O
for	O
contrary	O
to	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
Portugal	B-place
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
experienced	O
one	O
Day	O
so	O
hot	O
as	O
by	O
Mr-	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
Account	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
and	O
never	O
hardly	O
are	O
without	O
rain	O
,	O
and	O
Northerly	O
Winds	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
know	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
all	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
you	O
about	O
Caldas	B-place
,	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
only	O
add	O
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
kind	O
Anxieties	O
about	O
me	O
and	O
how	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
shall	O
be	O
,	O
Yrs	O
.	O
--	O
C.	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Caldes	B-place
July	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
——	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Duplicate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
Moment	O
finish	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
distreſsing	O
and	O
Mortifying	O
Intelligence	O
we	O
received	O
last	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
Mercury	O
Packet	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
carrying	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
;	O
they	O
are	O
thank	O
God	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
landed	O
at	O
Vigo	B-place
,	O
in	O
Spain	B-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
American	O
Privateer	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Chace	O
of	O
12	O
hours	O
,	O
2	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
sail	O
'd	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
.	O
Their	O
Horror	O
was	O
great	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
fallen	O
into	O
such	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
proved	O
very	O
humane	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
they	O
were	O
landed	O
at	O
Vigo	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
was	O
8	O
Days	O
coming	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
imagine	O
how	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
we	O
are	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
back	O
here	O
safe	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Particulars	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
Letter	O
that	O
goes	O
by	O
sea	O
,	O
but	O
least	O
any	O
Accident	O
or	O
delay	O
should	O
retard	O
the	O
Veſsel	O
that	O
carries	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
this	O
Duplicate	O
by	O
the	O
Land	O
Post	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
enclosed	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
Letter	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
to	O
say	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
were	O
all	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
inform	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
Intelligence	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
hurried	O
by	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
carries	O
this	O
to	O
Lisbon	B-place
to	O
save	O
the	O
Land	O
Post	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
my	O
Duty	O
and	O
Love	O
as	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
my	O
other	O
Letter	O
of	O
this	O
same	O
Date	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
from	O
Yr-	O
ever	O
Afftne-	O
CFinch	B-pers
Lord	B-pers
Winchelsea	I-pers
goes	O
on	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
wrote	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
slow	O
in	O
recovering	O
Strength	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
by	O
a	O
Packet	O
that	O
sail	O
'd	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
long	O
before	O
wrote	O
3	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
with	O
which	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
was	O
charged	O
.	O
