TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
Happy	O
If	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
Accomodate	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
Believe	O
It	O
quite	O
Impoſsible	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Place	O
;	O
My	O
Ticket	O
Is	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
--	O
the	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
only	O
wish	O
to	O
Hear	O
the	O
Meſsiah	O
;	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
next	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
to	O
go	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
s	O
Box	O
;	O
The	O
two	O
Tickets	O
He	O
gave	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
compleatly	O
filled	O
His	O
Places	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
Believe	O
every	O
Manager	O
;	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
Number	O
to	O
Oblige	O
their	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
only	O
10	O
;	O
If	O
I	O
dont	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
give	O
My	O
Ticket	O
Away	O
--	O
which	O
will	O
Serve	O
for	O
any	O
Other	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Abbey	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
My	O
Seat	O
;	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
s	O
Box	O
;	O
to	O
any	O
Friend	O
--	O
But	O
must	O
Inform	O
Him	O
If	O
I	O
dont	O
go	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Use	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
--	O
If	O
It	O
will	O
suit	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
sooner	O
;	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
It	O
Is	O
not	O
in	O
My	O
Power	O
to	O
fix	O
on	O
any	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
engaged	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
if	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Putney	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
but	O
have	O
Made	O
up	O
your	O
Franks	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
them	O
directed	O
the	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yrs	O
.	O
Most	O
Affecly	O
--	O
Frances	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Wednesday	O
