TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deserve	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
you	O
have	O
shewn	O
me	O
in	O
suffering	O
your	O
obliging	O
Letter	O
to	O
have	O
remained	O
so	O
long	O
unanswered	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
are	O
both	O
infinitely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Congratulations	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
anxious	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
friends	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prospect	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
London	B-place
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
be	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
house	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
that	O
being	O
beyond	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
my	O
Finances	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
The	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
my	O
connexion	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
are	O
somewhat	O
singular	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
Child	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
,	O
&	O
beloved	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
degree	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
his	O
consent	O
to	O
our	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
settled	O
his	O
estate	O
upon	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
given	O
us	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
,	O
I	O
beleive	O
,	O
will	O
give	O
;	O
so	O
much	O
stronger	O
is	O
his	O
Love	O
for	O
his	O
Guineas	O
then	O
his	O
daughter	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
entre	O
nous	O
.	O
My	O
little	O
woman	O
however	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
all	O
Goodneſs	O
,	O
does	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
strange	O
r	O
behaviour	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
.	O
Your	O
very	O
worthy	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
left	O
Windsor	B-place
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
:	O
She	O
honoured	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
visit	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
:	O
She	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
loved	O
you	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
longer	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
herself	O
or	O
to	O
indite	O
to	O
them	O
Letters	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
great	O
comfort	O
in	O
her	O
young	O
Companion	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
who	O
is	O
grown	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Girl	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
often	O
enquires	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
She	O
begins	O
to	O
find	O
herself	O
very	O
much	O
at	O
her	O
ease	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
she	O
is	O
upon	O
very	O
distant	O
terms	O
with	O
poor	O
Madam	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
whose	O
constant	O
state	O
of	O
Ill	O
health	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
sower	O
her	O
temper	O
:	O
the	O
good	O
old	O
Lady	O
has	O
however	O
a	O
good	O
heart	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
your	O
recollection	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Matters	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
house	O
pretty	O
much	O
as	O
usual	O
:	O
The	O
Sons	O
,	O
let	O
Papa	O
do	O
all	O
he	O
can	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
young	O
men	O
:	O
The	O
second	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
quite	O
drawn	O
into	O
the	O
Vortex	O
of	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
&	O
follows	O
hard	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
his	O
older	O
Brother	O
:	O
The	O
third	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
:	O
the	O
fourth	O
is	O
now	O
travelling	O
about	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
Geneva	B-place
.	O
Your	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Ferns	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
brought	O
upon	O
the	O
English	O
Bench	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
disagreement	O
between	O
the	O
Minister	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Minister	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
has	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
the	O
exchange	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
sustained	O
a	O
heavy	O
loſs	O
in	O
our	O
Church	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
our	O
worthy	O
Dean	O
,	O
but	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
has	O
appointed	O
a	O
Succesſor	O
with	O
whom	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
highly	O
pleased	O
Dr.	B-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
.	O
We	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
gay	O
here	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
We	O
are	O
certainly	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Installation	O
.	O
Three	O
Rooms	O
are	O
already	O
fitted	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
a	O
style	O
truly	O
Royal	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
great	O
alterations	O
are	O
making	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Georges	O
Chapel	O
,	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
which	O
will	O
amount	O
to	O
7,000	O
£	O
o	O
.	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Lover	O
of	O
the	O
Arts	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
great	O
works	O
going	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Cicerone	O
:	O
It	O
will	O
give	O
equal	O
pleasure	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
to	O
attend	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
if	O
she	O
can	O
pr	O
ev	O
ail	O
upon	O
herself	O
to	O
give	O
one	O
look	O
more	O
upon	O
old	O
Windsors	O
Towers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
somewhat	O
anxious	O
about	O
the	O
fate	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
recollect	O
very	O
imperfectly	O
the	O
direction	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
:	O
If	O
the	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
engages	O
all	O
your	O
attention	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
perha	O
ps	O
will	O
ha	O
ve	O
the	O
go	O
odneſs	O
to	O
favour	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
,	O
so	O
on	O
after	O
he	O
receives	O
this	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
Beleive	O
me	O
Dear	O
madam	O
your	O
most	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servt-	O
J	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
Jan	O
:	O
28	O
.	O
1788	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
la	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Revd	B-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Janry	O
28-	O
1788	O
