TOKEN	NE
Wednesday	O
22	O
d	O
June	O
1785	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
As	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
send	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
Affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
say	O
how	O
very	O
happy	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
us	O
by	O
your	O
intended	O
visit	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
fix	O
'd	O
your	O
time	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
us	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
will	O
rejoice	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
that	O
his	O
dear	O
Child	O
is	O
at	O
last	O
made	O
happy	O
for	O
life	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
my	O
sincere	O
friend	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
&	O
whose	O
friendship	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
deserve	O
will	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
every	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
goes	O
into	O
Derbyshire	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
will	O
meet	O
with	O
relations	O
who	O
must	O
&	O
will	O
love	O
her	O
.	O
may	O
every	O
bleſsing	O
&	O
happineſs	O
that	O
this	O
world	O
affords	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
sincere	O
wish	O
of	O
your	O
ever	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
turn	O
over	O
My	O
Mother	O
&	O
Myself	O
are	O
extremely	O
anxious	O
to	O
have	O
our	O
Dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
health	O
,	O
she	O
assured	O
us	O
last	O
night	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
looks	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
talks	O
of	O
finishing	O
their	O
affairs	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
wish	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
really	O
will	O
set	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
thinking	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
proper	O
)	O
that	O
perhaps	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
effect	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
convinc	O
'd	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
goes	O
not	O
on	O
harraſsing	O
her	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
it	O
nothing	O
else	O
)	O
it	O
will	O
very	O
materially	O
injure	O
her	O
health	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
excuse	O
the	O
liberty	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
very	O
sincerely	O
love	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
&	O
amiable	O
miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
&	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
being	O
very	O
anxious	O
.	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
engaged	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Sydenham	B-place
or	O
should	O
otherwise	O
have	O
accepted	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
with	O
pleasure	O
.	O
