TOKEN	NE
Monday	O
7	O
th	O
July	O
.	O
1783	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
about	O
--	O
are	O
you	O
dead	O
?	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
?	O
has	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
directd	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
.	O
fallen	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
never	O
reached	O
yours	O
?	O
I	O
wrote	O
yesterday	O
sev'Night	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
answer	O
have	O
I	O
yet	O
received	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
smallest	O
intimation	O
of	O
your	O
existence	O
--	O
Before	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
&	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
embracing	O
you	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
informed	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
bought	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Eſsex	B-place
and	O
has	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Cows	O
sheep	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
Courteen	O
hall	O
to	O
stock	O
the	O
grounds	O
on	O
this	O
new	O
purchase	O
--	O
is	O
it	O
there	O
they	O
mean	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
summer	O
?	O
--	O
and	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
?	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
admirable	O
sheme	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
suit	O
me	O
amazingly	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
tho	O
'	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
alive	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
from	O
yourself	O
--	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
told	O
something	O
of	O
your	O
intentions	O
--	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
a	O
Border	O
,	O
desiring	O
you	O
buy	O
me	O
17	O
Yds	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Hodgkins	O
immediatly	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
another	O
commiſsion	O
--	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
execute	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
as	O
ill	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
my	O
pain	O
returned	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
God	O
's	O
will	O
be	O
done	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
born	O
to	O
suffer	O
.	O
what	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Storm	O
of	O
Thunder	O
we	O
had	O
on	O
Wednesdy	O
I	O
was	O
thoroughly	O
terrified	O
--	O
it	O
burst	O
in	O
our	O
shrubbery	O
think	O
how	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
Shook	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
tremendous	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
Brother	O
has	O
left	O
us	O
for	O
sometime	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
h	O
yesterday	O
,	O
to	O
Weston	B-place
--	O
we	O
feel	O
quite	O
melancholy	O
&	O
want	O
you	O
of	O
all	O
things	O
--	O
on	O
Saturday	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
and	O
availed	O
ourselves	O
of	O
of	O
the	O
permiſsion	O
Mr	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
,	O
in	O
paſsing	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
grounds	O
I	O
inquired	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
expected	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
new	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
--	O
The	O
weather	O
is	O
heavenly	O
--	O
the	O
clouds	O
have	O
every	O
day	O
threatened	O
an	O
alteration	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Barometer	O
aſsures	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
continuance	O
of	O
rain	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
meantime	O
it	O
is	O
fine	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
we	O
enjoy	O
ourselves	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
this	O
Evening	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Harriett	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
Many	O
visits	O
hanging	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
oppreſsed	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
adieu	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
negative	O
way	O
--	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
immediatly	O
&	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jekyll	I-pers
N	O
o	O
27	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
