TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
Febry-	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
last	O
a	O
laconic	O
reply	O
.	O
In	O
its	O
being	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
conceive	O
,	O
consisted	O
its	O
principal	O
merit	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
both	O
You	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
saved	O
much	O
trouble	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
reading	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
satisfied	O
without	O
my	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
particular	O
account	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
If	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
obey	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
shocked	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
lead	O
a	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
regular	O
stupidity	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
breakfasted	O
,	O
I	O
walk	O
for	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
Committee	O
leads	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
remain	O
till	O
it	O
rises	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Young	B-pers
Roscius	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
been	O
at	O
Concert	O
,	O
Opera	O
,	O
or	O
Ball	O
.	O
At	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
in	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
&	O
between	O
that	O
hour	O
&	O
Twelve	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
stretched	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
extract	O
myself	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Could	O
the	O
antient	O
Virgin	O
who	O
prepares	O
my	O
sitting	O
Room	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
rise	O
earlier	O
than	O
She	O
does	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
grows	O
daily	O
more	O
intolerable	O
.	O
Good	O
breeding	O
is	O
entirely	O
forgotten	O
,	O
&	O
rudeneſs	O
reigns	O
triumphant	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
looks	O
old	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
hoped	O
all	O
my	O
family	O
were	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
that	O
teasing	O
Question	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
never	O
present	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
yours	O
to	O
Me	O
?	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
occupied	O
with	O
his	O
Ministers	O
in	O
deep	O
,	O
&	O
secret	O
consultation	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
his	O
appearance	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
Addreſs	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
looked	O
thin	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
walked	O
,	O
bent	O
forward	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
enjoyed	O
the	O
Fête	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
very	O
much	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
subject	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
from	O
personal	O
knowledge	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
amongst	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
Invited	O
.	O
Dont	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
any	O
mortification	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
supposed	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
thought	O
of	O
,	O
never	O
having	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
been	O
honoured	O
by	O
admiſsion	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
parties	O
.	O
All	O
my	O
great	O
connexions	O
,	O
Atholls	O
,	O
The	B-pers
LadCounteſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
seen	O
the	O
Counteſs	O
once	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
engaged	O
when	O
invited	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
thing	O
occurred	O
when	O
the	O
Portland	O
Place	O
Mansfield	O
's	O
wished	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
disappointed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
graciously	O
promised	O
them	O
to	O
eat	O
their	O
Mutton	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
an	O
appetite	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
is	O
doubtful	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expect	O
on	O
it	O
to	O
receive	O
accounts	O
of	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
being	O
sold	O
,	O
or	O
rejected	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Public	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
quite	O
right	O
in	O
saying	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
whether	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
allow	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
as	O
fortunate	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
very	O
much	O
doubt	O
.	O
I	O
pray	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
not	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
speak	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
what	O
You	O
have	O
to	O
expect	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
Louisa	B-pers
may	O
get	O
quit	O
of	O
her	O
Cold	O
,	O
without	O
delay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
may	O
not	O
break	O
his	O
Neck	O
after	O
the	O
Harriers	O
,	O
not	O
feeling	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
humour	O
to	O
write	O
Epistles	O
of	O
Condolence	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
that	O
Miſs	O
may	O
get	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
take	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
A	O
Forest	O
near	O
Alloa	B-place
!	O
!	O
!	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Clock	O
has	O
struck	O
Eleven	O
.	O
Good	O
Night	O
.	O
Best	O
Love	O
to	O
all	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Bells	O
are	O
of	O
modern	O
invention	O
Sozeman	O
Micah	O
ye	O
7	O
th	O
of	O
the	O
12	O
Minor	O
or	O
leſser	O
Prophets	O
some	O
esteem	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
author	O
of	O
Is	O
iah	O
aia	O
h	O
London	B-place
,	O
First	O
March	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
