TOKEN	NE
Miſs	O
tells	O
me	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
impertinent	O
&	O
desires	O
you	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
tell	O
her	O
for	O
answer	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
--	O
Your	O
Picture	O
is	O
finished	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
desired	O
the	O
bearer	O
of	O
it	O
Mr-	B-pers
Leslie	I-pers
(	O
Son	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Leven	I-pers
)	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
person	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
be	O
civil	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
likeneſs	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
I	O
have	O
&	O
so	O
you	O
must	O
e'en	O
content	O
yourself	O
and	O
do	O
as	O
the	O
Galloway	B-place
Wife	O
did	O
Adieu	O
--	O
Alexander	B-pers
March	O
3	O
d	O
1779	O
