TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Canterbury	B-place
Kent	O
Feby	O
9	O
th	O
1815	O
My	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
Having	O
been	O
favourd	O
two	O
days	O
since	O
by	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
informing	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
happy	O
Event	O
of	O
her	O
marriage	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
delay	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
her	O
dear	O
Parents	O
my	O
warm	O
congratulations	O
&	O
expreſs	O
my	O
wishes	O
for	O
the	O
permanent	O
happineſs	O
of	O
our	O
very	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
be	O
aſsured	O
I	O
feelingly	O
participate	O
in	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
so	O
sensible	O
of	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
Union	O
which	O
appears	O
to	O
anticipate	O
all	O
you	O
can	O
desire	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
enjoy	O
experience	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasures	O
I	O
could	O
enjoy	O
that	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
witneſs	O
of	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
inestimably	O
dear	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
remarkably	O
well	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
consider	O
as	O
the	O
result	O
of	O
a	O
mind	O
at	O
ease	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
now	O
call	O
upon	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
knowing	O
how	O
inceſsantly	O
you	O
are	O
engaged	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
quarrel	O
with	O
your	O
old	O
best	O
&	O
dearest	O
friends	O
Pen	O
&	O
Ink	O
perhaps	O
when	O
you	O
must	O
neceſsarily	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
you	O
may	O
insensibly	O
be	O
drawn	O
malgré	O
vous	O
into	O
a	O
close	O
correspondence	O
--	O
this	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
two	O
Sisters	O
who	O
wrote	O
every	O
other	O
day	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
&	O
a	O
Mother	O
&	O
Daughter	O
who	O
wrote	O
every	O
day	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roycroft	I-pers
Roycroft	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufreere	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
do	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
or	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
remember	O
with	O
pleasure	O
the	O
latter	O
with	O
lively	O
gratitude	O
should	O
occasion	O
offer	O
aſsure	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
far	O
advanced	O
in	O
years	O
