TOKEN	NE
If	O
I	O
were	O
well	O
enough	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
directly	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
yr	O
:	O
sweet	O
little	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
write	O
this	O
tonight	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
early	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
long	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
She	O
paſses	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
Vegitable	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
that	O
you	O
would	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
?	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
forbid	O
Brocoli	O
or	O
you	O
sd	O
:	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
aſsist	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
Dr	O
:	O
Child	O
do	O
indulge	O
me	O
by	O
letting	O
me	O
know	O
yrs	O
:	O
ever	O
PC	B-pers
Wednesday	O
Night	O
.	O
24	O
th	O
April	O
1788	O
