TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
August	O
13	O
th	O
:	O
1769	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
obey	O
'd	O
every	O
Command	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
with	O
Pleasure	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
late	O
years	O
wrote	O
so	O
little	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
quite	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
whenever	O
I	O
attempt	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
retired	O
situation	O
I	O
now	O
am	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
find	O
Subjects	O
the	O
least	O
entertaining	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
:	O
but	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
desire	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
my	O
stupidity	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tollerable	O
good	O
Journey	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
arrived	O
safe	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
all	O
my	O
Family	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
prodigious	O
great	O
Strangers	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
entertain	O
'd	O
some	O
hopes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
troubled	O
with	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
staid	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
proposed	O
.	O
We	O
find	O
this	O
Country	O
extreamly	O
cold	O
after	O
leaving	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
&	O
especially	O
Sarah	B-pers
(	I-pers
‘	I-pers
Sally	I-pers
’	I-pers
)	I-pers
s	O
warm	O
Rooms	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
got	O
a	O
severe	O
Cold	O
by	O
the	O
Change	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lawton	I-pers
often	O
talks	O
of	O
Sally	B-pers
,	O
her	O
little	O
Heart	O
is	O
warm	O
with	O
Gratitude	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
notice	O
you	O
took	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
Thanks	O
for	O
your	O
Civilities	O
.	O
Our	O
little	O
Habitation	O
commands	O
a	O
sweet	O
Prospect	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
Graſs	O
Plott	O
behind	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
a	O
pretty	O
Rivulet	O
,	O
Woods	O
,	O
Cottages	O
,	O
Sheep	O
,	O
Cows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
wishing	O
(	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
Scene	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
here	O
,	O
with	O
your	O
Camera	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
your	O
Pencil	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
not	O
diſagreeable	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
little	O
wild	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
fond	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
grow	O
tired	O
of	O
draw	O
in	O
g	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
Amusement	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
will	O
arrive	O
at	O
Perfection	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
persevere	O
.	O
“	O
One	O
thing	O
at	O
once	O
the	O
famed	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
profeſs	O
t	O
'd	O
,	O
‘	O
Was	O
all	O
his	O
Wisdom	O
e'er	O
presumed	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
‘	O
And	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
an	O
Artist	O
't	O
is	O
confeſs	O
'd	O
‘	O
Among	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
once	O
does	O
two	O
.	O
”	O
Source	O
not	O
yet	O
traced	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
attempt	O
an	O
hundred	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
you	O
scorn	O
the	O
beaten	O
Track	O
prescribed	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
Sex	O
,	O
&	O
wou	O
'd	O
soar	O
to	O
the	O
Skyes	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
Patience	O
my	O
dear	O
De	B-pers
Witt	I-pers
is	O
all	O
you	O
want	O
.	O
“	O
You	O
By	O
slow	O
degrees	O
the	O
liberal	O
Arts	O
were	O
won	O
,	O
&	O
Hercules	O
grew	O
Strong	O
.	O
”	O
John	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
‘	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Preserving	O
Health	O
’	O
(	O
1744	O
)	O
,	O
Bk	O
II	O
,	O
ll.474-5	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
so	O
young	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
knowledge	O
of	O
every	O
useful	O
Science	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
most	O
Women	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
read	O
English	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
always	O
give	O
me	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
Improvements	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
upon	O
so	O
short	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
higher	O
esteem	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
obedient	O
&	O
obliged	O
humble	O
Servt	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Please	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
Northampton	B-place
