TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
,	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Octr-	O
1789	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
begin	O
this	O
Letter	O
with	O
a	O
Proverb	O
,	O
but	O
knowing	O
the	O
Indigo	O
tint	O
of	O
your	O
disposition	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
fearfull	O
of	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
Chesterfield	B-pers
for	O
a	O
rebuke	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
much	O
satisfied	O
with	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Three	O
points	O
of	O
Admiration	O
are	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
feelings	O
at	O
so	O
uncommon	O
a	O
declaration	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
economy	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
made	O
three	O
dozen	O
.	O
I	O
proceed	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
Questions	O
--	O
not	O
from	O
the	O
dread	O
of	O
enraging	O
You	O
,	O
for	O
thank	O
God	O
your	O
tongue	O
can	O
not	O
reach	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
lazineſs	O
of	O
your	O
fingers	O
will	O
not	O
allow	O
You	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
a	O
scold	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
having	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
reading	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
ever	O
be	O
tempted	O
to	O
epistolize	O
me	O
in	O
future	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
(	O
since	O
you	O
dislike	O
imprimis	O
)	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
is	O
47	O
miles	O
from	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
In	O
the	O
second	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
sold	O
my	O
House	O
there	O
.	O
and	O
In	O
the	O
third	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
pay	O
£	O
5100	O
for	O
my	O
purchase	O
the	O
eleventh	O
day	O
of	O
next	O
November	O
,	O
besides	O
6	O
or	O
700	O
which	O
finishing	O
the	O
house	O
will	O
cost	O
Me	O
.	O
And	O
lastly	O
,	O
Harriot	B-pers
no	O
longer	O
lives	O
with	O
Me	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
Leaving	O
Edinr-	B-place
furnished	O
a	O
good	O
reason	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
separation	O
which	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
World	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
&	O
neither	O
party	O
are	O
reflected	O
on	O
for	O
parting	O
.	O
She	O
likes	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
We	O
like	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
These	O
subjects	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
fully	O
written	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
advise	O
any	O
man	O
to	O
quarter	O
his	O
Sister	O
on	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
agree	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
situation	O
is	O
most	O
disagreable	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
part	O
with	O
a	O
Wife	O
against	O
a	O
Sister	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
a	O
Sister	O
against	O
a	O
Wife	O
.	O
Harriot	B-pers
now	O
occupies	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
I	O
lived	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Bachelor	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
had	O
difficult	O
cards	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
very	O
sensible	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
blame	O
of	O
disunion	O
originated	O
,	O
&	O
heartily	O
rejoiced	O
when	O
the	O
disjunction	O
took	O
place	O
.	O
This	O
history	O
is	O
between	O
ourselves	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
politics	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
quiet	O
.	O
The	O
diſsolution	O
of	O
Parliament	O
will	O
occasion	O
the	O
Horns	O
of	O
the	O
Snail	O
to	O
creep	O
out	O
.	O
Happy	O
&	O
contented	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
flatter	O
my	O
Ambition	O
with	O
much	O
hopes	O
of	O
succeſs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
probability	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
appearing	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
with	O
credit	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
&	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
is	O
pretty	O
strong	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
fail	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Election	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
start	O
at	O
every	O
single	O
Election	O
afterwards	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
entitled	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
either	O
from	O
my	O
Rank	O
in	O
the	O
Peerage	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Where	O
Sixteen	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
chosen	O
,	O
accident	O
may	O
throw	O
the	O
choice	O
on	O
Me	O
,	O
but	O
vain	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
wished	O
to	O
start	O
singly	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
legacy	O
has	O
been	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Executor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cosgrave	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
bequests	O
.	O
The	O
Will	O
was	O
dated	O
23	O
rd	O
.	O
March	O
1780	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
)	O
it	O
begins	O
with	O
directions	O
for	O
her	O
Funeral	O
.	O
The	O
bequests	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
poor	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Tewin	I-place
£25	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Grandson	O
Fras-	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
£200	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Neice	O
Valentine	B-pers
Malyn	I-pers
£200	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Neice	O
Frances	B-pers
Malyn	I-pers
£200	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Revd-	B-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
(	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
)	O
£100	O
Irish	O
;	O
To	O
her	O
God	O
daughter	O
Frances	B-pers
Sabine	I-pers
£100	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Sabine	I-pers
£100	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Singleton	I-pers
of	O
Grosvenor	O
Street	O
(	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
)	O
£150	O
,	O
3	O
pr	O
Cent	O
.	O
Consols	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richd-	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
Anne	B-pers
(	O
formerly	O
her	O
Maid	O
)	O
his	O
daughter	O
Margery	B-pers
(	O
who	O
allways	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
)	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
Richard	B-pers
£50	O
each	O
3	O
pr	O
Cent	O
.	O
Consol	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
said	O
Margery	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
the	O
further	O
Sum	O
of	O
£1000	O
Irish	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Cheshyre	I-pers
(	O
an	O
old	O
neighbour	O
)	O
£100	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
Esqr-	I-pers
£100	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
Two	O
small	O
Salvers	O
&	O
½	O
a	O
dozen	O
Silver	O
Table	O
Spoons	O
.	O
(	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
died	O
before	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
)	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Colly	I-pers
,	O
her	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
£100	O
,	O
3	O
pr	O
C	O
Consols	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
annuity	O
of	O
£30	O
per	O
for	O
life	O
,	O
all	O
her	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
some	O
furniture	O
,	O
half	O
the	O
household	O
Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
bread	O
basket	O
&	O
three	O
Table	O
Spoons	O
.	O
To	O
Margery	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Household	O
Linnen	O
,	O
some	O
furniture	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
Silver	O
bread	O
basket	O
&	O
three	O
silver	O
Table	O
Spoons	O
.	O
To	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pilgrim	I-pers
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
furniture	O
&	O
Utensils	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
back	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
&	O
Laundry	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
Annuity	O
of	O
£20	O
for	O
life	O
.	O
To	O
Sarah	B-pers
Perrot	I-pers
the	O
House	O
Maid	O
,	O
some	O
furniture	O
&	O
£20	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
the	O
Dairy	O
Maid	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
Calves	O
&	O
Poultry	O
,	O
&	O
everything	O
in	O
the	O
Dairy	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
mentioned	O
Maid	O
Servts-	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
&	O
furniture	O
in	O
the	O
Garrets	O
.	O
To	O
James	B-pers
Reilly	I-pers
&	O
Phillip	B-pers
Reilly	I-pers
,	O
Gardeners	O
,	O
£30	O
a	O
peice	O
&	O
to	O
each	O
a	O
Saddle	O
horse	O
.	O
To	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Calver	I-pers
,	O
postilion	O
,	O
a	O
One	O
horse	O
Chaise	O
,	O
Harneſs	O
&	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Will	B-pers
Calver	I-pers
&	O
John	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
the	O
errand	O
Boy	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
each	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
day	O
labourers	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
hogs	O
,	O
pigs	O
,	O
the	O
Aſs	O
&	O
foal	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
equally	O
divided	O
.	O
To	O
six	O
poor	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
three	O
Guineas	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
remainder	O
of	O
her	O
fortune	O
is	O
bequeathed	O
by	O
the	O
Will	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cosgrave	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
likewise	O
named	O
Sole	O
Executor	O
--	O
By	O
a	O
Codicil	O
,	O
dated	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Octr-	O
1784	O
,	O
She	O
confirms	O
her	O
Will	O
dated	O
in	O
March	O
1780	O
,	O
except	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
alterations	O
&	O
additions	O
following	O
,	O
To	O
her	O
Cousin	O
John	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
Caversham	B-place
near	O
Reading	B-place
,	O
Berks	B-place
,	O
£100	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Eldest	O
Son	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Diamond	O
Watch	O
,	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
&	O
Diamond	O
Equipage	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Eldest	O
Daughter	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Case	O
with	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
&	O
forks	O
&	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
.	O
In	O
case	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
second	O
Son	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
an	O
Annuity	O
of	O
£20	O
(	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
died	O
before	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
)	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Colly	I-pers
over	O
&	O
above	O
what	O
is	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Will	O
,	O
£20	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
&	O
every	O
other	O
Servant	O
living	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
decease	O
,	O
£10	O
each	O
.	O
To	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Reilly	I-pers
nephew	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Colly	I-pers
,	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
.	O
To	O
Richd-	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
&	O
Anne	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
over	O
&	O
above	O
what	O
is	O
given	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Will	O
,	O
£20	O
each	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Son	O
Richd-	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
£100	O
,	O
over	O
&	O
above	O
what	O
is	O
given	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Will	O
.	O
To	O
Richd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
&	O
Anne	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
longest	O
liver	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
an	O
annuity	O
of	O
Forty	O
Pounds	O
during	O
their	O
lives	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
her	O
legacies	O
except	O
to	O
some	O
Servants	O
,	O
who	O
from	O
having	O
quitted	O
her	O
family	O
,	O
lost	O
their	O
right	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cosgrove	I-pers
informs	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
funds	O
consisted	O
of	O
£8118	O
..	O
7	O
..	O
6	O
Irish	O
Mortgage	O
(	O
£2000	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
disputed	O
)	O
&	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
funds	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
beleive	O
not	O
to	O
exceed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
case	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
very	O
great	O
gainer	O
by	O
the	O
Executry	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
perceive	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
were	O
never	O
once	O
thought	O
of	O
.	O
Indeed	O
their	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
far	O
too	O
magnificent	O
to	O
please	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
married	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Jointure	O
settled	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
law	O
,	O
became	O
entitled	O
to	O
one	O
third	O
of	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
gave	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
.	O
So	O
scrupulous	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
retaining	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
property	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
his	O
own	O
receipt	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
£300	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Earrings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
accept	O
on	O
any	O
other	O
terms	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
Jewells	O
,	O
You	O
allude	O
to	O
,	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
remember	O
right	O
,	O
they	O
composed	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Solitaire	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
an	O
ornament	O
for	O
the	O
hair	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
for	O
£50	O
or	O
£60	O
.	O
The	O
anecdote	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
before	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
probably	O
fact	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
perhaps	O
exaggerated	O
.	O
The	O
Baron	O
was	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
C——n	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
;	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
I	O
consider	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
least	O
half	O
Mad	O
.	O
He	O
very	O
poſsibly	O
might	O
have	O
behaved	O
rudely	O
to	O
the	O
Baron	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
the	O
holding	O
the	O
stirrup	O
was	O
very	O
accidental	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
it	O
happened	O
.	O
Military	O
people	O
are	O
sometimes	O
severe	O
,	O
on	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
fortunate	O
than	O
themselves	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
unnecessarily	O
partial	O
to	O
the	O
noble	O
Baron	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
credit	O
for	O
not	O
wishing	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
relation	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
s	O
acquaintance	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
probable	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
perfect	O
recovery	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
our	O
families	O
may	O
meet	O
.	O
If	O
ever	O
we	O
do	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
we	O
shall	O
look	O
prim	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
by	O
Lavater	B-pers
s	O
rules	O
to	O
discover	O
,	O
whether	O
we	O
are	O
pickpockets	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Having	O
tired	O
of	O
so	O
silly	O
an	O
occupation	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
give	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
natural	O
corruption	O
of	O
our	O
Nature	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
meeting	O
will	O
certainly	O
resemble	O
the	O
march	O
of	O
a	O
Troop	O
of	O
Geese	O
from	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
.	O
Much	O
cackling	O
,	O
much	O
gabbling	O
,	O
all	O
wishing	O
to	O
ask	O
questions	O
&	O
none	O
waiting	O
for	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
This	O
description	O
is	O
not	O
intended	O
to	O
include	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
I	O
trust	O
to	O
his	O
rationality	O
for	O
bringing	O
us	O
back	O
to	O
a	O
proper	O
behaviour	O
.	O
Your	O
Louisa	B-pers
too	O
,	O
will	O
out-talk	O
my	O
Mary	B-pers
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
is	O
this	O
day	O
three	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
&	O
exactly	O
measures	O
three	O
feet	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
see	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
heighth	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
the	O
poor	O
fellow	O
to	O
be	O
suspended	O
in	O
the	O
Air	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
perfectly	O
well	O
account	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
waiting	O
from	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
ending	O
the	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
Septr-	O
,	O
without	O
poſseſsing	O
any	O
strong	O
degree	O
of	O
the	O
spirit	O
of	O
divination	O
I	O
have	O
composed	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
Ink	O
,	O
&	O
find	O
the	O
whole	O
idea	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poetical	O
fiction	O
,	O
to	O
cover	O
,	O
what	O
in	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
call	O
lazineſs	O
&	O
indifference	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
may	O
endeavour	O
to	O
frame	O
another	O
apology	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
will	O
please	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
efforts	O
of	O
your	O
ingenuity	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
Parkgate	B-place
,	O
nor	O
n	O
ever	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
It	O
looks	O
towards	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
affectionate	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
last	O
half	O
line	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
Hannah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
ish	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
affectionate	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
)	O
.	O
If	O
You	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
Country	O
&	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
ruined	O
Castles	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
show	O
you	O
many	O
.	O
Castles	O
in	O
ruins	O
,	O
are	O
likewise	O
no	O
rarity	O
,	O
&	O
Castles	O
in	O
the	O
Air	O
,	O
thrive	O
at	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
high	O
perfection	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
most	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
Grand	O
Master	O
Mason	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
difficult	O
to	O
discover	O
proper	O
foundations	O
for	O
those	O
I	O
build	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
perfectly	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
author	O
of	O
Candide	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
(	O
this	O
to	O
shew	O
my	O
reading	O
)	O
that	O
,	O
whatever	O
is	O
,	O
is	O
right	O
.	O
Your	O
insense	O
was	O
not	O
incense	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
explanation	O
was	O
a	O
direct	O
attack	O
on	O
my	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
pun	O
on	O
the	O
word	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
cost	O
you	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
treble	O
Letter	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
grudge	O
to	O
pay	O
double	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
reading	O
the	B-pers
old	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
's	O
Will	O
at	O
D	O
rs	O
.	O
Commons	O
would	O
have	O
cost	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
myself	O
sincerely	O
attached	O
to	O
You	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Brat	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
an	O
additional	O
Brat	O
to	O
my	O
number	O
next	O
Month	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Your	O
Uncle	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Son	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
Noodle	O
;	O
perhaps	O
he	O
remains	O
so	O
still	O
.	O
The	O
Pechells	O
returned	O
to	O
England	B-place
last	O
Spring	O
,	O
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
has	O
(	O
since	O
her	O
arrival	O
)	O
produced	O
a	O
Son	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
thank	O
the	O
Rain	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
inceſsant	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
Epistle	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
impossibility	O
of	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
could	O
ever	O
have	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
scribble	O
over	O
two	O
sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Tiviot	O
is	O
full	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
banks	O
&	O
my	O
Cascade	O
is	O
tumbling	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
torrent	O
of	O
froth	O
&	O
smoak	O
.	O
These	O
appearances	O
are	O
very	O
beautifull	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Oats	O
are	O
spoiling	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
field	O
cut	O
down	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
past	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
sheaves	O
into	O
the	O
stack	O
yard	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
fine	O
encouragement	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
