TOKEN	NE
11	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1801	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
When	O
you	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
frank	O
your	O
Letters	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
write	O
their	O
Addreſses	O
in	O
a	O
legible	O
character	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Bliſset	I-pers
,	I-pers
Bleſset	I-pers
,	I-pers
or	I-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
,	O
may	O
perhaps	O
receive	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
imitate	O
your	O
Chinese	O
Characters	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
bad	O
pen	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
making	O
the	O
imitation	O
more	O
correct	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
our	O
beloved	O
King	B-pers
,	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
complaint	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Brain	O
Fever	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
mention	O
.	O
The	O
report	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
to	O
day	O
is	O
“	O
His	B-pers
“	I-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Fever	O
,	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
abated	O
“	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
fairest	O
prospect	O
of	O
his	O
“	O
speedy	O
recovery	O
”	O
--	O
For	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
God	O
.	O
All	O
my	O
hopes	O
&	O
prospects	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
obnubilated	O
.	O
Whenever	O
they	O
begin	O
to	O
clarify	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
my	O
Plans	O
or	O
motions	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
So	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
Brat	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
I	O
saw	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
crawling	O
along	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
.	O
His	O
Lady	O
drove	O
down	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
ago	O
,	O
The	O
Greville	O
Mansfield	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
asked	O
to	O
an	O
At	O
Home	O
at	O
the	O
Portland	O
Place	O
Counteſs	O
es	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
like	O
these	O
unsubstantial	O
Invitations	O
--	O
London	B-place
,	O
Seventh	O
March	O
1801	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
