TOKEN	NE
My	O
drst	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
send	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
S	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
this	O
M	O
.	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
kind	O
request	O
tho	O
I	O
'm	O
afraid	O
She	O
extorted	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
this	O
time	O
for	O
our	O
very	O
great	O
Leſsons	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
a	O
sad	O
incumbrenceincumbrance	O
on	O
me	O
if	O
deferred	O
till	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
back	O
from	O
Wimbledon	B-place
till	O
4	O
o'clock	O
--	O
will	O
Mondey	O
suit	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Botanick	O
Garden	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
long	O
Leſson	O
deys	O
&	O
my	O
Task	O
of	O
Drawing	O
shd	O
.	O
come	O
in	O
too	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
propose	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
M	O
.	O
suits	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
you	O
¼	O
before	O
11.	O
for	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
how	O
soon	O
an	O
hour	O
slips	O
away	O
there	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
M.Monday	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
so	O
fully	O
determined	O
either	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
or	O
to	O
be	O
back	O
to	O
our	O
time	O
&	O
heard	O
it	O
strike	O
12	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
actually	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Green	O
houses	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
a	O
mom̄ent	O
for	O
my	O
little	O
dr	O
.	O
Puſs	O
&	O
am	O
only	O
sorry	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
quite	O
to	O
your	O
last	O
minute	O
Yrs	O
affy	O
in	O
haste	O
S.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
Saturday	O
M	O
.	O
since	O
I	O
wrote	O
this	O
my	O
Mr	O
.	O
tells	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
this	O
Morning	O
&	O
prey	O
send	O
me	O
word	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
stays	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
if	O
poſsible	O
before	O
going	O
to	O
Wimbledon	B-place
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
