TOKEN	NE
June	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
(	O
longest	O
day	O
)	O
Sent	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
trouble	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
--	O
sent	O
my	O
diary	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Note	O
of	O
excuse	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
made	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
set	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
for	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
.	O
We	O
arrived	O
there	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
3	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
out	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
fault	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
earlier	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
but	O
Mr	B-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
never	O
punctual	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
immediately	O
after	O
us	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
through	O
most	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
rooms	O
&	O
opened	O
the	O
Cabinets	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
not	O
opened	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
who	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
)	O
wch	O
.	O
contain	O
fine	O
Miniatures	O
&	O
various	O
fine	O
&	O
curious	O
things	O
both	O
Modern	O
&	O
Antique	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
ennumerate	O
--	O
the	O
whole	O
stile	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
is	O
true	O
Gothic	O
--	O
every	O
Room	O
--	O
closet	O
--	O
Boudoir	O
Gallery	O
&	O
c.	O
has	O
painted	O
Glaſs	O
Windows	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
perfect	O
thing	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
kind	O
in	O
England	B-place
I	O
believe	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
in	O
Europe	O
&	O
still	O
further	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
lands	O
--	O
one	O
ought	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
Month	O
to	O
see	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Vertu	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
particularly	O
attentive	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
gave	O
himself	O
much	O
trouble	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
I	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
real	O
pleasure	O
,	O
in	O
looking	O
at	O
ye-	O
Pictures	O
&	O
other	O
curious	O
&	O
beautiful	O
works	O
of	O
Art	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
again	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
last	O
year	O
)	O
ye	O
.	O
beautiful	O
drawings	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dia	I-pers
:	I-pers
Beauclerk	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
built	O
on	O
purpose	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
only	O
opens	O
for	O
his	O
most	O
particular	O
friends	O
--	O
these	O
Drawings	O
are	O
tak	O
subjects	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
Play	O
he	O
wrote	O
of	O
the	O
Mysterious	O
Mother	O
--	O
a	O
Tragedy	O
I	O
once	O
hea	O
r	O
d	O
read	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tyghe	I-pers
the	O
Story	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
horrid	O
to	O
be	O
conceived	O
--	O
but	O
these	O
drawings	O
tho	O
'	O
.	O
they	O
recall	O
to	O
mind	O
ye	O
.	O
horrid	O
Subject	O
are	O
most	O
affectingly	O
interesting	O
ye	O
countenances	O
are	O
very	O
expreſsive	O
.	O
At	O
4	O
oClock	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
elegant	O
one	O
incomparably	O
well	O
served	O
--	O
it	O
shewed	O
yt	O
ye	O
.	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
fortune	O
&	O
taste	O
accustom	O
'd	O
to	O
elegancies	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
but	O
those	O
I	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
next	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
he	O
honor	O
'd	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
show	O
of	O
his	O
attention	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
the	O
2	O
gentlemen	O
rose	O
when	O
we	O
did	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
carried	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
China	O
Closet	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Modern	O
&	O
old	O
China	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
there	O
for	O
sometime	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
--	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
our	O
time	O
after	O
Coffee	O
&	O
Tea	O
in	O
very	O
agreeable	O
converse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
½	O
an	O
hours	O
private	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
she	O
loves	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
most	O
lively	O
affection	O
.	O
I	O
communicated	O
to	O
her	O
my	O
present	O
prospect	O
of	O
future	O
happineſs	O
--	O
she	O
shed	O
tears	O
of	O
joy	O
&	O
aſsured	O
me	O
she	O
should	O
from	O
my	O
representation	O
receive	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
with	O
open	O
arms	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
more	O
warm	O
or	O
friendly	O
heart	O
than	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G——	I-pers
's	O
she	O
poſseſses	O
a	O
truly	O
great	O
Soul	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
8	O
we	O
reluctantly	O
took	O
our	O
leave	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
his	O
beautiful	O
Grounds	O
as	O
it	O
ha	O
rain	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
his	O
Neice	O
Lady	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Waldgrave	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Glocester	O
House	O
.	O
My	O
head	O
ach	O
'd	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
could	O
ill	O
join	O
'd	O
in	O
conversation	O
in	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
however	O
complain	O
,	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
of	O
very	O
Small	O
fortune	O
&	O
her	O
friends	O
apprehend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
be	O
dissatisfied	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Match	O
.	O
I	O
declined	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
sup	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
were	O
2	O
hours	O
coming	O
from	O
Twickenham	B-place
--	O
I	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
at	O
home	O
I	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
June	O
Monday	O
Recd	O
..	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
:	I-pers
Dr	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
herself	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs's-	I-pers
invites	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
in	O
ye	O
..	O
Autumn	O
--	O
or	O
when	O
she	O
Returns	O
from	O
Margate	B-place
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
so	O
ill	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Betty	B-pers
gave	O
me	O
some	O
hot	O
peppermint	O
water	O
--	O
her	O
prescription	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
--	O
for	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
fever	O
I	O
slept	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
since	O
Thursday	O
--	O
sent	O
Mr	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
to	O
G	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
June	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
I	O
felt	O
this	O
Morning	O
as	O
if	O
just	O
recovering	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
illneſs	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
tea	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
not	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
habit	O
maker	O
came	O
I	O
bespoke	O
a	O
new	O
Riding	O
habit	O
--	O
wrote	O
&	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
then	O
settled	O
accounts	O
wth	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
letters	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
AMaria	B-pers
answere	O
'd	O
them	O
&	O
sent	O
ym	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
who	O
was	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
but	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
employ	O
myself	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
&	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
interrupted	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
who	O
made	O
a	O
friendly	O
unexpected	O
visit	O
--	O
she	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Windsor	O
(	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
wth	O
.	O
M	O
r	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
)	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
Oxford	B-place
&	O
from	O
there	O
on	O
home	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
told	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
imprudent	O
one	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
except	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
I	O
think	O
behaved	O
gratefully	O
and	O
openly	O
towards	O
her	O
best	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
said	O
many	O
pleasing	O
&	O
flattering	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
what	O
was	O
most	O
grateful	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
repetition	O
of	O
kind	O
things	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smelts	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
had	O
said	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
When	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
inclined	O
to	O
walk	O
--	O
we	O
made	O
haste	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
tea	O
&	O
set	O
out	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
Place	O
--	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
Miss	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
left	O
me	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
ladies	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
they	O
soon	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
very	O
agreeable	O
with	O
this	O
very	O
excellent	O
pleasing	O
&	O
amiable	O
Woman	O
--	O
she	O
did	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
favor	O
to	O
aſsure	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
extremely	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
being	O
personally	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
now	O
intended	O
to	O
reside	O
in	O
London	B-place
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
often	O
--	O
communicated	O
to	O
me	O
her	O
plans	O
respecting	O
her	O
4	O
Sons	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
sometime	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
should	O
speak	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S——	I-pers
character	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
every	O
good	O
mind	O
must	O
admire	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
estimable	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
who	O
were	O
just	O
Return	O
'd	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
preſs	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
stay	O
supper	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
drank	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
health	O
--	O
&	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
were	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
enclosed	O
in	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
dated	O
ye	O
.	O
17	O
th	O
but	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Oxford	B-place
therefore	O
she	O
cld	O
.	O
not	O
send	O
it	O
sooner	O
--	O
this	O
letter	O
contain	O
'd	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
her	O
family	O
are	O
comfortably	O
settled	O
once	O
more	O
at	O
Courteenhall	B-place
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
June	O
2	O
4	O
th	O
1784	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Betty	B-pers
s	O
sister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
she	O
cut	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
affair	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
set	O
out	O
wth	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
for	O
Richmond	O
Hill	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
rainy	O
day	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
quite	O
a	O
fair	O
one	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
paſs	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
&	O
Saordy	B-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Road	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
Kew	O
Bridge	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
Court	O
--	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
felt	O
when	O
I	O
compared	O
my	O
present	O
liberty	O
to	O
that	O
life	O
of	O
restraint	O
.	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
--	O
As	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Party	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
aſsemble	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
left	O
me	O
&	O
went	O
&	O
paid	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mountagu	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Buccleugh	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
alone	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
ink	O
&	O
Paper	O
&	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
rode	O
from	O
Town	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
4	O
--	O
he	O
never	O
sleeps	O
here	O
&	O
only	O
comes	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
dine	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
is	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
top	O
of	O
R	O
:	O
Hill	O
&	O
commands	O
ye	O
..	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Views	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
Lord	B-pers
Palmerston	I-pers
says	O
so	O
,	O
who	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
told	O
me	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Prospect	O
Hunter	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
often	O
expressed	O
this	O
has	O
seen	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Views	O
in	O
Switzerland	B-place
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Town	O
contrary	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
advice	O
of	O
her	O
Physician	O
Sr-	B-pers
George	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
--	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
slow	O
fever	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
woman	O
,	O
lively	O
&	O
unaffected	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
all	O
the	O
Party	O
were	O
aſsembled	O
wch	O
.	O
consisted	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Bingham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Molesworth	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
Asaph	O
his	O
Wife	O
Mrs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Georgiana	I-pers
Shipley	I-pers
&	O
Gell	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mordant	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Company	O
were	O
all	O
lively	O
&	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
paſs	O
'd	O
cheerfully	O
.	O
A	O
i	O
t	O
rain	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Aft	O
ernoon	O
therefore	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
fine	O
Pictures	O
by	O
old	O
Masters	O
--	O
Pouſsin	B-pers
&	O
c	O
both	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
&	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
two	O
large	O
Rooms	O
one	O
one	O
ye	O
.	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
&	O
one	O
above	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
Commands	O
ye	O
.	O
View	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Same	O
size	O
&	O
have	O
a	O
large	O
Window	O
.	O
These	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
principle	O
Rooms	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
we	O
all	O
separated	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
we	O
got	O
to	O
Town	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
's	O
Marriage	O
--	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Laura	I-pers
Kepples	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fitzroy	I-pers
s	O
running	O
away	O
Yesterday	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
they	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
sup	O
wth	O
..	O
them	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
letter	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
&	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
diary	O
.	O
June	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Thursday	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
&	O
answer	O
'd	O
notes	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Agill	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Shoemaker	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
visit	O
--	O
began	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
after	O
dinner	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
wh	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
this	O
Post	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
who	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
to	O
Town	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
Dr.	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
were	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
company	O
--	O
an	O
agreeable	O
afternoon	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
we	O
staid	O
till	O
supper	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
some	O
fine	O
flowers	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
brought	O
from	O
Hampton	B-place
June	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Thursd	O
Friday	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
Sunning-Hill	O
--	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
s	O
on	O
Wedn	O
.	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
both	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
he	O
must	O
now	O
give	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
prevailing	O
on	O
me	O
&	O
accept	O
his	O
hand	O
--	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
in	O
saying	O
It	O
was	O
i	O
p	O
m	O
poſsible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
relinquish	O
his	O
hopes	O
--	O
his	O
happineſs	O
was	O
too	O
ly	O
deeply	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
my	O
engagement	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
he	O
was	O
extremely	O
affected	O
by	O
this	O
intelligence	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
indeed	O
then	O
give	O
her	O
up	O
--	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
every	O
happiness	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
was	O
was	O
really	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
that	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
unhappy	O
&	O
miserable	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
imagine	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
&	O
did	O
live	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
ye	O
..	O
World	O
--	O
who	O
was	O
advanced	O
in	O
life	O
&	O
had	O
Children	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
fond	O
attach	O
'd	O
could	O
have	O
felt	O
so	O
much	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
so	O
few	O
opportunities	O
of	O
seeing	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
left	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
--	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
heart	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
alas	O
her	O
heart	O
is	O
a	O
broken	O
one	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
never	O
recover	O
ye	O
.	O
loſs	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
they	O
lived	O
together	O
34	O
years	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
utmost	O
harmony	O
--	O
he	O
died	O
her	O
lover	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Husband	O
&	O
friend	O
--	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
.	O
a	O
relief	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
shed	O
tears	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
one	O
who	O
sympathised	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
we	O
talkd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Congratulation	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
that	O
was	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Cover	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
--	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
,	O
to	O
thank	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Turbot	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
informd	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
again	O
been	O
ill	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
grateful	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
--	O
Miss	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
's	O
Servt	O
.	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
she	O
left	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
before	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Horton	B-place
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
Amaria	B-pers
home	O
--	O
Ms	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
hers	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
Kettleston	B-place
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
,	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
call	O
(	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
)	O
upon	O
her	O
Father	O
&	O
Mother	O
.	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
&	O
c	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Wed——	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
therefore	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
could	O
not	O
arrive	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
Thursday	O
or	O
late	O
on	O
Wedy	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
who	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
frighten	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
days	O
ago	O
--	O
by	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
who	O
whilst	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
close	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
s	O
heart	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
haste	O
&	O
deliver	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
together	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
all	O
hopes	O
of	O
AM	B-pers
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
accompanied	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
home	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
trifling	O
&	O
lively	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
so	O
fine	O
I	O
proposed	O
walking	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
agreed	O
to	O
as	O
S	O
t	O
here	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
danger	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
our	O
Man	O
Servt	O
.	O
to	O
guard	O
us	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
we	O
retired	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Saturday	O
26	O
th	O
-	O
1784	O
June	O
.	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
visit	O
--	O
I	O
communicated	O
to	O
him	O
my	O
engagement	O
wth	O
..	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
he	O
said	O
I	O
certainly	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
judge	O
of	O
what	O
wd	O
.	O
contribute	O
to	O
my	O
happineſs	O
--	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
such	O
advice	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
natural	O
for	O
a	O
prudent	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
much	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
to	O
give	O
,	O
I	O
listen	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
heart	O
was	O
averse	O
to	O
many	O
things	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
neceſsary	O
prudence	O
is	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
e	O
I	O
will	O
suppreſs	O
what	O
I	O
what	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
--	O
&	O
only	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
my	O
Uncle	O
has	O
a	O
sincere	O
regard	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
Lord	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
Orkney	I-pers
--	O
of	O
family	O
disappointments	O
--	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
ingratitude	O
of	O
Kings	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
also	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Family	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
characters	O
of	O
her	O
Brothers	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
my	O
Uncle	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
long	O
ago	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
she	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
--	O
I	O
Work	O
'd	O
&	O
she	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
pages	O
of	O
a	O
foolish	O
Novel	O
wch	O
..	O
was	O
in	O
too	O
bad	O
a	O
stile	O
to	O
continue	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
indelicate	O
but	O
sad	O
poor	O
stuff	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
reading	O
a	O
book	O
I	O
begun	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
Remarks	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
french	O
&	O
English	O
Ladies	O
by	O
Andrews	B-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
much	O
like	O
ye	O
.	O
Author	O
's	O
stile	O
of	O
writing	O
but	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
thorough	O
knowledge	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Characters	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
french	O
women	O
--	O
at	O
leat	O
it	O
agrees	O
wth	O
.	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
their	O
society	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
from	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
Harewood	B-place
to	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
--	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
had	O
Wm	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Penny	O
Post	O
hours	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
where	O
we	O
met	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Mulso	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
son	O
.	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
in	O
general	O
sensible	O
&	O
informing	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
seems	O
a	O
Young	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
parts	O
--	O
his	O
language	O
is	O
correct	O
&	O
he	O
converses	O
wth	O
.	O
ease	O
&	O
vivacity	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
set	O
Mr	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
down	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
begun	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
Voltaire	B-pers
s	O
Mémoires	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
published	O
--	O
&	O
wch	O
:	O
is	O
the	O
present	O
rage	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
curious	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
book	O
,	O
being	O
really	O
written	O
by	O
this	O
great	O
tho	O
'	O
wicked	O
author	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
contain	O
'd	O
a	O
just	O
character	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
,	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
faithful	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
his	O
friend	O
&	O
enemy	O
Voltaire	B-pers
thought	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
book	O
I	O
repented	O
having	O
endulged	O
my	O
curiosity	O
--	O
why	O
should	O
one	O
wish	O
to	O
become	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
vicious	O
&	O
wicked	O
people	O
No	O
woman	O
ought	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
book	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
ashamed	O
to	O
own	O
she	O
has	O
read	O
--	O
I	O
reproach	O
myself	O
for	O
having	O
read	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
Vesey	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
.	O
but	O
were	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
Sunday	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1784	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
&	O
Answer	O
'd	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
She	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
--	O
It	O
pour	O
'd	O
such	O
deluges	O
of	O
Rain	O
it	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
read	O
prayers	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
&	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
began	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Carriage	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
:	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
ourselves	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Beattie	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
abt	O
.	O
14	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
before	O
dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
&	O
painting	O
Room	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
treat	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
oClock	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
were	O
met	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
ladies	O
besides	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
&	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
celebrated	O
Dr.	B-pers
Beattie	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Paoli	I-pers
--	O
&	O
his	O
friend	O
whose	O
Name	O
I	O
always	O
forget	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
--	O
a	O
foreigner	O
whom	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
&	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
introduced	O
by	O
Miss	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
to	O
her	O
first	O
favorite	O
Lord	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
--	O
I	O
sat	O
next	O
him	O
at	O
dinner	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
soon	O
acquainted	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
character	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
his	O
Wife	O
his	O
Children	O
Sisters	O
are	O
all	O
excellent	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
railliry	O
of	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
's	O
profeſsd	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Paoli	I-pers
aſsured	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
raved	O
abt	O
.	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Abbey	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
&	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
lively	O
or	O
agreeable	O
than	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
set	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
head	O
of	O
her	O
painting	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
quite	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
stile	O
--	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
instruction	O
but	O
observing	O
her	O
Uncle	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
finished	O
any	O
thing	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
paints	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
faults	O
.	O
She	O
play	O
'd	O
&	O
sang	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
great	O
sweetneſs	O
of	O
voice	O
,	O
this	O
accomplishment	O
too	O
is	O
self-taught	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
ye	O
.	O
agreeable	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fo	O
u	O
nd	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
pretty	O
well	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
but	O
I	O
reserved	O
my	O
information	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
for	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
then	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
Lord	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
m	O
u	O
ch	O
better	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
truth	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
report	O
of	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
giving	O
over	O
busineſs	O
he	O
aſsured	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Court	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
franks	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
at	O
10	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
fulfill	O
my	O
promise	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
last	O
Monday	O
of	O
a	O
daughter	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
also	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Monday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1784	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
habit	O
Maker	O
came	O
brought	O
home	O
my	O
new	O
habit	O
--	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
£	O
4.14	O
6	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Town	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
looking	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
yt	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
just	O
stop	O
'd	O
for	O
letters	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
coming	O
in	O
--	O
had	O
letters	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
en	O
chemin	O
faisant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
sung	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
an	O
old	O
Spa	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
entertain	O
'd	O
in	O
listening	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
great	O
favorites	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
uncommon	O
character	O
--	O
I	O
mean	O
by	O
his	O
superiour	O
excellence	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
their	O
Rooms	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
for	O
½.	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
--	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dick——	I-pers
letter	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Tuesday	O
--	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1784	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
we	O
settled	O
some	O
accounts	O
together	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
H	O
sheet	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
well	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
word	O
M	O
rs	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
yt	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Grandson	O
Master	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
.	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
West	O
Minster	O
School	O
came	O
in	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
long	O
visits	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
another	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsciord	O
--	O
we	O
separated	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
till	O
7	O
met	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Tea	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
J	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
&	O
her	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
unexpectedly	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
fond	O
of	O
Music	O
--	O
I	O
prevailed	O
on	O
my	O
Cousin	O
to	O
sing	O
we	O
adjoined	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
harpsicord	O
was	O
--	O
She	O
sang	O
two	O
fine	O
Italian	O
Songs	O
--	O
after	O
wch	O
..	O
she	O
Mrs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
left	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
surprised	O
at	O
my	O
Cousin	O
s	O
Singing	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
We	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
took	O
impreſsion	O
of	O
seals	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Prospects	O
Lord	B-pers
Melcombe	I-pers
s	O
diary	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
enjoy	O
his	O
quiet	O
evening	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
So	O
well	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
his	O
reception	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
up	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
famous	O
Dance	O
of	O
le	O
Deserteur	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
went	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
2	O
letters	O
--	O
sent	O
that	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
by	O
this	O
nights	O
Post	O
Bell	B-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
talking	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
o.Clock	O
Wednesday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1784	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
I	O
breakfas	O
ted	O
below	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	O
&	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
ym	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
en	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
two	O
Notes	O
to	O
beg	O
I	O
wd	O
..	O
either	O
come	O
down	O
or	O
admit	O
à	O
my	O
toilet	O
--	O
some	O
laughable	O
meſsages	O
paſs	O
'd	O
from	O
above	O
to	O
below	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
seeing	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Morng	O
.	O
with	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
we	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
in	O
making	O
Nonsense	O
Verses	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
an	O
extract	O
from	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
concern	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Storment	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
¼	O
before	O
5.	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
--	O
little	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
desert	O
&	O
were	O
wth	O
us	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
uninterrupted	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
I	O
communicated	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
story	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
single	O
objection	O
&	O
aſsured	O
me	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
&	O
shd	O
shew	O
him	O
every	O
attention	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
favorable	O
impreſsion	O
Idea	O
she	O
had	O
conceived	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
inform	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Warwick	B-pers
my	B-pers
Uncles	I-pers
&	O
other	O
near	O
Relations	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
opinion	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
choice	O
I	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
husband	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
he	O
always	O
seems	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
confidential	O
discourse	O
abt	O
.	O
his	O
eldest	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
prose	O
Epistle	O
to	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
D	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mre	I-pers
:	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
10	O
I	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
as	O
usual	O
//	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
meet	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
ym-	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
besides	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
Supper	O
but	O
ye	O
table	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
fruit	O
from	O
Mr-	B-pers
G——	I-pers
Villa	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cs	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Spirits	O
tried	O
.	O
Thursday	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Ju	O
ne	O
ly	O
1784	O
AM	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
out	O
very	O
early	O
this	O
morng	O
.	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
French	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Manuscript	O
Journal	O
written	O
when	O
in	O
france	B-place
&	O
Italy	B-place
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Visit	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
--	O
AM	B-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Wife	O
)	O
made	O
us	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
away	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
diſsipated	O
life	O
ye	O
.	O
people	O
of	O
fashion	O
leded	O
led	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
.	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
dinner	O
was	O
over	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
fine	O
desert	O
of	O
fruit	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Chapone	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
speak	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
favorable	O
manner	O
--	O
ye	O
..	O
Company	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
s	O
were	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
her	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Son	O
ye	O
.	O
Clergyman	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
new	O
Taxes	O
were	O
spoke	O
of	O
&	O
approved	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
was	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
begin	O
ye	O
World	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
by	O
being	O
well	O
known	O
&	O
esteem	O
'd	O
get	O
good	O
preferment	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
popular	O
Preacher	O
at	O
Edinburgh	B-place
Mr.	B-pers
Poultney	I-pers
has	O
just	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
living	O
of	O
150	O
P	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
at	O
Sudbro	B-place
Thrapston	B-place
,	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
I	O
believe	O
near	O
Peterborough	B-place
the	O
afternoon	O
paſs	O
'd	O
agreeably	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
down	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
enquiries	O
relative	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
whom	O
she	O
has	O
known	O
many	O
years	O
--	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
la	O
r	O
ge	O
fortune	O
s	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
12	O
years	O
she	O
lost	O
him	O
&	O
3	O
daughters	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
space	O
of	O
2	O
years	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
was	O
20	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
--	O
handsome	O
&	O
very	O
amiable	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
16	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
14	O
all	O
3	O
were	O
charming	O
young	O
women	O
--	O
she	O
also	O
lost	O
a	O
Son	O
a	O
fine	O
youth	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Army	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
America	B-place
during	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
War	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
now	O
five	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Eldest	O
lives	O
on	O
his	O
Estate	O
is	O
married	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Place	O
in	O
Northumberland	B-place
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
in	O
ye	B-place
.	I-place
East	I-place
Indies	I-place
--	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
Married	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
fortune	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
in	O
Cornwall	B-place
--	O
ye	O
.	O
youngest	O
Daughter	O
unmarried	O
a	O
modest	O
well	O
accomplished	O
young	O
woman	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
is	O
a	O
sensible	O
friendly	O
agreeable	O
Woman	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
stile	O
without	O
parade	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
made	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
were	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
when	O
I	O
rcd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
at	O
home	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
to	O
sup	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
oClock	O
AMaria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
wch	O
.	O
l	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
this	O
Eveg	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
&	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Nosegay	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
W.	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
also	O
call	O
'd	O
Friday	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
early	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
arranged	O
some	O
papers	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Visit	O
--	O
he	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
a	O
very	O
high	O
opinion	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
my	O
character	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell	O
glaſs	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
flowers	O
&	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
came	O
&	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
c	O
she	O
quite	O
opened	O
her	O
heart	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
life	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
which	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
near	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
envited	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
to	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
G	O
reen	O
Park	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
s.	O
I	O
left	O
ym	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
she	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
son	O
William	B-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
clever	O
boy	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
14	O
Yesterday	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Law	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
(	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Vice	O
Chamberlain	O
)	O
this	O
Morng	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
being	O
again	O
ill	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
H	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
H	O
:	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q	I-pers
:	I-pers
Yesterday	O
to	O
excuse	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
Court	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
op̄reſsion	O
of	O
breath	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
When	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
beg	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
woud	O
come	O
&	O
sent	O
her	B-pers
Son	I-pers
into	O
ye	O
..	O
Park	O
for	O
them	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
,	O
Bell	B-pers
was	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
I	O
introduced	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
--	O
Recd	O
&	O
answerd	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
to	O
reproach	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
written	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
her	O
last	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
few	O
leſsons	O
we	O
separated	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
met	O
to	O
tea	O
after	O
tea	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
left	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
aloud	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Diary	O
&	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Sat	O
up	O
till	O
12	O
Began	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Saturday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
.	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
came	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
house	O
Taxes	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
distreſs	O
's	O
of	O
ye	O
..	O
Nation	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
left	O
us	O
--	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
he	O
told	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
&	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Nephew	O
&	O
our	O
cousin	O
Coll	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
spoke	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
commons	O
yesterday	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
subject	O
was	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
affairs	O
in	O
India	B-place
on	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
qualified	O
to	O
speak	O
he	O
has	O
having	O
Coolneſs	O
,	O
sense	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
tone	O
of	O
Voice	O
&	O
an	O
engaging	O
Countenance	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
a	O
charming	O
Young	O
Man	O
&	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
figure	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
he	O
ha	O
d	O
s	O
already	O
gain	O
'd	O
great	O
credit	O
for	O
his	O
bravery	O
&	O
is	O
universally	O
&	O
deservedly	O
beloved	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
handsome	O
prepoſsing	O
&	O
engaging	O
--	O
modest	O
&	O
elegant	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
from	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
3	O
--	O
She	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
next	O
week	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
confidential	O
things	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
her	O
love	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
her	O
esteem	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
right	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
engagement	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
she	O
was	O
much	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
prospect	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
future	O
happineſs	O
&	O
greatly	O
approved	O
my	O
choice	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
meet	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Carriage	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
considering	O
--	O
she	O
complained	O
however	O
of	O
a	O
Nervous	O
deafneſs	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
of	O
dear	O
little	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
's	O
ye	B-pers
Napiers	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Her	O
2	O
Brothers	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
attend	O
his	O
duty	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Tower	O
Guard	O
--	O
we	O
complimented	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
on	O
his	O
succeſs	O
Yesterday	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
character	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
he	O
said	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
was	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
told	O
us	O
how	O
well	O
Master	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
had	O
behaved	O
(	O
he	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
tutor	O
)	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Masfield	I-pers
--	O
I	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
ca	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
be	O
deprived	O
of	O
seeing	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
wishd	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
course	O
of	O
Conversation	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
much	O
interest	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
took	O
in	O
my	O
happineſs	O
she	O
had	O
communicated	O
to	O
him	O
my	O
engagement	O
&	O
c	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
that	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
was	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
choice	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
person	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
of	O
who	O
poſseſsed	O
sentiment	O
without	O
acting	O
imprudent	O
l	O
y	O
or	O
being	O
Romantic	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
heard	O
to	O
day	O
yt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
..	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
I	O
sent	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
present	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
wanted	O
one	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
herb	O
snuf	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
orderd	O
to	O
take	O
Miſs	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
We	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Nosegay	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
after	O
her	O
return	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
uneasy	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
at	O
not	O
having	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
her	O
Grace	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
longer	O
letter	O
by	O
Mondays	O
Post	O
--	O
After	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
left	O
me	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Sunday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Went	O
to	O
day	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
Master	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Agar	I-pers
's	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
very	O
capital	O
Pictures	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Agar	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
us	O
very	O
politely	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
fortune	O
to	O
make	O
Some	O
proper	O
observations	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
pleased	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
--	O
he	O
expects	O
5	O
Pictures	O
from	O
Rome	B-place
every	O
day	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
William	I-pers
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
Town	O
I	O
will	O
then	O
attempt	O
some	O
description	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
leisure	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
After	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
A	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
parted	O
from	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
O	I-pers
.	I-pers
her	O
daughter	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
S——	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
peace	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Winter	O
--	O
here	O
we	O
heard	O
ye	B-pers
..	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
was	O
better	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
O	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
3	O
--	O
AM	B-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
Ball	O
&	O
I	O
excused	O
ourselves	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
we	O
separated	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
drew	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
.	O
Ball	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
--	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
ye	O
.	O
Moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
real	O
Summers	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Monday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
early	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
to	O
beg	O
I	O
would	O
dine	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Tollemache	I-pers
&	O
sleep	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
left	O
me	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
he	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
train	O
I	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
inform	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
this	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
writing	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
all	O
Morng	O
:	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
begun	O
one	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
at	O
4	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Carriage	O
came	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
--	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
dear	O
boys	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
Richard	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
two	O
letters	O
--	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
one	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
both	O
,	O
kind	O
friendly	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
promote	O
a	O
reconciliation	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
gain	O
'd	O
some	O
ground	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
small	O
Miniature	O
by	O
Saunders	B-pers
of	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
likeneſs	O
&	O
prettily	O
painted	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
price	O
5	O
Guineas	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
size	O
for	O
a	O
Ring	O
--	O
Saunders	B-pers
lives	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
I	O
must	O
positively	O
set	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
picture	O
&	O
make	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
in	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
franks	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
M	I-pers
is	O
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
his	O
complaints	O
are	O
Nervous	O
&	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
sleep	O
well	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Coal	O
Tax	O
nor	O
ye	O
.	O
Horse	O
Tax	O
would	O
take	O
place	O
--	O
that	O
they	O
Thought	O
Superfine	O
Sugars	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
tax	O
'd	O
--	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
Came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
at	O
home	O
finished	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dſowr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
sent	O
3	O
letters	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
one	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
one	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Tuesday	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
½	O
an	O
our	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
1	O
,	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
extracts	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
some	O
Compliments	O
upon	O
My	O
industry	O
--	O
&	O
not	O
only	O
approved	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
but	O
made	O
me	O
happy	O
by	O
saying	O
I	O
might	O
keep	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
return	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
Packet	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
letters	O
wch	O
..	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
poſseſsion	O
&	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
endeavour	O
to	O
procure	O
all	O
those	O
in	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ports	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Sister	O
s	O
)	O
poſseſsion	O
had	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
introduce	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
yt	O
.	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
so	O
good	O
&	O
respectable	O
a	O
Man	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
however	O
open	O
say	O
anything	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
nature	O
of	O
my	O
friendship	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
As	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
desired	O
he	O
might	O
accompany	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
broiling	O
Heat	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
was	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
staid	O
sometime	O
I	O
sat	O
i	O
n	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
her	O
Son	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
of	O
H	O
ome	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
many	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
confirmed	O
ye	O
.	O
opinion	O
I	O
before	O
had	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
's	O
Character	O
--	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
--	O
I	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
she	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
come	O
in	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
talk	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
abt	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
communicated	O
wth	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
we	O
cld-	O
not	O
converse	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
as	O
Vesey	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
to	O
several	O
places	O
--	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
whilst	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dacre	I-pers
--	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
in	O
ye	O
.	O
course	O
of	O
next	O
Week	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
fatigued	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
heat	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
ye	O
power	O
of	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
till	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
--	O
where	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
who	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
stay	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
sometime	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
play	O
&	O
sang	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
well	O
taught	O
&	O
sings	O
wth	O
.	O
judgment	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
Voice	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
settled	O
a	O
plan	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
together	O
--	O
she	O
entertain	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Offers	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
had	O
had	O
--	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
she	O
led	O
in	O
India	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
walked	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Miss	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
..	O
us	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Wednesday	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
a	O
Note	O
X	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
to	O
preſs	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
he	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
desires	O
he	O
will	O
persuade	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
go	O
.	O
/	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
sat	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Morng	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
drew	O
she	O
word	O
'd	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
after	O
dinner	O
AM	B-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
leſsons	O
we	O
separated	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
till	O
7	O
6	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
visit	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
's	I-pers
after	O
tea	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
where	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B——	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
till	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
Miss	B-pers
G——	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
drew	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
H	O
Street	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
l	O
y	O
a	O
y	O
ing	O
in	O
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
friendly	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
in	O
reply	O
to	O
my	O
congratulations	O
upon	O
her	O
Marriage	O
Thursday	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
X	O
Mr	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
Note	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
drawing	O
--	O
got	O
Blair	B-pers
s	O
Sermons	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
send	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
as	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
meſsage	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
I	O
would	O
inform	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Mourning	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
Court	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Harrington	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
entertain	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
should	O
apply	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
this	O
important	O
information	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
his	O
Grace	O
my	O
opinion	O
.	O
AM	B-pers
.	I-pers
returnd	O
frm	O
Lambeth	B-place
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
,	O
met	O
there	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Harries	I-pers
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Parnel	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Watts	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Knox	I-pers
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Well	I-pers
's	O
son	O
)	O
--	O
a	O
pleasant	O
party	O
!	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burke	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
enter	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
different	O
Topics	O
of	O
conversation	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
wch-	O
had	O
been	O
neglected	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
supper	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
12	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
miserable	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
--	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
Friday	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachell	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
Boy	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
on	O
Tuesday	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
or	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
this	O
Evg	O
..	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
as	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
busiſs	O
busineſs	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
settled	O
--	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
put	O
in	O
any	O
train	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
Country	O
engagements	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
fill	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
entrea	O
ties	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
Pepys	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
on	O
Sunday	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
came	O
at	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
came	O
at	O
11	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
talking	O
over	O
his	O
distreſs	O
on	O
his	O
Brother	O
s	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
ye-	O
poor	O
Man	O
my	O
opinion	O
&	O
advice	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
from	O
12	O
til	O
past	O
1	O
--	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
new	O
plan	O
he	O
had	O
adopted	O
for	O
his	O
Son	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
saw	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
..	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
affectionate	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
agreeable	O
aſsurances	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
s	O
approbation	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
recd	O
.	O
also	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
expreſses	O
much	O
impatience	O
for	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
before	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
our	O
Cousin	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
us	O
--	O
she	O
really	O
is	O
a	O
friendly	O
good	O
Creature	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
in	O
his	O
fine	O
Library	O
till	O
dinner	O
,	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Rooms	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
the	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
except	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Visit	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Legge	I-pers
.	O
we	O
had	O
as	O
usual	O
ye	O
.	O
two	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boys	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
was	O
very	O
entertaining	O
&	O
agreeable	O
--	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
again	O
attempted	O
to	O
bring	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
reconci	O
a	O
liation	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
heart	O
between	O
ye	O
.	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Niece	O
,	O
&	O
think	O
I	O
gain	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
ground	O
.	O
saw	O
two	O
Pictures	O
of	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
Hamilton	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
Sister	O
have	O
--	O
by	O
these	O
pictures	O
&	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Lady	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
H	O
very	O
elegant	O
pretty	O
Woman	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Had	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
reasons	O
of	O
our	O
not	O
meeting	O
them	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
2	O
oClock	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
for	O
tomorrows	O
post	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Argyll	I-pers
has	O
resign	O
'd	O
her	O
Place	O
as	O
Lady	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bedchamber	O
--	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
very	O
declining	O
health	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
kiss	O
'd	O
hands	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Yesterday	O
on	O
being	O
appointed	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
Saturday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Wrote	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
--	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
settled	O
some	O
important	O
triffles	O
,	O
wth	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
Isabella	B-pers
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
c	O
had	O
aſsured	O
me	O
of	O
their	O
approbation	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
I	O
had	O
their	O
sanction	O
for	O
going	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
of	O
perfect	O
good	O
character	O
without	O
a	O
Chaperon	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
airing	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
where	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
amused	O
me	O
by	O
relating	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
curious	O
Anecdotes	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
boast	O
of	O
recollecting	O
them	O
for	O
my	O
thoughts	O
were	O
too	O
often	O
wandering	O
into	O
Ds	O
shire	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
attention	O
th	O
is	O
conversation	O
merited	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
yt	O
..	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
fellow	O
travēler	O
--	O
for	O
people	O
that	O
love	O
to	O
talk	O
themselves	O
require	O
nothing	O
more	O
from	O
one	O
than	O
a	O
look	O
of	O
attention	O
--	O
the	O
words	O
yes	O
&	O
no	O
,	O
a	O
well	O
tim	O
'd	O
smile	O
--	O
a	O
grave	O
face	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
much	O
easier	O
matter	O
to	O
please	O
than	O
some	O
will	O
allow	O
.	O
Sometime	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
down	O
my	O
thoughts	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
--	O
I	O
detest	O
art	O
of	O
every	O
kind	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
duty	O
we	O
owe	O
society	O
to	O
t	O
appear	O
perfectly	O
attentive	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
expreſs	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
joy	O
at	O
seeing	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
sincere	O
.	O
She	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
improvements	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
flattering	O
manner	O
surprised	O
me	O
by	O
shewing	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
elegant	O
decoration	O
&	O
new	O
furniture	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dreſsing	O
Room	O
to	O
a	O
Bedchamber	O
wch	O
..	O
is	O
always	O
call	O
'd	O
Miſs	O
H——	O
's	O
as	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
seat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
shruberry	O
wch	O
.	O
commands	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
at	O
Dinner	O
than	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
(	O
her	O
only	O
daughter	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
14	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
accomplishd	O
Young	O
Person	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
mistreſs	O
of	O
Music	O
--	O
&	O
painting	O
--	O
Models	O
in	O
a	O
surprising	O
Manner	O
--	O
knows	O
perfectly	O
Modern	O
&	O
Ancient	O
History	O
French	O
,	O
Italian	O
--	O
Geography	O
,	O
Mathematics	O
--	O
Astronomy	O
ye	O
.	O
English	O
Claſsics	O
--	O
is	O
learning	O
Spanish	O
&	O
Latin	O
&	O
c.	O
though	O
I	O
think	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
will	O
reap	O
many	O
advantages	O
from	O
having	O
received	O
so	O
very	O
superiour	O
an	O
education	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
prevent	O
her	O
enjoying	O
the	O
innocent	O
pleasure	O
of	O
society	O
for	O
every	O
other	O
female	O
will	O
not	O
only	O
envy	O
but	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Men	O
in	O
general	O
are	O
so	O
jealous	O
of	O
our	O
being	O
as	O
wise	O
as	O
themselves	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
shun	O
her	O
,	O
None	O
will	O
aſsociate	O
wth-	O
her	O
but	O
Colledge	O
Pedants	O
or	O
rigid	O
Philosophers	O
or	O
pretended	O
Femmes	O
Savantes	O
--	O
&	O
an	O
affected	O
Femme	O
Savante	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
a	O
most	O
disagreeable	O
animal	O
--	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
this	O
is	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
pretend	O
to	O
more	O
knowledge	O
than	O
than	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
ignorant	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
are	O
part	O
affected	O
&	O
useleſs	O
members	O
of	O
society	O
the	O
only	O
Woman	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
whose	O
talents	O
deserved	O
the	O
highest	O
cultivation	O
is	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
I	O
imagine	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
learned	O
female	O
that	O
ever	O
lived	O
--	O
hers	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
mere	O
superficial	O
knowledge	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
most	O
wise	O
&	O
Good	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
now	O
indulge	O
myself	O
with	O
writing	O
an	O
eloge	O
on	O
this	O
Dear	O
Woman	O
the	O
subject	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
too	O
far	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Chapone	I-pers
&	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
I	O
could	O
name	O
whom	O
I	O
likewise	O
would	O
except	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
list	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
Femmes	O
Savantes	O
.	O
for	O
their	O
talents	O
&	O
amiable	O
precepts	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
society	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Medaillion	O
Seat	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
Coffee	O
.	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
also	O
drank	O
tea	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
paſsing	O
objects	O
such	O
as	O
pleasure	O
boats	O
,	O
Barges	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
River	O
&	O
the	O
Carriages	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
shore	O
made	O
an	O
agreeable	O
variety	O
.	O
this	O
Villa	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
Surry	B-place
Side	O
immediately	O
opposite	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
Palace	O
2	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Pavilions	O
are	O
ye	O
.	O
principle	O
object	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
is	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
Trees	O
,	O
the	O
Terrace	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
Garden	O
is	O
so	O
high	O
that	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
a	O
Telescope	O
from	O
this	O
Seat	O
one	O
can	O
easily	O
distinguish	O
who	O
are	O
walking	O
there	O
if	O
one	O
is	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
Tea	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Shruberry	O
&	O
round	O
the	O
Ferme	O
orné	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
laid	O
out	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
taste	O
as	O
42	O
Acres	O
of	O
flat	O
ground	O
can	O
well	O
be	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
has	O
just	O
begun	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
conservertory	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
agreeable	O
addition	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
open	O
into	O
a	O
China	O
Closet	O
wch	O
.	O
opens	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
largest	O
drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
treated	O
us	O
with	O
Reading	O
Paſsages	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscripts	O
she	O
has	O
in	O
her	O
poſseſsion	O
--	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
was	O
a	O
curious	O
account	O
of	O
transactions	O
in	O
Ruſsia	B-place
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
Short	O
hand	O
from	O
a	O
relation	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vigo	I-pers
had	O
given	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Russia	B-place
when	O
Jane	B-pers
Vigor	I-pers
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
orders	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Czar	I-pers
.	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
now	O
so	O
generally	O
known	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
detail	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
ye	B-pers
present	I-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
retired	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Cloth	O
was	O
removed	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
was	O
so	O
interesting	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
forgot	O
the	O
hour	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
rule	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
is	O
to	O
separate	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
she	O
accompanied	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
repeated	O
her	O
kind	O
profeſsing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Widow	O
&	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
celebrated	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
--	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
portion	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
s	O
Wit	O
--	O
is	O
more	O
inform	O
'd	O
than	O
most	O
women	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
highly	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
esteem	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
judges	O
to	O
be	O
first	O
Lady	O
Painter	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Coningsby	I-pers
must	O
be	O
admired	O
for	O
her	O
talents	O
--	O
&	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
more	O
allowances	O
for	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
strong	O
a	O
mind	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
as	O
herself	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
loved	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
keen	O
&	O
sometimes	O
severe	O
&	O
wants	O
a	O
certain	O
softneſs	O
,	O
without	O
wch	O
.	O
no	O
female	O
can	O
appear	O
truly	O
amiable	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
public	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
ungrateful	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
from	O
my	O
our	O
first	O
acquaintance	O
been	O
perfectly	O
equal	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
has	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
feeling	O
for	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
careful	O
not	O
to	O
censure	O
the	O
failings	O
of	O
others	O
or	O
get	O
into	O
habits	O
of	O
detraction	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
investigate	O
every	O
character	O
that	O
falls	O
under	O
our	O
own	O
observation	O
--	O
Reading	O
the	O
characters	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
living	O
often	O
affords	O
better	O
instruction	O
than	O
reading	O
whole	O
volumes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
observations	O
of	O
others	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
fortune	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
power	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Thousand	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
besides	O
Money	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
stile	O
,	O
lives	O
like	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
fashion	O
&	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
œconomist	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
she	O
lives	O
expensively	O
not	O
extragavantly	O
.	O
Sunday	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
I	O
got	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
6	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
book	O
wth-	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
engage	O
my	O
thoughts	O
to	O
its	O
contents	O
I	O
read	O
some	O
letters	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
thoughts	O
that	O
perhaps	O
the	O
writer	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
then	O
thinking	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
endulged	O
ye	O
.	O
hopes	O
that	O
ye	O
..	O
time	O
would	O
arrive	O
when	O
we	O
should	O
together	O
enjoy	O
every	O
pleasing	O
scene	O
--	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
sometime	O
or	O
other	O
together	O
admire	O
ye	O
.	O
beauties	O
of	O
Nature	O
&	O
adore	O
that	O
Being	O
who	O
has	O
so	O
bountifuly	O
stredwd	O
his	O
bleſsings	O
over	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
permitted	O
yt	O
.	O
we	O
shall	O
enjoy	O
this	O
happiness	O
--	O
that	O
same	O
Being	O
will	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
support	O
our	O
minds	O
to	O
bear	O
the	O
disappointment	O
properly	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
,	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Birds	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Nests	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
--	O
we	O
fed	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
become	O
tame	O
.	O
At	O
9	O
we	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
strolld	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
said	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
separate	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
make	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
stay	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Medaillion	O
Seat	O
&	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
with	O
conversing	O
&	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
Telescopes	O
till	O
3	O
--	O
at	O
1	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
elegant	O
little	O
Repast	O
brought	O
of	O
fruits	O
Cakes	O
&	O
Ice	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
at	O
3	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
Maid	O
attended	O
me	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
own	O
Maid	O
--	O
At	O
4	O
oClock	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
arrived	O
--	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
no	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
he	O
had	O
sent	O
his	O
excuse	O
being	O
ill	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
(	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
only	O
Son	O
)	O
came	O
from	O
London	B-place
to	O
dine	O
&	O
sleep	O
stay	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
these	O
3	O
years	O
--	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
(	O
his	O
father	O
s	O
Brother	O
)	O
Lord	B-pers
Shannon	I-pers
is	O
in	O
his	O
three	O
&	O
twent	O
ieth	O
year	O
a	O
handsome	O
lively	O
wellbred	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
sensible	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Guards	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
diſsipated	O
&	O
extravagant	O
--	O
but	O
how	O
few	O
how	O
very	O
few	O
Young	O
Men	O
are	O
otherwise	O
!	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Eldest	O
daughter	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
also	O
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Catherine	I-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
is	O
a	O
great	O
favorite	O
of	O
mine	O
she	O
is	O
natural	O
lively	O
and	O
unaffected	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
about	O
16	O
in	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
bloom	O
of	O
youth	O
!	O
&	O
though	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
agree	O
wth	O
.	O
others	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
beauty	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
a	O
handsome	O
Young	O
Woman	O
she	O
is	O
above	O
ye	O
.	O
common	O
size	O
is	O
well	O
form	O
'd	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
air	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
as	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
near	O
5	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Catherine	I-pers
s	O
resignation	O
and	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
s	O
appointment	O
as	O
Lady	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bedchamber	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
was	O
ye	O
.	O
principle	O
topic	O
with	O
other	O
tattle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
--	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
run	O
away	O
Match	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fritzroy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Laura	I-pers
Keppel	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
laughing	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
pathetic	O
letter	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
told	O
us	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
B——	I-pers
wrote	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Daughter	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
--	O
“	O
My	O
Child	O
,	O
my	O
Child	O
Oh	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Child	O
--	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
Child	O
--	O
Oh	O
come	O
&	O
comfort	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
Child	O
”	O
--	O
the	O
Prince	O
went	O
&	O
comforted	O
ye	O
.	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
Mother	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Keppel	I-pers
had	O
sat	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
with	O
her	O
Daughter	O
the	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Keppel	I-pers
having	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Sisters	O
to	O
Ranelagh	B-place
...	O
her	O
eyes	O
were	O
red	O
with	O
weeping	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Laura	I-pers
had	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
consent	O
to	O
her	O
marrying	O
Mrs.	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
daughter	O
and	O
to	O
amuse	O
her	O
read	O
the	O
very	O
Moral	O
&	O
instructive	O
Novel	O
of	O
the	O
Sorrows	O
of	O
Werter	O
.	O
They	O
separated	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
this	O
tender	O
judicious	O
sensible	O
Mother	O
charged	O
her	O
other	O
Daughters	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
or	O
laugh	O
quite	O
so	O
loud	O
as	O
usual	O
for	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
afflicted	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
try	O
by	O
sleep	O
to	O
forget	O
her	O
Sorrows	O
&	O
those	O
of	O
Werters	O
.	O
but	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
surprise	O
when	O
they	O
paſs	O
'd	O
her	O
Chambers	O
door	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
&	O
Laura	B-pers
was	O
fled	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
rose	O
from	O
table	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
M	O
:	O
Seat	O
after	O
Coffee	O
we	O
separated	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
conversd	O
without	O
form	O
or	O
restraint	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
enjoying	O
some	O
private	O
conversations	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
&	O
agreeable	O
friend	O
Laura	B-pers
she	O
shoew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
our	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s.	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
more	O
pleasing	O
Woman	O
than	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
She	O
is	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
perfect	O
grace	O
&	O
good	O
breeding	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
propriety	O
in	O
her	O
manners	O
&	O
conduct	O
wch	O
.	O
convince	O
you	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
sense	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
open	O
so	O
candid	O
so	O
engenuous	O
so	O
free	O
from	O
affectation	O
&	O
Art	O
that	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
be	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
without	O
loving	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
introduce	O
a	O
certain	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
invite	O
us	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
--	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
invite	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
(	O
wth	O
.	O
whom	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
many	O
years	O
acquainted	O
)	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
..	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Catherine	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
opposite	O
Shore	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
beautiful	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
W——	I-pers
who	O
lodge	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
in	O
the	O
Pavilions	O
.	O
before	O
supper	O
we	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
in	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
Prints	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Waldgraves	I-pers
s	O
Voyage	O
,	O
Cook	B-pers
entertain	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
by	O
reading	O
ye	O
.	O
descriptions	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
ye	O
..	O
Late	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eaton	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
whose	O
characters	O
afforded	O
us	O
ample	O
matter	O
for	O
conversation	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Coombes	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
were	O
spoke	O
of	O
by	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
as	O
they	O
merited	O
some	O
other	O
time	O
I	O
will	O
amuse	O
myself	O
in	O
making	O
memorandums	O
of	O
the	O
strange	O
anecdotes	O
relative	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
:	O
Coomes	B-pers
would	O
attend	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
She	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
time	O
for	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
longer	O
Visit	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
but	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
She	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Niece	O
)	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
to	O
stay	O
some	O
time	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
&	O
accomplished	O
woman	O
I	O
shall	O
endeavour	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
before	O
she	O
leaves	O
her	O
.	O
Monday	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
before	O
breakfast	O
--	O
&	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
leſson	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
plays	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
was	O
perfectly	O
well	O
grounded	O
&	O
understood	O
what	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
has	O
much	O
taste	O
or	O
feeling	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
breakfast	O
--	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
an	O
hour	O
earlier	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
gain	O
'd	O
great	O
credit	O
for	O
joining	O
us	O
so	O
early	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
charged	O
me	O
to	O
remember	O
my	O
promise	O
of	O
paying	O
her	O
a	O
longer	O
Visit	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
many	O
plans	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
places	O
&	O
c	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
should	O
not	O
enjoy	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
he	O
quite	O
gain	O
'd	O
my	O
heart	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
children	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
Woman	O
&	O
merits	O
the	O
praises	O
he	O
bestow	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
to	O
Town	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
as	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
answers	O
to	O
meſsages	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Pepy	I-pers
's	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
introduced	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
P——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
take	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
tomorrow	O
--	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Peachell	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
rose	O
from	O
Table	O
--	O
Received	O
letters	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
(	O
ye	O
.	O
authoreſs	O
of	O
Cecilia	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
&	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
read	O
my	O
letters	O
&	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
my	B-pers
Cousin	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
booksellers	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
last	O
publication	O
--	O
Viellé	O
du	O
Chateau	O
--	O
after	O
jumbling	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
exercise	O
for	O
ye	O
old	O
folks	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Madme-	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
where	O
we	O
met	O
the	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
was	O
in	O
charming	O
spirits	O
&	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
oClock	O
Tuesday	O
13	O
th	O
:	O
July	O
1784	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
:	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Amaria	B-pers
&	O
another	O
Man	O
brought	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
fine	O
Vase	O
to	O
deposit	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Care	O
.	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
drawings	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
from	O
it	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
indeed	O
inimitably	O
executed	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Caprianne	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
not	O
obeyed	O
his	O
orders	O
in	O
carrying	O
ye	O
.	O
Vase	O
to	O
shew	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
c	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
C	B-pers
:	I-pers
a	O
Person	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
contain	O
this	O
precious	O
work	O
of	O
Art	O
.	O
J	B-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
denied	O
.	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
affectionate	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
E——	I-pers
's	O
Father	O
recd	O
..	O
also	O
--	O
long	O
letters	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
(	O
her	O
Son	O
)	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
we	O
had	O
as	O
usual	O
dumb	O
Waiters	O
,	O
&	O
no	O
Servts	O
..	O
wch	O
..	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
comfortable	O
methods	O
of	O
dining	O
as	O
it	O
lays	O
no	O
restraint	O
on	O
conversation	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
day	O
afternoon	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
with	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
meſsage	O
from	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Lady	B-pers
Stor	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
another	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
--	O
their	O
Reasons	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
a	O
drawing	O
box	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
to	O
arrange	O
&	O
give	O
orders	O
about	O
to	O
her	O
Cabinet	O
Maker	O
--	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
Chariot	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
after	O
them	O
&	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
to	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
tomorrows	O
Post	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
had	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Vase	O
&	O
safely	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
tormenting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Sen	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
promising	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
Saturday	O
&	O
then	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
accompany	O
me	O
to	O
White-Hall	O
--	O
there	O
we	O
separated	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
AMaria	B-pers
--	O
had	O
a	O
conference	O
with	O
her	O
Porter	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
apartments	O
&	O
gave	O
those	O
orders	O
she	O
had	O
requested	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
letter	O
of	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
during	O
my	O
absence	O
&	O
left	O
word	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
one	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
left	O
ym	O
.	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
one	O
for	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
to	O
days	O
Post	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D——	I-pers
Sen	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
before	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
ye	O
..	O
Villa	O
wch	O
..	O
is	O
situated	O
on	O
the	O
banks	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
--	O
between	O
Bātersea	O
&	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
left	O
her	O
sweet	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
my	O
care	O
whilst	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Julia	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Cousin	O
Master	B-pers
Dawon	I-pers
Vesey	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
much	O
occupied	O
in	O
attending	O
to	O
a	O
Hen	O
&	O
her	O
chickens	O
wch	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
had	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
company	O
at	O
Dinner	O
--	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
boys	O
--	O
Julia	B-pers
ye	O
.	O
Tutor	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Town	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
I	O
strolled	O
about	O
ye	O
garden	O
ye	O
.	O
Shruberry	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
made	O
me	O
tell	O
her	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
she	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
made	O
me	O
very	O
happy	O
by	O
aſsuring	O
me	O
of	O
their	O
warmest	O
approbation	O
&	O
said	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
their	O
warm	O
kind	O
friendship	O
for	O
me	O
dictated	O
Nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
agreeable	O
than	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
Lord	B-pers
D——y	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
collection	O
of	O
Medals	O
he	O
had	O
purchased	O
--	O
Gold	O
&	O
Silver	O
all	O
English	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Wars	O
Queens	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
at	O
11	O
one	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
's	O
Maid	O
's	O
attended	O
to	O
undreſs	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
distiled	O
Rose	O
&	O
Mint	O
Water	O
to	O
remember	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
still	O
Thursday	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
6	O
&	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
the	O
freshneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Morning	O
air	O
&	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Habit	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
brush	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
to	O
finish	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
en	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
,	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
&	O
make	O
Breakfast	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
join	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
.	O
breakfast	O
Room	O
--	O
Vesey	B-pers
Dawon	I-pers
always	O
breakfasts	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
tutor	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
came	O
from	O
Town	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
he	O
was	O
wth-	O
us	O
by	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
:	O
Lord	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
,	O
she	O
repeated	O
to	O
me	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
me	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
approved	O
my	O
future	O
preference	O
in	O
chusing	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartry	I-pers
s	O
character	O
She	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
another	O
day	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
not	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
above	O
a	O
Night	O
from	O
Town	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
this	O
dear	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
friend	O
at	O
'	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
Lord	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
flowers	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
&	O
carried	O
some	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
yesterday	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
engaged	O
both	O
