TOKEN	NE
Exeter	B-place
Friday	O
10	O
Sepr	O
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Paynters	B-pers
set	O
off	O
on	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
o	O
ldest	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
may	O
die	O
very	O
suddenly	O
--	O
The	O
younger	O
has	O
an	O
uncommon	O
red	O
face	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
his	O
Eye	O
brows	O
like	O
Mrs	B-pers
White	I-pers
&	O
is	O
so	O
near	O
sited	O
that	O
he	O
comes	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
his	O
Eyes	O
closed	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
advanced	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
yards	O
his	O
Eye	O
Lids	O
begin	O
to	O
Twinkle	O
&	O
you	O
can	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
Eyes	O
--	O
by	O
Candlelight	O
they	O
have	O
uncommonly	O
brilliancy	O
&	O
look	O
beautiful	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
breakfast	O
this	O
morning	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Nose	O
had	O
bled	O
twice	O
yesterday	O
&	O
this	O
morning	O
he	O
awoke	O
wh-	O
his	O
Mouth	O
full	O
of	O
blood	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
clever	O
young	O
Man	O
--	O
They	O
disappointed	O
us	O
of	O
setting	O
out	O
to	O
day	O
as	O
they	O
seemed	O
undecided	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
hint	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
--	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
fishing	O
rod	O
but	O
the	O
water	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
State	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Gun	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
fin	O
d	O
Thursday	O
--	O
The	O
morning	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
&	O
kept	O
us	O
in	O
susp	O
ense	O
about	O
12	O
it	O
cleared	O
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
yr-	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
letter	O
arrived	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
&	O
stopt	O
to	O
feed	O
our	O
horses	O
at	O
Brickleigh	B-place
where	O
Bamfield	B-pers
More	I-pers
Cerew	I-pers
was	O
born	O
&	O
buried	O
--	O
in	O
our	O
Way	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
we	O
paſsed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
's	O
of	O
Worth	O
whos	O
wife	O
committed	O
a	O
faux	O
pas	O
with	O
a	O
Footman	O
&	O
was	O
packed	O
off	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Man	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
fortune	O
&	O
was	O
made	O
very	O
miserable	O
by	O
the	O
misconduct	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
had	O
several	O
Children	O
--	O
We	O
also	O
paſsed	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
Washfield	B-place
where	O
Hatfield	B-pers
lived	O
&	O
flourished	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
with	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Wife	O
before	O
he	O
married	O
Mary	B-pers
of	I-pers
Buttermere	I-pers
&	O
was	O
hanged	O
for	O
franking	O
a	O
Letter	O
--	O
We	O
paſsed	O
at	O
a	O
Miles	O
distance	O
Killerton	B-place
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
T.	I-pers
Dyke	I-pers
Ackland	I-pers
&	O
saw	O
Sir	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Northcote	I-pers
s	O
place	O
--	O
The	O
Vale	O
from	O
Tiverton	B-place
is	O
very	O
fine	O
&	O
at	O
Brickleigh	B-place
it	O
begins	O
to	O
expand	O
thro	O
very	O
rich	O
land	O
&	O
forms	O
a	O
wide	O
Valley	O
with	O
the	O
Ex	B-place
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
the	O
hills	O
covered	O
at	O
intervalls	O
with	O
fine	O
Woods	O
--	O
adjoining	O
every	O
House	O
&	O
Cottage	O
is	O
an	O
Orchard	O
--	O
this	O
year	O
wearing	O
a	O
melancholy	O
appearance	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
great	O
dependance	O
on	O
Apples	O
for	O
Cyder	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
beverage	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
these	O
Orchards	O
when	O
the	O
Trees	O
are	O
in	O
bloom	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
charming	O
Effect	O
as	O
few	O
things	O
equal	O
in	O
beauty	O
the	O
Apple	O
bloſsom	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
promised	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
from	O
the	O
prospect	O
from	O
3	O
mile	O
hill	O
near	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
said	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
fancied	O
the	O
imagination	O
was	O
already	O
satisfied	O
&	O
expected	O
the	O
natural	O
Consequence	O
--	O
but	O
my	O
Admiration	O
of	O
the	O
Scene	O
far	O
exceeded	O
all	O
expectation	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
raptures	O
--	O
The	O
View	O
is	O
bounded	O
in	O
various	O
parts	O
by	O
the	O
horizon	O
at	O
such	O
distance	O
that	O
a	O
further	O
extent	O
could	O
not	O
gratify	O
the	O
natural	O
sight	O
&	O
the	O
Mind	O
remains	O
satisfied	O
--	O
this	O
enchanting	O
Scenery	O
consists	O
of	O
/an	O
immense	O
extent	O
of	O
the	O
richest	O
Land	O
&	O
the	O
Green	O
is	O
so	O
thickly	O
interspersed	O
wh-	O
the	O
Yellow	O
that	O
it	O
increases	O
the	O
gratification	O
by	O
a	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
plenty	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
Cultivation	O
of	O
so	O
rich	O
a	O
Soil	O
with	O
the	O
bleſsing	O
of	O
providence	O
--	O
the	O
Hills	O
rise	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
heigth	O
&	O
are	O
either	O
clothed	O
wh-	O
fine	O
Woods	O
or	O
cultivated	O
to	O
their	O
Summits	O
--	O
on	O
what	O
side	O
soever	O
you	O
look	O
the	O
Scenery	O
is	O
equally	O
fine	O
--	O
When	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
Summit	O
of	O
the	O
hill	O
we	O
looked	O
down	O
upon	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
Exmouth	B-place
&	O
the	O
Country	O
beyond	O
these	O
places	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exceed	O
in	O
beauty	O
any	O
where	O
--	O
We	O
got	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
at	O
6	O
&	O
immediately	O
began	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
we	O
saw	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
almost	O
every	O
part	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
concluding	O
a	O
Rehearsal	O
for	O
Monday	O
when	O
Catalani	B-pers
is	O
to	O
sing	O
&	O
we	O
fixed	O
wh-	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
Organ	O
for	O
us	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
walk	O
near	O
the	O
the	O
Castle	O
called	O
Northonly	O
--	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
broad	O
Walks	O
midst	O
lofty	O
Elms	O
that	O
conceal	O
the	O
Rays	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
&	O
where	O
several	O
thousands	O
may	O
walk	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
--	O
here	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
aſsemble	O
the	O
whole	O
people	O
of	O
Exeter	B-place
who	O
are	O
inclined	O
to	O
walks	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
stationed	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
bands	O
of	O
Music	O
at	O
different	O
parts	O
--	O
You	O
can	O
form	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
beauty	O
&	O
luxury	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
without	O
seeing	O
it	O
--	O
We	O
dined	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
became	O
dark	O
&	O
in	O
course	O
of	O
time	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
sallied	O
out	O
before	O
my	O
Companion	O
was	O
up	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
which	O
has	O
cost	O
an	O
immense	O
sum	O
--	O
I	O
measured	O
600	O
feet	O
in	O
front	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Barracks	O
which	O
are	O
very	O
extensive	O
--	O
A	O
Cart	O
load	O
of	O
Lime	O
Stone	O
paſsed	O
containing	O
a	O
beautiful	O
red	O
Stone	O
striated	O
wh-	O
white	O
that	O
gives	O
it	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
Marble	O
--	O
After	O
breakfast	O
--	O
at	O
wch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
youngest	O
Son	O
partook	O
--	O
a	O
fine	O
boy	O
of	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
the	O
Schoolboy	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Leakey	I-pers
to	O
see	O
his	O
pictures	O
--	O
his	O
portraits	O
are	O
good	O
&	O
his	O
likeneſses	O
strong	O
&	O
his	O
Landscapes	O
have	O
great	O
Merit	O
--	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
Organ	O
&	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Bishop	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
magnificent	O
throne	O
&	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
--	O
Parkin	B-pers
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Organ	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
excuse	O
&	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
took	O
an	O
Oppy	O
during	O
the	O
Chant	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
delicate	O
expreſsion	O
of	O
the	O
full	O
Organ	O
which	O
astonished	O
me	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
separate	O
Arrangment	O
of	O
pipes	O
of	O
prodigious	O
thickneſs	O
diameter	O
that	O
produces	O
a	O
Sound	O
unexampled	O
--	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Exmouth	B-place
&	O
I	O
disputed	O
wh-	O
James	B-pers
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
wrong	O
way	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
repeatedly	O
at	O
Exmouth	B-place
so	O
I	O
submitted	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
proceeded	O
a	O
mile	O
we	O
met	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
acquaintances	O
who	O
laught	O
at	O
him	O
&	O
set	O
us	O
right	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
wrong	O
headedneſs	O
we	O
lost	O
3	O
miles	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
right	O
road	O
again	O
at	O
Sir	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
at	O
Wear	B-place
2	O
miles	O
fm	O
.	O
Exeter	B-place
a	O
pretty	O
place	O
--	O
When	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
on	O
a	O
Voyage	O
he	O
observed	O
a	O
Pig	O
had	O
fallen	O
into	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
he	O
immeadiately	O
ordered	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
poor	O
pig	O
he	O
cr	O
ied	O
out	O
will	O
be	O
drown	O
lower	O
a	O
boat	O
directly	O
&	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
--	O
Some	O
one	O
unfortunately	O
said	O
the	O
pig	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Midshipman	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
said	O
Oh	O
poor	O
pig	O
must	O
be	O
drowned	O
--	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
stop	O
the	O
Ship	O
for	O
a	O
pig	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
One	O
day	O
meetg	O
several	O
poor	O
Women	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
--	O
They	O
answered	O
My	O
Lady	O
had	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
some	O
Broth	O
--	O
Broth	O
Broth	O
said	O
the	O
Niggard	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
Broth	O
here	O
--	O
Go	O
about	O
yr-	O
busineſs	O
--	O
!	O
!	O
A	O
Gentn	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Neighborhood	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
wh-	O
him	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Hay	O
or	O
Corn	O
for	O
the	O
horses	O
&	O
after	O
dinner	O
the	O
Meat	O
was	O
put	O
away	O
&	O
Nothing	O
for	O
the	O
Servants	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Servants	O
took	O
the	O
horses	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
fed	O
both	O
parties	O
they	O
returned	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Master	O
home	O
.	O
who	O
wrote	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
visit	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
--	O
The	O
road	O
turned	O
short	O
at	O
the	O
town	B-place
of	I-place
Topsham	I-place
&	O
we	O
rode	O
thro	O
the	O
town	O
&	O
had	O
great	O
difficulty	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
horses	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
upermost	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
dreadful	O
place	O
we	O
miſsed	O
our	O
way	O
again	O
--	O
We	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
get	O
to	O
Exmouth	B-place
from	O
whence	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
finest	O
view	O
of	O
Sea	O
&	O
Land	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
imagined	O
--	O
the	O
Sea	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
Small	O
Craft	O
&	O
acroſs	O
the	O
River	O
is	O
seen	O
Lord	B-pers
Lisburne	I-pers
's	O
fine	O
place	O
Mamhead	B-place
&	O
Powderham	B-place
Castle	I-place
--	O
the	O
Wretch	O
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
America	B-place
--	O
Saturday	O
1	O
OClock	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
over	O
all	O
yesterday	O
for	O
this	O
letter	O
--	O
At	O
10	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Bishop	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
sent	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Choiristers	O
for	O
the	O
Youth	O
who	O
was	O
playing	O
the	O
Organ	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
join	O
in	O
Te	O
Deum	O
Laudamus	O
composed	O
by	O
Jackson	B-pers
&	O
afterwards	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
previous	O
to	O
his	O
singing	O
an	O
Anthem	O
Soleas	O
by	O
Kent	O
except	O
the	O
concluding	O
Chorus	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
perfectly	O
enchanted	O
with	O
the	O
Anthem	O
--	O
his	O
Voice	O
is	O
the	O
finest	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
&	O
the	O
Organ	O
is	O
reckoned	O
the	O
grandest	O
in	O
Europe	O
--	O
the	O
pipes	O
being	O
2	O
Inches	O
in	O
Diameter	O
wider	O
than	O
the	O
Organ	O
at	O
Ulm	O
--	O
We	O
staid	O
after	O
the	O
Service	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Rehearsal	O
for	O
Monday	O
--	O
The	O
Bishop	O
came	O
in	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
friendly	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
liked	O
the	O
Anthems	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
delighted	O
he	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
&	O
said	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
ungrateful	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
as	O
he	O
ordered	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
lamented	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
full	O
Organ	O
--	O
he	O
instantly	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
played	O
&	O
the	O
Choir	O
sung	O
that	O
noble	O
Chorus	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
&	O
his	O
Rider	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
truly	O
magnificent	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
just	O
setting	O
out	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
wh	O
.	O
every	O
thing	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
&	O
heard	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
you	O
must	O
make	O
this	O
out	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
--	O
Present	O
my	O
dutiful	O
Love	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
&	O
Comps	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
Single	O
Sheet	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
