TOKEN	NE
Margate	B-place
October	O
27	O
th	O
1789	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
has	O
elapsed	O
since	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
.	O
In	O
August	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
October	O
!	O
shocking	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
justifying	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
silence	O
,	O
even	O
by	O
your	O
example	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
excuse	O
it	O
.	O
various	O
indeed	O
are	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Events	O
&	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
3	O
Months	O
!	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
surprised	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
who	O
never	O
move	O
from	O
Horton	B-place
,	O
from	O
June	O
to	O
January	O
!	O
poor	O
Bell	B-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
all	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
low	O
fever	O
&	O
other	O
nervous	O
complaints	O
,	O
and	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
thought	O
seabathing	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
in	O
October	O
--	O
we	O
fixed	O
upon	O
this	O
place	O
as	O
the	O
nearest	O
to	O
London	B-place
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
most	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
bathing	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
arrived	O
here	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
the	O
begini	O
n	O
g	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
after	O
stopping	O
two	O
days	O
in	O
Town	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
.	O
we	O
like	O
it	O
vastly	O
,	O
the	O
country	O
about	O
it	O
&	O
almost	O
the	O
whole	O
Island	O
is	O
extremely	O
pretty	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
walks	O
&	O
drive	O
's	O
beautiful	O
--	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
of	O
People	O
we	O
knew	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
acquaintance	O
we	O
found	O
were	O
Colel	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
York	I-pers
&	O
Ld	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
gone	O
long	O
since	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
quite	O
deserted	O
&	O
the	O
only	O
people	O
left	O
are	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
since	O
our	O
arrival	O
here	O
whom	O
we	O
live	O
with	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
like	O
extremely	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
has	O
received	O
the	O
greatest	O
imaginable	O
benefit	O
from	O
the	O
bathing	O
,	O
&	O
air	O
,	O
her	O
strength	O
and	O
appetite	O
are	O
returned	O
&	O
every	O
bad	O
sympt	O
om	O
abated	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
removed	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
his	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
no	O
object	O
to	O
interest	O
him	O
&	O
no	O
occupation	O
,	O
&	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
long	O
since	O
gratified	O
his	O
curiosity	O
in	O
riding	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
tired	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
--	O
we	O
leave	O
it	O
tomorrow	O
sev'night	O
,	O
make	O
a	O
visit	O
on	O
our	O
road	O
to	O
London	B-place
&	O
shall	O
be	O
there	O
about	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
stays	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
on	O
busineſs	O
and	O
then	O
returns	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
till	O
the	O
begin	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
I	O
duri	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
time	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
&	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
&	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
meet	O
&	O
settle	O
in	O
Town	O
at	O
before	O
Xmas	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
news	O
that	O
will	O
surprise	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
preface	O
my	O
communication	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
by	O
an	O
injunction	O
of	O
secrecy	O
&	O
must	O
beg	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Inshort	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
last	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
--	O
I	O
see	O
your	O
astonishment	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
recollect	O
how	O
seriously	O
I	O
aſsured	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
truth	O
in	O
the	O
reports	O
that	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
word	O
that	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
truth	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
an	O
event	O
now	O
so	O
near	O
taking	O
place	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
even	O
myself	O
how	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
brought	O
about	O
--	O
suffice	O
it	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
original	O
obvious	O
objections	O
to	O
the	O
connection	O
still	O
remain	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
myself	O
to	O
submit	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
consideration	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
merits	O
&	O
good	O
qualities	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
prospect	O
of	O
rea	O
son	O
able	O
happineſs	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
until	O
the	O
beginni	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
January	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
is	O
now	O
in	O
Dorsetshire	B-place
with	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
left	O
Horton	B-place
&	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
here	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
then	O
in	O
to	O
Dorsetshire	B-place
--	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
who	O
were	O
extremely	O
kind	O
&	O
gracious	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
desired	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
kept	O
a	O
secret	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
thanked	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
your	O
long	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
hapy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
recovered	O
&	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dick	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
receivd	O
so	O
much	O
benefit	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
us	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
love	O
to	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
who	O
I	O
imagine	O
grows	O
more	O
&	O
more	O
a	O
comfort	O
&	O
delight	O
to	O
you	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
till	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
&	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
this	O
old	O
old	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
stomack	O
which	O
I	O
suffered	O
from	O
for	O
so	O
many	O
years	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
leave	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sufferi	O
n	O
g	O
cruelly	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
&	O
must	O
leave	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
after	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
aſsured	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
attachment	O
&	O
Friendship	O
--	O
adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
most	O
affec	O
:	O
yours	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
G——	I-pers
Bell	B-pers
is	O
not	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
truth	O
whatever	O
in	O
the	O
report	O
you	O
heard	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
