TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
Janry	O
15	O
th	O
1770	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
not	O
measure	O
my	O
regard	O
by	O
my	O
writeing	O
for	O
bellieve	O
me	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
faill	O
towards	O
you	O
in	O
reality	O
however	O
much	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
lately	O
in	O
Appearance	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
yours	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
Accounts	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
my	O
only	O
Sister	O
since	O
then	O
,	O
yr	O
two	O
Eldest	O
Cousins	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Measels	O
Frank	B-pers
a	O
feaver	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
a	O
Severe	O
Rhumatism	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
you	O
See	O
has	O
been	O
greatly	O
against	O
Writteing	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
hold	O
me	O
excused	O
&	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
soon	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
do	O
this	O
very	O
cold	O
Weather	O
none	O
of	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
we	O
Wish	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
this	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
do	O
us	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
bellieve	O
--	O
.	O
Last	O
Post	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
--	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
asures	O
me	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
&	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
their	O
present	O
Situation	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
goes	O
well	O
there	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
news	O
from	O
hence	O
could	O
Amuse	O
you	O
this	O
town	O
begins	O
to	O
grow	O
very	O
Gay	O
How	O
do	O
yr	O
Babylonians	O
amuse	O
themselves	O
?	O
we	O
have	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
with	O
us	O
too	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
Weeds	O
that	O
grow	O
in	O
every	O
Soill	O
--	O
Accept	O
all	O
our	O
best	O
compts	O
:	O
(	O
&	O
though	O
late	O
)	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Saison	O
--	O
&	O
present	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
your	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
--	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
will	O
ever	O
forgett	O
all	O
yr	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
us	O
when	O
wth	O
you	O
--	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
bellieve	O
me	O
Ever	O
your	O
Affect	O
&	O
faithfull	O
Hum	O
ble	O
Sert	O
:	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Enclose	O
as	O
Useal	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
