TOKEN	NE
Monday	O
13	O
James	B-pers
went	O
a	O
Coursing	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
&	O
returned	O
to	O
breakfast	O
--	O
&	O
went	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
that	O
was	O
over	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
came	O
at	O
ten	O
&	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
morning	O
for	O
fishing	O
&	O
the	O
Water	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
state	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
directly	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
fish	O
very	O
cautious	O
&	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
humour	O
to	O
take	O
our	O
flies	O
,	O
however	O
by	O
dint	O
of	O
Persevereance	O
&	O
superior	O
skill	O
we	O
caught	O
30	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
fished	O
on	O
horseback	O
--	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
is	O
downright	O
poaching	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
he	O
fishes	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
&	O
can	O
throw	O
his	O
flies	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
the	O
largest	O
fish	O
harbour	O
--	O
Nothwithstanding	O
my	O
disadvantage	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
half	O
his	O
Number	O
&	O
a	O
blister	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
We	O
caught	O
several	O
small	O
fishes	O
that	O
are	O
very	O
like	O
Trout	O
&	O
are	O
only	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
Ex	B-place
&	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
They	O
are	O
very	O
pretty	O
&	O
have	O
a	O
Van	O
Dyke	O
pattern	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
the	O
proper	O
Names	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
--	O
Dayvy	B-pers
dined	O
here	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
returned	O
with	O
a	O
Hare	O
&	O
a	O
Leveret	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
At	O
8	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
's	O
of	O
Morebath	B-place
A	O
Man	O
came	O
at	O
7	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
very	O
bad	O
&	O
desired	O
James	B-pers
to	O
christen	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
stopt	O
him	O
near	O
Bampton	B-place
Mr.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Bere	I-pers
's	O
Servt	O
.	O
met	O
me	O
to	O
conduct	O
me	O
acroſs	O
the	O
Country	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Oppy	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Scenery	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
stationed	O
at	O
a	O
Farm	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Rendezvous	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
waiting	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Farm	O
House	O
&	O
chatted	O
with	O
the	O
respectable	O
looking	O
Dame	O
--	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Potatoes	O
which	O
were	O
now	O
sold	O
at	O
4/	O
pr	O
.	O
Sack	O
of	O
8	O
pecks	O
was	O
so	O
plentiful	O
the	O
Year	O
after	O
the	O
great	O
Scarcity	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
at	O
2½	O
pr	O
.	O
Sack	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Bere	I-pers
came	O
at	O
11	O
&	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
few	O
Birds	O
&	O
each	O
killed	O
one	O
--	O
The	O
Land	O
lies	O
so	O
uneven	O
&	O
in	O
many	O
parts	O
is	O
as	O
steep	O
of	O
the	O
Roof	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
they	O
are	O
cultivated	O
unleſs	O
they	O
use	O
Goats	O
to	O
draw	O
their	O
ploughs	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
some	O
hills	O
where	O
Corn	O
had	O
grown	O
&	O
also	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
very	O
fine	O
Turnips	O
--	O
James	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
went	O
a	O
coursing	O
wh-	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
but	O
had	O
no	O
succeſs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
dined	O
there	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Niece	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
his	O
Elder	O
Brothers	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
&	O
Sister	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
B	I-pers
--	O
I	O
observed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
always	O
addreſsed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bedcock	I-pers
to	O
soften	O
as	O
much	O
poſsible	O
the	O
asperity	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
--	O
The	O
Gentn	O
.	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
9	O
&	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
tired	O
by	O
running	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
those	O
precipices	O
&	O
some	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
had	O
been	O
exceſsively	O
hot	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Bere	I-pers
came	O
at	O
9	O
&	O
we	O
sallied	O
out	O
again	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
shooting	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
a	O
coursing	O
--	O
We	O
shooters	O
found	O
some	O
Birds	O
&	O
killed	O
two	O
Brace	O
which	O
were	O
preſsed	O
on	O
Me	O
&	O
also	O
a	O
Bird	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
Description	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
shot	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
grounds	O
&	O
which	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
giving	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
keep	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
fixed	O
for	O
putting	O
Salt	O
on	O
their	O
tails	O
--	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
Coursers	O
&	O
returned	O
at	O
2	O
--	O
had	O
some	O
Luncheon	O
&	O
tho	O
much	O
preſsed	O
to	O
stay	O
another	O
day	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
home	O
--	O
laden	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
,	O
heavily	O
wh-	O
spirit	O
--	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Thursday	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
by	O
a	O
Meſsenger	O
who	O
is	O
going	O
,	O
not	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
6	O
Bird	O
's	O
--	O
James	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
fixed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
this	O
morning	O
to	O
kill	O
if	O
poſsible	O
a	O
Hare	O
to	O
send	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
8	O
that	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
however	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Times	O
Newspaper	O
here	O
which	O
Somebody	O
had	O
sent	O
detailing	O
Bonaparte	B-pers
s	O
Succeſs	O
at	O
Dresden	B-place
,	O
which	O
dampens	O
hopes	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
surprising	O
Being	O
he	O
is	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
the	O
same	O
paſsion	O
for	O
a	O
Garden	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
--	O
She	O
employs	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
Weeds	O
&	O
gives	O
her	O
4	O
d	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
is	O
an	O
immense	O
size	O
&	O
upwards	O
of	O
80	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
thinks	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
Work	O
--	O
it	O
contributes	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Womans	O
health	O
&	O
she	O
does	O
something	O
for	O
the	O
Charity	O
--	O
The	O
Soil	O
here	O
tho	O
stoney	O
is	O
so	O
favorable	O
to	O
Vegetation	O
that	O
Trees	O
&	O
Shrubs	O
grow	O
too	O
fast	O
&	O
the	O
Fruits	O
ripen	O
here	O
perfectly	O
well	O
tho	O
the	O
Situation	O
is	O
very	O
high	O
--	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
's	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
kind	O
of	O
fruit	O
ripe	O
--	O
tho	O
his	O
place	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
retired	O
Valley	O
his	O
House	O
is	O
very	O
pretty	O
&	O
the	O
Garden	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
neat	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
farmer	O
&	O
has	O
beautiful	O
Cattle	O
--	O
Oxen	O
are	O
used	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
&	O
the	O
Drivers	O
use	O
a	O
continual	O
Noise	O
in	O
driving	O
them	O
wch	O
has	O
a	O
melancholy	O
tone	O
--	O
they	O
cheer	O
the	O
Beasts	O
by	O
callg	O
out	O
their	O
Names	O
which	O
are	O
--	O
such	O
as	O
these	O
--	O
Good	O
Luck	O
--	O
Forty	O
--	O
Young	O
&	O
Tender	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
whole	O
ends	O
with	O
a	O
plaintive	O
Note	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
singular	O
Effect	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
the	O
Country	O
seems	O
quite	O
in	O
motion	O
as	O
every	O
body	O
is	O
busy	O
in	O
taking	O
in	O
their	O
Corn	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
heard	O
on	O
every	O
side	O
--	O
Last	O
night	O
We	O
walked	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
driving	O
&	O
addreſsing	O
the	O
Oxen	O
--	O
Sledges	O
are	O
used	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
&	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Ponies	O
which	O
will	O
contain	O
a	O
prodigious	O
quantity	O
of	O
Corn	O
or	O
Hay	O
&	O
is	O
used	O
on	O
the	O
precipices	O
where	O
no	O
Sledge	O
could	O
be	O
drawn	O
up	O
the	O
Steep	O
--	O
these	O
ponies	O
are	O
most	O
formidable	O
Things	O
to	O
meet	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
Lane	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
wide	O
&	O
so	O
large	O
&	O
would	O
terrify	O
a	O
foreign	O
horse	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
farm	O
supposing	O
this	O
mark	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
saddle	O
&	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
whole	O
Lane	O
when	O
loaded	O
--	O
Crook	O
is	O
the	O
proper	O
Name	O
--	O
9	O
OClock	O
it	O
rains	O
therefore	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
rural	O
Sports	O
--	O
The	O
Barometer	O
is	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
rise	O
therefore	O
it	O
may	O
clear	O
up	O
at	O
12	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
will	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Sketch	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
to	O
remember	O
myself	O
--	O
My	O
Sketches	O
require	O
d	O
explanation	O
Viz	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
meant	O
for	O
a	O
Tree	O
&	O
so	O
on	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
understand	O
them	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
some	O
Company	O
to	O
dine	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
a	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Teale	I-pers
who	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Neighborhood	O
--	O
Others	O
invited	O
who	O
were	O
engaged	O
--	O
we	O
dine	O
tomorrow	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
Sunday	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
preach	O
I	O
eggspect	O
to	O
be	O
zatizfied	O
wh-	O
the	O
preaching	O
&	O
zinging	O
wch	O
I	O
hear	O
iz	O
exzellent	O
Hayden	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
offered	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
or	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
introduction	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
motion	O
after	O
Monday	O
therefore	O
if	O
You	O
write	O
on	O
Saturday	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
Poor	O
Robert	B-pers
has	O
been	O
ill	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
bad	O
leg	O
from	O
a	O
kick	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
gave	O
him	O
--	O
his	O
blood	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
state	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Bleſsing	O
if	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
please	O
God	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
object	O
--	O
his	O
Eyes	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
fixed	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
his	O
hands	O
are	O
of	O
little	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
walks	O
wh-	O
great	O
difficulty	O
&	O
speaks	O
with	O
more	O
--	O
yet	O
is	O
very	O
sensible	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
fits	O
frequently	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Stag	O
Hunt	O
yesterday	O
--	O
They	O
commenced	O
about	O
ten	O
miles	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
wished	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
but	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
contrive	O
it	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
Distance	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
unique	O
Diversion	O
,	O
hunting	O
the	O
Wild	O
Stag	O
&	O
confined	O
to	O
their	O
Country	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Haunch	O
that	O
weighed	O
47½	O
lb	O
&	O
the	O
fat	O
was	O
near	O
3	O
Inches	O
thick	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
ye-	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
that	O
its	O
flavour	O
far	O
exceeds	O
Pork	O
Venison	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
fuſs	O
is	O
made	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
The	O
Hinds	O
are	O
hunted	O
in	O
October	O
--	O
Adieu	O
till	O
12	O
OClock	O
as	O
probably	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Most	O
Affy	O
Yrs	O
.	O
J.D	B-pers
--	O
Best	O
Regards	O
from	O
hence	O
--	O
James	B-pers
spoke	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Coleridge	I-pers
's	O
/a	O
native	O
of	O
Devon	B-place
/	O
examination	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
with	O
prodigious	O
Enthusiasm	O
his	O
Examns	O
.	O
took	O
up	O
2	O
days	O
--	O
it	O
embraced	O
almost	O
every	O
Science	O
Latin	O
Greek	O
&	O
Hebrew	O
--	O
in	O
every	O
Thing	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
frequently	O
was	O
interrupted	O
by	O
universal	O
Applause	O
--	O
He	O
says	O
Mant	B-pers
s	O
Bampton	O
Lectures	O
were	O
admired	O
beyond	O
any	O
since	O
White	B-pers
's	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
--	O
The	O
day	O
is	O
clearing	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
fair	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
a	O
fishing	O
&	O
shall	O
meet	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
--	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
