TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
presents	O
his	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
begs	O
she	O
will	O
do	O
him	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
accept	O
the	O
Drawing	O
of	O
Pevensea	O
Castle	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
have	O
waited	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
thought	O
a	O
visit	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
supposes	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
busied	O
in	O
preparing	O
for	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
flatters	O
himself	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
offer	O
her	O
the	O
Compliments	O
of	O
the	O
Season	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Jan	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
