TOKEN	NE
Wing	B-place
--	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
--	O
May	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
We	O
are	O
all	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
Letter	O
you	O
wrote	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
impatient	O
for	O
a	O
repetition	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
treat	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
a	O
great	O
favor	O
to	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
--	O
as	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
.	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
them	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
real	O
state	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
the	O
Accounts	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
papers	O
are	O
tremendous	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
some	O
people	O
say	O
that	O
they	O
hope	O
matters	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
extremities	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Government	O
will	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
to	O
write	O
again	O
--	O
so	O
are	O
my	O
Sisters	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
reason	O
--	O
we	O
might	O
hazard	O
an	O
opinion	O
--	O
or	O
they	O
might	O
interpret	O
something	O
--	O
into	O
an	O
opinion	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
doubt	O
the	O
integrity	O
of	O
our	O
Agent	O
.	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
employments	O
under	O
Government	O
.	O
besides	O
being	O
an	O
Army	O
Agent	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
no	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
ease	O
to	O
my	O
mind	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
relieved	O
from	O
this	O
suspense	O
.	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
ever	O
so	O
bad	O
.	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
the	O
worst	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
sister	O
dare	O
brook	O
worse	O
than	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
--	O
they	O
both	O
absolutely	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
bed	O
last	O
Night	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
agitation	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
Camphire	O
Julep	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
for	O
hours	O
.	O
the	O
accounts	O
in	O
the	O
Sun	O
of	O
this	O
2	O
d	O
Mutiny	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
alarming	O
,	O
that	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
its	O
Influence	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
terrible	O
people	O
within	O
4	O
Miles	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
that	O
they	O
sunk	O
my	O
spirits	O
almost	O
to	O
despair	O
--	O
I	O
culd	O
not	O
have	O
suppos	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Mutiny	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
fleet	O
,	O
could	O
have	O
afforded	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
any	O
ones	O
Soul	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
report	O
that	O
Tho	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
brought	O
from	O
Market	O
was	O
--	O
that	O
the	O
Baptists	O
were	O
all	O
hiſsing	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
&	O
Concluding	O
that	O
a	O
Revolution	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
if	O
not	O
already	O
begun	O
--	O
but	O
of	O
this	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
in	O
yr	O
Answer	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
this	O
morg	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
discontents	O
at	O
these	O
taxes	O
are	O
very	O
alarming	O
--	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
Partner	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
came	O
here	O
this	O
morg	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
who	O
mention	O
'd	O
his	O
apprehensions	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
ready	O
for	O
revolt	O
.	O
his	O
uneasineſs	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
falling	O
of	O
the	O
Stocks	O
.	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Property	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
some	O
Consolation	O
respecting	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
his	O
particular	O
truble	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
Man	O
who	O
attends	O
all	O
Fairs	O
&	O
Markets	O
is	O
too	O
good	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
dispositions	O
of	O
the	O
common	O
people	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
letters	O
from	O
London	B-place
yesterday	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Wedding	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
fashionable	O
Silk	O
for	O
Gowns	O
--	O
her	O
future	O
Consort	O
slept	O
at	O
Aylsbury	B-place
one	O
Night	O
last	O
Week	O
he	O
eat	O
Mutton	O
Chops	O
very	O
heartily	O
--	O
&	O
gave	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
great	O
comfort	O
for	O
as	O
they	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Excellent	O
appetite	O
--	O
also	O
yr	O
Cousin	O
Mansfield	O
s	O
approaching	O
Marriage	O
at	O
19	O
was	O
announc	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
these	O
Events	O
occupy	O
the	O
Gay	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Dr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
London	B-place
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
to	O
wait	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
or	O
fortnight	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
down	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
visit	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
postpon	O
'd	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
.	O
who	O
is	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
my	O
reluctance	O
.	O
to	O
move	O
--	O
makes	O
it	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
dread	O
the	O
interview	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
made	O
Ireland	B-place
my	O
excuse	O
,	O
for	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
--	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Holderneſs	I-pers
is	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
but	O
the	O
Operation	O
does	O
not	O
surprise	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
as	O
her	O
waiting	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
before	O
it	O
took	O
place	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Accept	O
our	O
United	O
&	O
most	O
affect	O
.	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
Health	O
&	O
prosperity	O
of	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
remember	O
us	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
.	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
ever	O
Affect	O
.	O
&	O
obliged	O
Friend	O
DBloſset	B-pers
--	O
NB	O
.	O
pray	O
never	O
mind	O
a	O
Frank	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
timely	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Charges	O
,	O
if	O
Ireland	B-place
sd	O
.	O
make	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
beg	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
about	O
£400	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Country	O
--	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
the	O
worst	O
Single	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
58	O
Lower	O
Brook	O
Street	O
Bond	O
Street	O
London	B-place
