TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
recovering	O
so	O
well	O
after	O
your	O
confinement	O
&	O
that	O
your	O
little	O
acquisition	O
is	O
also	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
state	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
who	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
yesterday	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
this	O
agreeable	O
information	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
favor	O
to	O
give	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
Nurse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
repay	O
you	O
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Paper	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
relative	O
to	O
your	O
Bond	O
which	O
I	O
discharged	O
last	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
instructions	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
advancing	O
extremely	O
well	O
,	O
its	O
situation	O
is	O
beyond	O
measure	O
beautiful	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
plan	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
disapproved	O
of	O
,	O
my	O
great	O
object	O
is	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
hereafter	O
be	O
worth	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
nearly	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
expend	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
rather	O
upon	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
scale	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
something	O
moderate	O
only	O
is	O
intended	O
,	O
our	O
ideas	O
enlarge	O
as	O
we	O
advance	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
too	O
often	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
we	O
parry	O
the	O
censure	O
of	O
vanity	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
escape	O
that	O
of	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
resolution	O
.	O
dont	O
expect	O
news	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
as	O
Bath	B-place
every	O
thing	O
is	O
known	O
immediately	O
--	O
Robert	B-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
grown	O
a	O
great	O
size	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
Madame	B-pers
Chauvet	I-pers
reproach	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
having	O
a	O
dirty	O
face	O
he	O
answerd	O
,	O
je	O
vous	O
demande	O
excuse	O
c'est	O
ma	O
barbe	O
Madame	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
248	O
Feby	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
-	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Feby	O
1787	O
