TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
--	O
August	O
6	O
th	O
:	O
1787	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
done	O
myself	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
answering	O
your	O
Letter	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Deal	O
of	O
Hurry	O
,	O
lately	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
easily	O
believe	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Mother	O
suddenly	O
took	O
the	O
Resolution	O
of	O
coming	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
:	O
she	O
had	O
long	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
;	O
not	O
for	O
any	O
Material	O
Indisposition	O
;	O
only	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
Head-Ach	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
says	O
,	O
is	O
bilious	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
because	O
of	O
our	O
new	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
we	O
expect	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
,	O
at	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
propose	O
staying	O
five	O
Weeks	O
longer	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
we	O
can	O
more	O
conveniently	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
London	B-place
,	O
than	O
at	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Bath	O
Season	O
.	O
Nothing	O
can	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
better	O
than	O
drinking	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
bathing	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
ago	O
--	O
You	O
ask	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
like	O
her	O
Choice	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Halsey	I-pers
has	O
all	O
the	O
Appearance	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
good-	O
natur	O
'd	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
whose	O
Disposition	O
is	O
suited	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Halsey	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Halsey	I-pers
was	O
not	O
delighted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
is	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
she	O
had	O
thoughts	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
;	O
not	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Health	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
Miſs	B-pers
A——	I-pers
C——	I-pers
(	O
having	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
Difficulties	O
,	O
)	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
break	O
up	O
House-keeping	O
;	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
--	O
he	O
therefore	O
,	O
suggested	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
Children	O
,	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
perhaps	O
a	O
few	O
Years	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Embaraſsments	O
.	O
Naples	B-place
was	O
the	O
Place	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Friends	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
an	O
eligible	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
Thoughts	O
o	O
f	O
it	O
an	O
d	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
of	O
Ge	O
neva	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
M	O
onths	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Family	O
of	O
great	O
respectability	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
on	O
a	O
Plan	O
of	O
Oeconomy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Stratford	I-pers
pretty	O
often	O
last	O
Winter	O
:	O
not	O
as	O
often	O
in	O
private	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
;	O
owing	O
partly	O
to	O
her	O
numerous	O
Occupations	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
)	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
frequently	O
indispos	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
does	O
not	O
act	O
all	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Precaution	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
paſs	O
some	O
Time	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
;	O
and	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
her	O
Summer	O
,	O
in	O
various	O
Visits	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
your	O
pretty	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
has	O
happily	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
now	O
reckon	O
her	O
Beauty	O
safe	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
We	O
hear	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
frequently	O
,	O
who	O
always	O
gives	O
us	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
is	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
's	O
Compts	O
:	O
attend	O
you	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
mine	O
also	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
sincerely	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
a	O
short	O
Time	O
before	O
we	O
left	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Cheshire	B-place
.	O
Supposed	O
--	O
Near	O
Macclesfield	B-place
