TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
26	O
th	O
My	O
dear	O
Hammy	B-pers
It	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
powour	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
till	O
to	O
Day	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
asure	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
ded	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
have	O
done	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
hear	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
night	O
we	O
set	O
with	O
mama	O
and	O
worked	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
night	O
we	O
played	O
at	O
commers	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
pole	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
s	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
Mr	B-pers
lite	I-pers
one	O
and	O
besides	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
yesterday	O
Mama	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
papa	O
in	O
the	O
faton	O
and	O
my	O
Brothers	O
and	O
conolel	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
went	O
on	O
Horse	O
back	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
asure	O
you	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
very	O
happy	O
here	O
.	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
there	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Holdderneſs	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
wamouth	I-pers
you	O
no	O
how	O
I	O
do	O
dislike	O
her	O
and	O
like	O
Lady	B-pers
Holderneſs	I-pers
but	O
I	O
do	O
promeſs	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
a	O
great	O
dile	O
of	O
cere	O
not	O
to	O
set	O
by	O
her	O
at	O
Diner	O
I	O
long	O
for	O
tusdy	O
my	O
Sisters	O
are	O
just	O
gane	O
out	O
of	O
walking	O
with	O
papa	O
and	O
Mama	O
and	O
all	O
My	O
Brothers	O
and	O
Goully	B-pers
and	O
all	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
tell	O
Ernest	B-pers
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
but	O
rather	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
him	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Hammy	B-pers
I	O
am	O
your	O
ever	O
efection	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
I	O
do	O
e	O
x	O
I	O
do	O
expect	O
this	O
Letter	O
ancered	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
