TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
Dec	O
:	O
3	O
d	O
1785	O
My	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
happy	O
your	O
long	O
expected	O
letter	O
made	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
despaired	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
thinking	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
give	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
yourself	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
no	O
such	O
letter	O
as	O
you	O
mention	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
since	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
I	O
answered	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
day	O
from	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
To	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
Health	O
&	O
happineſs	O
,	O
always	O
gives	O
me	O
unspeakable	O
happineſs	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
your	O
leisure	O
will	O
admit	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
--	O
excepting	O
an	O
accidental	O
Cold	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
--	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
after	O
the	O
great	O
loſs	O
I	O
have	O
sustained	O
--	O
You	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
every	O
pli	O
et	O
repli	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
will	O
conceive	O
what	O
it	O
has	O
felt	O
and	O
still	O
feels	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
give	O
to	O
my	O
situation	O
the	O
compaſsion	O
it	O
deserves	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
adore	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
how	O
tenderly	O
I	O
love	O
the	O
Sister	O
of	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
always	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
amiable	O
she	O
is	O
grown	O
,	O
how	O
strengthend	O
in	O
every	O
virtue	O
,	O
&	O
improved	O
in	O
every	O
grace	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
not	O
that	O
that	O
in	O
that	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
sincere	O
Friend	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
conceal	O
a	O
thought	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
as	O
she	O
enhanced	O
every	O
enjoyment	O
,	O
consoled	O
me	O
for	O
every	O
misfortune	O
At	O
the	O
dreadful	O
moment	O
of	O
separation	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
however	O
but	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
Heaven	O
with	O
gratitude	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
departed	O
in	O
tolerable	O
Health	O
--	O
excepting	O
loſs	O
of	O
appetite	O
&	O
sleep	O
,	O
all	O
her	O
Symtoms	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
she	O
will	O
receive	O
much	O
benefit	O
from	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
&	O
a	O
quiet	O
life	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
malgré	O
moi	O
in	O
very	O
bad	O
spirits	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
exerted	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
,	O
nothing	O
can	O
exceed	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
Kindneſs	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
away	O
the	O
moment	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
never	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
myself	O
one	O
Day	O
since	O
--	O
I	O
regularly	O
drive	O
&	O
sup	O
there	O
every	O
Day	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
till	O
the	B-pers
Argylls	I-pers
came	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
now	O
give	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
is	O
grown	O
fat	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
one	O
Evening	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
early	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
read	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
begun	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
harpsicord	O
,	O
practising	O
musick	O
takes	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
--	O
not	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
the	O
constant	O
letters	O
to	O
Nancy	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Winter	O
.	O
How	O
shocked	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
poor	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
misfortune	O
,	O
whether	O
her	O
Friends	O
can	O
call	O
it	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
doubt	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
shock	O
,	O
so	O
unexpected	O
,	O
so	O
sudden	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
the	O
other	O
Day	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Courteen	O
Hall	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
likewise	O
added	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
wipes	O
away	O
every	O
disagreeable	O
impreſsion	O
made	O
by	O
that	O
information	O
--	O
So	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
into	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
--	O
yes	O
that	O
because	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
verily	O
believed	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
would	O
not	O
have	O
died	O
had	O
we	O
been	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
So	O
the	O
fates	O
have	O
decreed	O
it	O
--	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mention	O
London	B-place
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
?	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
is	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
myself	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
good	O
graces	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
never	O
taken	O
the	O
least	O
notice	O
of	O
me	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
or	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
--	O
I	O
shall	O
remind	O
Bell	B-pers
of	O
a	O
promise	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
will	O
with	O
great	O
pleas	O
ure	O
fulfil	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
think	O
of	O
my	O
never	O
having	O
yet	O
heard	O
from	O
them	O
since	O
they	O
left	O
Calais	B-place
,	O
of	O
their	O
safe	O
arrival	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
does	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
till	O
after	O
XmaſsChristmass	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
remembrance	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
from	O
Courteenhall	O
excuse	O
this	O
horrid	O
scrawl	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wretched	O
Pen	O
&	O
am	O
hurried	O
for	O
the	O
Post	O
--	O
adieu	O
God	O
Almighty	O
bleſs	O
&	O
preserve	O
you	O
--	O
adieu	O
your	O
affec	O
:	O
CMG——	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
to	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Macclesfield	B-place
Cheshire	B-place
