TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
1789	O
--	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
15	O
July	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
mortified	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
my	O
Letter	O
was	O
five	O
minutes	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
post	O
--	O
writing	O
brought	O
on	O
a	O
Headach	O
wch	O
kept	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
playing	O
,	O
writg	O
&	O
c	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Water	O
Drink	O
--	O
but	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
short	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
anxious	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
my	O
affectionate	O
&	O
amiable	O
Wife	O
--	O
16	O
/	O
I	O
bathed	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Major	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
&	O
the	O
two	O
eldest	O
girls	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
's	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Rain	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
--	O
17	O
/	O
I	O
sat	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
--	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
Visit	O
she	O
made	O
to	O
Madam	B-pers
Schwellenbergen	I-pers
--	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
's	O
sending	O
for	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
&	O
of	O
her	O
graciousness	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
the	O
eldest	O
Princesses	O
&	O
her	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
young	O
Whelps	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
day	O
in	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Major	O
--	O
who	O
breaks	O
into	O
my	O
plan	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
makes	O
ample	O
amends	O
by	O
communicating	O
to	O
me	O
his	O
knowledge	O
of	O
human	O
Nature	O
--	O
I	O
always	O
leave	O
him	O
in	O
Spirits	O
--	O
we	O
expect	O
his	O
Brother	O
Sir	B-pers
David	I-pers
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Navy	O
--	O
the	O
Major	O
describes	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
an	O
excellent	O
Understanding	O
,	O
but	O
haughty	O
&	O
impetuous	O
--	O
brave	O
&	O
too	O
proud	O
to	O
bow	O
to	O
those	O
in	O
power	O
--	O
without	O
a	O
single	O
Air	O
he	O
feels	O
all	O
the	O
original	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
&	O
his	O
Blood	O
boils	O
almost	O
to	O
madneſs	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
persons	O
of	O
mean	O
Birth	O
&	O
Talents	O
raised	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
--	O
merely	O
from	O
their	O
suppleness	O
--	O
the	O
Major	O
says	O
his	O
mind	O
is	O
jaundic	O
'd	O
--	O
by	O
repeated	O
disappointments	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
pride	O
&	O
intolerable	O
ha	O
u	O
teur	O
have	O
brought	O
upon	O
him	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
was	O
fine	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
rainy	O
--	O
18	O
/	O
In	O
our	O
morning	O
's	O
walk	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Vanbrugh	O
's	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
agreeably	O
engaged	O
--	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
spent	O
in	O
Italian	O
,	O
Singing	O
&	O
Musick	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
La	O
belle	O
Catherine	O
for	O
Eliza	B-pers
&	O
Herschell	B-pers
has	O
set	O
a	O
Base	O
to	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Herschell	B-pers
has	O
proposed	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
an	O
old	O
Violono	O
.	O
of	O
his	O
for	O
4-4-0	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
probably	O
get	O
for	O
twice	O
the	O
money	O
or	O
much	O
more	O
in	O
buying	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
+	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
resolved	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
as	O
this	O
great	O
Evil	O
gallops	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
at	O
an	O
amazing	O
rate	O
not	O
withstanding	O
all	O
my	O
care	O
&	O
grumblings	O
--	O
Some	O
part	O
I	O
lay	O
to	O
your	O
charge	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Vanbrughs	I-pers
--	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Card	O
players	O
there	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
&	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
who	O
made	O
Enquiries	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
asked	O
about	O
the	O
Letter	O
I	O
had	O
recd-	O
upon	O
my	O
expreſsg	O
an	O
anxiety	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
mentioned	O
a	O
Letter	O
had	O
been	O
brot	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
morng	O
&	O
she	O
desired	O
the	O
post	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
himself	O
concludg	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
--	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
&	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
who	O
's	O
division	O
we	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
delivered	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
--	O
Away	O
I	O
posted	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
--	O
but	O
no	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
--	O
no	O
letter	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
&	O
walked	O
gravely	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
alone	O
&	O
as	O
ever	O
very	O
pleasant	O
--	O
we	O
talked	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
the	O
present	O
dreadful	O
situation	O
of	O
France	B-place
&	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
petition	O
&	O
summation	O
which	O
their	O
(	O
long	O
)	O
parliament	O
sent	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
you	O
will	O
certainly	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
papers	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
shall	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
shews	O
,	O
the	O
Spirit	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
&	O
that	O
their	O
own	O
terms	O
must	O
be	O
complied	O
with	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
witht	O
an	O
horrible	O
effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
&	O
eat	O
my	O
Supper	O
wt-	O
her	O
I	O
excused	O
my	O
self	O
as	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Bath	O
&	O
was	O
anxious	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
your	O
L	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
had	O
ye-	O
pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
charming	O
Trait	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
God	O
grant	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
like	O
her	O
Mother	O
&	O
tread	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Virtuous	O
Steps	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
bleſsing	O
may	O
she	O
be	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
please	O
God	O
to	O
spare	O
our	O
Lives	O
--	O
She	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
delight	O
&	O
comfort	O
of	O
our	O
declining	O
years	O
--	O
or	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
divine	O
Will	O
to	O
bereave	O
us	O
of	O
our	O
Darling	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
indulge	O
melancholy	O
thoughts	O
--	O
and	O
but	O
endeavour	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
thankful	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
bleſsings	O
I	O
enjoy	O
--	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
August	O
--	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
Coach	O
comes	O
by	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
days	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
--	O
it	O
vexes	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
3	O
days	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
to	O
say	O
that	O
if	O
will	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
them	O
a	O
visit	O
on	O
Saturday	O
next	O
--	O
my	O
plan	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
friday	O
after	O
drinking	O
the	O
Waters	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
spend	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
in	O
my	O
way	O
--	O
&	O
on	O
Saturday	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Cowslip	B-place
green	I-place
&	O
return	O
here	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Evg	O
--	O
by	O
this	O
plan	O
I	O
shall	O
omit	O
only	O
two	O
days	O
drinking	O
the	O
waters	O
&	O
2	O
leſsons	O
--	O
unfortunately	O
Rauzzini	B-pers
is	O
engaged	O
to	O
superintend	O
the	O
musick	O
meeting	O
at	O
Wells	B-place
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
seldom	O
--	O
you	O
must	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
notes	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
few	O
--	O
my	O
modesty	O
flies	O
to	O
my	O
cheeks	O
every	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
ashamed	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
attempt	O
that	O
can	O
never	O
succeed	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
naughty	O
creature	O
you	O
are	O
--	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
lovely	O
day	O
indeed	O
--	O
/19	O
/	O
This	O
morning	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Son	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
ye-	O
Letter	O
&	O
to	O
offer	O
me	O
a	O
seat	O
in	O
the	O
Octagon	O
Chapel	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
celebrated	O
preacher	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sermon	O
,	O
wch	O
was	O
delivered	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
far	O
above	O
mediocrity	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
harmonious	O
Voice	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
manages	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sometimes	O
falls	O
into	O
a	O
common	O
error	O
of	O
laying	O
his	O
emphasis	O
upon	O
the	O
verb	O
or	O
adjective	O
in	O
a	O
sentence	O
when	O
the	O
substantive	O
gives	O
the	O
sense	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pity	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
Schools	O
and	O
Colleges	O
set	O
apart	O
for	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
Clergymen	O
only	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
quiet	O
pronunciation	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
Language	O
&	O
a	O
thorough	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
should	O
be	O
chiefly	O
attended	O
to	O
--	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
finely	O
without	O
a	O
good	O
Ear	O
&	O
an	O
harmonious	O
voice	O
to	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
added	O
a	O
reasonable	O
degree	O
of	O
vanity	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
stimulus	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
disgusted	O
with	O
every	O
species	O
of	O
affectation	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
there	O
appeared	O
some	O
in	O
ye-	O
Preacher	O
which	O
caused	O
my	O
risibility	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
disappointed	O
--	O
Major	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
speaking	O
of	O
Clergymen	O
mentioned	O
an	O
Anecdote	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
of	O
Flamborough	B-place
in	O
hampshire	B-place
--	O
a	O
man	O
universally	O
beloved	O
by	O
his	O
parish	O
which	O
contains	O
1800	O
people	O
&	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
this	O
attachment	O
to	O
him	O
they	O
voluntarily	O
raised	O
his	O
Income	O
upwards	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Major	O
alluded	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Season	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
this	O
--	O
the	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
told	O
his	O
Congregation	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
a	O
n	O
injury	O
to	O
the	O
wise	O
dispensations	O
of	O
providence	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
su	O
ppose	O
that	O
the	O
great	O
Creator	O
of	O
the	O
Universe	O
could	O
be	O
displeased	O
wi	O
th	O
them	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
secure	O
that	O
harvest	O
which	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
gr	O
eat	O
goodneſs	O
he	O
had	O
provided	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
that	O
the	O
restraints	O
on	O
the	O
Sabbath	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
nature	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
next	O
sunday	O
appeared	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
observations	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
a	O
bell	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
rung	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
first	O
wet	O
day	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
kept	O
as	O
a	O
Sunday	O
--	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
a	O
bell	O
was	O
rung	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
farmers	O
attended	O
to	O
their	O
harvest	O
&	O
on	O
wednesday	O
morng	O
another	O
Bell	O
gave	O
them	O
notice	O
to	O
offer	O
up	O
their	O
prayers	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
more	O
fervently	O
than	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
done	O
before	O
--	O
the	O
Bell	O
rings	O
for	O
dinner	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
obey	O
the	O
summons	O
--	O
adieu	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
mia	O
cara	O
sposa	O
,	O
sono	O
vostro	O
sposo	O
affezionato	O
--	O
20/	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
from	O
table	O
yesterday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
Lady	O
&	O
walked	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
pleas	O
an	O
t	O
Grove	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
what	O
think	O
you	O
of	O
these	O
assignations	O
--	O
I	O
c	O
a	O
n't	O
tell	O
you	O
Who	O
the	O
Lady	O
is	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
women	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
here	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Serres	I-pers
a	O
painter	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
copies	O
Vandervelt	B-pers
so	O
exactly	O
that	O
he	O
defies	O
any	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
not	O
made	O
his	O
Stile	O
of	O
painting	O
his	O
particular	O
study	O
,	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Copy	O
--	O
this	O
S——	B-pers
is	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Creature	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
from	O
his	O
Son	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
leſsons	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
acquire	O
a	O
few	O
tecknical	O
terms	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
an	O
advantage	O
--	O
for	O
people	O
who	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
tolerable	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
not	O
say	O
bravura	O
for	O
peano	O
--	O
Lord	O
what	O
a	O
creature	O
that	O
is	O
)	O
have	O
often	O
more	O
credit	O
given	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
taste	O
&	O
judgement	O
than	O
they	O
are	O
entitled	O
to	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
delightful	O
day	O
yesterday	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
charming	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
reaſsume	O
the	O
sc	O
h	O
oolboy	O
with	O
my	O
Satchel	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
--	O
adieu	O
again	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
my	O
drawing	O
Master	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Scholar	O
that	O
improved	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Leſson	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
spare	O
before	O
this	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
Recet	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
afft	O
Letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
here	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
ease	O
his	O
Fears	O
about	O
my	O
Health	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
when	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
&	O
best	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
most	O
affy	O
.	O
J.D——	B-pers
Bleſsing	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
I	O
see	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
got	O
his	O
degree	O
of	O
M.A	O
Mrs.	B-place
Dickenson	I-place
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
