TOKEN	NE
England	B-place
--	O
Gundamor	B-pers
took	O
a	O
violent	O
&	O
active	O
part	O
against	O
this	O
great	O
&	O
unfortunate	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
Gundamor	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Spain	B-place
--	O
he	O
boasted	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
cheif	O
instrument	O
promoter	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
affair	O
wch	O
.	O
to	O
criminate	O
d	O
Rawleigh	B-pers
&	O
boasted	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
block	O
--	O
judge	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
feelings	O
of	O
Gundamor	B-pers
when	O
his	O
Mother	O
told	O
him	O
--	O
“	O
then	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
murderer	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
.	O
the	O
second	O
Anecdote	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Horace	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
had	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Poet	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
gallery	O
of	O
the	O
Play	O
House	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
conversation	O
with	O
a	O
Lady	O
who	O
set	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
handsome	O
&	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
conversation	O
sensible	O
&	O
agreeable	O
.	O
he	O
liked	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
flatter	O
'd	O
himself	O
their	O
acquaintance	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
drop	O
there	O
&	O
desired	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
home	O
--	O
she	O
consented	O
provided	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
solemn	O
promise	O
--	O
never	O
to	O
make	O
enquires	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
whenever	O
they	O
might	O
meet	O
by	O
chance	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
faithful	O
promise	O
--	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
unknown	O
Lady	O
yt	O
.	O
night	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
near	O
Liecester	O
fields	O
&	O
afterwards	O
frequently	O
visited	O
her	O
.	O
One	O
day	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
croſsing	O
a	O
Street	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
struck	O
with	O
seeing	O
this	O
Lady	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
dreſs	O
of	O
a	O
Beggar	O
Woman	O
asking	O
alms	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
paſsengers	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
by	O
a	O
look	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
he	O
recollected	O
his	O
promise	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
another	O
day	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Harley	B-pers
(	O
Lord	O
Oxford	O
)	O
then	O
Ld	O
.	O
High	O
Treasury	O
ye	O
.	O
servants	O
desired	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
to	O
wait	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Anti	O
-Room	O
as	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Lady	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
on	O
Busineſs	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
wait	O
long	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
paſs	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Anti	O
Room	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
--	O
again	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
female	O
friend	O
who	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
fashion	O
--	O
she	O
again	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
significant	O
look	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
he	O
obey	O
'd	O
--	O
several	O
times	O
did	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
meet	O
this	O
Mysterious	O
Lady	O
in	O
different	O
disguises	O
--	O
he	O
kept	O
up	O
his	O
intrigue	O
wth-	O
her	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
penetrate	O
into	O
her	O
secrets	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
promise	O
she	O
had	O
extorted	O
from	O
him	O
prevented	O
him	O
making	O
enquiries	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
Night	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Company	O
at	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
at	O
Sommerset	O
House	O
--	O
a	O
note	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
immediately	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
unknown	O
Lady	O
who	O
was	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
--	O
she	O
conjured	O
him	O
to	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
secrets	O
of	O
importance	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
immediately	O
but	O
to	O
his	O
grief	O
&	O
regret	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
often	O
told	O
this	O
story	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
undoubted	O
fact	O
.	O
he	O
made	O
many	O
fruitleſs	O
attempts	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
4	O
she	O
5	O
was	O
6	O
after	O
1	O
her	O
2	O
death	O
3	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
succeed	O
--	O
many	O
People	O
conjecture	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
spy	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
service	O
of	O
the	O
Ministers	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
.	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
we	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
home	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
down	O
--	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
better	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
or	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
home	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Wednesday	O
18	O
th	O
:	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Butler	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
thank	O
me	O
for	O
having	O
recommeded	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Coal	O
Merchant	O
&	O
has	O
time	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
his	O
trade	O
though	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
D——y	I-pers
's	I-pers
Service	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
meſsage	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
Julianna	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
paſsages	O
out	O
of	O
letters	O
of	O
a	O
desceased	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Character	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
4	O
oClock	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
dined	O
at	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunnings	I-pers
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
anxious	O
about	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
I	O
put	O
of	O
going	O
--	O
Found	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
rather	O
better	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
dine	O
below	O
.	O
therefore	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
head	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
--	O
we	O
only	O
set	O
down	O
4	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
2	O
d	O
.	O
Brother	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
a	O
Clergyman	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
his	O
Tutor	O
--	O
(	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
)	O
immediately	O
after	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Wine	O
&	O
desert	O
brought	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
before	O
7	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Evening	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
had	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Bad	O
head	O
aches	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
enter	O
much	O
into	O
conversation	O
.	O
Politicks	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
principle	O
subject	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
defend	O
her	O
favorite	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
down	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
was	O
engaged	O
to	O
a	O
Converz	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
found	O
both	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C-	I-pers
's	I-pers
at	O
home	O
sat	O
wth-	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
sent	O
over	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
supper	O
at	O
11	O
but	O
we	O
excused	O
ourselves	O
Thursday	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
frm	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
worse	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
m	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
&	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
(	O
whilst	O
my	O
Hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
)	O
in	O
R	B-pers
--	O
Eloise	O
we	O
made	O
our	O
Comments	O
--	O
sometimes	O
admiring	O
&	O
sometimes	O
detesting	O
ye	O
.	O
sentiments	O
.	O
My	O
Jean	B-pers
Jacques	I-pers
Rousseau	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
an	O
hour	O
alone	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
circumstances	O
of	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Cousin	O
)	O
intimacy	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
his	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
--	O
his	O
having	O
proposed	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Niece	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
2	O
Nephews	O
being	O
confin	O
'd	O
(	O
viz	O
Cols	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Cathcart	B-pers
)	O
wth	O
.	O
bad	O
Colds	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Greville	B-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
paid	O
a	O
Visit	O
first	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
read	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
reasons	O
why	O
she	O
parted	O
wth-	O
her	O
Sister	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
--	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
right	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
of	O
Taste	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
a	O
polished	O
Mind	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
devoid	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
had	O
his	O
Coach	O
--	O
Only	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
besides	O
ourselves	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
House	O
just	O
nearly	O
opposite	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
found	O
Dear	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Bedroom	O
,	O
wth	O
her	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
a	O
Bad	O
Night	O
but	O
thought	O
herself	O
better	O
she	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
from	O
Rheumatic	O
Pains	O
&	O
Cold	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
went	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Plumtree	I-pers
were	O
come	O
--	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Circle	O
&	O
I	O
to	O
break	O
through	O
it	O
--	O
proposed	O
--	O
playing	O
at	O
dumb-	O
Crambo	O
Mr-	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
were	O
of	O
this	O
Party	O
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
forfiets	O
&	O
laugh	O
'd	O
heartily	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
went	O
away	O
before	O
supper	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
staid	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
we	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
found	O
notes	O
&	O
Visits	O
Friday	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Feby	O
1784	O
Rec	O
'd	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
Col	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
,	O
till	O
past	O
two	O
--	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
invite	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
s	O
(	O
his	O
fathers	O
)	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Birthday	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
because	O
I	O
expected	O
Company	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
sent	O
their	O
excuses	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Colds	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
to	O
congratulate	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
Son	O
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
&	O
to	O
recommend	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
her	O
charity	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Maid	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
read	O
in	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
(	O
manuscript	O
)	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
has	O
lent	O
me	O
till	O
near	O
8	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
Daughter	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
of	O
Edinburg	B-place
--	O
who	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
a	O
pretty	O
work	O
--	O
“	O
a	O
Fathers	O
Legacy	O
to	O
his	O
Daughters	O
”	O
--	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
Doct	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
took	O
this	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
under	O
her	O
protection	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
is	O
upon	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
footing	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
hoped	O
Miſs	B-pers
G—y	I-pers
will	O
enable	O
her	O
always	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
stile	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
G—	I-pers
is	O
good-	O
humour	O
'd	O
&	O
sensible	O
and	O
is	O
,	O
deservedly	O
I	O
think	O
esteem	O
'd	O
&	O
liked	O
by	O
all	O
who	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
the	O
time	O
Afternoon	O
cheerfully	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
Manuscript	O
Poems	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
=	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Room	O
I	O
continued	O
reading	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
letters	O
--	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
's	I-pers
went	O
to	O
their	O
Rooms	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Saturday	O
21	O
st	O
:	O
Feby	O
.	O
1784	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
whilst	O
my	O
Hair	O
was	O
dng-	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
at	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
settle	O
the	O
Affair	O
for	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Rent	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
James	O
Street	O
--	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
ye	O
.	O
meſsage	O
to	O
one	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
People	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Frederick	B-pers
his	O
future	O
intentions	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggens	I-pers
was	O
better	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
soon	O
went	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
stay	O
'd	O
½	O
hour	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
yesterday	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
--	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Abbé	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
s	O
death	O
who	O
was	O
secretly	O
poison	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Jesuits	O
--	O
who	O
artfully	O
contrived	O
to	O
have	O
poison	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Chocolate	O
--	O
this	O
worthy	O
Pope	O
was	O
many	O
Months	O
dying	O
--	O
the	O
perpetrators	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
horrid	O
deed	O
were	O
never	O
discoverd	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
suffer	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
crime	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
is	O
a	O
very	O
Old	O
Man	O
--	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
by	O
Birth	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
fled	O
to	O
Rome	B-place
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Ganganelli	B-pers
--	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
England	B-place
wth	O
.	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
ending	O
his	O
days	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
finds	O
ye	O
.	O
Climate	O
will	O
not	O
suit	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
Abbé	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
read	O
Pretender	B-pers
's	O
letters	O
&	O
made	O
Extracts	O
from	O
them	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
'	I-pers
y	I-pers
.	O
I	O
continued	O
below	O
reading	O
the	O
Letters	O
--	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
poorly	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
better	O
--	O
Sr-	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
Stapletons	O
Club	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
--	O
Sr-	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
still	O
lame	O
&	O
looking	O
Ill	O
--	O
she	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Charlotte	B-pers
went	O
out	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Caten	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
chatted	O
together	O
--	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
had	O
Supper	O
upstairs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
came	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
10	O
--	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Invalids	O
--	O
had	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
Extracts	O
till	O
12	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
--	O
Miſs	O
Clarkes	O
came	O
home	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
Supper	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
acting	O
(	O
ye	O
.	O
Mourning	O
Bride	O
)	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D—y	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
s	O
Musick	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
A	O
complete	O
Thaw	O
today	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Frost	O
has	O
lasted	O
8	O
weeks	O
&	O
2	O
days	O
Sunday	O
22	O
d	O
-	O
Febry	O
.	O
Sent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
for	O
not	O
dining	O
wth	O
:	O
her	O
--	O
as	O
Handel	B-pers
was	O
ill	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
poor	O
Account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
who	O
is	O
ill	O
again	O
--	O
A	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
from	O
Hanover	B-place
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
ma	O
d	O
k	O
e	O
Extracts	O
frm	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
.	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Busche	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
--	O
b	O
oth	O
ut	O
both	O
her	O
Girls	O
poorly	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
he	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Speaker	O
s	O
--	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
below	O
--	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Tutor	O
--	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
we	O
had	O
desart	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
to	O
their	O
busineſs	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
soon	O
--	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
C—	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Catten	I-pers
&	O
I	O
.	O
(	O
in	O
turn	O
)	O
read	O
one	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Sermons	O
After	O
that	O
read	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Minor	O
Poems	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
had	O
Porteous	B-pers
's	O
Coach	O
went	O
to	O
Milton	B-pers
s	O
.	O
found	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
old	O
woman	O
in	O
high	O
beauty	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
White	O
Sattin	O
&	O
her	O
best	O
lace	O
Cap	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
s	O
Birthday	O
who	O
is	O
70	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
met	O
the	O
Dſs	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
Roſs	B-pers
--	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Exeter	I-pers
&	O
Hurd	B-pers
--	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wocester	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
very	O
agreeable	O
&	O
lively	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Soame	I-pers
Jennings	I-pers
entertain	O
'd	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Proud	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
--	O
how	O
Mr.	B-pers
Soame	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Somerset	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
used	O
to	O
torment	O
him	O
by	O
mortifying	O
his	O
vanity	O
--	O
one	O
instance	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
following	O
--	O
the	O
Mr.	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Henley	I-pers
charged	O
his	O
servants	O
never	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Way	O
but	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
family	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Northington	I-pers
--	O
he	O
always	O
travel	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
vast	O
R	O
i	O
e	O
t	O
e	O
i	O
nue	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
&	O
6	O
--	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Somerset	I-pers
who	O
was	O
once	O
travelling	O
overtook	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Norfolk	I-pers
--	O
he	O
bid	O
his	O
Servants	O
call	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
--	O
so	O
ye	O
.	O
old	O
ye	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
difficulty	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
lane	O
gave	O
room	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Norfolk	I-pers
with	O
his	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
window	O
ready	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
bow	O
--	O
when	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
S—	I-pers
sa	O
t	O
l	O
u	O
l	O
t	O
ed	O
his	O
Grace	O
by	O
ye	O
Name	O
of	O
Charles	O
--	O
wishing	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
journey	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
&	O
Lord	O
N	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Wit	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
profligate	O
&	O
detestable	O
principles	O
--	O
Henly	B-pers
was	O
equally	O
vicious	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Brother	O
who	O
is	O
still	O
living	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
&	O
if	O
poſsible	O
is	O
a	O
worse	O
man	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
his	O
Brothers	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
9.	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Northington	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
only	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
we	O
staid	O
supper	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Monday	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
Busy	O
in	O
notable	O
work	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Leveé	O
&	O
c	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
busy	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Veseys	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Horace	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
Dowg	I-pers
.	I-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
&	O
his	O
son	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
the	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
&	O
his	O
wife	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Landaff	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Asaph	O
--	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
Chester	I-pers
.	O
and	O
2	O
Foreigner	O
's	O
from	O
Provence	B-place
a	O
Chevalier	O
of	O
Malta	B-place
&	O
a	O
Count	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
their	O
names	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Youngest	O
--	O
they	O
seem	O
agreeable	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Porteous	I-pers
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
Supper	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
.	O
Shipley	B-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
A	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
24	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
's	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
The	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Chester	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
Chaperon	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs	B-pers
Porteous	I-pers
s	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Antique	O
Vase	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
--	O
I	O
introduced	O
ym	O
.	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
ym	O
.	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
William	B-pers
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Guilford	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
ill	O
again	O
&	O
has	O
an	O
ague	O
&	O
fever	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
her	O
well	O
day	O
--	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
affraid	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
wait	O
for	O
her	O
Coach	O
.	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Hotel	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
--	O
she	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
soon	O
came	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
expreſs	O
'd	O
much	O
pleasure	O
in	O
having	O
seen	O
ye	O
.	O
Vase	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
's	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
busy	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
helping	O
to	O
finish	O
some	O
things	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
wear	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
Man	O
wth	O
.	O
Lace	O
Ruffles	O
chose	O
some	O
for	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
he	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Hanif	O
.	O
&	O
Robbins	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
4	O
my	O
Uncle	O
both	B-pers
ye	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Portman	O
Square	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
looks	O
wretchedly	O
.	O
met	O
at	O
William	B-pers
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
M—	I-pers
Ducheſs	B-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
Duke	B-pers
&	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Buccleugh	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
his	O
wife	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lock	I-pers
&	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
Watson	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Le	B-pers
Duc	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chaulnes	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
had	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
curious	O
drawings	O
of	O
Chinese	O
Buildings	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
interio	O
u	O
r	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
discover	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
method	O
of	O
making	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
colors	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chinese	O
M	O
S	O
de	O
th	O
ac	O
fl	O
a	O
ha	O
hi	O
s	O
Ye	O
.	O
M	O
o	O
Suc	O
nce	O
na	O
m	O
See	O
I	O
a	O
m	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
these	O
drawings	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
The	B-pers
Duc	I-pers
de	I-pers
C—	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
went	O
away	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
staid	O
dinner	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Conversation	O
was	O
chiefly	O
on	O
Chymistry	O
&	O
Natural	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Earth	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
show	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
drawings	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
&	O
of	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Egyptian	O
Pyramids	O
--	O
Pompey	O
's	O
Pillar	O
--	O
he	O
explain	O
'd	O
their	O
structure	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Egypt	B-place
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
at	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
B	I-pers
s	O
went	O
to	O
Le	B-pers
Duc	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chaulnes	I-pers
s	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
engaged	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveng	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
apology	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Sober	O
Party	O
.	O
only	O
Mr.	B-pers
Legge	I-pers
&	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Carri	O
a	O
ge	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
undreſs	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
comfortable	O
&	O
then	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
25	O
th	O
:	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
they	O
each	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Revely	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
morning	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsiord	O
--	O
till	O
7	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
(	O
in	O
Spring-	O
Gardens	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
wth	O
:	O
upon	O
a	O
Sopha	O
She	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
&	O
hurt	O
her	O
Leg	O
.	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
as	O
also	O
Lady	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Tryconnel	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
Grandaughter	O
who	O
is	O
abt	O
12	O
lives	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
a	O
very	O
Sensible	O
girl	O
lively	O
&	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
--	O
but	O
very	O
plain	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
working	O
Party	O
--	O
sociable	O
but	O
nothing	O
very	O
bright	O
advanced	O
.	O
had	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
J	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
at	O
10	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
at	O
Supper	O
staid	O
with	O
ym	O
.	O
till	O
11	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
J—	I-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Thursday	O
26	O
th	O
Feby	O
:	O
1784	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
succeeded	O
in	O
his	O
application	O
--	O
yt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
c	O
:	O
thought	O
his	O
a	O
reasonable	O
claim	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
finishd	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
at	O
¼	O
pas	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
oClock	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
places	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
at	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
who	O
is	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
her	O
well	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
bed	O
side	O
till	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
her	O
Siſter	O
was	O
also	O
there	O
nursing	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
real	O
tenderneſs	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
sat	O
up	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
our	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
Education	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
at	O
4	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
it	O
was	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
who	O
enters	O
into	O
ye	O
:	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
year	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
--	O
she	O
looks	O
wretchedly	O
&	O
is	O
I	O
fear	O
in	O
a	O
decline	O
.	O
none	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
to	O
dinner	O
except	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
pool	O
at	O
Commerce	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
people	O
--	O
&	O
there	O
came	O
to	O
Tea	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
--	O
the	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Smiths	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
join	O
us	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
--	O
Only	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
staid	O
Supper	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
brought	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
me	O
home	O
in	O
their	O
Coach	O
.	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
alone	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
Friday	O
27	O
th	O
:	O
Feby	O
.	O
1784	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
Preceptor	O
to	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
)	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
:	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
family	O
.	O
&	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Govenor	O
--	O
his	O
temper	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
Govenor	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
Young	O
Princes	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
his	O
ignorance	O
&	O
vulgarity	O
.	O
when	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
drawing	O
was	O
interrupted	O
at	O
3	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
coming	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
a	O
terribly	O
affected	O
Woman	O
with	O
Studdied	O
Ph	O
r	O
ases	O
&	O
hard	O
words	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
&	O
good	O
amiable	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
paſs	O
'd	O
--	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
working	O
&	O
I	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
conversing	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
was	O
in	O
charming	O
spirits	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
curious	O
law	O
Anecdotes	O
--	O
of	O
Wills	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
Party	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
's	O
&	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
little	O
Songs	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Saturday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Vento	B-pers
came	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
wth	O
:	O
me	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
of	O
above	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
little	O
God-Daughter	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
wrote	O
notes	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
(	O
our	O
Cousin	O
)	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
&	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
Conversation	O
that	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
at	O
our	O
Aunts	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
between	O
our	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
occasion	O
a	O
Coolneſs	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
saw	O
little	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
&	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
Genl	B-pers
:	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
yesterday	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
.	O
w	O
h	O
en	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Mary	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
visits	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
only	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Adelphi	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
town	B-place
to	O
day	O
--	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
left	O
meſsages	O
at	O
different	O
houses	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Streets	O
in	O
ye	O
City	O
were	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
People	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Windows	O
crowded	O
with	O
Spectators	O
--	O
waiting	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
paſs	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
quite	O
tired	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Jumble	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
request	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
friends	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
a	O
fine	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
theirs	O
abt	O
4	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
had	O
tea	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
&	O
amused	O
myself	O
with	O
Reading	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Manuscript	O
letters	O
&	O
transcribing	O
paſsages	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
this	O
Morning	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
till	O
11	O
&	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
when	O
lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
word	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveng	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
came	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
his	O
Servt	O
.	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
note	O
--	O
I	O
scolded	O
him	O
for	O
coming	O
at	O
so	O
unreasonable	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
however	O
he	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
&	O
Cheese	O
&	O
wine	O
&	O
water	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
&	O
he	O
agree	O
'd	O
in	O
thinking	O
my	O
Uncle	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
discreet	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
were	O
Retired	O
to	O
their	O
Rooms	O
--	O
Sunday	O
29	O
th	O
:	O
Febry-	O
1784	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stor	I-pers
:	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
prayers	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
came	O
--	O
had	O
not	O
sat	O
long	O
before	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
mutually	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
at	O
3	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
consulted	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Physician	O
about	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
hopes	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
ye	O
.	O
better	O
of	O
her	O
complaints	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Elliot	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
Spirits	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
both	O
unhappy	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
uneasy	O
abt	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
who	O
went	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
to	O
Eſsex	B-place
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Cold	O
East	O
Wind	O
&	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
alone	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
hasty	O
meal	O
&	O
amused	O
myself	O
in	O
reading	O
&	O
transcribing	O
Marianne	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
below	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
letter	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
alone	O
(	O
only	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
)	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
her	O
well	O
indeed	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
indisposed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
&	O
was	O
blooded	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
came	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
much	O
congratulation	O
paſs	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
happy	O
Birth	O
of	O
Young	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
son	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
great	O
Grandson	O
to	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
&	O
Grandson	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
--	O
it	O
was	O
pleasing	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
how	O
happy	O
these	O
two	O
good	O
Women	O
were	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
--	O
he	O
staid	O
only	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
had	O
been	O
disturbd	O
&	O
alarmed	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
riotous	O
behaviour	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mob	O
last	O
night	O
Who	O
broke	O
windows	O
&	O
c	O
this	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
--	O
much	O
conversation	O
paſs	O
'd	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
am	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
humour	O
political	O
topics	O
&	O
party	O
divisions	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
patience	O
to	O
write	O
down	O
all	O
I	O
hear	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
indifferent	O
to	O
party	O
&	O
my	O
prayers	O
&	O
wishes	O
are	O
for	O
“	O
peace	O
&	O
goodwill	O
among	O
Men	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
comfortable	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
after	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
were	O
gone	O
&	O
had	O
their	O
friendly	O
embrace	O
&	O
request	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
oftener	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
amazingly	O
recover	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
dismiſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
who	O
had	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
there	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
&	O
was	O
nursing	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Cradle	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
otherwise	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
excellent	O
Spirits	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
degree	O
of	O
Gout	O
he	O
has	O
is	O
not	O
violent	O
&	O
does	O
him	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
they	O
had	O
sup	O
'd	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
&	O
Wine	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
2	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
receiving	O
such	O
Honors	O
yesterday	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
11	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
Monday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1784|1	O
st	O
March	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
came	O
at	O
10.	O
to	O
breakfast	O
Breakfasted	O
below	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
he	O
staid	O
chatting	O
&	O
we	O
working	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
new	O
watch	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Willertons	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
regulated	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
below	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
&	O
began	O
drawing	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
day	O
she	O
talks	O
generally	O
sensibly	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
taste	O
--	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
kind	O
of	O
Woman	O
--	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
.	O
I	O
often	O
meet	O
with	O
sensible	O
&	O
good	O
People	O
whom	O
notwithstanding	O
I	O
respect	O
them	O
tire	O
me	O
to	O
death	O
--	O
After	O
she	O
went	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sakton	I-pers
came	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
.	O
then	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
who	O
staid	O
near	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Cautious	O
manner	O
a	O
hint	O
of	O
wht	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
without	O
res	O
erve	O
traint	O
--	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
enemy	O
to	O
family	O
divisions	O
&	O
always	O
endeavour	O
to	O
put	O
things	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
light	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
daughter	O
Frederick	B-pers
--	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S—	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
that	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
me	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
Daughter	O
came	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
as	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Head	O
ache	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saville	I-pers
stay	O
'd	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
I	O
drew	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
Mrs.	O
Iremongers	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
only	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
After	O
tea	O
an	O
Old	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
he	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
he	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
recovery	O
from	O
a	O
dreadful	O
accident	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
from	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
catching	O
fire	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremon-	I-pers
ger	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Entertain	O
m	O
ent	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Riot	O
was	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
agreeable	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
family	O
--	O
my	O
quitting	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
alone	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
came	O
home	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
her	O
Sister	O
)	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
till	O
near	O
one	O
oClock	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
March	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
I—	I-pers
call	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
only	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
&	O
going	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
doing	O
my	O
hair	O
when	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
as	O
it	O
the	O
was	O
Streets	O
were	O
dry	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
found	O
Betty	B-pers
at	O
home	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
Large	O
Room	O
--	O
well	O
furnish	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
comfortable	O
manner	O
wth	O
.	O
Books	O
-	O
&	O
elegancies	O
China	B-place
--	O
Japan	B-place
--	O
Birds	O
--	O
Flowers	O
--	O
Cabinets	O
--	O
pretty	O
tables	O
Secretaires	O
--	O
Trinkets	O
--	O
a	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
things	O
--	O
yet	O
all	O
in	O
order	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
inflammation	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Eyes	O
--	O
she	O
lookd	O
poorly	O
&	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
is	O
confined	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Brother	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
had	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
accident	O
&	O
sp	O
r	O
ained	O
his	O
wrist	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
who	O
live	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
Street	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
were	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
--	O
met	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
we	O
talkd	O
for	O
some	O
minutes	O
--	O
Genl-	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
paſs	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
--	O
she	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
near	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
different	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Town	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
&	O
pursued	O
my	O
walk	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Col.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
then	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
a	O
Scot	O
t	O
c	O
h	O
Cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
--	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
--	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
confined	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
fall	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
months	O
ago	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
in	O
(	O
two	O
Scotch	O
men	O
)	O
--	O
from	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
got	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
s	O
at	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Lord	B-pers
Caſsels	I-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
debates	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
Commons	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
6	O
Mr.	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
my	O
Cousin	O
came	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
before	O
her	O
intended	O
visit	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
--	O
sent	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
back	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
found	O
excuses	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
not	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
adjourn	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
persuade	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
but	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
soon	O
came	O
accompanied	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
they	O
agree	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
proposal	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
without	O
loſs	O
of	O
time	O
to	O
Albermarle	O
Street	O
--	O
we	O
made	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
give	O
in	O
other	O
Names	O
&	O
our	O
little	O
joke	O
succeeded	O
in	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
fuſs	O
&	O
occasion	O
'd	O
some	O
mirth	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
read	O
Macbeth	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
in	O
Turn	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G—	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
who	O
lives	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
were	O
our	O
audience	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Scene	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
Kings	O
Murder	O
is	O
discover	O
'd	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
(	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Uncle	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
man	O
&	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
ye	O
Book	O
was	O
then	O
laid	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
took	O
up	O
their	O
Work	O
&	O
we	O
heard	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
talk	O
Politicks	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
before	O
ten	O
oClock	O
--	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Cust	I-pers
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
Brownlow	I-pers
alone	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
--	O
had	O
our	O
little	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
calld	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye-	O
Morning	O
Wednesday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
(	O
she	O
is	O
Frederick	B-pers
s	O
oldest	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honor	O
)	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
Woman	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
ye.Queen	B-pers
to	O
dinner	O
Col	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
is	O
one	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
s	O
Gentlemen	O
Uſhers	O
--	O
a	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
Coxcomb	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
ye	O
.	O
dinning	O
room	O
till	O
7	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
came	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Room	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tuttridge	I-pers
went	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
afternoon	O
in	O
hearing	O
ye	O
.	O
sensible	O
Conversation	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
--	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Horace	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
(	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tuttridge	I-pers
s	O
wife	O
)	O
&	O
2	O
of	O
her	O
daughters	O
--	O
the	O
2	O
youngest	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
Niece	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
her	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
went	O
awa	O
y	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
S—	I-pers
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
R	I-pers
&	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
had	O
had	O
a	O
Card	O
Party	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
We	O
had	O
our	O
Bread	O
&	O
Cheese	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
chatted	O
over	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
hea	O
r	O
d	O
&	O
whom	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
&	O
separated	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
Thursday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
therefore	O
excused	O
myself	O
from	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Drawing	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
family	O
,	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
modest	O
&	O
sensibl	O
y	O
e	O
Man	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
&	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ernst	I-pers
wife	O
came	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
left	O
us	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Visit	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
vast	O
deal	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Uncle	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G—	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
then	O
Lord	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
agreeably	O
she	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
2	O
hours	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beauvoir	I-pers
--	O
neice	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
a	O
t	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
a	O
lively	O
pretty	O
Young	O
Woman	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
visits	O
he	O
cld	O
.	O
pay	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
excuse	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
&	O
me	O
after	O
dinner	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
.	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
B	O
.	O
Room	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
drawing	O
things	O
&	O
c	O
abt	O
.	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
Sr.	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
--	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
found	O
her	O
father	O
&	O
Sister	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
8	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
of	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
People	O
of	O
fashion	O
led	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
disliked	O
it	O
--	O
then	O
complain	O
'd	O
&	O
found	O
fault	O
wth	O
.	O
every	O
set	O
of	O
society	O
for	O
their	O
are	O
various	O
ones	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
maintained	O
that	O
it	O
depended	O
upon	O
oneself	O
for	O
if	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
amazed	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
might	O
find	O
entertainment	O
&	O
instruction	O
either	O
by	O
observation	O
in	O
some	O
sets	O
or	O
attention	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
in	O
others	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
prefer	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
--	O
society	O
in	O
general	O
&	O
manner	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
French	O
--	O
of	O
this	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
judge	O
never	O
having	O
lived	O
in	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
is	O
a	O
polished	O
&	O
agreeable	O
Man	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
from	O
8	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
dreſs	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Works	O
--	O
his	O
plays	O
particularly	O
--	O
of	O
some	O
fine	O
People	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
had	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
found	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
G—	I-pers
alone	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
.	O
Several	O
Cards	O
,	O
Visits	O
,	O
Notes	O
answer	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
--	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
then	O
separated	O
Friday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
got	O
up	O
late	O
.	O
Young	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
for	O
he	O
cld	O
.	O
not	O
stay	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
G	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
&	O
they	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
fatigued	O
wth	O
.	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
:	O
her	O
--	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
little	O
girl	O
&	O
very	O
clever	O
&	O
engaging	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
amused	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
drawing	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
not	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
excuse	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
better	O
to	O
nurse	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
just	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
also	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
below	O
&	O
drew	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
&	O
was	O
alone	O
till	O
11	O
oClock	O
.	O
rec	O
'd	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
in	O
the	O
morning	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
accompany	O
her	O
to	O
Carlton	O
House	O
next	O
Wed	O
to	O
a	O
Ball	O
&	O
supper	O
wch	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
to	O
give	O
--	O
I	O
answered	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
note	O
&	O
said	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
I	O
could	O
in	O
a	O
handsome	O
way	O
excuse	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
too	O
small	O
a	O
fortune	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
bear	O
ye	O
.	O
expence	O
of	O
dreſs	O
--	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
quiet	O
moderate	O
way	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
ambition	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Circles	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
was	O
pleased	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
invited	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
refuse	O
going	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
proper	O
a	O
Chaperon	O
--	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
request	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
his	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
came	O
in	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
--	O
enquired	O
--	O
how	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S—	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
c	O
did	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
--	O
that	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
sent	O
word	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
soon	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
visits	O
&	O
enquiries	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
other	O
places	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
Saturday	O
.	O
--	O
was	O
better	O
got	O
up	O
pretty	O
early	O
&	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
consult	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schewellenberg	I-pers
's	O
.	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
&	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
Ball	O
&	O
c	O
My	O
Uncle	O
said	O
provided	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Hagerdorn	B-pers
he	O
thought	O
it	O
right	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
came	O
--	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
card	O
of	O
invitation	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
were	O
both	O
of	O
opinion	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
refuse	O
.	O
&	O
she	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
Milliner	O
to	O
dreſs	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
a	O
Black	O
Velvet	O
Body	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
wait	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
out	O
)	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
s	O
--	O
neither	O
she	O
or	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
or	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
just	O
run	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
her	O
father	O
&	O
Sister	O
were	O
wth	O
:	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
then	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
then	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
's	O
Milliner	O
--	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
orders	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
then	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jaqquire	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
&	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
St	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
s	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
he	O
spoke	O
very	O
kindly	O
of	O
him	O
&	O
handsomely	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
heard	O
ye	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
mourning	O
till	O
Thursday	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Wm	B-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
as	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
was	O
not	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
till	O
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
--	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
then	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
dinner	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
of	O
Abington	B-place
.	O
I	O
staid	O
below	O
till	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
&	O
sent	O
her	O
my	O
diary	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
their	O
Sister	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
to	O
a	O
party	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Youth	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
a	O
nephew	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Sailor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
but	O
poorly	O
--	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catten	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
approved	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
&	O
c	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
acroſs	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Marrianne	B-pers
s	O
having	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
confin	O
'd	O
him	O
upstairs	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
Mr.	B-pers
D.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
they	O
were	O
at	O
Cards	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
a	O
ir	O
leave	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Bal	O
l	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
paſs	O
'd	O
times	O
his	O
connexion	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gladdel	I-pers
&	O
various	O
political	O
&	O
other	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
12	O
before	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Revely	I-pers
--	O
(	O
a	O
good	O
natured	O
old	O
Irish	O
Gentleman	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
&	O
accompanied	O
us	O
home	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
in	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
I	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
undreſsing	O
--	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
note	O
from	O
Major	B-pers
Veaitch	I-pers
who	O
was	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
having	O
received	O
ye	O
.	O
invitation	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sunday	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
Mr.	B-pers
J—	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Millener	O
came	O
for	O
orders	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
dreſs	O
took	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
materials	O
I	O
had	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
the	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
2	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
she	O
was	O
shown	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
B	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
we	O
chatted	O
together	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Madame	B-pers
Jaqquire	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
good	O
Aunt	O
just	O
call	O
'd	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
an	O
Airing	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
took	O
her	O
leave	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
her	O
great	O
Neice	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
turn	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Croud	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
she	O
too	O
approved	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Carlton	O
House	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
Scotch	O
Cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
knew	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
my	O
coming	O
early	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
were	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
they	O
soon	O
went	O
--	O
we	O
conversed	O
together	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
her	O
Neice	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
a	O
child	O
of	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
us	O
Miſs	B-pers
Anstruther	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Character	O
of	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
--	O
(	O
a	O
Miſs	O
Hamilton	O
)	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
France	B-place
--	O
the	O
chief	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Conversation	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
Scotch	O
connexions	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Physician	O
came	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
(	O
another	O
Cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
melancholy	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
youngest	O
Son	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Mac——	I-pers
on	O
board	O
his	O
Ship	O
.	O
he	O
&	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Crew	O
were	O
frost	O
bound	O
&	O
starved	O
to	O
death	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
promising	O
Youth	O
.	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cameron	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
sat	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Fordyce	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
People	O
at	O
home	O
...	O
at	O
10	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
11	O
Lady	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
--	O
got	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
&	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
Mr.	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
mean	O
while	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
complaind	O
of	O
seeing	O
me	O
so	O
seldom	O
in	O
a	O
comfortable	O
way	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
fault	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
&	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
excuses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
undreſsing	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
offer	O
me	O
some	O
black	O
velvet	O
she	O
had	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
save	O
me	O
buying	O
some	O
for	O
my	O
ball	O
dreſs	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Thynnes	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
Monday	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Stay	O
Maker	O
came	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
&	O
took	O
measure	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pr	O
.	O
of	O
Corsets	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
e	O
n	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
in	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
B	O
:	O
&	O
caught	O
me	O
so	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
my	O
Hair	O
all	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
Ears	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
ym	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Sisters	O
Siscotti	B-pers
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
Morning	O
inoculated	O
her	O
Youngest	O
Child	O
--	O
whom	O
she	O
has	O
still	O
at	O
her	O
breast	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
At	O
two	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
--	O
but	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Party	O
tomorrow	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
carry	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
this	O
Party	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Bas	O
Blue	O
stile	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
but	O
am	O
engaged	O
.	O
to	O
meet	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J—	I-pers
s	O
--	O
at	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Grevilles	O
Politicks	O
--	O
party	O
violence	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
some	O
fine	O
Buckles	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
accepted	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
me	O
long	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
who	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bad	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
&	O
sister	O
s	O
health	O
--	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Nosegay	O
for	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
When	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
scribbled	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
--	O
wrote	O
notes	O
&	O
memorandums	O
for	O
visits	O
&	O
enquiries	O
--	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
who	O
is	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Went	O
down	O
stairs	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
whilst	O
she	O
din	O
'd	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Mahon	I-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Birth-day	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
at	O
dinner	O
besides	O
us	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
two	O
American	O
Gentlemen	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Tutor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
--	O
the	O
men	O
talk	O
'd	O
only	O
of	O
Politicks	O
--	O
little	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
desert	O
she	O
was	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
fever	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Men	O
&	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
after	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
visited	O
her	O
dear	O
girl	O
--	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Pianoforté	O
&	O
sung	O
some	O
sweet	O
Scotch	O
airs	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
does	O
with	O
great	O
taste	O
&	O
feeling	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Antrobus	B-pers
Julia	B-pers
&	O
their	O
Neice	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
tea	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
second	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
went	O
at	O
8	O
to	O
ye	O
H	O
of	O
Commons	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
went	O
away	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Children	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
with	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
his	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
--	O
who	O
poor	O
Young	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
declining	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
us	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
&	O
then	O
join	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Whist	O
party	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
amongst	O
us	O
Women	O
was	O
tolerably	O
agreeable	O
--	O
nothing	O
very	O
bright	O
said	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
there	O
remained	O
in	O
our	O
Room	O
only	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
but	O
had	O
Sandwichs	O
--	O
&	O
chatted	O
very	O
comfortably	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
told	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
Object	O
of	O
Charity	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
several	O
objects	O
of	O
distreſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wake	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
were	O
out	O
I	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
..	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catten	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
chatted	O
to	O
wth	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1784	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Sister	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
to	O
paper	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
Hair	O
in	O
order	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
hands	O
--	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
some	O
beautiful	O
artificial	O
Roses	O
to	O
wear	O
as	O
a	O
Bouquet	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Milliner	O
--	O
she	O
brought	O
my	O
Cap	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
my	O
Hair	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
her	O
Italian	O
friend	O
who	O
spoke	O
very	O
highly	O
of	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth-	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
After	O
Then	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
gave	O
meſsages	O
to	O
Madame	B-pers
Jaqquire	I-pers
&	O
wrote	O
notes	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
5	O
my	O
Uncle	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
--	O
met	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
--	O
--	O
after	O
Dinner	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
took	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
pretty	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
drawings	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
had	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
who	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
shew	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
she	O
gave	O
some	O
orders	O
for	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
them	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
our	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
--	I-pers
S—	I-pers
was	O
warm	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
--	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
reconcile	O
matters	O
--	O
the	O
G	O
:	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Coffee	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
was	O
lively	O
&	O
pleasant	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
Jaqquire	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
My	O
uncle	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Uncle	O
down	O
at	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
William	B-pers
there	O
by	O
appointment	O
--	O
found	O
him	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Legge	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
at	O
tea	O
.	O
he	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
acquaintance	O
I	O
had	O
introduced	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
many	O
places	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
&	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
her	O
buckles	O
Wednesday	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1784	O
The	O
Morning	O
paſs	O
'd	O
in	O
writing	O
Notes	O
--	O
cleaning	O
my	O
diamonds	O
sorting	O
my	O
things	O
--	O
having	O
my	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
tried	O
on	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
some	O
fine	O
flowers	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
.	O
din	O
'd	O
soon	O
after	O
3	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
at	O
5	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
after	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
done	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
&	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Women	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
all	O
attended	O
my	O
toilette	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Madame	B-pers
Jaqquire	I-pers
s	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
dreſs	O
to	O
carry	O
an	O
account	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
as	O
she	O
cld	O
.	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
at	O
length	O
ye	O
.	O
important	O
task	O
was	O
finished	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
civil	O
attendants	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
met	O
there	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Ducheſs	B-pers
Dowr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
Wife	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
--	O
a	O
pleasing	O
pretty	O
looking	O
woman	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
10	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
s	O
daughter	O
by	O
his	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
wife	O
)	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Careleton	O
House	O
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Room	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
very	O
gracious	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
seeing	O
me	O
--	O
had	O
two	O
long	O
conversations	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
afterwards	O
during	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
old	O
friendly	O
stile	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
5	O
&	O
600	O
people	O
no	O
distinction	O
of	O
party	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
both	O
the	O
ins	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
outs	O
--	O
people	O
most	O
of	O
The	O
ladies	O
were	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
with	O
taste	O
&	O
elegance	O
&	O
every	O
body	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
new	O
Clothes	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
occasion	O
--	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
People	O
&	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
thought	O
old	O
--	O
were	O
decorated	O
en	O
Habit	O
de	O
Bal	O
--	O
great	O
variety	O
&	O
no	O
set	O
form	O
of	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
to	O
dance	O
--	O
she	O
excused	O
herself	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
with	O
Child	O
--	O
he	O
began	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
by	O
dancing	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Country	O
dance	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
daughter	O
to	O
his	B-pers
R.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	O
he	O
then	O
left	O
off	O
dancing	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
in	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
people	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
crouded	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
dance	O
I	O
walked	O
from	O
room	O
to	O
room	O
My	O
Uncle	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
&	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
my	O
Relations	O
were	O
there	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
2	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
room	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
went	O
home	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
'd	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
protection	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Bertie	I-pers
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ancaster	I-pers
but	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
sup	O
at	O
his	O
table	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dining	O
Room	O
some	O
other	O
rooms	O
on	O
this	O
floor	O
were	O
had	O
also	O
tables	O
for	O
supper	O
Abt	O
.	O
2	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
Room	O
danced	O
a	O
Minuet	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
he	O
dances	O
very	O
finely	O
.	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
other	O
Minuets	O
dancd	O
--	O
but	O
without	O
ceremony	O
or	O
precision	O
as	O
to	O
Rank	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Supper	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Lower	O
Rooms	O
--	O
every	O
thing	O
handsome	O
&	O
proper	O
&	O
well	O
attended	O
--	O
The	O
Pages	O
were	O
all	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
uniform	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
color	O
'd	O
Cloath	O
--	O
trim	O
'd	O
handsomely	O
wth-	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
footmen	O
&	O
c	O
who	O
waited	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
tables	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Livery	O
more	O
trim	O
'd	O
&	O
new	O
In	O
short	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
entertainment	O
&	O
as	O
well	O
conducted	O
as	O
poſsible	O
for	O
so	O
pr	O
great	O
a	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
--	O
The	O
Prince	O
's	O
attentions	O
were	O
properly	O
divided	O
.	O
&	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
proper	O
--	O
more	O
gracious	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
&	O
a	O
Prince	O
than	O
his	O
behaviour	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
pity	O
that	O
one	O
who	O
know	O
so	O
well	O
how	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
is	O
right	O
ever	O
fails	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
!	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Supper	O
Rooms	O
--	O
I	O
being	O
very	O
prudent	O
.	O
got	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Bertie	I-pers
to	O
conduct	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Chair	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
Carlton	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
clear	O
'd	O
before	O
9	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
.	O
Thursday	O
March	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Rutland	I-pers
came	O
at	O
11	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
Side	O
to	O
hear	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Campell	I-pers
--	O
My	O
Miſs	B-pers
Erskine	I-pers
--	O
little	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Course	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
.	O
My	O
Old	O
Maid	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Call	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
Company	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
as	O
did	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
of	O
Cosgrove	B-place
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
either	O
him	O
or	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
Goodyar	B-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
to	O
dinner	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
Room	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
Picture	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
had	O
brought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
look	O
at	O
--	O
the	O
Subject	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
teaching	O
some	O
Boys	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Merit	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Exerter	I-pers
is	O
a	O
self	O
taught	O
painter	O
&	O
has	O
really	O
genius	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Meadows	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
there	O
Opie	B-pers
(	O
her	O
Sister	O
)	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
both	O
ye	O
.	O
Mother	O
&	O
daughter	O
are	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
taste	O
.	O
Opie	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
came	O
in	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Society	O
--	O
had	O
met	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
there	O
.	O
that	O
this	O
my	O
Uncle	O
had	O
shewn	O
his	O
fine	O
Vase	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Antiqurian	O
Society	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
out	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
in	O
--	O
to	O
enquire	O
abt	O
.	O
his	O
Brother	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
to	O
us	O
Yesterday	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
footman	O
--	O
&	O
our	O
other	O
Servt	O
.	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
came	O
home	O
we	O
chatted	O
a	O
little	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
I—	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Friday	O
March	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
&	O
answer	O
'd	O
Notes	O
--	O
excused	O
myself	O
to	O
dining	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
next	O
Sunday	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
domestic	O
affairs	O
--	O
&	O
other	O
matters	O
--	O
she	O
poſseſses	O
one	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
hearts	O
&	O
sweetest	O
temper	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
is	O
sensible	O
&	O
is	O
truly	O
good	O
&	O
amiable	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
came	O
&	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
my	O
Old	O
maid	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
France	B-place
with	O
her	O
Lady	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
that	O
she	O
liked	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jaquiere	I-pers
very	O
much	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
people	O
of	O
Large	O
fortune	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
daughter	O
to	O
Goodyar	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Nesbitt	I-pers
I	O
beleive	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
she	O
lived	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Court	O
&	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
because	O
I	O
could	O
no	O
longer	O
afford	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Servt	O
.	O
in	O
that	O
Stile	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
N——	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Manner	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Goodyar	B-pers
is	O
a	O
most	O
unaffected	O
--	O
elegant	O
,	O
pleasing	O
&	O
friendly	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
came	O
after	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
abt	O
2	O
oClock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
(	O
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
)	O
came	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
staid	O
on	O
till	O
near	O
4.	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
described	O
his	O
great	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
high	O
opinion	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
liveliest	O
manner	O
--	O
he	O
intreated	O
ye	O
.	O
continuance	O
of	O
my	O
friendship	O
&	O
advice	O
--	O
nay	O
he	O
even	O
wept	O
with	O
agony	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
withdrawn	O
my	O
regard	O
from	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
aſsure	O
him	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
continue	O
to	O
advise	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
--	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
reproofs	O
&	O
we	O
parted	O
amicably	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Miſs	O
Clarkes	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
a	O
friend	O
of	O
theirs	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
again	O
to	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
cld	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Chair	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
&	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
who	O
is	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
after	O
Dinner	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
paintings	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
very	O
capital	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
her	O
very	O
beautiful	O
drawings	O
of	O
Feathers	O
--	O
Birds	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
painted	O
in	O
Water	O
Colors	O
on	O
Vellum	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
porte	O
Folio	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
undoubtedly	O
most	O
finely	O
executed	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Chair	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
my	O
diary	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
went	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Hodgkinson	I-pers
Banks	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
with	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
--	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
chatting	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sandwich	O
&	O
wine	O
&	O
Water	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
Patience	O
must	O
help	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
easy	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
altered	O
Thomas	O
Dunham	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
The	O
life	O
and	O
original	O
correspondence	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
Radcliffe	O
,	O
the	O
friend	O
of	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Strafford	O
(	O
London	O
,	O
1810	O
)	O
,	O
p.98	O
,	O
Letter	O
dated	O
Feb.	O
16	O
[	O
1614	O
]	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Graye	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
Feb	O
16	O
.	O
1614	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
revolting	O
aſsurance	O
&	O
bluntness	O
in	O
quque	O
Quaker	O
's	O
even	O
in	O
th	O
ese	O
females	O
of	O
that	O
sect-	O
Miſs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
Welbeck	O
St	O
:	O
Saturday	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
help	O
in	O
ordering	O
&	O
setting	O
out	O
a	O
smart	O
Breakfast	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
at	O
before	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
.	O
he	O
admired	O
ye	O
.	O
comfortable	O
look	O
of	O
our	O
little	O
Mansion	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Radcliffe	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
interesting	O
&	O
agreeable	O
--	O
description	O
of	O
Volcano	O
's	O
--	O
the	O
Belles	O
Lettres	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
1	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
recent	O
Marriage	O
&	O
intended	O
Marriage	O
in	O
the	O
Egerton	O
family	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lively	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
Man	O
&	O
much	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
--	O
(	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Harringtons	O
)	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
singular	O
Character	O
--	O
not	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
--	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
ye	O
:	O
Late	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
fortune	O
--	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
Court	O
--	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
having	O
something	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
he	O
does	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
favor	O
to	O
like	O
me	O
so	O
very	O
much	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
tormented	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
5	O
6	O
years	O
of	O
his	O
with	O
his	O
civilities	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
person	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
seem	O
rude	O
to	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
wd	O
:	O
take	O
offence	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
tiresome	O
,	O
good	O
creature	O
for	O
he	O
means	O
extremely	O
well	O
--	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
require	O
it	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
wd	O
.	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
furthest	O
end	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
to	O
oblige	O
serve	O
me	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
&	O
at	O
my	O
request	O
wrote	O
out	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
dreſs	O
ye	O
:	O
Ball	O
night	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
myself	O
to	O
describe	O
this	O
parafernalia	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
came	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
8.	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
chearfull	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Chandos	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
were	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
also	O
there	O
--	O
but	O
soon	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Packet	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
leisure	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
letter	O
&	O
Diary	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
Carelton	O
House	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
enclose	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
exact	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
allowance	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
flowerery	O
language	O
of	O
a	O
Newspapers	O
.	O
Saturday	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
our	O
poor	O
man	O
(	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
)	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
for	O
his	O
Saturday	O
meal	O
&	O
had	O
told	O
their	O
Servts	O
.	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
yesterday	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
Twins	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
her	O
usual	O
benevolence	O
immediately	O
gave	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
me	O
½	O
a	O
Crown	O
--	O
Edward	B-pers
Maid	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Same	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
same	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
got	O
some	O
linnen	O
&	O
cut	O
out	O
things	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
Children	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
to	O
work	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
a	O
large	O
Peice	O
of	O
flannel	O
to	O
make	O
Blankets	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
.	O
we	O
soon	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
sat	O
&	O
chatted	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
had	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
staid	O
on	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
but	O
his	O
Eyes	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
his	O
gout	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Sunday	O
14	O
March	O
1784	O
found	O
a	O
long	O
incomprehensive	O
Note	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
some	O
franks	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
procure	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
read	O
over	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
s	O
letter	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sunday	O
March	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
therefore	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Service	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
11	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
at	O
began	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
sentiments	O
o	O
f	O
n	O
ye	O
.	O
conduct	O
&	O
behaviour	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
of	O
The	O
high	O
ton	O
--	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
such	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
censure	O
they	O
merit	O
--	O
When	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
her	O
daughters	O
were	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
we	O
set	O
ym	O
.	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
took	O
up	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
whom	O
we	O
left	O
at	O
Stapletons	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Busche	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
they	O
were	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Adam	O
's	O
--	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
likewise	O
out	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
out	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Kings	O
Mewse	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
who	O
is	O
ill	O
the	O
Servt	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
left	O
a	O
note	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isabella	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
only	O
the	O
family	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
dinner	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
read	O
to	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
&	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
William	B-pers
's	O
Sermons	O
on	O
the	O
Religious	O
friendships	O
--	O
a	O
well	O
written	O
&	O
interesting	O
discourse	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
c	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
out	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
repeated	O
Porteous	B-pers
s	O
Prayer	O
or	O
rather	O
Adams	O
in	O
his	O
Paradise	O
Lost	O
...	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
behaviour	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
8	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
his	O
Chariot	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
--	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
select	O
Concert	O
of	O
Musick	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
me	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
--	O
Milton	B-pers
--	O
