TOKEN	NE
Copy	O
of	O
ye	O
King	B-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
s	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
7	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1784	O
I	O
have	O
ye	O
pleasure	O
of	O
returning	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
ye	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
s	O
collection	O
of	O
Musick	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
frm	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
will	O
sufficiently	O
prove	O
how	O
much	O
He	O
is	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
manner	O
in	O
wch-	O
She	O
has	O
executed	O
His	O
Comiſsion	O
--	O
I	O
avail	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
worthiest	O
of	O
our	O
Sex	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
Regard	O
and	O
Esteem	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
Novbr	O
.	O
7	O
1784	O
Charlotte	B-pers
is	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
correct	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
has	O
obligingly	O
executed	O
ye	O
Comiſsion	O
of	O
obtaining	O
an	O
exact	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Collection	O
of	O
Mr-	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
s	O
Music	O
--	O
&	O
desires	O
she	O
will	O
forward	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Handel	I-pers
--	O
at	O
ye	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
Dr.	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
has	O
communicated	O
Dr	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Burney	I-pers
s	O
willingneſs	O
of	O
letting	O
ye	O
King	O
see	O
those	O
Volumes	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
list	O
of	O
His	O
original	O
Collection	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
desired	O
at	O
any	O
convenient	O
opportunity	O
to	O
let	O
ye	O
.	O
following	O
ones	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
great	O
care	O
shall	O
be	O
taken	O
that	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
without	O
damage	O
returned	O
25	O
Cernadige	O
10	O
Opera	O
of	O
Ameneto	O
22	O
Tasis	O
25	O
&	O
36	O
Vol	O
of	O
Deuts	O
39	O
Miscellanies	O
&	O
Water	O
Works	O
as	O
also	O
ye	O
Quarto	O
Man	O
:	O
of	O
Song	O
Composed	O
of	O
ye	O
great	O
Master	O
in	O
8	O
Parts	O
beginning	O
Still	O
I	O
adore	O
though	O
you	O
deny	O
me	O
