TOKEN	NE
13	O
June	O
1803	O
--	O
Eighteen	O
Years	O
ago	O
what	O
a	O
Simpleton	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
bestow	O
yourself	O
on	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
spent	O
this	O
anniversary	O
of	O
our	O
happy	O
Union	O
at	O
Home	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
loved	O
you	O
&	O
that	O
my	O
Esteem	O
my	O
friendship	O
&	O
my	O
Love	O
can	O
know	O
no	O
Increase	O
That	O
sweet	O
Daughter	O
of	O
ours	O
that	O
amiable	O
pledge	O
of	O
our	O
Love	O
is	O
very	O
dear	O
to	O
my	O
Heart	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
an	O
additional	O
gratification	O
from	O
observing	O
the	O
similarity	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
in	O
thing	O
's	O
most	O
eſsential	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Wife	O
--	O
may	O
you	O
enjoy	O
many	O
Years	O
of	O
Health	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
&	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
yr	O
Louisa	B-pers
united	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
matrimonial	O
Bleſsings	O
he	O
may	O
enjoy	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
Yr	O
Faithful	O
&	O
Affe	O
Husband	O
JD	B-pers
This	O
flood	O
distreſses	O
my	O
pocket	O
--	O
every	O
exertion	O
must	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
save	O
what	O
graſs	O
we	O
can	O
to	O
mow	O
--	O
desire	O
the	O
Horses	O
may	O
be	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
furthest	O
piece	O
in	O
Dove	O
House	O
Close	O
as	O
I	O
recommended	O
in	O
a	O
former	O
letter	O
&	O
let	O
the	O
Lucern	O
&	O
Graſs	O
from	O
the	O
Shrubbery	O
&	O
c	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Horses	O
--	O
What	O
with	O
one	O
Loſs	O
or	O
another	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Bedford	B-place
soon	O
in	O
good	O
ernest	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fret	O
about	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
remedied	O
,	O
having	O
too	O
many	O
c	O
auses	O
to	O
feel	O
myself	O
the	O
happiest	O
Man	O
in	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds-	B-place
