TOKEN	NE
Dec	O
Friday	O
St	O
Jamess	O
--	O
15	O
1786	O
Nothing	O
could	O
exceed	O
my	O
surprise	O
,	O
at	O
seeing	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
my	O
Table	O
to	O
day	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
my	O
airing	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Post	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
thinking	O
of	O
you	O
these	O
several	O
Days	O
paſsed	O
fixed	O
at	O
Northamton	B-place
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
wishing	O
for	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
absolutely	O
expecting	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
liked	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
you	O
felt	O
in	O
,	O
your	O
new	O
situations	O
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
alarmed	O
me	O
exceedingly	O
so	O
sudden	O
a	O
change	O
in	O
your	O
plans	O
,	O
seemed	O
to	O
indicate	O
an	O
immediate	O
neceſsity	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
quite	O
frightful	O
--	O
Thank	O
God	O
you	O
and	O
conclude	O
by	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
both	O
of	O
yourself	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
easy	O
about	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
that	O
anything	O
should	O
vex	O
you	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
without	O
inconvenience	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
how	O
his	O
Health	O
improves	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
your	O
spirits	O
continue	O
good	O
--	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
conceive	O
what	O
I	O
feel	O
when	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
“	O
pray	O
come	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
contrive	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
trivial	O
Obstacle	O
prevent	O
your	O
coming	O
”	O
Alas	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
anything	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
ill	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
an	O
hours	O
warning	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
imagine	O
I	O
wish	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
The	B-pers
Bridgemans	I-pers
are	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
,	O
whom	O
above	O
all	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
!	O
For	O
how	O
long	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
met	O
!	O
How	O
long	O
perhaps	O
nay	O
most	O
likely	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
meet	O
again	O
!	O
what	O
would	O
I	O
give	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
here	O
just	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
comfortable	O
Evening	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
ever	O
since	O
this	O
Day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
better	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
comes	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
whenev	O
er	O
she	O
can	O
get	O
out	O
--	O
once	O
I	O
had	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
--	O
Madame	B-pers
Reventelau	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
again	O
too	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
quite	O
alone	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
Girl	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Companion	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
never	O
makes	O
impertinent	O
remarks	O
,	O
very	O
docil	O
&	O
very	O
charming	O
--	O
Did	O
the	O
Hours	O
otherwise	O
paſs	O
heavily	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
occupy	O
&	O
amuse	O
me	O
sufficiently	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
always	O
find	O
more	O
occupation	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
time	O
for	O
--	O
However	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
it	O
aside	O
tho	O
'	O
without	O
regret	O
for	O
that	O
of	O
conversing	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
Would	O
I	O
could	O
promise	O
myse	O
lf	O
that	O
comfort	O
in	O
any	O
fixed	O
future	O
time	O
!	O
To	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Scheme	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
is	O
too	O
well	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
now	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
go	O
in	O
Spring	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
neither	O
have	O
the	O
power	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
wish	O
of	O
accompanyi	O
n	O
g	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
comfortable	O
Lodgi	O
n	O
gs	O
my	O
dear	O
my	O
Father	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
procure	O
any	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
become	O
more	O
so	O
now	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
?	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
the	O
Local	O
&	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
humours	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
you	O
will	O
lead	O
too	O
retired	O
&	O
quiet	O
a	O
life	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
detestable	O
.	O
That	O
continually	O
livi	O
n	O
g	O
in	O
publick	O
,	O
that	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
being	O
denied	O
,	O
the	O
Tittle	O
Tattle	O
,	O
the	O
heat	O
,	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
the	O
dirt	O
--	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
detestable	O
sejour	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
how	O
she	O
conducts	O
herself	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
her	O
manners	O
,	O
behaviour	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
thought	O
&	O
said	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
expect	O
from	O
your	O
sincere	O
,	O
impartial	O
Friendship	O
--	O
I	O
fancy	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
remains	O
of	O
that	O
illneſs	O
&	O
those	O
low	O
spirits	O
which	O
absolutely	O
made	O
my	O
life	O
wretched	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
this	O
Autumn	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
lead	O
s	O
too	O
diſsipated	O
a	O
life	O
--	O
Tell	O
my	O
how	O
are	O
my	O
dear	O
Fat	O
spirits	O
--	O
does	O
he	O
play	O
at	O
Whist	O
every	O
night	O
--	O
I	O
hop	O
e	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
them	O
--	O
now	O
for	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
myself	O
Turton	B-pers
comes	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
healed	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Rheumatism	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
pain	O
at	O
night	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
symptom	O
--	O
yet	O
nothing	O
has	O
hitherto	O
relieved	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
take	O
Bark	O
in	O
quantity	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
awake	O
&	O
in	O
spirits	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
for	O
every	O
night	O
is	O
spent	O
in	O
Pain	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
have	O
I	O
an	O
Hours	O
sound	O
sleep	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
otherwise	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
happy	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
to	O
Courteenhall	O
,	O
not	O
knowi	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
more	O
exact	O
direction	O
--	O
Let	O
me	O
hear	O
how	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
--	O
I	O
answer	O
your	O
letter	O
immediatly	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
this	O
on	O
Sunday	O
--	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
walk	O
any	O
more	O
up	O
to	O
Brock	O
Street	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
adieu	O
your	O
affec	O
:	O
since	O
re	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
No	O
2	O
Abbey	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
1786	O
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
