TOKEN	NE
August	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
12	O
oClock	O
It	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
my	O
dearest	O
and	O
amiable	O
friend	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
comfortable	O
leisure	O
hour	O
to	O
hold	O
sweet	O
converse	O
with	O
you	O
since	O
last	O
Monday	O
two	O
post	O
days	O
without	O
writing	O
,	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
long	O
silence	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
delight	O
each	O
day	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
lines	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
shall	O
employ	O
this	O
hour	O
of	O
silence	O
to	O
answer	O
yours	O
--	O
&	O
shall	O
borrow	O
from	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
before	O
me	O
those	O
dear	O
letters	O
of	O
yours	O
wch-	O
are	O
unanswered	O
&	O
shall	O
proceed	O
regularly	O
to	O
answer	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
mistake	O
&	O
omiſsion	O
.	O
The	O
Xtening	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
Babel	B-place
for	O
Rhea	B-pers
wrote	O
to	O
tell	O
Perfecta	B-pers
it	O
wd	O
.	O
Louvre	B-place
,	O
&	O
I	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
child	O
will	O
be	O
Xtened	O
at	O
five	O
weeks	O
old	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
--	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Week	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Birth	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
yt	O
.	O
event	O
you	O
know	O
must	O
remain	O
rather	O
uncertain	O
--	O
she	O
expects	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
week	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
entertain	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sack-race	O
--	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
myself	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Barnes	B-place
Garden	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
your	O
Han̅overian	O
Hanoverian	O
Lady	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
shall	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
find	O
a	O
rival	O
in	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
you	O
very	O
selfish	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
me	O
discover	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
jealousy	O
in	O
my	O
composition	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
were	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
your	O
remembrance	O
of	O
them	O
&	O
desired	O
their	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
last	O
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
describe	O
--	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Tuesday	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Ball	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
them	O
by	O
some	O
Nephews	O
and	O
Neices	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
M	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	O
Dr	B-pers
Bajott	I-pers
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
has	O
a	O
living	O
at	O
Jevington	B-place
about	O
4	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
where	O
he	O
resides	O
abt	O
.	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
months	O
a	O
year	O
--	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
superior	O
abilities	O
and	O
character	O
)	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bajott	I-pers
having	O
two	O
Brothers	O
&	O
Sisters	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
engaging	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
other	O
families	O
to	O
join	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
a	O
pretty	O
little	O
dance	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
invited	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
heating	O
myself	O
I	O
declin	O
'd	O
going	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
however	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Perfecta	B-pers
abt	O
.	O
10	O
oClock	O
just	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
upon	O
the	O
dancers	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
ym	O
.	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
dance	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
amused	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suffer	O
for	O
this	O
diſsipation	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
pour	O
prendre	O
longe	O
t	O
--	O
Caled	B-pers
lent	O
M	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
&	O
me	O
his	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Jevington	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
having	O
civily	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
knowing	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
receive	O
her	O
visit	O
at	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
house	O
.	O
we	O
found	O
ym	O
.	O
at	O
tea	O
&	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
appears	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
much	O
polish	O
'd	O
--	O
the	O
same	O
her	O
sisters	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
enter	O
more	O
into	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
r	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
countenance	O
is	O
interesting	O
--	O
his	O
person	O
has	O
quite	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
studious	O
man	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
such	O
as	O
one	O
often	O
fancies	O
studious	O
Men	O
must	O
have	O
--	O
so	O
thin	O
so	O
very	O
thin	O
is	O
Dr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
he	O
appears	O
the	O
Shadow	O
of	O
a	O
Shadow	O
.	O
during	O
our	O
drive	O
M.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
conversed	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
lead	O
on	O
from	O
one	O
thing	O
to	O
another	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
conversation	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
kindneſs	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
gentle	O
&	O
unpresuming	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
manner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
should	O
regret	O
having	O
known	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
hope	O
to	O
continue	O
the	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
Town	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
astonished	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
expreſs	O
at	O
insolence	O
--	O
How	O
mean	O
to	O
take	O
privilege	O
of	O
her	O
sex	O
to	O
say	O
such	O
rude	O
&	O
groſs	O
things	O
--	O
what	O
could	O
have	O
provoked	O
her	O
to	O
attack	O
Benedict	B-pers
--	O
for	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
men	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
one	O
more	O
delicate	O
or	O
more	O
attentive	O
in	O
his	O
manner	O
&	O
conversation	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
therefore	O
to	O
say	O
rude	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
must	O
require	O
no	O
common	O
share	O
of	O
effrontery	O
.	O
what	O
are	O
the	O
Subjects	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Books	O
Edwin	B-pers
has	O
sent	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
length	O
free	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
correspondence	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
terrible	O
long	O
ones	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
last	O
month	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
example	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
got	O
to	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.-	O
Caled	B-pers
received	O
your	O
Compts	O
.	O
with	O
pleasure	O
&	O
I	O
managed	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
answer	O
,	O
otherwise	O
than	O
through	O
me	O
was	O
not	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
give	O
my	O
grateful	O
thanks	O
to	O
Benedict	B-pers
&	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
shall	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
Guineas	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
subscription	O
has	O
been	O
raised	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
Widow	O
;	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
,	O
--	O
Ah	O
when	O
will	O
that	O
be	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
exclaim	O
.	O
--	O
Do	O
not	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
judge	O
too	O
unfavorable	O
of	O
Caled	B-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
I	O
beleive	O
so	O
amiable	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
--	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
him	O
a	O
proper	O
person	O
for	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
fills	O
--	O
he	O
will	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
much	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
tricks	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
wch	O
.	O
often	O
makes	O
him	O
advance	O
illiberal	O
notions	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
Hamet	B-pers
&	O
Omar	B-pers
I	O
am	O
fully	O
persuaded	O
are	O
most	O
estimable	O
characters	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
rather	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
rides	O
opened	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
candour	O
&	O
confidence	O
of	O
friendship	O
.	O
You	O
make	O
me	O
tremble	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
account	O
you	O
send	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
--	O
Oh	O
beware	O
of	O
endulging	O
yourself	O
to	O
think	O
over	O
past	O
events	O
--	O
for	O
surely	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
that	O
only	O
you	O
could	O
allude	O
--	O
“	O
pity	O
you	O
”	O
--	O
yes	O
I	O
do	O
from	O
my	O
Soul	O
--	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
--	O
how	O
could	O
my	O
friend	O
imagine	O
I	O
ever	O
should	O
“	O
despise	O
”	O
her	O
--	O
my	O
God	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
write	O
the	O
word	O
--	O
do	O
I	O
not	O
know	O
&	O
feel	O
that	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
s	O
mind	O
is	O
superior	O
--	O
she	O
never	O
can	O
act	O
wrong	O
--	O
she	O
may	O
indeed	O
feel	O
too	O
much	O
--	O
you	O
have	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
alarm	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
conjure	O
you	O
keep	O
me	O
not	O
in	O
ignorance	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
relative	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
you	O
have	O
indeed	O
promised	O
me	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
depend	O
upon	O
your	O
promises	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
“	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
”	O
;	O
esteem	O
me	O
”	O
--	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
into	O
my	O
Heart	O
you	O
wld-	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
lov	O
'd	O
--	O
&	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
esteem	O
where	O
I	O
greatly	O
love	O
.	O
Thank	O
God	O
You	O
are	O
better	O
in	O
Health	O
.	O
--	O
't	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
w	O
h	O
ether	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
Babel	B-place
or	O
Leuctra	B-place
at	O
my	O
return	O
.	O
Yours	O
of	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
is	O
apparently	O
apparently	O
written	O
in	O
great	O
agitation	O
of	O
spirits	O
--	O
Benedict	B-pers
s	O
indisposition	O
will	O
certainly	O
increase	O
your	O
complaints	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
receive	O
better	O
accounts	O
of	O
him	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
indiscreet	O
to	O
heat	O
yourself	O
by	O
walking	O
--	O
surely	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
occasion	O
so	O
preſsing	O
to	O
oblige	O
You	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
August	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
waters	O
they	O
always	O
stand	O
your	O
friend	O
.	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
agree	O
equally	O
well	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
formerly	O
.	O
--	O
Monday	O
Morng	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
telling	O
You	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
excursion	O
we	O
took	O
on	O
Friday	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
postpone	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
post	O
--	O
Yours	O
of	O
Satry	O
.	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
--	O
my	O
fears	O
are	O
realliz	O
'd	O
--	O
Your	O
letter	O
has	O
dejected	O
me	O
beyond	O
expreſsion	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
next	O
post	O
--	O
fail	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
suffer	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
kept	O
in	O
suspence	O
--	O
God	O
Almighty	O
protect	O
you	O
&	O
restore	O
Health	O
to	O
Benedict	B-pers
&	O
Yourself	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
friend	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
for	O
more	O
Adieu	O
Miranda	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
desires	O
you	O
will	O
accept	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
obliged	O
if	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
send	O
the	O
inclosed	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
27	O
th	O
August	O
1780	O
