TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
sensible	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
part	O
in	O
so	O
kind	O
a	O
manner	O
in	O
my	O
interests	O
If	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S_t	I-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
more	O
candid	O
in	O
his	O
publick	O
transactions	O
than	O
in	O
his	O
conduct	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
dismiſsion	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
cause	O
of	O
much	O
regret	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
wrote	O
by	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S——t	I-pers
's	O
particular	O
direction	O
,	O
he	O
disapproves	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
approved	O
but	O
even	O
corrected	O
him	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
my	O
Memorial	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
meanly	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
present	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
short	O
in	O
that	O
letter	O
in	O
many	O
unmeaning	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
regard	O
he	O
declined	O
giving	O
me	O
any	O
aſsistance	O
whatever	O
,	O
as	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Preferments	O
,	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
own	O
words	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
department	O
.	O
His	O
opinion	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
consult	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
equally	O
frivolous	O
&	O
unsincere	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
spoke	O
out	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
real	O
regard	O
for	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
that	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
no	O
claim	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
construction	O
I	O
must	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
by	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
next	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
stay	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
proceed	O
on	O
my	O
journey	O
to	O
Geneva	B-place
,	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
arrive	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
great	O
heats	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
If	O
by	O
chance	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
procure	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
to	O
any	O
respectable	O
Family	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
much	O
use	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
depend	O
entirely	O
upon	O
the	O
acquaintances	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
very	O
respectable	O
Persons	O
connected	O
with	O
that	O
Country	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
preliminaries	O
of	O
some	O
difficulty	O
to	O
settle	O
before	O
my	O
Preferment	O
can	O
be	O
surrenderd	O
,	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
too	O
well	O
understood	O
in	O
these	O
days	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
explain	O
'd	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
pleasure	O
in	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
showing	O
you	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
them	O
objects	O
well	O
deserving	O
my	O
whole	O
attention	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Jane	B-pers
will	O
be	O
more	O
fortunate	O
than	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
understanding	O
with	O
excellent	O
principles	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
foundation	O
for	O
a	O
polish	O
'd	O
education	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
poſseſses	O
every	O
requisite	O
talent	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
appointed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Balfour	I-pers
to	O
be	O
my	O
Agent	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
directions	O
to	O
be	O
punctual	O
in	O
making	O
your	O
annual	O
Remittance	O
which	O
I	O
conclude	O
he	O
will	O
always	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
sends	O
my	O
yearly	O
Rent	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
generally	O
receive	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
Feby	O
.	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
the	O
Tenants	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
payments	O
sooner	O
.	O
What	O
changes	O
the	O
great	O
revolutions	O
in	O
the	O
Administration	O
will	O
produce	O
here	O
time	O
will	O
show	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
satisfied	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
of	O
Politicks	O
is	O
particularly	O
unsatisfactory	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observe	O
you	O
always	O
avoid	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
views	O
are	O
now	O
much	O
contracted	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
expectations	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
I	O
shall	O
at	O
least	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
fewer	O
disappointments	O
.	O
My	O
spirits	O
are	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
broken	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
can	O
enjoy	O
agreeable	O
society	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
kind	O
of	O
society	O
that	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
find	O
here	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Grevilles	I-pers
,	O
you	O
have	O
never	O
mention	O
'd	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
disposed	O
to	O
think	O
extremely	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
very	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affece	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sackville	O
Street	O
April	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
some	O
Hôtel	O
for	O
the	O
few	O
days	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
stay	O
in	O
London	B-place
