TOKEN	NE
Curzon	O
Street	O
Mar	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
1791	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
consider	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
favored	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
your	O
friendship	O
&	O
regard	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
return	O
my	O
particular	O
acknowledgements	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
led	O
to	O
prefer	O
the	O
Opinion	O
&	O
practice	O
of	O
those	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
structure	O
of	O
the	O
Human	O
body	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
medicines	O
their	O
constant	O
&	O
regular	O
study	O
,	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
such	O
advantages	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
told	O
me	O
last	O
Winter	O
,	O
my	O
Complaint	O
lay	O
so	O
deep	O
,	O
that	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
any	O
external	O
application	O
would	O
reach	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
trust	O
to	O
time	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
Constitution	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
lately	O
much	O
troubled	O
the	O
profeſsion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
certainly	O
a	O
freer	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
leg	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
amendment	O
is	O
very	O
slow	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
content	O
Myself	O
with	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
share	O
of	O
activity	O
&	O
motion	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
advised	O
against	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Warm	O
bathing	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
inclined	O
to	O
have	O
tried	O
Buxton	B-place
,	O
&	O
certainly	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
strong	O
inducement	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
paying	O
our	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
yrself	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
Happy	O
to	O
receive	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Her	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
's	O
Complaint	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
is	O
much	O
leſs	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
We	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
town	B-place
,	O
but	O
her	O
Health	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
perfect	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
friends	O
wish	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
intends	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Her	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
beleive	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
prudent	O
Man	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
surprized	O
indeed	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
only	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
escaped	O
the	O
inconveniencies	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
fall	O
into	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
begin	O
to	O
build	O
,	O
of	O
exceeding	O
their	O
original	O
intentions	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
approve	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
alterations	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
finished	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
both	O
will	O
have	O
health	O
to	O
injoy	O
them	O
.	O
Though	O
We	O
approve	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
's	O
measures	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
&	O
wish	O
Him	O
to	O
continue	O
Minister	O
,	O
yet	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
best	O
friends	O
object	O
to	O
the	O
frequent	O
alarms	O
of	O
War	O
;	O
&	O
still	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
proceed	O
farther	O
;	O
they	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
unsettled	O
state	O
of	O
france	B-place
,	O
from	O
which	O
Country	O
our	O
cheif	O
danger	O
lies	O
,	O
We	O
ought	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
the	O
leſsening	O
our	O
immense	O
debt	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
now	O
there	O
so	O
fair	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
new	O
Sinking	O
fund	O
redeeming	O
every	O
year	O
£1,700,000	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
p	O
er	O
ct	O
.	O
;	O
they	O
farther	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
Ruſsia	B-place
would	O
be	O
our	O
most	O
Uſeful	O
ally	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
little	O
imports	O
England	B-place
,	O
to	O
whom	O
Constantinople	B-place
should	O
belong	O
.	O
as	O
you	O
live	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
occupy	O
some	O
land	O
.	O
Where	O
the	O
Quantity	O
is	O
in	O
proportion	O
to	O
the	O
Establishment	O
&	O
the	O
Consumption	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
,	O
there	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
much	O
loſs	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
afford	O
some	O
amusement	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Daughter	O
&	O
Catherine	B-pers
(	O
who	O
grows	O
tall	O
&	O
is	O
delicate	O
)	O
join	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
presenting	O
our	O
best	O
Wishes	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sr	O
.	O
yr	O
.	O
faithful	O
&	O
obliged	O
Servt	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
