TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
obligeing	O
Letter	O
&	O
Your	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
kindneſs	O
meritted	O
an	O
earlier	O
acknowledgement	O
than	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
offer	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
was	O
too	O
much	O
charmed	O
wt	O
yr	O
Company	O
to	O
expect	O
he	O
'd	O
spare	O
you	O
a	O
Moment	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
bellieve	O
me	O
the	O
only	O
Letters	O
Ive	O
had	O
from	O
him	O
were	O
filled	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
pray	O
indulge	O
him	O
in	O
yr	O
Correspondance	O
he	O
wants	O
such	O
agreeable	O
aſsistances	O
to	O
Support	O
his	O
Spirits	O
in	O
dull	O
Country	O
Quarters	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
very	O
sorry	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
Indisposed	O
but	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
shes	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
agree	O
wt	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Prescription	O
of	O
Buxton	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
in	O
Mainie	B-pers
's	O
name	O
&	O
my	O
own	O
for	O
yr	O
kind	O
present	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
which	O
are	O
come	O
saffe	O
to	O
hand	O
be	O
asured	O
she	O
stood	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
Nothing	O
to	O
keep	O
you	O
in	O
her	O
Mind	O
but	O
will	O
wear	O
&	O
prize	O
them	O
infinatly	O
for	O
your	O
sake	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
wrote	O
her	O
acknowledg	O
ements	O
herself	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
so	O
constant	O
an	O
Engagement	O
at	O
a	O
french	O
Boarding	O
Schooll	O
where	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
day	O
Boarder	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
Moment	O
to	O
herself	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
here	O
join	O
her	O
in	O
their	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Remembrances	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
as	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
&	O
in	O
vain	O
Endevoured	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
enclose	O
to	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
but	O
he	O
asured	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
wt	O
out	O
delay	O
&	O
send	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
:	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
&	O
I	O
'll	O
attackt	O
him	O
again	O
--	O
.	O
by	O
a	O
Letter	O
received	O
last	O
Post	O
from	O
my	O
Btr	O
dated	O
the	O
3	O
/	O
14	O
July	O
I	O
am	O
made	O
very	O
Uneasy	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Ill	O
of	O
a	O
feaver	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
getting	O
gradualy	O
better	O
&	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
time	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Bark	O
five	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
.	O
&	O
proposed	O
if	O
no	O
relapse	O
hapned	O
to	O
embark	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Flora	O
en	O
famille	O
the	O
Monday	O
fortnight	O
after	O
his	O
Letter	O
was	O
wrote	O
he	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
that	O
the	O
feaver	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
his	O
Constitution	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
Sea	O
Voyage	O
would	O
s	O
erve	O
to	O
Reastablish	O
his	O
Health	O
:	O
he	O
bids	O
me	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
again	O
for	O
unleſs	O
he	O
was	O
worse	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
write	O
again	O
till	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
.	O
though	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
is	O
well	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
being	O
Anxious	O
where	O
so	O
much	O
is	O
at	O
Stake	O
--	O
Im	O
sorry	O
but	O
not	O
Surprized	O
you	O
find	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
so	O
little	O
better	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
heartily	O
pity	O
though	O
I	O
fear	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
can	O
relieve	O
her	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
did	O
was	O
only	O
what	O
Humanity	O
required	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
glad	O
she	O
returns	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
the	O
Dr	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
the	O
best	O
chance	O
for	O
her	O
Recovery	O
to	O
give	O
that	O
place	O
a	O
fair	O
trial	O
--	O
which	O
as	O
yet	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
from	O
reasons	O
she	O
can	O
tell	O
You	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
ev'ry	O
thing	O
considerd	O
her	O
chance	O
is	O
but	O
precarious	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
wishes	O
attend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
best	O
affection	O
is	O
ever	O
Yours	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
