TOKEN	NE
28	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Albans	O
Street	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1800	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
Note	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
,	O
arrived	O
safe	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
latter	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
after	O
having	O
carefully	O
torn	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
excellent	O
reasons	O
for	O
doing	O
so	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
Man	O
s	O
Shoe	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
presented	O
my	O
Wife	O
with	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
Book	O
,	O
many	O
many	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
Of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
inform	O
You	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
your	O
Puppy	O
of	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
alert	O
,	O
for	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
this	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
packet	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
Me	O
.	O
On	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
Compliments	O
stared	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
is	O
really	O
very	O
provoking	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
molested	O
carrying	O
female	O
Nonsense	O
,	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
As	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Books	O
are	O
well	O
bound	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
civilly	O
received	O
by	O
my	O
Females	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Man	O
John	B-pers
will	O
condescend	O
to	O
trouble	O
himself	O
with	O
taking	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
throw	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chaise	O
Window	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
and	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Aſsure	O
Yourself	O
of	O
my	O
constant	O
abhorrence	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
hate	O
all	O
Givers	O
of	O
Presents	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Envy	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
example	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
sincere	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
First	O
July	O
1800	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
