TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Wherever	O
you	O
are	O
situated	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
,	O
have	O
my	O
sincere	O
wishes	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
happineſs	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
so	O
loved	O
the	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
delightful	O
occupations	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
old	O
,	O
that	O
love	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
has	O
so	O
much	O
increased	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
feel	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
your	O
Friends	O
may	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
quitting	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
reside	O
in	O
the	O
tumultuous	O
City	O
--	O
Probably	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
felt	O
otherwise	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
the	O
Bleſsing	O
still	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
once	O
poſseſsed	O
;	O
That	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
may	O
long	O
,	O
long	O
have	O
your	O
Bleſsing	O
,	O
/	O
your	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
continue	O
what	O
she	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
hearty	O
wish	O
.	O
With	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
&	O
my	O
best	O
Regards	O
to	O
you	O
All	O
,	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
's	O
faithfully	O
PCremorne	B-pers
Chelsea	B-place
Farm	O
15	O
November	O
1809	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Chelsea	B-place
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Single	O
