TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
writes	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
announce	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
's	O
death	O
1792	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
deſired	O
to	O
by	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
request	O
you	O
would	O
communicate	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenſon	I-pers
the	O
severe	O
loſs	O
she	O
has	O
experienced	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accounts	O
of	O
which	O
arrived	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
The	O
last	O
resource	O
of	O
a	O
Sea	O
Voyage	O
did	O
not	O
check	O
the	O
progreſs	O
of	O
her	O
Illneſs	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
consolation	O
we	O
have	O
ariſes	O
from	O
our	O
knowing	O
that	O
her	O
last	O
moments	O
were	O
composed	O
&	O
Easy	O
,	O
&	O
Excluſive	O
of	O
the	O
Eminent	O
Skill	O
of	O
Dr	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
as	O
a	O
Physician	O
;	O
the	O
particular	O
attentions	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
shewn	O
contributed	O
much	O
to	O
alleviate	O
the	O
distreſs	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
They	O
will	O
attend	O
her	O
remains	O
to	O
Bourdeaux	B-place
,	O
&	O
from	O
thence	O
proceed	O
by	O
Sea	O
or	O
Land	O
as	O
Circumstances	O
occur	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
pen	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
excuſe	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
having	O
employed	O
me	O
on	O
this	O
painful	O
occaſion	O
.	O
It	O
gives	O
me	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenſon	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
sincere	O
regard	O
Your	O
most	O
faithful	O
Humle	O
Sert	O
C	B-pers
FGreville	I-pers
Portland	O
place	O
.	O
July	O
13	O
1792	O
.	O
