TOKEN	NE
Chelsea	B-place
Wedy	O
:	O
Morng	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
omit	O
sending	O
an	O
answer	O
my	O
D	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
your	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
such	O
gracious	O
Meſsages	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Princeſses	O
,	O
pray	O
present	O
my	O
humble	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Duty	O
,	O
&	O
take	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
informing	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
that	O
the	O
little	O
Book	O
is	O
at	O
length	O
arrived	O
from	O
Bristol	B-place
&	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Bookbinder	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
I	O
think	O
equal	O
--	O
some	O
Sections	O
are	O
much	O
inferior	O
to	O
others	O
all	O
written	O
by	O
a	O
pious	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
equally	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
to	O
be	O
approved	O
.	O
pray	O
present	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
;	O
&	O
aſsure	O
their	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſses	I-pers
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
their	O
gracious	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
seeing	O
Them	O
again	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
grateful	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
for	O
so	O
kindly	O
remembering	O
Me	O
,	O
&	O
aſsure	O
her	O
,	O
The	O
Work	O
Bag	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
kept	O
in	O
my	O
Lavendar	O
Drawer	O
--	O
where	O
I	O
keep	O
every	O
thing	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
high	O
Value	O
on	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
only	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
on	O
High	O
Days	O
&	O
Holidays	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
this	O
Moment	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
tells	O
me	O
He	O
has	O
rode	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
vext	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
ride	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
my	O
Meſsenger	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
you	O
this	O
Letter	O
;	O
he	O
begs	O
hard	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
it	O
sooner	O
by	O
my	O
sending	O
it	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
Day	O
;	O
upon	O
recollection	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
it	O
directly	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
My	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
half	O
worn	O
out	O
with	O
having	O
seen	O
Sights	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
think	O
She	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
Their	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Family	I-pers
;	O
I	O
mean	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
Publick	O
--	O
now	O
as	O
her	O
State	O
of	O
health	O
makes	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
Dreſs	O
&	O
go	O
to	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
tempted	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
whenever	O
their	O
Majesty	O
's	O
go	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
so	O
highly	O
honoured	O
her	O
Friend	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
gracious	O
Marks	O
of	O
Favour	O
--	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
poſsibly	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
this	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
vastly	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
pray	O
tell	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
I	O
went	O
to	O
Wirgman	B-pers
's	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
Pencil	O
with	O
a	O
magnifying	O
Glaſs	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Princeſses	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
Adieu	O
my	O
D	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
Yrs	O
:	O
very	O
Affectly	O
PDartrey	B-pers
I	O
am	O
glad	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
is	O
recovered	O
.	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
yr	O
:	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
Lisbon	B-place
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
Age	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Feilding	I-pers
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
last	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Feilding	I-pers
Ly.-	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
vastly	O
recovered	O
.	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
is	O
returned	O
&	O
begs	O
his	O
best	O
Comps	O
:	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
's	O
little	O
Girl	O
s	O
Christening	O
at	O
Bayford	B-place
next	O
Monday	O
--	O
charming	O
,	O
easy	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
insists	O
upon	O
my	O
leaving	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
seemed	O
to	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
Him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Glimpe	O
of	O
Mrs.-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
in	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Deal	B-place
.	O
She	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
charmed	O
with	O
Les	O
Adieux	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
got	O
Lord	B-pers
Kames	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Culture	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
--	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
.	O
