TOKEN	NE
Albemarle	O
Street	O
Oct	O
..	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
has	O
this	O
moment	O
receiv	O
'd	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
truly	O
affectionate	O
letter	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
thank	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
sincerest	O
manner	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Father	O
continues	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
our	O
dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
better	O
,	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
nights	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
slept	O
well	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
opiates	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
takes	O
every	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
mother	O
is	O
extremely	O
wretched	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
grow	O
fearful	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
hurt	O
herself	O
,	O
her	O
spirits	O
are	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
wonder	O
at	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
constant	O
anxiety	O
&	O
misery	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
of	O
a	O
fearful	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
apprehended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
as	O
Dr.	B-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
have	O
never	O
flatter	O
'd	O
us	O
since	O
they	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
think	O
he	O
may	O
continue	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
strength	O
still	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
in	O
no	O
pain	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
comfort	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
patient	O
,	O
he	O
neither	O
murmurs	O
nor	O
complains	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
thinks	O
himself	O
in	O
danger	O
.	O
Oh	O
my	O
dearest	O
dear	O
friend	O
what	O
a	O
loſs	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
duty	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
our	O
maker	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
hard	O
very	O
hard	O
trial	O
whenever	O
the	O
fatal	O
day	O
approaches	O
comes	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
no	O
doubt	O
meet	O
with	O
that	O
happineſs	O
hereafter	O
,	O
which	O
dearest	O
best	O
of	O
men	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
he	O
has	O
never	O
experienced	O
.	O
We	O
most	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
offer	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
never	O
doubted	O
your	O
faithful	O
friendship	O
,	O
no	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
we	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
coming	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
says	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
afflict	O
your	O
tender	O
heart	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
herself	O
nothing	O
but	O
time	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
use	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
begs	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
her	O
not	O
writing	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
spirits	O
are	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
put	O
pen	O
to	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
add	O
another	O
line	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
,	O
will	O
finish	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
My	O
Father	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
night	O
&	O
is	O
as	O
usu	O
l	O
a	O
l	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
mother	O
told	O
him	O
yesterday	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
kind	O
offer	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
struggle	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
get	O
amongst	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
dearest	O
man	O
I	O
wish	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
hopes	O
of	O
his	O
getting	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
is	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
all	O
our	O
friends	O
are	O
kind	O
in	O
sending	O
,	O
&	O
none	O
more	O
attentive	O
than	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
is	O
grown	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Strothoff	I-pers
to	O
whose	O
behaviour	O
I	O
intirely	O
attribute	O
this	O
last	O
attack	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
excuse	O
is	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
brother	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
quite	O
overcome	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
ill	O
ever	O
since	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burgeſs	I-pers
's	O
death	O
;	O
&	O
my	O
Father	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
hurt	O
.	O
Our	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
returns	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to-morrow	O
for	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
four	O
days	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
&	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Harwood	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
she	O
hopes	O
that	O
her	O
affairs	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
way	O
of	O
being	O
settled	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
&	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
my	O
astonishment	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
J——	I-pers
should	O
not	O
himself	O
have	O
been	O
anxious	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
&	O
children	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
settled	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
sav	O
'd	O
our	O
amiable	O
friend	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
anxiety	O
.	O
Pray	O
thank	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
very	O
amiable	O
siſters	O
for	O
their	O
kind	O
concern	O
on	O
our	O
accounts	O
,	O
&	O
tell	O
them	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
sincere	O
regard	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
though	O
at	O
present	O
personally	O
unknown	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
)	O
for	O
their	O
very	O
affectionate	O
&	O
tender	O
regard	O
for	O
our	O
dear	O
and	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
Our	O
Affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
dont	O
be	O
jealous	O
)	O
we	O
very	O
very	O
often	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
both	O
&	O
with	O
no	O
small	O
pleasure	O
to	O
reflect	O
how	O
happy	O
you	O
both	O
are	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
's	O
maid	O
Clarke	B-pers
sets	O
up	O
every	O
night	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
we	O
persuade	O
her	O
to	O
change	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
maids	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
likes	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
clever	O
about	O
sick	O
people	O
,	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
&	O
lays	O
for	O
four	O
f	O
or	O
five	O
hours	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
comfort	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
takes	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
nourishment	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
broth	O
,	O
Sago	O
,	O
Caudle	O
,	O
&	O
Chocolate	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
desired	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
send	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
everyday	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
continue	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
puting	O
you	O
to	O
an	O
unneſsesary	O
expence	O
,	O
&	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
either	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
myself	O
will	O
certainly	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
our	O
dear	O
Father	O
goes	O
on	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
desires	O
her	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
Ever	O
oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
we	O
beg	O
our	O
best	O
Compts	O
..	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickensons	I-pers
.	O
Friday	O
28	O
th	O
..	O
My	O
Father	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
no	O
worse	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
news	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
applied	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Reveley	I-pers
last	O
summer	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
she	O
wrote	O
should	O
esteem	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
favor	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
Mr-	B-pers
Bems	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Excise	O
office	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
..	I-pers
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
appointed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
brandy	O
officer	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
William	B-pers
is	O
very	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
.	O
Once	O
more	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
Adieu	O
.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Oct	O
:	O
25	O
th	O
1785	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
