TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
Oct	O
:	O
5	O
.	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Having	O
experienced	O
so	O
many	O
instances	O
of	O
your	O
esteem	O
&	O
regard	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
feel	O
myself	O
highly	O
blameable	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
any	O
longer	O
delayed	O
informing	O
you	O
of	O
an	O
event	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
last	O
followed	O
the	O
example	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
worthy	O
friends	O
,	O
&	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
holy	O
estate	O
of	O
Matrimony	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pleasing	O
sensible	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
child	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
,	O
who	O
like	O
a	O
true	O
Miser	O
more	O
easily	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Daughter	O
than	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
indeed	O
settled	O
his	O
estate	O
upon	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
nothing	O
at	O
her	O
marriage	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
a	O
pleasing	O
companion	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
interest	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
object	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hesitate	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
Devonshire	B-place
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
arrived	O
here	O
only	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
on	O
her	O
birthday	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
Wife	O
wishes	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
relations	O
in	O
Norfolk	B-place
,	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
stay	O
here	O
above	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
longer	O
:	O
we	O
therefore	O
receive	O
no	O
visits	O
at	O
present	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
however	O
deny	O
myself	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
carrying	O
my	B-pers
little	I-pers
woman	I-pers
to	O
your	O
dear	O
&	O
valuable	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
who	O
received	O
us	O
with	O
that	O
goodneſs	O
which	O
so	O
peculiarly	O
distinguishes	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
tolerable	O
health	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
is	O
perfectly	O
recovered	O
.	O
--	O
Matters	O
at	O
the	O
Lodge	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
smoothly	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
&	O
his	O
two	O
elder	O
Sons	O
are	O
all	O
upon	O
good	O
terms	O
.	O
No	O
establishment	O
talked	O
of	O
for	O
the	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
:	O
the	O
third	O
Daughter	O
is	O
perfectly	O
restored	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gold——y	I-pers
is	O
in	O
so	O
indifferent	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
her	O
station	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
D	O
.	O
of	O
Y	O
.	O
has	O
appointed	O
General	B-pers
Budé	I-pers
his	O
Secretary	O
for	O
Foreign	O
affairs	O
:	O
The	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
filled	O
up	O
three	O
Rooms	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
noble	O
style	O
:	O
The	O
Cartoons	O
of	O
Raphael	O
are	O
removed	O
from	O
Buckingham	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
the	O
principal	O
ornament	O
:	O
the	O
Rooms	O
were	O
opened	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
on	O
monday	O
with	O
a	O
Ball	O
in	O
honour	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Princess	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
entertainment	O
was	O
truly	O
Royal	O
:	O
the	O
Supper	O
was	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Georges	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Lodge	O
.	O
As	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
Letters	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
my	O
go	O
d	O
o	O
d	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
would	O
excuse	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
break	O
off	O
abruptly	O
.	O
Have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Comp	O
:	O
t	O
o	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
beleive	O
me	O
Dear	O
madam	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
Your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
&	O
faith	O
ful	O
humble	O
Servant	O
J	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
