TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Turin	B-place
Sepr	O
.	O
1764	O
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
will	O
be	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
perhaps	O
still	O
more	O
when	O
he	O
sees	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
date	O
my	O
letter	O
;	O
the	O
case	O
is	O
plainly	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
who	O
behaved	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
possibly	O
wish	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
France	B-place
to	O
fix	O
my	O
residence	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
absolutely	O
objected	O
against	O
Aix	B-place
or	O
Marseille	B-place
the	O
former	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
dear	O
place	O
&	O
crowded	O
with	O
English	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
being	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
thought	O
Thoulouse	B-place
might	O
answer	O
my	O
purpose	O
till	O
we	O
also	O
started	O
strong	O
objections	O
against	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
in	O
short	O
as	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
that	O
my	O
inclination	O
was	O
for	O
Italy	B-place
,	O
she	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
without	O
further	O
ceremony	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
then	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
certainty	O
of	O
fixing	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
perfectly	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
not	O
liable	O
to	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
moving	O
from	O
one	O
place	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
what	O
people	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Italy	B-place
on	O
account	O
of	O
one	O
's	O
health	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
France	B-place
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
opinion	O
upon	O
this	O
matter	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
sincerity	O
&	O
affection	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
agreed	O
so	O
perfectly	O
with	O
my	O
inclination	O
I	O
loſsd	O
no	O
time	O
o	O
i	O
n	O
proceeding	O
on	O
my	O
journey	O
&	O
am	O
now	O
thus	O
far	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Florence	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
agreeably	O
settled	O
&	O
at	O
no	O
great	O
expence	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Badioli	B-pers
's	O
upper	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Florentin	O
and	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
clever	O
fellow	O
has	O
wrote	O
to	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Florence	B-place
who	O
he	O
aſsures	O
me	O
will	O
fix	O
me	O
there	O
to	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Appartments	O
ready	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
two	O
Servants	O
a	O
Man	O
&	O
a	O
maid	O
;	O
with	O
this	O
small	O
appointment	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
on	O
upon	O
my	O
plan	O
without	O
any	O
danger	O
of	O
exceeding	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
,	O
troubblesone	O
&	O
expensive	O
journey	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
is	O
much	O
fatigued	O
&	O
has	O
caught	O
a	O
violent	O
cold	O
by	O
being	O
exposed	O
to	O
a	O
heavy	O
rain	O
on	O
our	O
paſsage	O
over	O
Mont	B-place
Cenis	I-place
.	O
We	O
expect	O
to	O
arrive	O
at	O
Florence	B-place
in	O
eight	O
days	O
more	O
,	O
we	O
go	O
very	O
slow	O
as	O
we	O
go	O
by	O
Voiture	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
defer	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
fortnight	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
my	O
destination	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
full	O
&	O
explicit	O
account	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
desirous	O
of	O
knowing	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
present	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
Compts	O
.	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
remember	O
us	O
to	O
our	O
poor	O
Child	O
I	O
am	O
&	O
shall	O
ever	O
remain	O
most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
Yours	O
Mary	B-pers
Turin	B-place
September	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1764	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
Gentilhomme	O
Anglois	O
à	O
Florence	B-place
