TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
very	O
fine	O
Grouse	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
in	O
perfect	O
order	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
all	O
the	O
benefit	O
he	O
expected	O
by	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
waters	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
arrived	O
here	O
from	O
Germany	B-place
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
grown	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
hardly	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
near	O
5	O
feet	O
10	O
inches	O
in	O
stature	O
,	O
&	O
perfectly	O
strait	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
idea	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
England	B-place
some	O
time	O
ago	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fabricius	I-pers
which	O
he	O
denied	O
very	O
positively	O
,	O
as	O
Robert	B-pers
does	O
also	O
to	O
my	O
perfect	O
conviction	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
attended	O
to	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
expect	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
complaints	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
bringing	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
this	O
day	O
18	O
complete	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
labouring	O
with	O
great	O
diligence	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
fit	O
for	O
his	O
new	O
station	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
figure	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
thought	O
a	O
capital	O
Recruit	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
disposed	O
I	O
am	O
inclined	O
to	O
hope	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
ashamed	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
received	O
your	O
letter	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
soon	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
herself	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Family	O
in	O
general	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
249	O
August	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
's	O
being	O
in	O
Town	O
is	O
always	O
so	O
uncertain	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
letters	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
intend	O
to	O
favor	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
have	O
enclosed	O
to	O
him	O
