TOKEN	NE
Caulk	B-place
October	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
Return	O
you	O
My	O
best	O
Thanks	O
for	O
your	O
last	O
Kind	O
Letter	O
;	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
Trouble	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
on	O
Acc	O
.	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
serve	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
Make	O
Apology	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
;	O
as	O
being	O
perfectly	O
convinced	O
,	O
It	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
equal	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Instrumental	O
,	O
in	O
promoting	O
their	O
wishes	O
;	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
feel	O
,	O
&	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Importance	O
of	O
the	O
View	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
;	O
in	O
this	O
Desire	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
Really	O
do	O
Believe	O
,	O
no	O
Persons	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
Zealously	O
,	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Devoted	O
--	O
in	O
Heart	O
&	O
Life	O
,	O
than	O
they	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
It	O
May	O
Justly	O
be	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
Is	O
their	O
Meat	O
,	O
&	O
Drink	O
;	O
“	O
to	O
Glorify	O
,	O
&	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
Heavenly	O
Father	O
”	O
--	O
yet	O
;	O
this	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
,	O
rather	O
an	O
Objection	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
Recommendation	O
,	O
to	O
Many	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Moral	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
good	O
Conduct	O
;	O
for	O
Real	O
Religion	O
,	O
extending	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Affections	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
;	O
&	O
a	O
leading	O
Desire	O
of	O
Glorifying	O
God	O
;	O
Is	O
very	O
rarely	O
to	O
be	O
Met	O
with	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
Cause	O
,	O
I	O
Believe	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
Conviction	O
of	O
the	O
Divine	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
;	O
Making	O
Human	O
Conjectures	O
,	O
&	O
Philosopical	O
Reasonings	O
,	O
their	O
Standard	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
Believe	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
comprehend	O
;	O
so	O
define	O
;	O
dispute	O
&	O
cavil	O
at	O
Many	O
Points	O
of	O
Scripture	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
Eſsential	O
Points	O
of	O
Doctrine	O
,	O
&	O
If	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
Immediately	O
or	O
clearly	O
Answered	O
;	O
Make	O
this	O
a	O
Reason	O
;	O
to	O
disbelieve	O
&	O
Reject	O
the	O
Divine	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
;	O
--	O
to	O
Instance	O
;	O
one	O
Objection	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Investigation	O
of	O
Volcanos	O
;	O
Absolutely	O
contradict	O
the	O
Mosaic	O
Acc	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Creation	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
Date	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Observations	O
Made	O
,	O
on	O
their	O
Eruptions	O
&	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Vegetation	O
can	O
take	O
Place	O
;	O
clearly	O
proves	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
Is	O
of	O
Much	O
greater	O
Antiquity	O
--	O
This	O
Single	O
Instance	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
Heard	O
Alledged	O
,	O
in	O
contradiction	O
to	O
the	O
Authority	O
of	O
Scripture	O
;	O
I	O
Really	O
am	O
not	O
learned	O
in	O
these	O
Philosophical	O
Enquiries	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
;	O
that	O
all	O
who	O
study	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
proper	O
Disposition	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
enabled	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
feel	O
,	O
Its	O
Power	O
;	O
&	O
be	O
convinced	O
It	O
was	O
wrote	O
by	O
Divine	O
Inspiration	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
daily	O
see	O
;	O
It	O
Is	O
not	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
or	O
Wisdom	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
give	O
us	O
,	O
saving	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
inform	O
my	O
friends	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
will	O
feel	O
Much	O
Obliged	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
Content	O
,	O
in	O
whatever	O
;	O
situation	O
may	O
be	O
Allotted	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
Hear	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
had	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
Fall	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
suffered	O
so	O
Eſsentially	O
by	O
It	O
;	O
I	O
Hope	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
Both	O
quite	O
well	O
;	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
another	O
Time	O
be	O
More	O
Succeſsfull	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
Heard	O
once	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
since	O
Her	O
Return	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
;	O
She	O
tells	O
Me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Improvement	O
of	O
Her	O
Children	O
;	O
--	O
My	O
Son	O
;	O
goes	O
next	O
Week	O
;	O
to	O
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
;	O
&	O
will	O
stay	O
some	O
Days	O
--	O
He	O
has	O
promised	O
to	O
Attend	O
,	O
My	O
Brother	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
a	O
Dinner	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
He	O
Is	O
chosen	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Warwick	B-place
;	O
no	O
very	O
agreable	O
Office	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
preſsed	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
excused	O
Myself	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
think	O
of	O
paying	O
them	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
Is	O
not	O
yet	O
fixed	O
,	O
&	O
Whether	O
We	O
go	O
from	O
Hence	O
;	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
or	O
London	B-place
;	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
Is	O
tolerably	O
Well	O
;	O
but	O
sometimes	O
has	O
slight	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Gout	O
;	O
but	O
of	O
no	O
Continuance	O
;	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
fixed	O
any	O
Time	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
,	O
or	O
any	O
Plan	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
;	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
All	O
well	O
;	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
again	O
Breeding	O
--	O
the	O
last	O
Letter	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
My	O
Brother	O
,	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
His	O
two	O
Sons	O
of	O
6	O
.	O
&	O
5	O
.	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Cheſs	O
,	O
&	O
seemed	O
quite	O
Eager	O
in	O
their	O
Game	O
;	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
Is	O
well	O
at	O
Winchester	B-place
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
,	O
has	O
great	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Idea	O
of	O
seeing	O
Him	O
,	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
where	O
They	O
are	O
going	O
on	O
Sr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
s	O
Acct	O
.	O
.	O
He	O
Is	O
tolerably	O
well	O
;	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
has	O
frequent	O
&	O
severe	O
Attacks	O
of	O
the	O
Disorder	O
in	O
His	O
Stomach	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
He	O
Is	O
,	O
advised	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
;	O
I	O
mention	O
you	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Car	I-pers
:	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
desires	O
Compts	O
.	O
Thanks	O
,	O
&	O
best	O
Wishes	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Son	O
;	O
are	O
at	O
Westdean	B-place
;	O
the	O
Child	O
Is	O
weakly	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
Moment	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
;	O
She	O
Is	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
Her	O
Sons	O
,	O
Mast	B-pers
.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
Is	O
with	O
Her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
She	O
says	O
He	O
Is	O
grown	O
stouter	O
&	O
goes	O
on	O
vastly	O
Well	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
Hear	O
from	O
Her	O
;	O
as	O
She	O
Mentions	O
,	O
intending	O
soon	O
to	O
Write	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
Is	O
Better	O
;	O
&	O
has	O
lately	O
had	O
Society	O
,	O
in	O
Attending	O
Lady	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
;	O
Who	O
has	O
a	O
Son	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
Her	O
Family	O
Were	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
soon	O
find	O
It	O
Cold	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
;	O
It	O
begins	O
to	O
look	O
Wintery	O
,	O
Here	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Leaves	O
fall	O
&	O
change	O
daily	O
;	O
perhaps	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
affected	O
by	O
severe	O
Cold	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
Which	O
Is	O
the	O
Re	O
aso	O
n	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
thinking	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Removal	O
from	O
;	O
towards	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
not	O
being	O
Calculated	O
for	O
Cold	O
Weather	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
have	O
Many	O
Warm	O
Rooms	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
continue	O
to	O
Drive	O
often	O
;	O
as	O
no	O
Exercise	O
agrees	O
so	O
Well	O
w	O
.	O
Me	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
shall	O
often	O
;	O
be	O
prevented	O
by	O
Weather	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
Ride	O
,	O
Drive	O
,	O
or	O
Walk	O
Most	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
May	O
be	O
too	O
fatiguing	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
My	O
Brs	O
.	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
vastly	O
pleased	O
with	O
their	O
Tour	O
;	O
&	O
are	O
Both	O
Well	O
;	O
--	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
preparing	O
His	O
Cavalry	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Waiting	O
;	O
w	O
.	O
begins	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
--	O
&	O
will	O
continue	O
3	O
Months	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
It	O
Is	O
neceſsary	O
His	O
Horses	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
good	O
Order	O
,	O
&	O
Exercise	O
,	O
in	O
Which	O
He	O
Is	O
very	O
exact	O
,	O
&	O
Attentive	O
--	O
I	O
Beg	O
My	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
Hope	O
you	O
Behave	O
Well	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
not	O
quite	O
spoilt	O
;	O
&	O
am	O
ever	O
Yours	O
Most	O
Affecly-	O
Frances	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Single	O
Sheet	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
