TOKEN	NE
Aft	O
er	O
Breakfast	O
we	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Man——	B-place
home	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
--	O
You	O
L	O
--	O
I	O
say	O
in	O
per	O
me	O
with	O
being	O
3	O
days	O
in	O
writing	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
surely	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
previous	O
journals	O
--	O
my	O
Journey	O
has	O
been	O
employed	O
in	O
shopping	O
&	O
talking	O
to	O
pretty	O
Girls	O
in	O
Satterfields	O
Shop	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
almost	O
all	O
my	O
purchases	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Imperial	O
here	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
promise	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
disappointment	O
attended	O
the	O
purchase	O
I	O
meant	O
for	O
Peg	B-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
looked	O
at	O
500	O
prints	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
please	O
the	O
Lady	O
--	O
I	O
bought	O
Mems	O
.	O
for	O
Jas	B-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
tall	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	O
Cooksey	B-pers
--	O
2	O
Virgins	O
--	O
Creatures	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
particular	O
at	O
the	O
curious	O
marking	O
--	O
3-	O
Decbr	O
1799	O
.	O
--	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
humor	O
with	O
Quakers	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
fraternity	O
having	O
nicked	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
6	O
Guineas	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Carriage	O
horses	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Brearcliffe	I-pers
told	O
a	O
Story	O
yesterday	O
--	O
at	O
a	O
considerable	O
meetg	O
in	O
Manr	B-place
.	I-place
lately	O
,	O
after	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
Health	O
being	O
drank	O
a	O
Quaker	O
was	O
preſsed	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
toast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
declined	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
up	O
his	O
Glaſs	O
said	O
“	O
May	O
George	B-pers
never	O
be	O
sick	O
”	O
&	O
the	O
Sentiment	O
was	O
warmly	O
applauded	O
Now	O
I	O
say	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
that	O
this	O
fineſse	O
&	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
mortal	O
Reservation	O
is	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
cheating	O
the	O
Devil	O
--	O
