TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
July	O
25	O
--	O
1789	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
health	O
&	O
will	O
begin	O
another	O
to	O
follow	O
it	O
soon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
easy	O
--	O
26/	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Major	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Michael	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
when	O
“	O
we	O
praise	O
thee	O
O	O
Lord	O
”	O
was	O
chaunted	O
delightfully	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Sacrament	O
day	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Sermon	O
--	O
I	O
attended	O
my	O
party	O
home	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
glaſs	O
a	O
water	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
abbey	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Sermon	O
--	O
I	O
walked	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
I	O
found	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
,	I-pers
Randolf	I-pers
the	O
famous	O
preacher	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
perceived	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
pensive	O
&	O
low	O
in	O
the	O
extreme	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
priest	O
took	O
himself	O
away	O
I	O
enquired	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
She	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
quite	O
overcome	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
's	O
Sermon	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
it	O
might	O
contribute	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
languid	O
as	O
he	O
preached	O
full	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
observed	O
last	O
Sunday	O
that	O
her	O
Tears	O
flowed	O
plentifully	O
--	O
to	O
do	O
Mr.	B-pers
R——	I-pers
justice	O
--	O
he	O
certainly	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
preacher	O
--	O
the	O
Sermon	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
the	O
prodigal	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
before	O
us	O
in	O
every	O
poſsible	O
point	O
of	O
view	O
&	O
drew	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Conclusion	O
from	O
it	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
called	O
on	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
&	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
my	O
returning	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
's	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Isted	B-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
(	O
eldest	O
brother	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
who	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
s	O
)	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Eyes	O
shot	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
School	O
boy	O
at	O
Westminſter	B-place
--	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jekil	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
--	O
also	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
--	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
Turtle	O
feast	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
about	O
the	O
family	O
at	O
Abindon	B-place
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
thought	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
second	O
Son	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
treated	O
as	O
a	O
fool	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
his	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
discouragement	O
to	O
ye	O
young	O
man	O
--	O
&	O
must	O
check	O
all	O
desire	O
in	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
well	O
--	O
one	O
day	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
made	O
enquiries	O
after	O
ye	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
“	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
days	O
”	O
,	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
&	O
paſsed	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
--	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
received	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
seems	O
to	O
hate	O
him	O
&	O
as	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
his	O
odd	O
behaviour	O
I	O
must	O
mention	O
one	O
circumstance	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
wont	O
permit	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
horses	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
keeps	O
6	O
hunters	O
&	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
besides	O
--	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
is	O
extremely	O
ignorant	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
says	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
Mode	O
of	O
treatment	O
is	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
improve	O
his	O
head	O
or	O
his	O
Heart	O
--	O
his	O
destiny	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
army	O
--	O
How	O
Horrid	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
hated	O
by	O
that	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
our	O
Existence	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
has	O
very	O
little	O
feeling	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
L——	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
talked	O
very	O
seriously	O
to	O
Miss	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
her	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
social	O
Board	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Huntingdon	I-pers
's	O
Chapel	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
Singing	O
,	O
which	O
drew	O
me	O
there	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
the	O
Sermon	O
was	O
ended	O
for	O
a	O
psalm	O
which	O
was	O
delightfully	O
sung	O
--	O
27	O
/	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
setting	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Weymouth	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
neceſsity	O
for	O
my	O
staying	O
here	O
longer	O
than	O
20	O
days	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
for	O
if	O
the	O
Dog	O
days	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
hot	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
after	O
my	O
little	O
Tour	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
better	O
Judge	O
&	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Croſs	O
Bath	O
&	O
taking	O
his	O
Medicine	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
your	O
dear	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
22	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
my	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
empoſsible	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
consistent	O
with	O
your	O
Love	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
an	O
unreasonable	O
request	O
--	O
therefore	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
expreſs	O
ever	O
a	O
Wish	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
entirely	O
lay	O
aside	O
my	O
favorite	O
amusement	O
--	O
your	O
wishes	O
shall	O
be	O
complied	O
with	O
dont	O
think	O
my	O
Love	O
that	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
hastened	O
by	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Shooting	O
--	O
No	O
such	O
thing	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
too	O
ardently	O
not	O
to	O
long	O
exceſsively	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
so	O
unhappy	O
,	O
a	O
to	O
leave	O
home	O
again	O
without	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Wife	O
&	O
Child	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
cast	O
Lotts	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Pray	O
thank	O
my	O
dear	O
father	O
for	O
his	O
tenderneſs	O
for	O
me	O
This	O
is	O
Wednesday	O
29	O
th	O
July	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
spare	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
Spirits	O
--	O
the	O
Irritation	O
is	O
almost	O
totally	O
gone	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
good	O
Appetite	O
eat	O
&	O
sleep	O
well	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
done	O
till	O
lately	O
--	O
no	O
person	O
can	O
be	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
this	O
Scrap	O
with	O
my	O
whole	O
heart	O
except	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
for	O
Louisa	O
,	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
portion	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
no	O
Anxieties	O
about	O
me	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
My	O
best	O
Friend	O
Ever	O
Yrs	O
.	O
JD	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
x	O
post	O
Derbyshire	B-place
