TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
December	O
twenty	O
three	O
1810	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Welbeck	O
Street	O
.	O
Cambridge	B-place
.	O
London	B-place
.	O
