TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
December	O
28	O
th	O
:	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
,	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
friend	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
are	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
young	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
--	O
We	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
frequently	O
,	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
Governor	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Our	O
House	O
is	O
cover	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
now	O
expect	O
frequent	O
falls	O
of	O
Snow	O
--	O
We	O
like	O
this	O
Situation	O
better	O
and	O
better	O
,	O
every	O
Day	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
,	O
a	O
delightful	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
you	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
in	O
your	O
last	O
Letter	O
but	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
remarkably	O
cheerful	O
,	O
and	O
agreeable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
--	O
she	O
too	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Frank	O
for	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
to-morrow	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Music-Party	O
,	O
tomorrow	O
Evening	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
--	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
benefit	O
from	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
conclude	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
drinking	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
think	O
Bath	B-place
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Place	O
?	O
I	O
remember	O
thinking	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
much	O
improved	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
sweet	O
friend	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
,	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
just	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
anxiety	O
of	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
with	O
her	O
youngest	O
Child	O
--	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
inoculate	O
him	O
thus	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
perfectly	O
right	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sooner	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
is	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
perform	O
,	O
only	O
twice	O
this	O
Season	O
,	O
as	O
yet	O
--	O
In	O
Belvidera	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Venice	O
preserv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Hermione	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
of	O
The	O
Distreſs	O
'd	O
Mother	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
unneceſsary	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
as	O
enchanting	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
so	O
grown	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
were	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
hardly	O
know	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
and	O
he	O
improves	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
.	O
We	O
see	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
oftener	O
,	O
than	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
considerably	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
are	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
to	O
bring	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Christmas	O
Holydays	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Idea	O
of	O
coming	O
here	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
a	O
great	O
event	O
to	O
Children	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Evening	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
speaking	O
Italian	O
--	O
I	O
speak	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
facility	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
practice	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
taking	O
Leſsons	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
lately	O
,	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
many	O
Enquiries	O
after	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
--	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
one	O
Evening	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Party	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
.	O
Tho	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
trite	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
Season	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Compliments	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
,	O
very	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
happy	O
,	O
returns	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
kindly	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
happy	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
Pe	O
eminent	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
busineſs	O
,	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
particularly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
favourite	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
yours	O
sincerely	O
--	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
We	O
all	O
beg	O
kind	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
1786	O
