TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
which	O
indicates	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
your	O
heart	O
in	O
the	O
oblivion	O
of	O
past	O
misunderstandings	O
which	O
I	O
equally	O
regret	O
their	O
ever	O
having	O
taken	O
place	O
;	O
too	O
ardent	O
a	O
disposition	O
frequently	O
leads	O
us	O
beyond	O
the	O
bounds	O
of	O
discretion	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
subject	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
longer	O
dwelt	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
so	O
unfavorable	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
on	O
that	O
score	O
;	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
loſs	O
I	O
have	O
sustain	O
'd	O
still	O
bear	O
very	O
heavy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
years	O
render	O
me	O
almost	O
unfit	O
for	O
society	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
encreasing	O
deafneſs	O
adds	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
uncomfortableneſs	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
&	O
makes	O
me	O
totally	O
averse	O
to	O
trouble	O
my	O
friends	O
with	O
my	O
visits	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
great	O
solitude	O
having	O
even	O
given	O
up	O
card	O
parties	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
my	O
chief	O
amusement	O
is	O
in	O
trivial	O
reading	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
on	O
but	O
heavily	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
failing	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
other	O
faculties	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
has	O
left	O
me	O
near	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
recoverd	O
from	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
illneſs	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
skill	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
who	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
had	O
very	O
serious	O
apprehensions	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
disorder	O
was	O
brought	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
constant	O
&	O
severe	O
agitation	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
cruel	O
treatment	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
whose	O
plan	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
a	O
total	O
dereliction	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
without	O
any	O
provision	O
but	O
in	O
entire	O
dependence	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
cruel	O
situation	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
her	O
conduct	O
towards	O
him	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
most	O
affectionate	O
&	O
proper	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
neglected	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
that	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
she	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
effectual	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
made	O
very	O
ample	O
provision	O
for	O
her	O
after	O
my	O
decease	O
by	O
a	O
considerable	O
Annuity	O
in	O
Trust	O
out	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
survives	O
me	O
be	O
in	O
good	O
circumstances	O
if	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
suffer	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
cajoled	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Annuity	O
or	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
produce	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
subject	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
my	O
exhortations	O
in	O
very	O
solemn	O
terms	O
.	O
This	O
Annuity	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Sum	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
totally	O
deprived	O
of	O
ready	O
money	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
with	O
an	O
advanced	O
Income	O
.	O
My	O
Trustees	O
in	O
this	O
business	O
are	O
Chas	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
the	O
former	O
having	O
conducted	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
idea	O
of	O
my	O
unfortunate	O
daughter	O
being	O
totally	O
deserted	O
after	O
my	O
decease	O
,	O
&	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
benevolence	O
of	O
her	O
relations	O
for	O
her	O
support	O
,	O
presented	O
itself	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
horror	O
attending	O
such	O
cruel	O
circumstances	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
God	O
inspired	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
rescuing	O
my	O
Child	O
really	O
a	O
deserving	O
object	O
,	O
from	O
such	O
dreadful	O
misery	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
hardly	O
recover	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
an	O
improper	O
impatience	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
London	B-place
,	O
not	O
very	O
flattering	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
dislike	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
have	O
advised	O
to	O
endeavor	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
a	O
residence	O
suitable	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
to	O
consult	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
nothing	O
shall	O
warp	O
my	O
affection	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
her	O
addreſs	O
without	O
comment	O
is	O
n	O
o	O
.	O
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
Street	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
regards	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
to	O
my	O
worthy	O
God	O
daughter	O
,	O
whose	O
behavior	O
to	O
her	O
Parents	O
must	O
command	O
universal	O
approbation	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
of	O
your	O
invitation	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
depreſs	O
'd	O
spirits	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
unpleasant	O
visitor	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
November	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1807	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
single	O
Bedfordſhire	B-place
a	O
prebendary	O
of	O
Lincoln	B-place
to	O
whom	O
this	O
House	O
we	O
occupy	O
&	O
the	O
prebendal	O
property	O
in	O
this	O
parish	O
lately	O
following	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
foresight	O
in	O
the	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
in	O
whose	O
family	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
held	O
by	O
Lease	O
on	O
Lifes	O
for	O
160	O
years	O
--	O
&	O
our	O
residence	O
here	O
depends	O
on	O
an	O
agreement	O
between	O
the	O
parties	O
which	O
till	O
of	O
late	O
has	O
not	O
appeared	O
at	O
all	O
probable	O
Mr.	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Nov	O
1810	O
