TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
omiſsion	O
in	O
not	O
having	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
before	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
that	O
I	O
had	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
draw	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
your	O
Interest	O
Money	O
as	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
;	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
it	O
escaped	O
my	O
memory	O
however	O
that	O
matter	O
is	O
now	O
completely	O
rectified	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
I	O
think	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
me	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
perfect	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
my	O
omiſsion	O
to	O
myself	O
only	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
also	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
near	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
all	O
like	O
Stanton	B-place
extremely	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
Country	O
is	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
the	O
roads	O
excellent	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
received	O
great	O
civilities	O
from	O
very	O
agreeable	O
&	O
respectable	O
neighbours	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
stay	O
only	O
a	O
Week	O
&	O
then	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
plan	O
is	O
to	O
paſs	O
five	O
months	O
every	O
summer	O
at	O
Stanton	B-place
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
please	O
God	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
judged	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
paying	O
a	O
most	O
enormous	O
price	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
inhabiting	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Street	O
for	O
seven	O
months	O
only	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
determined	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
do	O
it	O
quietly	O
&	O
upon	O
satisfactory	O
terms	O
;	O
&	O
this	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
effected	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
having	O
sold	O
it	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
furniture	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Campbell	I-pers
of	O
Pembrokeshire	B-place
,	O
who	O
married	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
Daughter	O
last	O
winter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
Nine	O
Thousand	O
Three	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
£3000	O
go	O
to	O
pay	O
off	O
a	O
mortgage	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Balance	O
£6300	O
remains	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
Mr.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
's	O
Bond	O
bearing	O
Interest	O
5	O
pr.Ct	O
.	O
&	O
also	O
a	O
mortgage	O
upon	O
the	O
Premises	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
received	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
hand	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
money	O
comes	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
must	O
when	O
I	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
Six	O
months	O
notice	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
you	O
accommodated	O
me	O
with	O
so	O
very	O
handsomely	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
has	O
also	O
purchased	O
the	O
contiguous	O
House	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
's	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
laying	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
finished	O
will	O
make	O
as	O
noble	O
&	O
complete	O
a	O
Residence	O
as	O
most	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
surprised	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
complain	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
constant	O
rains	O
&	O
bad	O
weather	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Harvest	O
&	O
as	O
fine	O
a	O
season	O
afterwards	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
remember	O
'd	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
unsettled	O
climate	O
of	O
Derbyshire	B-place
is	O
a	O
great	O
drawback	O
upon	O
that	O
County	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
returns	O
of	O
your	O
bilious	O
complaint	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
yet	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
wish	O
that	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
come	O
there	O
from	O
neceſsity	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
have	O
secured	O
a	O
Convenient	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Saville	O
Row	O
contiguous	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Rooms	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
,	O
who	O
informs	O
me	O
his	O
Regt	O
.	O
is	O
to	O
quit	O
their	O
Quarters	O
at	O
Croydon	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
do	O
Foot	O
duty	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
unusual	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
expects	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
will	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
idea	O
,	O
unleſs	O
we	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
engaged	O
in	O
a	O
Continental	O
War	O
,	O
which	O
God	O
forbid	O
.	O
Such	O
an	O
event	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
unfortunate	O
for	O
Robert	B-pers
who	O
has	O
no	O
Constitution	O
or	O
bodily	O
strength	O
to	O
undergo	O
great	O
hardships	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
boast	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
discretion	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
disliked	O
the	O
Dragoon	O
Profeſsion	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
choice	O
,	O
he	O
seems	O
now	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
it	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
reflection	O
wishes	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
not	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
judgement	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
my	O
Friends	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
imputed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
plan	O
of	O
œconomy	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
I	O
confeſs	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
fit	O
for	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ignorant	O
,	O
speaking	O
French	O
tolerably	O
&	O
German	O
a	O
little	O
being	O
his	O
whole	O
acquired	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
us	O
all	O
most	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
happy	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
both	O
so	O
much	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
your	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
my	O
God	O
Daughter	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
here	O
not	O
very	O
conveniently	O
situated	O
for	O
getting	O
Franks	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Stanton	B-place
--	O
Bury	B-place
St.	I-place
Edmund	I-place
's	I-place
October	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
