TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
Notwithstanding	O
the	O
great	O
dislike	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
nothing	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
;	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
my	O
inquiries	O
after	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
health	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
time	O
how	O
you	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
;	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
She	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
how	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
since	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
return	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
the	O
happiest	O
of	O
all	O
beings	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
enjoying	O
such	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
with	O
good	O
spirits	O
,	O
&	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
in	O
short	O
he	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
--	O
ever	O
since	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
improveing	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
barren	O
ground	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
mine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
East	O
fence	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
spot	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
centre	O
is	O
a	O
swell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
trees	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
adornd	O
with	O
shrubs	O
&	O
flowers	O
;	O
this	O
kind	O
thought	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
makes	O
my	O
heart	O
flow	O
with	O
gratitude	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
for	O
ever	O
reverence	O
that	O
spot	O
of	O
ground	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
succeſsion	O
of	O
company	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Clarkes	O
,	O
have	O
left	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
we	O
expect	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
depriv	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
C	O
company	O
this	O
Summer	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
is	O
needleſs	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
happineſs	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Child	O
under	O
my	O
Roof	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
Occasion	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
account	O
,	O
gave	O
us	O
some	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
Sir	B-pers
Willliam	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
is	O
he	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
persuaided	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
or	O
Buxton	B-place
;	O
the	O
great	O
benifit	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
,	O
may	O
have	O
some	O
influence	O
over	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
;	O
with	O
our	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
both	O
.	O
--	O
from	O
Your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
desires	O
his	O
love	O
,	O
Sept	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
