TOKEN	NE
Weymouth	B-place
November	O
13	O
th	O
1790	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
It	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
your	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
Carne	B-place
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Li	I-pers
:	I-pers
Damer	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
were	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
long	O
letter	O
you	O
mention	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
often	O
wondered	O
why	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
to	O
have	O
inquired	O
the	O
Cause	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
inquired	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
led	O
so	O
unsettled	O
&	O
wanderi	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
life	O
ever	O
since	O
June	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Sister	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
absent	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
most	O
miserable	O
corresponde	O
nt	O
&	O
obliged	O
to	O
throw	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sincerely	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
happineſs	O
&	O
comfort	O
which	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
pretty	O
well	O
established	O
ever	O
since	O
you	O
married	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
health	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
circumstance	O
wanting	O
to	O
compleat	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
must	O
indeed	O
be	O
a	O
continual	O
source	O
of	O
pleasure	O
and	O
delight	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
your	O
House	O
is	O
become	O
&	O
becoming	O
a	O
comfortable	O
one	O
--	O
you	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
this	O
winter	O
or	O
spring	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Now	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
tho	O
'	O
not	O
constantly	O
there	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
west	O
where	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
visiting	O
about	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
even	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Devonshire	B-place
till	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
better	O
or	O
looked	O
better	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
--	O
certainly	O
never	O
was	O
happier	O
,	O
certainly	O
never	O
so	O
happy	O
--	O
&	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
heart	O
&	O
looking	O
up	O
to	O
Heaven	O
acknowledge	O
with	O
gratitude	O
and	O
delight	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
wish	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
continuance	O
of	O
the	O
bleſsings	O
I	O
enjoy	O
--	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
&	O
place	O
always	O
agrees	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
grown	O
quite	O
fat	O
&	O
rosy	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
here	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
who	O
were	O
come	O
for	O
her	O
's	O
&	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
bathing	O
&	O
meant	O
to	O
stay	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
taken	O
ill	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
arrived	O
&	O
confined	O
3	O
weeks	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
thought	O
that	O
bathing	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
still	O
here	O
&	O
shall	O
remain	O
near	O
a	O
week	O
longer	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
bathed	O
11	O
times	O
&	O
it	O
agrees	O
with	O
me	O
exceſsivly	O
--	O
my	O
F	O
.	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
left	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
visits	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
's	O
Ld	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Ilchester	I-pers
s	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
where	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
next	O
week	O
&	O
where	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
waters	O
&	O
bathe	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
Gout	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
indifferent	O
lately	O
with	O
flying	O
gouty	O
&	O
rheumatic	O
pains	O
which	O
we	O
hope	O
Bath	B-place
will	O
remove	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
Carne	B-place
but	O
expect	O
him	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
leaves	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesda	O
y	O
&	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
visits	O
in	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
till	O
Xmas	O
--	O
we	O
go	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
Kingston	B-place
(	O
Mrs	B-pers
I.	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
s	O
)	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
shall	O
meet	O
the	O
M.	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
&	O
Cholmondely	B-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
then	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Buckley	I-pers
s	O
then	O
to	O
Sherbourne	B-place
&	O
Redlynch	B-place
(	O
Ld	B-pers
Ilchester	I-pers
)	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	O
till	O
the	O
beginni	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
&	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
wish	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
duty	O
should	O
induce	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
hate	O
London	B-place
as	O
a	O
place	O
&	O
am	O
so	O
well	O
&	O
so	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
prefers	O
it	O
so	O
infinitly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
our	O
being	O
settled	O
there	O
entirely	O
with	O
infinite	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
receive	O
your	O
souvenir	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
send	O
you	O
my	O
first	O
attempt	O
in	O
the	O
painting	O
way	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hardly	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
your	O
acceptance	O
,	O
it	O
certainly	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
remembr	O
ance	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
very	O
little	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
but	O
continu	O
e	O
to	O
like	O
it	O
&	O
am	O
improved	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
absent	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
or	O
would	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
send	O
his	O
love	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
your	O
affec	O
:	O
&	O
sincere	O
C.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
