TOKEN	NE
Wing	B-place
Sunday	O
Feby	O
2	O
d	O
What	O
can	O
I	O
write	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
to	O
Expreſs	O
my	O
Thanks	O
for	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
adoration	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
Elegant	O
Piece	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
invited	O
my	O
Applause	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
purchas	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
Hardmans	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
render	O
'd	O
doubly	O
valuable	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
being	O
your	O
own	O
work	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
additional	O
mark	O
of	O
yr	O
Affection	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
Endeavour	O
to	O
deserve	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
Existence	O
--	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
yr	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
B——ks	I-pers
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
fear	O
that	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
a	O
thoughtleſs	O
Girl	O
--	O
I	O
trust	O
in	O
God	O
at	O
all	O
Events	O
the	O
Money	O
you	O
sent	O
was	O
not	O
considerable	O
--	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
part	O
I	O
Hesitate	O
now	O
so	O
deeply	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
afraid	O
to	O
mention	O
(	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
Confidential	O
friend	O
)	O
What	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
Thinking	O
of	O
the	O
Clique	O
to	O
Whom	O
these	O
poor	O
Girls	O
are	O
now	O
devoted	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
hint	O
what	O
I	O
gueſs	O
of	O
the	O
Supporter	O
or	O
Patron	O
of	O
this	O
Worthy	O
race	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
construed	O
into	O
Envy	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
right	O
in	O
my	O
Conjecture	O
Lou	B-pers
will	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
degradation	O
of	O
that	O
Power	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
seen	O
Acquir	O
'd	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
indeed	O
so	O
Astonishing	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
unaccountable	O
.	O
that	O
future	O
Generations	O
will	O
be	O
amaz	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
ever	O
could	O
happen	O
in	O
so	O
Enlighten	O
'd	O
a	O
Nation	O
.	O
&	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
Wealth	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
many	O
Talents	O
dispers	O
'd	O
amongst	O
them	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
B——s	I-pers
&	O
I	O
really	O
pray	O
heartily	O
that	O
in	O
this	O
one	O
instance	O
Justice	O
may	O
be	O
done	O
&	O
also	O
for	O
poor	O
Madrit	B-pers
--	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
&	O
humane	O
to	O
these	O
poor	O
helpleſs	O
abus	O
'd	O
people	O
I	O
hope	O
God	O
will	O
reward	O
you	O
--	O
we	O
rejoice	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
Dicky	B-pers
is	O
safe	O
&	O
so	O
well	O
recover	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Chance	O
of	O
breaking	O
his	O
Neck	O
in	O
a	O
part	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
the	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
B——d	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
to	O
Woburn	B-place
with	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Hounds	O
&	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
--	O
for	O
Tidings	O
--	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
announces	O
that	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
has	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
Preliminary	O
Article	O
.	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
Mediates	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
Peace	O
the	O
Statholder	O
shall	O
be	O
restor	O
'd	O
&	O
the	B-place
Netherlands	I-place
given	O
up	O
to	O
their	O
old	O
Master	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
that	O
the	O
Chouans	O
have	O
made	O
Peace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
their	O
Force	O
encreases	O
daily	O
&	O
that	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
high	O
reputation	O
who	O
has	O
served	O
in	O
Ruſsia	B-place
is	O
now	O
in	O
London	B-place
on	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
command	O
the	O
Royalists	O
--	O
also	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
Langton	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gloustershire	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
to	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
&	O
a	O
report	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
Tho	I-pers
's	I-pers
Moystyn	I-pers
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Hamiltons	O
so	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
may	O
make	O
out	O
a	O
connexion	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
in	O
Old	O
France	B-place
--	O
she	O
adds	O
that	O
every	O
body	O
says	O
that	O
Peace	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
that	O
the	O
Great	O
Question	O
will	O
be	O
again	O
defer	O
'd	O
to	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
supposd	O
every	O
thing	O
will	O
be	O
carried	O
with	O
a	O
high	O
Hand	O
However	O
,	O
in	O
despight	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Courtly	O
Authority	O
--	O
WE	O
think	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
Hint	O
--	O
&	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Hint	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
few	O
caveats	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
also	O
adds	O
her	O
kindest	O
remembrances	O
--	O
&	O
quite	O
delighted	O
with	O
her	O
letter	O
from	O
Lou	B-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
received	O
on	O
Thursday	O
last	O
.	O
so	O
with	O
our	O
Kind	O
love	O
--	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
I	O
bid	O
you	O
Heartily	O
farewell	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
Pray	O
God	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
entirely	O
in	O
his	O
good	O
keeping	O
.	O
from	O
yr	O
Loving	O
Friend	O
DBloſset	B-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
poorly	O
--	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
her	O
death	O
was	O
very	O
Shocking	O
.	O
unwell	O
in	O
the	O
Morg	O
.	O
saw	O
a	O
Medical	O
Person	O
who	O
thought	O
she	O
Ail	O
'd	O
not	O
much	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
chair	O
&	O
Expir	O
'd	O
--	O
yr	O
Note	O
is	O
consum	O
'd	O
to	O
Ashes	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
heard	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
but	O
as	O
Memories	O
