TOKEN	NE
June	O
27	O
th	O
1802	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
hear	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
so	O
indifferent	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D.	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
's	O
health	O
but	O
I	O
sincerely	O
with	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
kind	O
attention	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
her	O
good	O
nursing	O
he	O
will	O
soon	O
recover	O
I	O
am	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
she	O
continues	O
well	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
affte	O
love	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
but	O
as	O
her	O
Grandpapa	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
ill	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
her	O
time	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
writing	O
letters	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
troubled	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
It	O
is	O
to	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Anna	B-pers
&	O
entreat	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
abominable	O
affairs	O
make	O
her	O
so	O
uneasy	O
as	O
she	O
really	O
is	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
she	O
is	O
more	O
Altered	O
than	O
you	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
conceive	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
fearful	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
take	O
very	O
great	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
she	O
will	O
fall	O
into	O
a	O
dreadful	O
state	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
hoped	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
seaside	O
where	O
they	O
now	O
are	O
/	O
would	O
have	O
quite	O
restored	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
now	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
papers	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
busineſs	O
with	O
her	O
over	O
which	O
she	O
will	O
I	O
know	O
be	O
inceſsantly	O
pouring	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
so	O
has	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Barnard	O
but	O
all	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
conquer	O
the	O
nervous	O
state	O
she	O
has	O
fallen	O
into	O
Mrs	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
the	O
person	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
boards	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Aunt	O
makes	O
her	O
quite	O
melancholy	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Ramsgate	B-place
she	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
but	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
counting	O
over	O
the	O
boxes	O
papers	O
&	O
c	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
packed	O
up	O
)	O
&	O
which	O
she	O
meant	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
will	O
not	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
all	O
these	O
trifling	O
circumstances	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
that	O
an	O
indifferent	O
person	O
would	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
senses	O
If	O
either	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
would	O
be	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
you	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
doing	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
favor	O
as	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
a	O
strong	O
affection	O
for	O
my	O
Aunt	O
&	O
am	O
very	O
uneasy	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
she	O
now	O
is	O
in	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
aware	O
that	O
her	O
mind	O
must	O
be	O
much	O
distreſsed	O
by	O
the	O
affairs	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
she	O
wou	O
ld	O
make	O
a	O
resolution	O
not	O
to	O
fatigue	O
herself	O
in	O
ma	O
kin	O
g	O
unneceſsary	O
calculations	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
trust	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
probably	O
be	O
sooner	O
settled	O
&	O
her	O
health	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
so	O
much	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
make	O
her	O
suppose	O
she	O
is	O
worse	O
than	O
she	O
really	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
will	O
attend	O
to	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
enclose	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
B	O
le	O
the	O
Bishop	O
's	O
I	O
will	O
forward	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Frank	O
to	O
Ramsgate	B-place
which	O
will	O
save	O
the	O
postage	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
My	O
Sister	O
&	O
her	O
little	O
Girl	O
she	O
still	O
continues	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
is	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Nurse	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
both	O
her	O
&	O
the	O
dear	O
Baby	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
afraid	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
that	O
happineſs	O
till	O
next	O
year	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Bp	O
spend	O
the	O
remaind	O
er	O
of	O
this	O
summer	O
at	O
Brighton	B-place
&	O
Hastings	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St	B-place
Asaph	I-place
till	O
next	O
summer	O
they	O
have	O
very	O
kindly	O
said	O
they	O
hoped	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
I	O
hope	O
spend	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
summer	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
only	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
which	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
as	O
London	B-place
is	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
do	O
right	O
in	O
directing	O
this	O
to	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
returned	O
to	O
Leighton	O
House	O
I	O
conclude	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
understand	O
Dr	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
is	O
still	O
at	O
hastings	B-place
where	O
I	O
daresay	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
them	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Grote	I-pers
is	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
&	O
Believe	O
me	O
ever	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
sincerely	O
obligd	O
&	O
very	O
affty	O
yours	O
M	B-pers
J	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
beg	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
and	O
send	O
her	O
letter	O
enclosed	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	O
London	B-place
June	O
Twenty	O
Eighth	O
1802	O
Miss	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchester	B-place
Free	O
Rochester	B-pers
