TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
ye	O
2	O
st	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
intention	O
my	O
Dr	O
to	O
have	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
without	O
bidding	O
you	O
Adieu	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Pen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
flight	O
four	O
&	O
twenty	O
hours	O
sooner	O
then	O
was	O
intended	O
&	O
that	O
at	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
warning	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
from	O
your	O
Room	O
,	O
surrounded	O
by	O
your	O
Plants	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
greatest	O
Health	O
,	O
may	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
an	O
Emblem	O
of	O
in	O
their	O
every	O
respect	O
in	O
of	O
their	O
Quondam	O
Mistreſs	O
--	O
Sunday	O
Thus	O
far	O
did	O
I	O
get	O
yesterday	O
Sunday	O
&	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Cathedr	O
al	O
I	O
found	O
yr	O
kind	O
Letter	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dr	O
I	O
enter	O
thoroughly	O
i	O
n	O
to	O
yr	O
feelings	O
,	O
at	O
parting	O
with	O
such	O
Old	O
acquaintance	O
s	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
the	O
Tear	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
start	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
more	O
upon	O
this	O
Tender	O
Subject	O
is	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
Heroism	O
sufficient	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
properly	O
valued	O
--	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Foot	O
is	O
better	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
walks	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Children	O
thank	O
God	O
are	O
remarkably	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
except	O
P	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
who	O
is	O
dreſsing	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
we	O
expect	O
Lady	B-pers
A	I-pers
W	I-pers
at	O
present	O
we	O
are	O
en	O
Famille	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
chearful	O
&	O
goodhumoured	O
--	O
God	O
Bless	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
I	O
am	O
called	O
away	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
Life	O
sufficiently	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
excuse	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Sincly	O
Yr	O
Affce	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
we	O
left	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
ill	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
—	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Albemarle	O
Street	O
