TOKEN	NE
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Horace	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
s	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
wth-	O
ye	O
.	O
New	O
Edition	O
of	O
his	O
anecdotes	O
on	O
of	O
Painting	O
--	O
Berkely	O
Square	O
London	B-place
Novbr	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
having	O
been	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
edition	O
of	O
ye	O
Anecdotes	O
on	O
Painting	O
coud	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
History	O
of	O
English	O
Arts	O
resist	O
ye	O
agreeable	O
occasion	O
of	O
doing	O
justice	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
has	O
founded	O
a	O
new	O
branch	O
.	O
He	O
takes	O
hopes	O
therefore	O
yt-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
will	O
forgive	O
him	O
the	O
liberty	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
of	O
recording	O
Her	O
name	O
in	O
Vol	O
.	O
2	O
P.	O
242	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
will	O
Please	O
to	O
consider	O
how	O
cruel	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
Him	O
to	O
be	O
denied	O
ye	O
.	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
mentioning	O
Her	O
only	O
because	O
He	O
has	O
ye	O
.	O
Honor	O
&	O
happineſs	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
