TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
morng	O
.	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
Can	O
not	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
bring	O
me	O
her	O
little	O
Louise	B-pers
to	O
Day	O
?	O
Any	O
time	O
from	O
2	O
to	O
4	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
6	O
,	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
not	O
so	O
resent	O
my	O
failure	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
appointment	O
as	O
to	O
refuse	O
escorting	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
has	O
had	O
the	O
malice	O
--	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
in	O
his	O
nature	O
--	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
Breakfast	O
was	O
very	O
charming	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
probably	O
meet	O
my	O
father	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
--	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
yours	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
F.B	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burney	B-pers
June	O
1788	O
