TOKEN	NE
The	O
Hill	O
Top	O
.	O
March	O
30	O
th	O
:	O
1805	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Your	O
kind	O
letter	O
of	O
January	O
31	O
st	O
:	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
remained	O
so	O
long	O
unanswer	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
the	O
point	O
was	O
decided	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
an	O
Irish	O
excursion	O
this	O
season	O
at	O
least	O
--	O
it	O
then	O
became	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
prepare	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
this	O
place	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
furnished	O
and	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
comfortably	O
settled	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
against	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
return	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
prevented	O
my	O
availing	O
myself	O
of	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
House	I-place
--	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
ce	O
qui	O
est	O
différé	O
n'est	O
pas	O
perdu	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
busy	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
keeping	O
much	O
land	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
hands	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
ruinous	O
considering	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
frequent	O
absence	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
his	O
total	O
ignorance	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
farming	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tenant	O
to	O
seek	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
18	O
acres	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
reserved	O
enough	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
every	O
thing	O
within	O
ourselves	O
,	O
except	O
Wheat	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
friendly	O
neighbour	O
,	O
have	O
succeeded	O
in	O
letting	O
the	O
remainder	O
--	O
and	O
to	O
great	O
advantage	O
.	O
Now	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
involved	O
by	O
imposition	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
expences	O
are	O
got	O
over	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
cheap	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
pleasant	O
,	O
residence	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
large	O
for	O
our	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
situation	O
beautiful	O
.	O
--	O
As	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
you	O
speak	O
my	O
sentiments	O
so	O
precisely	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
need	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
full	O
opinion	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
eligibility	O
of	O
a	O
residence	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
see	O
any	O
probability	O
of	O
a	O
neceſsity	O
for	O
a	O
permanent	O
stay	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Should	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
chance	O
to	O
re-engage	O
for	O
another	O
season	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
because	O
having	O
head-quarters	O
to	O
leave	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
and	O
luggage	O
in	O
,	O
makes	O
an	O
excursion	O
more	O
practicable	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
reckoner	O
of	O
days	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
absence	O
,	O
that	O
nine	O
months	O
is	O
too	O
long	O
a	O
period	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
without	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
poſsible	O
to	O
avoid	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
him	O
till	O
August	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
concerned	O
at	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
for	O
an	O
age	O
;	O
but	O
remember	O
her	O
with	O
great	O
esteem	O
.	O
A	O
visit	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
should	O
hope	O
,	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
most	O
favourable	O
effects	O
on	O
her	O
spirits	O
.	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
regards	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
So	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
this	O
Spring	O
,	O
to	O
gratify	O
any	O
curiosity	O
on	O
his	O
subject	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
few	O
friends	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
conveniently	O
,	O
accomplish	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
frisk	O
there	O
and	O
has	O
seen	O
the	B-pers
young	I-pers
Roscius	I-pers
;	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Opera	O
,	O
--	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
partaken	O
of	O
what	O
amusements	O
are	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
thinking	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Cheltenham	B-place
.	O
How	O
is	O
the	B-pers
young	I-pers
Roscius	I-pers
?	O
and	O
,	O
how	O
goes	O
on	O
her	O
singing	O
?	O
As	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
totally	O
out	O
of	O
practice	O
;	O
but	O
intend	O
having	O
my	O
Forte-Piano	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
soon	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
leisure	O
enough	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
musical	O
one	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
near	O
neighbour	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Peploe	I-pers
's	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
mutually	O
useful	O
,	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
music	O
from	O
neglect	O
.	O
Remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
Cornewall	I-pers
;	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
when	O
an	O
opportunity	O
offers	O
of	O
renewing	O
my	O
Leſsons	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Present	O
my	O
best	O
regards	O
,	O
likewise	O
,	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
suits	O
your	O
convenience	O
.	O
Direct	O
--	O
The	O
Hill	O
Top	O
--	O
near	O
Weobley	B-place
--	O
Herefordshire	B-place
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
well	O
,	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
and	O
clever	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
sincerely	O
attached	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
.	O
Great	O
news	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
information	O
is	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
friendship	O
of	O
estimable	O
people	O
,	O
always	O
a	O
pleasing	O
reflection	O
to	O
dwell	O
upon	O
--	O
in	O
that	O
light	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
my	O
mention	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
whenever	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
--	O
and	O
beleive	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
very	O
truly	O
yours	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
.	I-place
