TOKEN	NE
My	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
I	O
write	O
from	O
your	O
dear	O
Mamma	O
's	O
Fire-side	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
something	O
better	O
to-day	O
&	O
slept	O
last	O
night	O
tolerably	O
--	O
the	O
D	O
r	O
:	O
was	O
here	O
last	O
night	O
&	O
gives	O
her	O
great	O
encouragement	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
begun	O
a	O
new	O
medicine	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
great	O
hopes	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
agree	O
with	O
her	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
sends	O
her	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
bids	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
her	O
legs	O
are	O
better	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
perhaps	O
surprise	O
you	O
by	O
writing	O
from	O
James	O
Street	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Sisters	O
well	O
at	O
Maple-durham	B-place
,	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
in	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
naughty	O
Miranda	B-pers
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
never	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
least	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
Letter	O
from	O
M	B-place
D	I-place
--	O
but	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
not	O
very	O
generous	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
bids	O
me	O
give	O
her	O
Love	O
&	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
glad	O
her	O
Dove	O
is	O
returned	O
,	O
although	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
alone	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
continually	O
with	O
your	O
Mamma	O
,	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
how	O
happy	O
should	O
I	O
be	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
says	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
Draft	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
must	O
take	O
more	O
money	O
shortly	O
,	O
she	O
desires	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Leathenstone	I-pers
--	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
your	O
Uncle	O
f	B-pers
to	O
desire	O
that	O
the	O
Land	O
may	O
be	O
let	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
thinks	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
Leonidas	B-pers
desires	O
his	O
Love	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
forgets	O
his	O
toast	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
pleasure	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
thinking	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
of	O
drinking	O
your	O
Health	O
.	O
Adieu	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Line	O
--	O
be	O
aſsured	O
of	O
my	O
constant	O
attention	O
to	O
your	O
Mother	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
Affection	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
Yours	O
,	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
James	O
Street	O
Wednesday	O
n	O
afternoon	O
