TOKEN	NE
11	O
th	O
:	O
Decbr	O
:	O
1790	O
Buxton	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mary	B-pers
Tho	O
I	O
am	O
full	O
of	O
pain	O
to	O
day	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
complaint	O
will	O
prove	O
Rheumatism	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
bad	O
enough	O
,	O
--	O
it	O
varies	O
about	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
my	O
body	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will-not	O
fix	O
any	O
where	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
confeſs	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
uneasy	O
from	O
a	O
supposition	O
that	O
it	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
repeated	O
hurts	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
--	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Case	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
I	O
gave	O
yr-	O
Letter	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
--	O
from	O
his	O
Mucles	O
I	O
augured	O
no	O
pleasant	O
communication	O
--	O
after	O
reading	O
yr-	O
letter	O
he	O
said	O
--	O
“	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
Connection	O
”	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
against	O
Cr	B-pers
which	O
makes	O
me	O
hope	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
comply	O
with	O
their	O
Wishes	O
--	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
warm	O
Advocate	O
in	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
flattered	O
by	O
the	O
Connection	O
and	O
approve	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
of	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
too	O
precipitate	O
in	O
expecting	O
an	O
immediate	O
Ansr	O
.	O
from	O
a	O
Parent	O
on	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
consequence	O
to	O
the	O
happiness	O
of	O
his	O
Child	O
--	O
After	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
“	O
saw	O
it	O
yesterday	O
”	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Newspaper	O
read	O
it	O
twice	O
over	O
&	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
&	O
stick	O
&	O
walked	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
consent	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
Time	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
saw	O
perfectly	O
yesterday	O
how	O
matters	O
were	O
going	O
on	O
&	O
slept	O
well	O
after	O
it	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sign	O
--	O
he	O
mentioned	O
it	O
at	O
dinner	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
before	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
&	O
You	O
should	O
know	O
each	O
other	O
perfectly	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
probable	O
that	O
my	O
Father	O
will	O
return	O
soon	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
away	O
--	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
come	O
here	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
agreeable	O
News	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
dispatch	O
it	O
immediately	O
--	O
Grandpapa	B-pers
almost	O
cried	O
at	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
distreſs	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
quite	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
prevented	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
from	O
sleeping	O
--	O
Addio	O
--	O
My	O
ever	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
If	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
marries	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
may	O
they	O
be	O
as	O
tenderly	O
attached	O
&	O
love	O
each	O
other	O
as	O
entirely	O
as	O
we	O
do	O
--	O
Then	O
a	O
great	O
addition	O
of	O
happineſs	O
will	O
accrue	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
most	O
Affe	O
.	O
Husband	O
JD	B-pers
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
Peggy	B-pers
s	O
staying	O
constantly	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
shall	O
give	O
a	O
months	O
notice	O
&	O
quit	O
her	O
place	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
that	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
New	B-place
mill	I-place
from	O
a	O
Love	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
