TOKEN	NE
Tuesday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Breakfasted	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
--	O
paid	O
AMaria	B-pers
a	O
short	O
Visit	O
--	O
her	O
Cold	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
visit	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
I	O
found	O
her	O
more	O
recover	O
'd	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
by	O
her	O
bed	O
side	O
she	O
seem	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
seeing	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
so	O
comfortable	O
settled	O
,	O
&	O
well	O
situated	O
for	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Shop	O
--	O
saw	O
her	O
husband	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
very	O
alert	O
--	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
home	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
poor	O
Johnston	B-pers
what	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
Lavender	O
Water	O
&	O
White	O
Wine	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
from	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
Bond	O
Street	O
to	O
buy	O
Lavender	O
Water	O
&	O
recollecting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Painter	O
lived	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
settld	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Miniature	O
picture	O
for	O
a	O
Ring	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
begin	O
it	O
next	O
Monday	O
Morng	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
persuasion	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
wch	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
carriage	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
inconvenient	O
as	O
he	O
lives	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
off	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
time	O
in	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
&	O
a	O
Chair	O
hire	O
is	O
expensive	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
pass	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
--	O
he	O
bow	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
answer	O
'd	O
Mr	B-pers
D——son	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
I	O
enclosed	O
my	O
Diary	O
--	O
Message	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartey	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
&	O
sleep	O
at	O
their	O
Villa	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accept	O
ye	O
.	O
agreeable	O
invitation	O
being	O
engaged	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
AMaria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
I	O
decorated	O
two	O
small	O
fine	O
screens	O
for	O
her	O
with	O
prints	O
&	O
Verses	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
made	O
us	O
a	O
little	O
Visit	O
as	O
did	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
I	O
continued	O
my	O
employment	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
&	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
politics	O
ye	O
.	O
reigning	O
topic	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Col	O
.	O
C	O
--	O
look	O
over	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
3	O
Papers	O
to	O
find	O
wch-	O
had	O
given	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
speech	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
yesterday	O
most	O
accurately	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
)	O
.	O
Woodfall	B-pers
s	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
mis-	O
stated	O
--	O
mis-represented	O
,	O
&	O
mis-placed	O
ye	O
.	O
order	O
of	O
words	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
added	O
&	O
omitted	O
things	O
.	O
heard	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
rode	O
on	O
Horseback	O
from	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
Yester	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
he	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
4	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
attended	O
only	O
by	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lake	I-pers
&	O
2	O
grooms	O
he	O
had	O
relays	O
of	O
horses	O
--	O
--	O
after	O
he	O
arrived	O
in	O
London	B-place
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
8	O
miles	O
--	O
&	O
rodd	O
rode	O
back	O
to	O
B——	B-place
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
B——	B-place
is	O
above	O
60	O
miles	O
from	O
London	B-place
.	O
--	O
some	O
people	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
meet	O
Charles	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
s	O
,	O
--	O
some	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
purchase	O
a	O
fan	O
for	O
a	O
Lady	O
--	O
&	O
others	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
invite	O
ye	O
.	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chartres	I-pers
to	O
B——	B-place
Lord	B-pers
St	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Col	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
for	O
sometime	O
wth	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
wht	O
.	O
alterations	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
by	O
Gobert	B-pers
at	O
Chats	O
woth	O
worth	O
.	O
how	O
rapidly	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
(	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Dke	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshires	I-pers
Agent	O
remonstrated	O
)	O
.	O
to	O
spoil	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
--	O
laid	O
out	O
1500	O
in	O
new	O
furnishing	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
&	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
putting	O
new	O
Chairs	O
&	O
Sophas	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
alteration	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Chimney	O
piece	O
this	O
Gobert	B-pers
was	O
a	O
Cook	O
--	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
people	O
to	O
decorated	O
their	O
houses	O
instead	O
of	O
their	O
tables	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
ye	O
.	O
principal	O
person	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
fitting	O
up	O
Carelton	O
House	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
till	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
extracts	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Wednesday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
.	O
84	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
:	O
AMaria	B-pers
--	O
Isabella	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
chatting	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
had	O
an	O
indifferent	O
night	O
.	O
from	O
12	O
till	O
3	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
arra	O
n	O
ging	O
some	O
curious	O
old	O
China	O
in	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
--	O
this	O
dear	O
Woman	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
trust	O
any	O
hands	O
but	O
mine	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
wiped	O
it	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jerningham	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
found	O
us	O
at	O
our	O
work	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
by	O
us	O
½	O
an	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
he	O
brought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
prints	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
Air	O
Baloon	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
off	O
next	O
.	O
tuesday	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
6	O
come	O
out	O
&	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Serv	O
t	O
.	O
for	O
one	O
immediately	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sanford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
4	O
small	O
specimens	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Egg	O
Shell	O
China	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
value	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
sake	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Donor	O
--	O
I	O
enclosed	O
ye	O
.	O
print	O
in	O
a	O
frank	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
AMaria	B-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
walking	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
broiling	O
Sun	O
&	O
having	O
fatigued	O
myself	O
in	O
standing	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
Mrs-	B-pers
.	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
occasion	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
Lord	B-pers
Stor	I-pers
:	I-pers
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
Cathcart	B-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Charles	B-pers
promised	O
his	O
Sister	O
to	O
sit	O
for	O
his	O
Picture	O
to	O
Romney	B-pers
--	O
we	O
consulted	O
together	O
after	O
dinner	O
wch	O
.	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
manner	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Young	O
Man	O
&	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
charming	O
interesting	O
Picture	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
dear	O
Boys	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
&	O
Politics	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
said	O
that	O
Wl	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
had	O
acted	O
in	O
an	O
unfair	O
manner	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Navy	O
Bills	O
&	O
India	O
affairs	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
C.C	B-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
left	O
Col	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
to	O
keep	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
company	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
Coach	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
sat	O
with	O
the	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
heard	O
to	O
day	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
George	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vise	I-pers
died	O
at	O
Stoke	B-place
in	O
Childbed	O
--	O
I	O
sincerely	O
pity	O
her	O
poor	O
father	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
only	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
11	O
she	O
has	O
left	O
2	O
Children	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
11	O
o'clock	O
that	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
being	O
Mr.	B-pers
Coupland	I-pers
came	O
again	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
he	O
sent	O
another	O
letter	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
wicked	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
wrong	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
an	O
improper	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
money	O
one	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
accept	O
of	O
no	O
other	O
relief	O
.	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
old	O
Chairman	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
dying	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Thursday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
again	O
.	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
--	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
&	O
sit	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
whilst	O
she	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
where	O
she	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
go	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
for	O
6	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
who	O
paſs	O
'd	O
by	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Arm	I-pers
stead	I-pers
s	O
--	O
fortunately	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
this	O
is	O
another	O
flying	O
excursion	O
from	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
--	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
spending	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
with	O
my	O
most	O
engaging	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
Friend	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
solicitous	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
really	O
felt	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
prospect	O
of	O
M	O
r	O
being	O
united	O
to	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
--	O
&	O
was	O
satisfied	O
with	O
my	O
aſsurances	O
in	O
the	O
affirmative	O
--	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
allow	O
her	O
in	O
(	O
some	O
time	O
hence	O
)	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
Lady	O
Louisa	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
engagement	O
--	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
all	O
those	O
friends	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
should	O
know	O
that	O
what	O
I	O
intended	O
doing	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
warmest	O
approbation	O
of	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
already	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
&	O
who	O
were	O
interested	O
in	O
my	O
happineſs	O
.	O
How	O
shall	O
I	O
ever	O
repay	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
kind	O
friends	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
with	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
the	O
most	O
fortunate	O
of	O
human	O
beings	O
--	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
give	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
dear	O
Friends	O
are	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
excellent	O
characters	O
&	O
best	O
principles	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
their	O
example	O
encouraged	O
to	O
persevere	O
in	O
Virtue	O
&	O
guard	O
myself	O
from	O
folly	O
&	O
vice	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
poſseſs	O
the	O
heart	O
of	O
an	O
amiable	O
Man	O
whom	O
I	O
love	O
,	O
&	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
preferred	O
to	O
every	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
not	O
only	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
truly	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
grateful	O
to	O
Providence	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
duty	O
these	O
beautiful	O
lines	O
of	O
Addison	B-pers
better	O
express	O
my	O
gratitude	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
--	O
Thy	O
bounteous	O
hand	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
worldly	O
bliss	O
Has	O
made	O
my	O
Cup	O
run	O
o'er	O
And	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
&	O
faithful	O
friend	O
Had	O
doubled	O
all	O
my	O
store	O
Ten	O
thousand	O
thousand	O
precious	O
gifts	O
My	O
daily	O
thanks	O
employ	O
;	O
Nor	O
is	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
a	O
cheerful	O
heart	O
,	O
That	O
tastes	O
those	O
gifts	O
wth	O
.	O
joy	O
.	O
Through	O
every	O
period	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
Thy	O
goodneſs	O
I	O
'll	O
pursue	O
And	O
after	O
death	O
in	O
distant	O
Worlds	O
The	O
glorious	O
theme	O
renew	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Addison	O
,	O
Spectator	O
no	O
.	O
453	O
,	O
9	O
August	O
1712	O
.	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
this	O
beautiful	O
ode	O
is	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
in	O
No	O
.	O
453	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Spectator	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
dear	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
spend	O
one	O
day	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
good	O
friends	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
charming	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
high	O
spirits	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Daughter	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
had	O
received	O
proposals	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
--	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
&	O
herself	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
approved	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
suitable	O
match	O
in	O
every	O
Respect	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
his	O
father	O
is	O
also	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
choice	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
--	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Houghman	I-pers
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
brought	O
home	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Picture	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
pleasing	O
likeneſs	O
but	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
find	O
fault	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
sat	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
me	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
picture	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
walk	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
I	O
sent	O
&	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
finish	O
'd	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
to	O
days	O
post	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
kindly	O
regrets	O
my	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
Visit	O
them	O
this	O
Summer	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
only	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
S	O
.	O
&	O
me	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Dr	O
:	O
Room	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
general	O
topics	O
--	O
heard	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Bertie	I-pers
was	O
to	O
marry	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lenox	I-pers
(	O
ye	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
s	O
Nephew	O
&	O
heir	O
)	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Strathaven	I-pers
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Aboyne	I-pers
s	O
Son	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
North	I-pers
(	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
Son	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
is	O
to	O
marry	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Hobarts	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
Twins	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
thought	O
likely	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
sixpence	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
ruined	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
likely	O
his	O
Grandfather	O
Lord	B-pers
Guilford	I-pers
will	O
part	O
with	O
any	O
Money	O
.	O
whilst	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Euston	I-pers
has	O
made	O
proposals	O
&	O
is	O
accepted	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Waldgrave	I-pers
--	O
but	O
his	O
father	O
ye	O
..	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Grafton	I-pers
will	O
not	O
give	O
consent	O
wch	O
:	O
is	O
thought	O
very	O
cruel	O
&	O
unreasonable	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
œconomy	O
in	O
every	O
situation	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
in	O
so	O
brilliant	O
a	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
--	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
&	O
very	O
great	O
expectations	O
as	O
all	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfeild	I-pers
s	O
fortune	O
will	O
be	O
his	O
--	O
speak	O
so	O
sensibly	O
on	O
a	O
subject	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
hardly	O
imagined	O
she	O
had	O
thought	O
on	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
household	O
establishment	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
one	O
--	O
4	O
men	O
out	O
of	O
livery	O
4	O
footmen	O
--	O
Under	O
Butler	O
--	O
Porter	O
.	O
2	O
Coachmen	O
under	O
Coachman	O
--	O
2	O
Postilion	O
,	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Grooms	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
is	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Manager	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
kept	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
number	O
of	O
Servts	O
.	O
both	O
as	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Office	O
--	O
no	O
other	O
Minister	O
can	O
say	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
Shilling	O
debt	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
much	O
better	O
than	O
last	O
Night	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
fatigued	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
join	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
kind	O
Neighbours	O
--	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
lost	O
Ireland	O
!	O
--	O
they	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
have	O
again	O
put	O
off	O
their	O
Journey	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Friday	O
7	O
6	O
th	O
:	O
August	O
1784	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
8.	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
getting	O
well	O
very	O
fast	O
--	O
received	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
my	O
cousin	O
Stormont	B-pers
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
day	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Spirits	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
arranged	O
a	O
Glaſs	O
Cabinet	O
of	O
foſsils	O
Spars	O
&	O
Minerals	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
specimens	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
from	O
Cornwall	B-place
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
before	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
fine	O
ones	O
from	O
Derbyshire	B-place
&	O
Lancashire	B-place
.	O
the	O
dear	O
old	O
Woman	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
herself	O
&	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
of	O
congratulations	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
--	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
present	O
mine	O
wch	O
.	O
would	O
save	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
&	O
fine	O
speeches	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
a	O
Present	O
from	O
good	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
of	O
some	O
valuable	O
small	O
tea	O
cups	O
&	O
Saucers	O
of	O
Egg	O
shell	O
China	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
bought	O
in	O
Holland	O
many	O
years	O
ago	O
&	O
knowing	O
I	O
was	O
beginning	O
a	O
collection	O
.	O
she	O
kindly	O
sent	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
immediately	O
to	O
thank	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
acceptance	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Silver	O
lamp	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
accept	O
it	O
--	O
She	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
fine	O
Old	O
Chinas	O
&	O
her	O
darling	O
Pidgeons	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
.	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
hanging	O
up	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Picture	O
&	O
other	O
jobs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
kind	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
sat	O
&	O
chatted	O
till	O
6	O
--	O
separated	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
met	O
in	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
were	O
together	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
safely	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Daughter	O
yet	O
she	O
bore	O
her	O
disappoint	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
quite	O
comforted	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
fine	O
boy	O
.	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
her	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Son	O
--	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Girl	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
4	O
boys	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
us	O
but	O
we	O
excused	O
ourselves	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
soon	O
after	O
11	O
--	O
Saturday	O
7	O
th	O
:	O
August	O
1784	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
7	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
at	O
8	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
below	O
--	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
employ	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
working	O
till	O
12.	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
Jackson	B-pers
s	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
day	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
were	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
myself	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
As	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
--	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
KenWood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Miſs	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
writing	O
to	O
Relation	O
's	O
to	O
acquaint	O
them	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
's	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
but	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
send	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
writ	O
ing	O
ten	O
himself	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
babe	O
were	O
charming	O
well	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
goes	O
back	O
to	O
Ken-Wood	O
but	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
every	O
Morng	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
is	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
only	O
Child	O
by	O
his	O
first	O
wife	O
who	O
died	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
Young	O
She	O
is	O
near	O
a	O
Year	O
older	O
than	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
law	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
26.	O
or	O
7	O
--	O
She	O
lives	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
was	O
educated	O
by	O
the	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
two	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Sisters	O
who	O
also	O
reside	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
She	O
is	O
pleasing	O
.	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
--	O
well	O
accomplished	O
,	O
&	O
conducts	O
herself	O
wth	O
.	O
that	O
propriety	O
wch	O
.	O
ought	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
fashion	O
&	O
good	O
education	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
then	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
saved	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
Visit	O
.	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
A	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Niece	O
Miſs	B-pers
Capper	I-pers
were	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
they	O
soon	O
went	O
away	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
so	O
prepoſseſsing	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
countenance	O
,	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
dreſs	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
desired	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
who	O
this	O
lady	O
was	O
.	O
&	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
following	O
account	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
--	O
was	O
suitably	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
good	O
fortune	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
match	O
of	O
inclination	O
&	O
they	O
were	O
mutually	O
happy	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
short	O
years	O
only	O
she	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
her	O
amiable	O
Husband	O
--	O
let	O
ye	O
.	O
feeling	O
heart	O
judge	O
what	O
she	O
felt	O
when	O
one	O
Morning	O
(	O
without	O
any	O
previous	O
illneſs	O
)	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
dead	O
by	O
her	O
side	O
.	O
for	O
12	O
Years	O
she	O
shut	O
herself	O
up	O
from	O
all	O
society	O
,	O
only	O
admitting	O
ye	O
.	O
Visits	O
of	O
her	O
nearest	O
Relations	O
--	O
the	O
last	O
12	O
Years	O
she	O
has	O
receivd	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
old	O
friends	O
&	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
pays	O
them	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
but	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
retired	O
manner	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	B-place
--	O
her	O
principal	O
amusement	O
is	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Garden	O
&	O
the	O
study	O
of	O
Botany	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
handsome	O
independency	O
&	O
lives	O
in	O
stile	O
suitable	O
to	O
an	O
elegant	O
mind	O
--	O
without	O
parade	O
--	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
her	O
is	O
neat	O
as	O
her	O
dreſs	O
,	O
&	O
proper	O
as	O
her	O
manner	O
.	O
Never	O
having	O
been	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
with	O
Children	O
--	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Brothers	O
Daughter	O
to	O
live	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
Young	O
Lady	O
I	O
saw	O
--	O
who	O
appears	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
credit	O
to	O
her	O
Aunt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Capper	I-pers
seems	O
to	O
be	O
abt	O
.	O
16.	O
not	O
handsome	O
,	O
but	O
looks	O
Modest	O
&	O
civil	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
Granville	I-pers
a	O
Cousin	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
succeeded	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
She	O
is	O
ye	O
only	O
one	O
left	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
--	O
A	O
Maiden	O
.	O
of	O
70	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honor	O
to	O
Queen	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
Niece	O
to	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Minister	O
Lord	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
congratulate	O
her	O
Nephew	O
Lord	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
approaching	O
marriage	O
of	O
his	O
daughter	O
Sophia	B-pers
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
two	O
Ladies	O
agreeably	O
occupied	O
in	O
bestowing	O
praises	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
s	O
children	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
after	O
promising	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
hospitable	O
Neighbours	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
Epictetus	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
so	O
long	O
at	O
Desert	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Work	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
told	O
us	O
some	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
People	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
&	O
of	O
places	O
there	O
.	O
few	O
people	O
relate	O
more	O
agreeably	O
than	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
her	O
imagination	O
is	O
so	O
luxuriant	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
embellishes	O
--	O
not	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
telling	O
falsehoods	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
sweetneſs	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Nature	O
always	O
makes	O
her	O
see	O
things	O
&	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
favourable	O
point	O
of	O
view	O
.	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
sometimes	O
an	O
unlucky	O
shade	O
in	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Picture	O
she	O
is	O
blind	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
of	O
course	O
her	O
descriptions	O
are	O
pleasing	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
to	O
like	O
to	O
contemplate	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
beautiful	O
objects	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
ye	O
.	O
art	O
of	O
describ	O
ing	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
You	O
see	O
all	O
the	O
objects	O
of	O
her	O
sometimes	O
poetic	O
Fancy	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
given	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
fine	O
Place	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
following	O
lines	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
them	O
aloud	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
tear	O
of	O
sensibility	O
steal	O
down	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
cheek	O
..	O
In	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
beautiful	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Lucan	O
near	O
Dublin	B-place
he	O
had	O
placed	O
an	O
Obelisk	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
walking	O
with	O
him	O
one	O
day	O
&	O
looking	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
expreſsed	O
a	O
Wish	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
burried	O
Under	O
it	O
&	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
died	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
grave	O
.	O
he	O
immediately	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
pencil	O
&	O
wrote	O
thise	O
lines	O
&	O
giving	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
said	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
comply	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
request	O
&	O
that	O
should	O
be	O
their	O
Epitaph	O
Near	O
this	O
fair	O
sculpture	O
sleeps	O
a	O
pair	O
In	O
Church	O
yard	O
his'try	O
wondrous	O
rare	O
,	O
Who	O
liked	O
the	O
busy	O
hum	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Then	O
joy	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
fields	O
again	O
,	O
Who	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Grove	O
,	O
or	O
led	O
ye	O
.	O
Rill	O
,	O
To	O
shine	O
and	O
bable	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
Hill	O
,	O
Who	O
Nature	O
felt	O
,	O
&	O
void	O
of	O
art	O
Gave	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
,	O
&	O
good	O
,	O
their	O
heart	O
,	O
Who	O
lov	O
'd	O
when	O
young	O
,	O
yet	O
died	O
old	O
friends	O
A	O
bleſsing	O
fate	O
but	O
seldom	O
sends	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
are	O
Cousins	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
from	O
their	O
cradles	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
early	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
united	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
--	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
was	O
forced	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Altar	O
at	O
15	O
by	O
the	O
arbitary	O
will	O
of	O
an	O
arbitary	O
Father	O
who	O
obliged	O
her	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
old	O
Man	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
beautiful	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
70	O
th	O
-	O
Year	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
captivated	O
to	O
reject	O
a	O
forced	O
consent	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
excuse	O
ye	O
.	O
father	O
had	O
for	O
sacrificing	O
his	O
daughter	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
his	O
friend	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
honor	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Child	O
in	O
marriage	O
--	O
this	O
Man	O
lived	O
some	O
Years	O
during	O
wch	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
behaved	O
irreproachably	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
a	O
Year	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
constancy	O
was	O
rewarded	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
give	O
some	O
orders	O
--	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
accompanied	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—	I-pers
down	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
afternoon	O
walk	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Eldest	O
Son	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
agreeable	O
genteel	O
Young	O
Man	O
--	O
a	O
Young	O
Lady	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
were	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Work	O
table	O
&	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
&	O
weddings	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
--	I-pers
Bingham	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
s	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Daughter	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lindsay	I-pers
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
a	O
great	O
Match	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
soon	O
after	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
forced	O
her	O
awar	O
as	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
fatigued	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
Company	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
we	O
took	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
up	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Coffee	O
house	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
he	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
instead	O
of	O
writing	O
letters	O
letters	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
I	O
endulged	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
my	O
extracts	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Sunday	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Breakfasted	O
alone	O
--	O
read	O
,	O
wrote	O
,	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
paid	O
a	O
little	O
Visit	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
went	O
to	O
May	O
fair	O
Chapel	O
,	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Handcock	B-pers
were	O
going	O
&	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
Coach	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sheelds	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Curate	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
excellent	O
Sermon	O
after	O
Church	O
I	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
--	O
met	O
a	O
poor	O
Young	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
hardly	O
clothes	O
to	O
cover	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
--	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
real	O
compaſsion	O
&	O
her	O
Story	O
was	O
an	O
artleſs	O
one	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Handcock	B-pers
drove	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
&	O
overtook	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
I	O
yielded	O
to	O
their	O
intreaties	O
willingly	O
to	O
accompany	O
them	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Niece	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
her	O
since	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Berkeley	O
Square	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
was	O
expected	O
as	O
Mrs.V——	B-pers
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
invite	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
our	O
mortification	O
the	O
Servt	O
.	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
we	O
then	O
drove	O
to	O
Leicester	O
Square	O
.	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
alone	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
much	O
recove	O
re	O
d	O
in	O
health	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
she	O
burst	O
into	O
tears	O
when	O
we	O
saluted	O
her	O
we	O
sat	O
wth	O
her	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
better	O
spirits	O
--	O
she	O
goes	O
into	O
Devonshire	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
but	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morn.g	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
.	O
Handcock	B-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
treated	O
ourselves	O
with	O
one	O
turn	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Picture	O
Gallery	O
&	O
Room	O
adjoining	O
from	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
only	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
to	O
Prayers	O
&	O
she	O
expected	O
ye	O
.	O
Clergyman	O
every	O
moment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
--	O
to	O
invite	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
this	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
was	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
was	O
to	O
have	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
expect	O
me	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
left	O
word	O
there	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
desired	O
ym	O
.	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Note	O
&	O
had	O
two	O
hours	O
quietly	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
unprofitable	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
4	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
who	O
had	O
insited	O
insisted	O
on	O
our	O
dining	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
at	O
Desert	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
argument	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
education	O
of	O
Women	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
were	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
Miſs	O
Clarke	O
as	O
usual	O
was	O
dumb	O
&	O
what	O
was	O
more	O
mortifying	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
even	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
our	O
debate	O
.	O
after	O
amusing	O
ourselves	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
friendly	O
opponents	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
Room	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
Coffee	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
the	O
happy	O
art	O
of	O
making	O
her	O
guests	O
feel	O
under	O
no	O
constraint	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
endulge	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
luxury	O
of	O
being	O
quiet	O
&	O
alone	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
one	O
of	O
Blair	B-pers
s	O
Sermons	O
&	O
wrote	O
out	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Child	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
.	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Tea	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
agreeable	O
lively	O
conversation	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
.	O
--	O
Superstition	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
marriages	O
--	O
&	O
how	O
people	O
love	O
to	O
interfere	O
judge	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
conduct	O
of	O
others	O
--	O
however	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
scandal	O
or	O
illnatured	O
remarks	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
ended	O
with	O
Madneſs	O
&	O
Bedlam	O
had	O
I	O
time	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
amusing	O
to	O
write	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
Dialogues	O
of	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
s	O
conversation	O
.	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
so	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
consented	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
therefore	O
staid	O
supper	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Spoke	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
well	O
deserved	O
.	O
As	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
made	O
me	O
consent	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
acquaint	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
my	O
engagement	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
upon	O
promise	O
they	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
in	O
general	O
Society	O
.	O
his	O
health	O
when	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
is	O
always	O
drank	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
V——	I-pers
generally	O
torments	O
me	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
idea	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
into	O
her	O
head	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
that	O
my	O
friends	O
will	O
lose	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
aſsuring	O
me	O
it	O
requires	O
all	O
her	O
charity	O
not	O
to	O
hate	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
after	O
chatting	O
on	O
indifferent	O
subjects	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
beg	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
.	O
Monday	O
9	O
th	O
..	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past7	O
--	O
B	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Ye	O
.	O
Painter	O
came	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
sat	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
giving	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
countenance	O
of	O
a	O
fool	O
for	O
I	O
felt	O
amazingly	O
silly	O
,	O
I	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
picture	O
ye	O
.	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
Ring	O
..	O
Saunders	B-pers
was	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
torment	O
him	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
paint	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
best	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
two	O
oClock	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
--	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
.	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Wed	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Planchée	I-pers
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Health	O
of	O
my	O
Clock	O
&	O
Watches	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
to	O
repair	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
made	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
of	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Manner	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
entirely	O
persuaded	O
of	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
opinion	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
well	O
founded	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
or	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
£	O
1000	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
without	O
deduction	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Estate	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
inherited	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
--	O
he	O
certainly	O
wd	O
.	O
raise	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
5	O
p	O
:	O
r	O
.	O
Cent	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
secured	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
chuse	O
to	O
let	O
remain	O
.	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
£	O
600	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
bond	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
on	O
giving	O
½	O
a	O
Years	O
Notice	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
in	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
1785	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
when	O
I	O
chose	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
&	O
give	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
inter	O
-	O
est	O
....	O
At	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
house	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
his	O
Villa	O
.	O
he	O
question	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
future	O
plans	O
,	O
I	O
aſsured	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
regulated	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
were	O
agreeable	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
whatever	O
he	O
proposed	O
,	O
wd	O
.	O
please	O
&	O
satisfy	O
all	O
those	O
kind	O
friends	O
Who	O
were	O
interested	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Dear	O
,	O
charming	O
,	O
amiable	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
flew	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
sweet	O
little	O
Julia	B-pers
to	O
receive	O
us	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
just	O
what	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
is	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
certain	O
yt	O
.	O
My	O
D——	B-pers
never	O
wd	O
.	O
repent	O
his	O
choice	O
.	O
what	O
a	O
pattern	O
is	O
this	O
Woman	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Sex	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
adored	O
justly	O
adored	O
by	O
all	O
who	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
now	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
describing	O
this	O
best	O
of	O
Women	O
.	O
Whilst	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
before	O
dinner	O
Julia	B-pers
took	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
favourites	O
her	O
chickens	O
--	O
her	O
Deer	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
s	O
tutor	O
,	O
an	O
agreeable	O
lively	O
Young	O
Man	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
sentiments	O
on	O
a	O
particular	O
subject	O
wch	O
.	O
show	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
&	O
understanding	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
met	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
me	O
--	O
when	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
left	O
us	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
gave	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
's	O
health	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
gave	O
his	O
dear	O
father	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
friendship	O
of	O
these	O
excellent	O
Persons	O
affect	O
me	O
always	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
wch	O
.	O
makes	O
ye	O
.	O
tear	O
ready	O
to	O
start	O
--	O
it	O
goes	O
in	O
a	O
peculiar	O
manner	O
to	O
my	O
heart	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
somehow	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
worthy	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
kinder	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
I	O
deserved	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
Desert	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
till	O
Coffee	O
,	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
by	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Swing	O
&	O
we	O
made	O
good	O
fat	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
take	O
her	O
share	O
in	O
this	O
exercise	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
lived	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
as	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
as	O
her	O
own	O
Maid	O
before	O
she	O
married	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
26	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
treated	O
wth	O
:	O
that	O
consideration	O
her	O
affection	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
D-	I-pers
merits	O
what	O
happy	O
beings	O
are	O
Lord	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Servants	O
!	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
quiet	O
chat	O
--	O
during	O
wch	O
.	O
time	O
we	O
were	O
amused	O
wth	O
.	O
two	O
tolerable	O
French	O
Horns	O
,	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
two	O
Men	O
often	O
come	O
&	O
play	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Windows	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
wch	O
.	O
being	O
close	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
effect	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
Antrobus	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
tea	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
floating	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
height	O
that	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
black	O
speck	O
--	O
&	O
was	O
soon	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
treated	O
me	O
with	O
one	O
sweet	O
song	O
--	O
“	O
To	O
fair	O
Fidelia	O
”	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
sat	O
up	O
rather	O
lat	O
t	O
er	O
than	O
Usual	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
two	O
small	O
Suns	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
Wheel	O
Play	O
'd	O
off	O
This	O
little	O
fire	O
work	O
she	O
had	O
imagined	O
to	O
please	O
&	O
surprise	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
Pope	O
Joan	O
for	O
pence	O
to	O
amuse	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dawson	I-pers
--	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
½	O
.	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
cheerful	O
innocent	O
conversation	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
received	O
an	O
invitation	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
this	O
Afternoon	O
to	O
spend	O
next	O
thursday	O
at	O
Windsor	O
being	O
ye	O
.	O
P	B-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Birth-day	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Mal	O
a	O
propos	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
however	O
she	O
sent	O
word	O
that	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
obey	O
her	O
Majesties	O
command	O
&	O
by	O
saying	O
she	O
put	O
of	O
her	O
Journey	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
day	O
evaded	O
ye	O
.	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
prolong	O
ye	O
.	O
Visit	O
as	O
she	O
generally	O
stays	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
when	O
invited	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
M	O
:	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
W	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Q	O
sent	O
word	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
a	O
private	O
party	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
only	O
a	O
Night	O
Gown	O
this	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
Birth=day	O
wch-	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
Kept	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
Compts	O
.	O
at	O
W	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
favourite	O
of	O
hers	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
liberty	O
she	O
never	O
will	O
suffer	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Maid	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
chattering	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
begging	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
wth	O
her	O
Lord	O
&	O
Lady	O
&	O
reproaching	O
me	O
with	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
made	O
them	O
more	O
frequent	O
Visits	O
this	O
Summer	O
Tuesady	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
close	O
my	O
Eyes	O
after	O
4	O
oClock	O
I	O
found	O
Thomson	B-pers
s	O
Seasons	O
--	O
with	O
his	O
beautiful	O
images	O
--	O
with	O
contemplation	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
frm	O
my	O
Windows	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
wandering	O
Thoughts	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
my	O
time	O
till	O
8	O
oClock	O
when	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
would	O
also	O
insist	O
upon	O
being	O
my	O
fêmé	O
de	O
Chambre	O
.	O
I	O
accompanied	O
her	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
continued	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
(	O
M	O
r	O
Dr	O
.	O
&	O
his	O
Tutor	O
alway	O
's	O
only	O
accidentally	O
make	O
their	O
appearance	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
)	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
wet	O
&	O
cold	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
:	O
dear	O
little	O
Julia	B-pers
made	O
her	O
appearance	O
before	O
we	O
rose	O
from	O
Breakfast	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
D——	I-pers
in	O
a	O
judicious	O
pleasant	O
way	O
taught	O
her	O
her	O
french	O
Verbs	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
came	O
to	O
give	O
advice	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
Tunbridge	B-place
Waters	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
settle	O
this	O
important	O
affair	O
&	O
amused	O
myself	O
with	O
looking	O
over	O
Cowley	B-pers
s	O
Geometrical	O
Plates	O
--	O
the	O
different	O
Problems	O
of	O
Euclid	B-pers
are	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Pasteboard	O
Paper	O
&	O
cut	O
so	O
that	O
You	O
may	O
lift	O
them	O
up	O
&	O
see	O
the	O
Solid	O
forms	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
suppose	O
a	O
profound	O
scholar	O
might	O
despise	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
pretty	O
Work	O
for	O
Ladys	O
or	O
young	O
beginners	O
.	O
When	O
Dr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
went	O
away	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	B-place
--	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
read	O
Prayers	O
to	O
her	O
Servts-	O
&	O
Children	O
--	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
above	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
she	O
always	O
does	O
it	O
unleſs	O
something	O
particular	O
prevents	O
her	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
good	O
reading	O
leſson	O
to	O
Julia	B-pers
--	O
who	O
reads	O
ye	O
.	O
Chapter	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
y	O
e	O
one	O
for	O
y	O
e	O
day	O
in	O
y	O
e	O
new	O
Testament	O
Psalms	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
only	O
reads	O
ye	O
.	O
Chapter	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
New	O
testament	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
in	O
Doddridge	B-pers
with	O
his	O
improvement	O
.	O
I	O
aſsisted	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
in	O
sorting	O
letters	O
till	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
several	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
s	O
Lord	B-pers
Shelburne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
they	O
all	O
did	O
credit	O
to	O
ye	O
..	O
writers	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
ones	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
--	O
so	O
much	O
fine	O
imagination	O
--	O
yet	O
so	O
natural	O
&	O
so	O
characteristic	O
.	O
so	O
entirely	O
from	O
ye	O
:	O
heart	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
My	O
Dear	O
friend	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
led	O
to	O
talk	O
over	O
past	O
events	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
--	O
painful	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
recollections	O
!	O
five	O
or	O
6	O
,	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
believe	O
more	O
,	O
of	O
our	O
intimates	O
who	O
were	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
were	O
dead	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
space	O
of	O
9	O
Years	O
&	O
very	O
many	O
of	O
our	O
mutual	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
46	O
--	O
“	O
Hence	O
fond	O
remembrance	O
prompts	O
unbidden	O
tears	O
,	O
“	O
And	O
something	O
sadly	O
solemn	O
mingles	O
still	O
,	O
“	O
With	O
every	O
thought	O
of	O
time	O
for	O
ever	O
gone	O
,	O
“	O
Distinct	O
from	O
past	O
events	O
of	O
good	O
or	O
ill	O
,	O
“	O
Or	O
View	O
of	O
life	O
's	O
swift	O
changes	O
hastening	O
on	O
:	O
“	O
Blast	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
fair	O
buds	O
of	O
hope	O
,	O
or	O
snatch	O
from	O
sight	O
“	O
The	O
dear	O
Companions	O
of	O
our	O
social	O
way	O
“	O
Absorb	O
'd	O
at	O
once	O
in	O
death	O
's	O
impervious	O
night	O
.	O
“	O
The	O
sadneſs	O
hence	O
:	O
but	O
hence	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
sweetneſs	O
too	O
“	O
For	O
well	O
spent	O
time	O
soft	O
whispers	O
to	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Mind	O
“	O
Hopes	O
of	O
a	O
blest	O
eternity	O
behind	O
.	O
“	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
when	O
eternal	O
day	O
“	O
shall	O
gladsome	O
dawn	O
,	O
at	O
once	O
its	O
glorious	O
ray	O
“	O
Shows	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
fair	O
scenes	O
of	O
happineſs	O
complete	O
:	O
“	O
Then	O
friends	O
,	O
Companions	O
,	O
Lovers	O
joyful	O
meet	O
,	O
“	O
Thence	O
never	O
more	O
to	O
part	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
At	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
shall	O
lose	O
ye	O
.	O
recollection	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
kind	O
things	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
parting	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
to	O
convey	O
me	O
to	O
Town	B-place
I	O
took	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
with	O
me	O
&	O
made	O
her	O
accompany	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
visit	O
alone	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
20	O
Minutes	O
&	O
promised	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
&	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
polite	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Rain	O
to	O
hand	O
us	O
into	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
his	O
little	O
Room	O
was	O
like	O
an	O
Oven	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
ye	O
:	O
air	O
again	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
Went	O
on	O
wth	O
:	O
me	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
busineſs	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
detain	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
Dr	O
.	O
AMaria	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
chatted	O
together	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
Bell	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
Our	O
good	O
Neighbours	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
set	O
off	O
for	O
Margate	B-place
to	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
&	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
made	O
us	O
all	O
low	O
&	O
uncomfortable	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
far	O
advanced	O
in	O
life	O
that	O
&	O
are	O
so	O
infirm	O
that	O
one	O
always	O
dreads	O
one	O
shall	O
not	O
Meet	O
again	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
6	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M——	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
from	O
½	O
till	O
past	O
¼	O
before	O
7	O
separated	O
--	O
met	O
then	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
at	O
7	O
accompan	O
ied	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
--	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
left	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
my	O
time	O
wth	O
.	O
these	O
two	O
amiable	O
old	O
Woman	O
much	O
more	O
to	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
than	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
gayest	O
&	O
most	O
brilliant	O
entertainment	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
yesterday	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
all	O
about	O
me	O
for	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
ill	O
of	O
me	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
did	O
me	O
Ye	O
.	O
honor	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
repeat	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
flattering	O
&	O
far	O
far	O
from	O
beyond	O
my	O
deserts	O
.	O
I	O
arranged	O
Prints	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
we	O
had	O
reasonable	O
sensible	O
converse	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
Coach	O
.	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
down	O
At	O
her	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
joind	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
my	O
D	B-pers
&	O
sent	O
a	O
portion	O
of	O
Diary	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
good	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
her	O
little	O
boy	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
before	O
8	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
breakfasted	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
notable	O
Work	O
till	O
11	O
when	O
Saunders	B-pers
came	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
whilst	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Picture	O
he	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
.	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
rect	O
.	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Acct	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
very	O
pleasant	O
intelligence	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morng	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
4.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
s	O
persecution	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
She	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
improper	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
Coach	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
frm	O
.	O
Derbyshire	B-place
--	O
I	O
also	O
recd	O
.	O
letters	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
heard	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
again	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
almost	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
5	O
hours	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
&	O
all	O
she	O
saw	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
Mob	O
were	O
so	O
enraged	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Chevalier	B-pers
Moret	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
it	O
ascend	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Rain	O
that	O
they	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
it	O
&	O
destroy	O
'd	O
what	O
cost	O
some	O
hundred	O
of	O
Pounds	O
--	O
besides	O
ye	O
.	O
labour	O
&	O
anxiety	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
to	O
answer	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
continued	O
.	O
Answered	O
my	O
D	B-pers
's	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
they	O
sup	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
many	O
questions	O
--	O
was	O
much	O
satisfied	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
answers	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
&	O
drank	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Sons	O
health	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
must	O
make	O
them	O
a	O
Visit	O
at	O
Sunning	O
Hill	O
--	O
they	O
promised	O
to	O
spend	O
every	O
Eveg	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
they	O
staid	O
in	O
Town	B-place
wch	O
.	O
is	O
till	O
Saturday	O
--	O
After	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
rec	O
'd	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
12	O
August	O
Thursday	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
B	O
:	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
Saunders	B-pers
came	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Sister	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
kept	O
me	O
sitting	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
made	O
me	O
an	O
agreeable	O
long	O
Visit	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
Yesterday	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Chinese	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
yt-	O
Most	O
people	O
thought	O
Mr.	B-pers
Moret	I-pers
must	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
succeed	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
faild	O
in	O
france	B-place
--	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Subscriptions	O
they	O
say	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Amount	O
of	O
£	O
2000	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Miracle	O
he	O
escaped	O
ye	O
.	O
fury	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mob	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
1	O
,	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
left	O
me	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
pretty	O
amiable	O
Cousin	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
bed	O
side	O
3	O
hours	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
charm	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
infant	O
&	O
think	O
him	O
very	O
pretty	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
is	O
so	O
fortunate	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
nurse	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
William	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
to	O
Nurse	O
George	B-pers
.	O
her	O
Brother	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
just	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
Lords	O
.	O
little	O
George	B-pers
was	O
allowed	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
dine	O
soon	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
on	O
various	O
topics	O
but	O
she	O
true	O
Mother	O
like	O
most	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Brother	O
(	O
youngest	O
Brother	O
)	O
Archibald	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lindsay	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Cousin	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
)	O
&	O
our	O
Aunt	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
were	O
to	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
Sponsors	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
Henry-Hamilton	B-pers
(	O
Murray	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
had	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
the	O
Stuffs	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
chose	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Coat	O
&	O
her	O
Habit	O
--	O
Wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
to	O
Kensington	B-place
&	O
at	O
7	O
got	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
came	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
ye	O
.	O
Marri	O
a	O
ges	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
particularly	O
Lord	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
went	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
illuminations	O
in	O
Honor	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
birth	O
day	O
wch-	O
were	O
uncommonly	O
beautiful	O
&	O
Brilliant	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
ourselves	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
what	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
had	O
said	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
last	O
letter	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
Much	O
pleased	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
a	O
kind	O
impatience	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
as	O
she	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
her	O
...	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
Mr-	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
's	O
Coach	O
was	O
ready	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
down	O
--	O
she	O
insisted	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
desired	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
should	O
accompany	O
me	O
home	O
as	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
riotous	O
&	O
there	O
were	O
hundreds	O
hallooing	O
&	O
throwing	O
Squibs	O
&	O
Crackers	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
heig	O
th	O
ht	O
of	O
Prudery	O
to	O
object	O
,	O
&	O
consented	O
.	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
was	O
so	O
crowded	O
that	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
great	O
Round	O
--	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
illuminations	O
was	O
very	O
pretty	O
.	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
great	O
rejoicings	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
party	O
affair	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
equal	O
to	O
it	O
on	O
any	O
the	O
King	B-pers
s	O
or	O
Queen	B-pers
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
.	O
how	O
apt	O
are	O
the	O
multitude	O
to	O
adore	O
the	O
rising	O
Sun	O
!	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
took	O
his	O
leave	O
after	O
politely	O
handing	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
our	O
Dear	O
Leonidas	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sup̄	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
&	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
friendly	O
converse	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
fatigued	O
&	O
his	O
eyes	O
were	O
bad	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
left	O
us	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Tues	O
Friday	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
at	O
11	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
came	O
she	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
polite	O
invitation	O
from	O
her	O
Aunts	O
to	O
come	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
.	O
she	O
pleased	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
telling	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
favourite	O
with	O
of	O
her	O
fathers	O
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
&	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
he	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
the	O
debates	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
yesterday	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
speeches	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
&	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
at	O
the	O
Lyceum	O
--	O
I	O
agreed	O
provided	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
accompany	O
us	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
having	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Consented	O
&	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
through	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Strand	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
very	O
hot	O
.	O
however	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
our	O
Walk	O
&	O
gratified	O
my	O
curiosity	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
curious	O
Vehicles	O
--	O
the	O
Balloon	O
is	O
a	O
perfect	O
Sphere	O
of	O
abt	O
.	O
33	O
feet	O
in	O
Diameter	O
&	O
102	O
feet	O
in	O
Circumference	O
.	O
it	O
contains	O
18200	O
Cubic	O
feet	O
of	O
inflammable	O
Air	O
&	O
composed	O
entirely	O
of	O
Oil	O
'd	O
silk	O
the	O
Colors	O
are	O
Green	O
&	O
Red	O
in	O
parts	O
thus	O
red	O
,	O
green	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
silk	O
join	O
'd	O
by	O
stong	O
stitching	O
ye	O
.	O
Oars	O
are	O
net	O
works	O
wth	O
.	O
flaps	O
of	O
oil	O
silk	O
Oil	O
silk	O
cases	O
or	O
pipes	O
through	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
inflammable	O
Oil	O
is	O
convey	O
'd	O
by	O
large	O
bellows	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
Wings	O
Galler	O
2	O
Loose	O
Oars	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
held	O
in	O
hand	O
&	O
are	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
&	O
directed	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
persons	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
ye	O
.	O
flapping	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Wings	O
&	O
Oars	O
are	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Oild	O
Silk	O
The	O
Gallery	O
contains	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Wings	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
raised	O
high	O
,	O
&	O
move	O
horizontally	O
,	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
purpose	O
of	O
increasing	O
ye	O
.	O
Motion	O
it	O
receives	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Wind	O
:	O
also	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Oars	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
move	O
vertically	O
;	O
&	O
are	O
meant	O
to	O
raise	O
or	O
depreſs	O
ye	O
.	O
Balloon	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Aerial	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lunardi	I-pers
&	O
an	O
English	O
Gentleman	O
will	O
ascend	O
into	O
ye	O
Atmosphere	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Genteel	O
handsome	O
looking	O
Young	O
Man	O
who	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
english	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
are	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
B	O
:	O
ascend	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
conveyed	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
Garden	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
ascend	O
be	O
launched	O
.	O
Tickets	O
are	O
iſsued	O
at	O
ye	O
Lyceum	O
at	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
½	O
a	O
G	O
:	O
&	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
entitling	O
ye	O
.	O
bearer	O
to	O
an	O
admiſsion	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Gardens	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
ye	O
.	O
Balloon	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
launched	O
,	O
&	O
also	O
to	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
leaves	O
ye	O
.	O
Lyceum	O
--	O
we	O
gave	O
1	O
shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
seen	O
this	O
curious	O
Machin	O
e	O
&	O
been	O
made	O
very	O
sick	O
by	O
the	O
horrid	O
smell	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
breathe	O
even	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Strand	O
.	O
in	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
two	O
Shops	O
bought	O
a	O
Morng	O
.	O
Gown	O
&	O
Threads	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stephens	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
both	O
(	O
Coll	O
.	O
S	O
:	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
Equerries	O
)	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
stare	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
&	O
wonder	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
flirting	O
with	O
--	O
we	O
got	O
home	O
¼	O
past	O
3	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
S——	I-pers
took	O
his	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
excuses	O
for	O
not	O
waiting	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
,	O
&	O
also	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
Company	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
felt	O
so	O
exhausted	O
with	O
my	O
walk	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
out	O
.	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
comfortably	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
play	O
'd	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
leſsons	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
separ	O
a	O
ted	O
from	O
6	O
till	O
7	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
met	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
with	O
writing	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
with	O
full	O
powers	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Mother	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
refusing	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
knowing	O
how	O
fond	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
Music	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
play	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
harpsicord	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
than	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
.	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
Sister	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Brudenal	I-pers
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
between	O
6	O
&	O
7	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
between	O
9	O
&	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
a	O
pretty	O
unaffected	O
child	O
.	O
her	O
genius	O
for	O
Music	O
is	O
astonishing	O
--	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
practise	O
much	O
&	O
though	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
well	O
taught	O
has	O
learnt	O
only	O
from	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
of	O
Oxford	B-place
.	O
She	O
play	O
'd	O
2	O
very	O
difficult	O
leſsons	O
of	O
Schroter	B-pers
s.	O
&	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
composer	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
charm	O
'd	O
--	O
such	O
wonderfull	O
execution	O
&	O
taste	O
--	O
&	O
her	O
pretty	O
little	O
hands	O
so	O
perfectly	O
well	O
placed	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
instrument	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
play	O
by	O
rote	O
but	O
read	O
the	O
Notes	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
who	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
&	O
nicest	O
judges	O
of	O
Music	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
has	O
said	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
finest	O
players	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
&	O
he	O
thought	O
this	O
Child	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
person	O
worthy	O
of	O
some	O
Music	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
last	O
time	O
)	O
from	O
Italy	B-place
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
11	O
.	O
as	O
they	O
return	O
to	O
Sunning	O
Hill	O
tomorrow	O
they	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
kind	O
and	O
friendly	O
manner	O
insisted	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
that	O
they	O
hoped	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
forming	O
a	O
friendship	O
with	O
them	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
friendly	O
manner	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
was	O
entirely	O
at	O
his	O
Service	O
for	O
any	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
he	O
chose	O
&	O
that	O
wd	O
.	O
leave	O
order	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
keeps	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
to	O
receive	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
father	O
&	O
the	O
Servts	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
left	O
us	O
.	O
Saturday	O
August	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Work	O
'd	O
notable	O
work	O
--	O
B	O
in	O
my	O
Own	O
Room	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
written	O
in	O
three	O
parts	O
one	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
&	O
Madlle-	B-pers
Moula	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
I	O
suppose	O
mention	O
'd	O
my	O
engagement	O
--	O
each	O
of	O
these	O
Lad	O
y	O
ie	O
s	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
the	O
warmest	O
Wishes	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
happineſs	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
reproach	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
not	O
having	O
communicated	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
yesterday	O
Call	O
'd	O
at	O
Wirgman	B-pers
ye	O
.	O
Jeweller	O
gave	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Picture	O
to	O
set	O
in	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
expected	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
long	O
letters	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
setting	O
out	O
for	O
Tunbridge	B-place
it	O
was	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
she	O
arrived	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
from	O
Windsor	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
came	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
12	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
Company	O
--	O
he	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
picture	O
&	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
but	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
&	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
found	O
fault	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
as	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
--	O
nor	O
was	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
--	O
in	O
short	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
contrariety	O
of	O
opinions	O
--	O
some	O
thought	O
ye	O
.	O
Mouth	O
too	O
large	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
feature	O
resembling	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
At	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
conversed	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
sat	O
sometime	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
join	O
our	O
party	O
--	O
but	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
Doctr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
s	O
at	O
North	O
End	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
pretty	O
very	O
small	O
Villa	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Cottage	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
T	I-pers
&	O
her	O
pretty	O
innocent	O
Cousin	O
Miſs	B-pers
Noseley	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
much	O
apparent	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
N	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
sh	O
o	O
ru	O
berry	O
&	O
Garden	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Acre	O
.	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
before	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
he	O
dyed	O
my	O
Cheeks	O
by	O
warm	O
Congratulations	O
&	O
wishes	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
yesterday	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
had	O
told	O
him	O
wthht	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
said	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
by	O
him	O
many	O
kind	O
reproaches	O
&	O
wishes	O
.	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Cottage	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
handsome	O
dinner	O
&	O
chearful	O
conversation	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
T——	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
a	O
n	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
House	O
Adam	B-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
build	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
.	O
upon	O
an	O
Estate	O
he	O
has	O
lately	O
purchased	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
T——	I-pers
is	O
very	O
Rich	O
--	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Heireſs	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
fortune	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
by	O
his	O
profeſsion	O
of	O
Physician	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
having	O
any	O
Children	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
him	O
he	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
happiest	O
Couple	O
I	O
know	O
--	O
attentive	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
degree	O
even	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
triffling	O
occasions	O
&	O
their	O
affection	O
seems	O
to	O
spring	O
immediately	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
heart	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
kind	O
&	O
good	O
friends	O
of	O
mine	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
love	O
me	O
most	O
sincerely	O
--	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
saying	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
them	O
by	O
introducing	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
that	O
they	O
hoped	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
was	O
built	O
we	O
should	O
often	O
spend	O
a	O
Month	O
there	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
mean	O
time	O
their	O
Cottage	O
&	O
house	O
in	O
Town	B-place
wd	O
.	O
often	O
be	O
visited	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
for	O
us	O
&	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
drink	O
her	O
Tea	O
with	O
us	O
under	O
the	O
Apricot	O
Tree	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
our	O
agreeable	O
entertainers	O
.	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
home	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
&	O
each	O
agree	O
'd	O
in	O
saying	O
how	O
happy	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
each	O
other	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
down	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
Place	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
insisted	O
so	O
strongly	O
upon	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Old	O
Ladies	O
approving	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
yield	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
my	O
polite	O
Beau	O
got	O
out	O
to	O
hand	O
me	O
&	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
sweet	O
babe	O
very	O
well	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
we	O
chatted	O
on	O
Various	O
Subjects	O
till	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Chair	O
--	O
as	O
Ldy	O
.	O
S——	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Horses	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
way	O
to	O
meet	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
who	O
went	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
to	O
see	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
night	O
or	O
tomorrow	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
indifferent	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
heard	O
that	O
Dr	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sunning	O
Hill	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
siezed	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
gout	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
however	O
better	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dyer	O
came	O
to	O
settle	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
sattins	O
Sunday	O
15	O
th	O
August	O
--	O
84	O
At	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
chatting	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
thing	O
serious	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
(	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
8	O
oClock	O
Chapel	O
at	O
St	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
)	O
I	O
sent	O
Richard	O
to	O
Church	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
till	O
near	O
3	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
after	O
her	O
little	O
excursion	O
of	O
yesterday	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
alone	O
till	O
near	O
2.	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
D	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
we	O
arranged	O
things	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Cabinets	O
.	O
she	O
trusted	O
me	O
to	O
repair	O
some	O
fine	O
delicate	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
her	O
friend	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
small	O
flowers	O
in	O
Ivory	O
--	O
Vases	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
myself	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
to	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
Aunts	O
we	O
would	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
a	O
M	O
rs	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
my	O
Work	O
&	O
listen	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
sensible	O
conversation	O
--	O
a	O
¼	O
before	O
3	O
My	O
servt	O
.	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
beloved	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
Palace	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
they	O
were	O
out	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
was	O
in	O
waiting	O
I	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
me	O
most	O
civily	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Month	O
ye	O
.	O
Bedchamber	O
Woman	O
is	O
in	O
waiting	O
they	O
dine	O
at	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honors	O
table	O
&	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
invite	O
1	O
Guest	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
From	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
read	O
some	O
Chapters	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Chapel	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
we	O
parted	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
I	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
him	O
quite	O
well	O
again	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
8.	O
we	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
sociably	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
our	O
good	O
friends	O
who	O
go	O
to	O
Sunning	O
Hill	O
tomorrow	O
had	O
their	O
Coach	O
to	O
bring	O
us	O
home	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Room	O
immediately	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Fredk_	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Monday	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
B——	O
with	O
Dearest	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
notable	O
work	O
--	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
who	O
brought	O
some	O
things	O
home	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fullwood	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
Porte	O
Fueille	O
of	O
Prints	O
--	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
invited	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
door	O
we	O
went	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
(	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
&	O
went	O
entirely	O
to	O
please	O
me	O
)	O
his	O
--	O
House	O
.	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
even	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
bed	O
Chambers	O
--	O
his	O
Pictures	O
--	O
his	O
China	O
--	O
his	O
little	O
Cabinets	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
few	O
good	O
Pictures	O
&	O
many	O
Copies	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
however	O
he	O
pleases	O
himself	O
with	O
thinking	O
originals	O
.	O
nothing	O
could	O
exceed	O
ye	O
.	O
neatneſs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
House	O
&	O
these	O
were	O
some	O
elegancies	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
spent	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
pleasing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fullwood	I-pers
by	O
admiring	O
his	O
collection	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
our	O
leaves	O
--	O
As	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
house	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
(	O
the	O
Young	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
)	O
came	O
.	O
they	O
staid	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Boscawan	I-pers
took	O
me	O
aside	O
&	O
said	O
many	O
very	O
flattering	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
after	O
having	O
made	O
me	O
blush	O
by	O
her	O
too	O
great	O
commendations	O
she	O
touch	O
'd	O
my	O
heart	O
very	O
sensibly	O
by	O
the	O
friendly	O
&	O
maternal	O
wishes	O
she	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
happineſs	O
.	O
She	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
contrive	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Villa	O
.	O
After	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
's	I-pers
to	O
put	O
off	O
our	O
going	O
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
heat	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
¼	O
before	O
three	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
English	O
Teacher	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
--	O
it	O
contain	O
'd	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
how	O
delighted	O
her	O
Aunts	O
were	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
accepted	O
their	O
invitation	O
--	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
long	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
acquaint	O
ed	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
merit	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
ye	O
.	O
vainest	O
creature	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
for	O
people	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
continue	O
to	O
derive	O
benefit	O
&	O
not	O
acquire	O
vanity	O
--	O
by	O
a	O
steady	O
perseverance	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
merit	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
those	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
honor	O
to	O
be	O
distinguished	O
&	O
liked	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
mending	O
some	O
China	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Cover	O
of	O
Cup	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
dear	O
deceased	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
trust	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
&	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
succeeding	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
finishing	O
my	O
Repairs	O
.	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
y	O
e	O
lovely	O
infant	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
we	O
chatted	O
on	O
various	O
subjects	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
had	O
objected	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Childs	O
having	O
two	O
Xtian	O
Names	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
must	O
give	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
a	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
--	O
that	O
a	O
Page	O
&	O
½	O
was	O
fill	O
'd	O
wth	O
:	O
kind	O
messages	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
most	O
afft	O
.	O
wishes	O
&	O
c	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
8.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Tunbridge	B-place
Yesterday	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
was	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
had	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Chariot	O
--	O
his	O
Servt	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
setting	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
heard	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
&	O
Cousin	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
were	O
come	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
--	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
¼	O
before	O
12	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
made	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
observation	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
Woman	O
of	O
high	O
rank	O
of	O
our	O
acquaintance	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
out	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Fashion	O
&	O
Quality	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
as	O
in	O
breeding	O
so	O
in	O
dreſs	O
,	O
People	O
of	O
real	O
fashion	O
are	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
by	O
ease	O
&	O
one	O
generally	O
may	O
observe	O
a	O
much	O
leſs	O
ostentation	O
of	O
ornamental	O
decoration	O
.	O
a	O
certain	O
chasteneſs	O
of	O
dreſs	O
is	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
admire	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
17	O
th	O
August	O
.	O
At	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
with	O
Dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
was	O
still	O
suffering	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
endow	O
'd	O
with	O
so	O
heavenly	O
a	O
disposition	O
that	O
nothing	O
alters	O
for	O
it	O
her	O
temper	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
oClo	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
early	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
&	O
therefor	O
e	O
had	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
.	O
a	O
Man	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
lease	O
leash	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Chester	O
Coach	O
from	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
a	O
brace	O
in	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
kept	O
one	O
for	O
our	O
Table	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wirgman	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Jeweller	O
brought	O
home	O
my	O
picture	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
--	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
pack	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
&	O
entrusted	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
care	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
to	O
the	B-place
City	I-place
to	O
send	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
to	O
thank	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Moorgame	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
guess	O
'd	O
from	O
whom	O
it	O
came	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormonts	I-pers
I	O
found	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
pains	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
had	O
not	O
gain	O
'd	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
ground	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
was	O
severe	O
in	O
his	O
censure	O
of	O
on	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
for	O
her	O
conduct	O
towards	O
me	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
Prints	O
of	O
Cook	B-pers
Voyages	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
&	O
sent	O
for	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
(	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
excuse	O
my	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
Note	O
from	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
engaged	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Justi	I-pers
&	O
Nurse	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
looking	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
pretty	O
things	O
ye	O
Child	O
was	O
to	O
wear	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Christening	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
came	O
&	O
interrupt	O
ed	O
us	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Raph	I-pers
Payne	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
give	O
me	O
two	O
franks	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
settled	O
wth-	O
him	O
abt	O
our	O
expedition	O
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
next	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
left	O
us	O
--	O
some	O
more	O
Matches	O
were	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Woodley	I-pers
to	O
be	O
marri	O
d	O
e	O
d	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
Admiral	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
Very	O
soon	O
to	O
a	O
½	O
Sister	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
heard	O
of	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
things	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
is	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
her	O
Wedding	O
Cloaths	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
till	O
near	O
4	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Hodgkinsons	O
to	O
chuse	O
some	O
Muslins	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
not	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
leſsons	O
we	O
parted	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
met	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
William	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
nearest	O
stage	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
try	O
in	O
ye	B-place
.	I-place
City	I-place
.	I-place
I	O
wrote	O
4	O
letters	O
viz	O
--	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Moula	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
.	O
at	O
8	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
of	O
3	O
hours	O
.	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
all	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
journey	O
through	O
Wales	B-place
,	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
affairs	O
--	O
we	O
talkd	O
of	O
Pictures	O
--	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
must	O
come	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
staid	O
a	O
Year	O
there	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
answer	O
our	O
expence	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Journey	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
most	O
Kind	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
very	O
happy	O
by	O
his	O
Visit	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
moment	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
scribbled	O
a	O
hasty	O
letter	O
to	O
inform	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
picture	O
was	O
sent	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
just	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
bell	O
man	O
when	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
trust	O
ye	O
.	O
box	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
wch	O
.	O
Coach	O
went	O
ye	O
.	O
nearest	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
12	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
came	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
Uncle	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
he	O
left	O
an	O
imploring	O
meſsage	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
&	O
c	O
