TOKEN	NE
Wellington	B-place
½	O
past	O
7	O
Tuesday	O
Evg	O
31	O
Augt	O
My	O
dearest	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
without	O
any	O
Companions	O
&	O
took	O
in	O
an	O
outside	O
paſsenger	O
at	O
Spinham	B-place
Lands	I-place
without	O
recg	O
any	O
advantage	O
--	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
Newberry	B-place
Happily	O
no	O
unpleasant	O
Reflections	O
disturbed	O
any	O
solitary	O
Meditations	O
&	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
12	O
Miles	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
Scenery	O
and	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
took	O
an	O
outside	O
place	O
for	O
this	O
town	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
wch-	O
is	O
new	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Wells	B-place
20	O
miles	O
is	O
unpleasant	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
tremendous	O
Hills	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
drive	O
down	O
them	O
wh-	O
rapidity	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
for	O
loſs	O
of	O
time	O
&	O
this	O
requires	O
a	O
nervous	O
apprentices	O
help	O
to	O
be	O
placidly	O
reconciled	O
to	O
--	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Wells	B-place
there	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Subject	O
for	O
a	O
Landscape	O
without	O
Water	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
conceived	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
wished	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
sketch	O
it	O
--	O
from	O
Wells	B-place
to	O
Glastonbury	B-place
the	O
road	O
is	O
charming	O
7	O
Miles	O
--	O
the	O
town	O
is	O
pretty	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
curious	O
Remains	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Abbey	O
,	O
the	O
Tower	O
looks	O
well	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
--	O
The	O
road	O
from	O
Glastonbury	B-place
to	O
Bridgewater	B-place
is	O
perfectly	O
good	O
13	O
miles	O
--	O
the	O
Mail	O
is	O
here	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
for	O
lost	O
time	O
&	O
we	O
frequently	O
flitted	O
ventre	O
a	O
terre	O
for	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
so	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
curious	O
ridge	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
road	O
runs	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
miles	O
which	O
commands	O
a	O
magnificent	O
prospect	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
--	O
Bridgewater	B-place
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
town	O
--	O
we	O
dined	O
on	O
a	O
Coach	O
dinner	O
at	O
Taunton	B-place
at	O
6	O
OClock	O
Taunton	B-place
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Town	O
&	O
then	O
came	O
here	O
--	O
tantivy	O
--	O
Since	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
paſsion	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
quiet	O
now	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
wh-	O
Composure	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Soul	O
in	O
this	O
town	O
who	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
Oakford	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
Office	O
--	O
Never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
spoken	O
to	O
Gemmen	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
--	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
place	O
--	O
The	O
Landlord	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
post	O
Boy	O
who	O
must	O
know	O
it	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
later	O
so	O
here	O
have	O
I	O
been	O
fuming	O
&	O
admiring	O
all	O
my	O
Relations	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
discreet	O
sensible	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
200	O
miles	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
direct	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Town	O
&	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
&	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
Driver	O
to	O
direct	O
his	O
horse	O
--	O
luckily	O
I	O
recollected	O
Bampton	B-place
is	O
the	O
Post	O
Town	O
&	O
that	O
place	O
is	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
miles	O
off	O
--	O
so	O
probably	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
20	O
miles	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
--	O
from	O
stupidity	O
--	O
The	O
Day	O
has	O
been	O
remarkably	O
calm	O
&	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
--	O
very	O
soon	O
I	O
shall	O
drink	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
Tea	O
&	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
tomorrow	O
Try	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
Wiseacres	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
&	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
pains	O
taking	O
it	O
seems	O
settled	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
14	O
miles	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
wild	O
Goose	O
Chase	O
--	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
feel	O
at	O
all	O
fatigued	O
&	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
expectations	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
spasms	O
in	O
my	O
knee	O
--	O
Your	O
party	O
is	O
just	O
aſsembling	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
spend	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Afternoon	O
Adieu	O
--	O
My	O
very	O
dear	O
friend	O
--	O
With	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Girl	O
&	O
Kindest	O
Regards	O
to	O
Morrison	B-pers
I	O
am	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
40	O
Years	O
Most	O
Tenderly	O
&	O
Affy	O
Yrs	O
.	O
JD	B-pers
I	O
found	O
my	O
Gun	O
here	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
