TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
Abbey	O
Septr	O
:	O
22	O
d	O
1771	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Though	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
my	O
Letters	O
have	O
either	O
been	O
Unsucceſsful	O
in	O
finding	O
their	O
way	O
or	O
in	O
prevailing	O
with	O
You	O
to	O
answer	O
them	O
--	O
bellieve	O
me	O
my	O
friendship	O
&	O
Anxiety	O
for	O
all	O
yr	O
Welfare	O
's	O
remain	O
ever	O
the	O
same	O
--	O
a	O
Paragraph	O
in	O
last	O
Nights	O
Pappers	O
roused	O
our	O
attention	O
too	O
much	O
&	O
too	O
disagreeably	O
to	O
admitt	O
of	O
a	O
moment	O
longer	O
Sillence	O
as	O
it	O
tells	O
me	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
&	O
You	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
greatest	O
of	O
all	O
Loſses	O
be	O
asured	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
sincearest	O
Sympathie	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
me	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
of	O
that	O
of	O
yr	O
Young	O
friends	O
on	O
this	O
very	O
Mellancholy	O
occaſsion	O
&	O
indulge	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
speedy	O
Act	O
.	O
of	O
yourself	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
who	O
we	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
Supported	O
from	O
Mottives	O
of	O
Raison	O
&	O
Relligion	O
to	O
bear	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
--	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
it	O
can	O
admitt	O
--	O
excuse	O
me	O
if	O
Anxiety	O
about	O
you	O
both	O
both	O
gets	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
Polliteneſs	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
question	O
that	O
from	O
one	O
leſs	O
sincearly	O
yr	O
friend	O
might	O
appear	O
Impertinent	O
but	O
excuse	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
regard	O
I	O
hope	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
Setled	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
for	O
both	O
yr	O
Interest	O
s	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
a	O
Strict	O
Entaill	O
will	O
admitt	O
of	O
--	O
do	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
So	O
;	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
by	O
wt	O
cause	O
yr	O
late	O
Misfortune	O
was	O
brought	O
about	O
.	O
If	O
ever	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
Use	O
to	O
you	O
be	O
asured	O
you	O
may	O
ever	O
command	O
me	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
most	O
Affect	O
.	O
compts	O
&	O
Condollences	O
to	O
yourself	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Most	O
Affect	O
.	O
Cousin	O
&	O
Faithful	O
Humble	O
Sert	O
.	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
By	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
ye	O
19	O
th	O
Augst	O
all	O
friends	O
in	O
Ruſsia	B-place
were	O
Well	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
you	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
them	O
