TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
May	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
delighted	O
at	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
by	O
Yourself	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
though	O
your	O
Daughter	O
certainly	O
writes	O
very	O
like	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
do	O
Louisa	B-pers
the	O
justice	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
read	O
her	O
writing	O
without	O
Spectacles	O
--	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
Yours	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
reached	O
Doncaster	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
Hunter	B-pers
,	O
and	O
at	O
Newcastle	B-place
of	O
his	O
Funeral	O
being	O
over	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
perfectly	O
resigned	O
,	O
and	O
ready	O
for	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
His	O
two	O
Sons	O
were	O
unfortunately	O
absent	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
detained	O
,	O
to	O
bury	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
their	O
Father	O
s	O
,	O
whose	O
death	O
was	O
not	O
communicated	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
arrive	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
place	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
preach	O
at	O
Leith	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
out	O
rainy	O
and	O
sleety	O
.	O
He	O
walked	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
supposed	O
then	O
to	O
have	O
caught	O
cold	O
,	O
which	O
brought	O
on	O
an	O
Inflammation	O
on	O
his	O
Lungs	O
,	O
which	O
terminated	O
his	O
existence	O
in	O
six	O
days	O
.	O
A	O
better	O
Man	O
never	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
consider	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
public	O
Loſs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Line	O
of	O
his	O
Profession	O
.	O
Whatever	O
he	O
preached	O
,	O
he	O
practised	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
an	O
affectionate	O
leave	O
of	O
such	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
prayed	O
for	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
absent	O
,	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
parishioners	O
.	O
His	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
producing	O
her	O
first	O
Child	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
expreſsing	O
his	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
united	O
to	O
a	O
deserving	O
man	O
,	O
&	O
recommending	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
situation	O
might	O
be	O
injured	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
his	O
diſsolution	O
.	O
His	O
two	O
Girls	O
will	O
have	O
£3000	O
each	O
,	O
&	O
h	O
is	O
younger	O
Son	O
,	O
£4000	O
.	O
The	O
eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Landed	O
Estate	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
£1200	O
pr	O
Ann	O
.	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
burdened	O
with	O
two	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
three	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
younger	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Cottagers	O
of	O
Glenburnie	O
exhibit	O
too	O
true	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
Claſs	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
,	O
whether	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
Book	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
reforming	O
them	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
the	O
price	O
will	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
their	O
purchasing	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
secondly	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
never	O
will	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
exposing	O
their	O
manners	O
to	O
the	O
Englishers	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
You	O
,	O
I	O
doubt	O
much	O
whether	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
understand	O
the	O
language	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
may	O
aſsist	O
as	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Morrison	B-pers
is	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Hampshire	B-place
,	O
&	O
a	O
most	O
intolerable	O
Daudle	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
It	O
w	O
as	O
an	O
unlucky	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
She	O
&	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
he	O
remains	O
in	O
Newgate	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
condescend	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
wilfully	O
prevaricate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
acted	O
justly	O
,	O
in	O
committing	O
him	O
for	O
doing	O
so	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
remain	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
Seſsion	O
lasts	O
.	O
My	O
Rib	O
&	O
c	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
everything	O
kind	O
,	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
your	O
Hub	O
,	O
and	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Charles	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Tenth	O
May	O
1809	O
Napier	B-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
