TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ancaster	I-pers
has	O
brought	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Card	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
Pantheon	O
where	O
they	O
will	O
give	O
your	O
Servant	O
the	O
Ticket	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
repeat	O
a	O
thousand	O
Wishes	O
of	O
amusement	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Sincerely	O
CFinch	B-pers
Kew	B-place
.	O
June	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C.Finch	I-pers
June	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1779	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
or	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
James	O
Street	O
Westminster	B-place
--	O
