TOKEN	NE
M	O
y	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
received	O
my	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
s	O
letter	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
She	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
cause	O
to	O
think	O
herself	O
neglected	O
by	O
those	O
who	O
love	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
acquit	O
our	O
friends	O
at	O
the	O
Cottage	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
left	O
the	B-place
Dale	I-place
above	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
;	O
&	O
to	O
my	O
certain	O
knowledge	O
they	O
have	O
writ	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
my	O
excuses	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
family	O
affairs	O
have	O
effected	O
our	O
spirits	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
persuaid	O
our	O
selves	O
to	O
put	O
pen	O
to	O
paper	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
your	O
Dear	O
friend	O
Leonidas	B-pers
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
be	O
connected	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
rose	O
--	O
At	O
present	O
our	O
House	O
is	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Bulls	O
Croſs	O
family	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mckonishie	I-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
latter	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
Self	O
it	O
will	O
doe	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
;	O
&	O
how	O
happy	O
shall	O
we	O
be	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
;	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
his	O
friend	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
gon	O
to	O
a	O
Sale	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
wee	O
all	O
whent	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Carpet	O
.	O
I	O
greatly	O
rejoice	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
once	O
more	O
a	O
free	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
Affair	O
hurt	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
very	O
much	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
dont	O
return	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
the	O
frank	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
every	O
disagreeable	O
thing	O
puts	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
sorts	O
now	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
once	O
not	O
the	O
case	O
--	O
But	O
with	O
pleasure	O
I	O
can	O
inform	O
you	O
he	O
Drinks	O
the	O
Waters	O
with	O
great	O
suckceſs	O
.	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
time	O
he	O
will	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
that	O
now	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
love	O
,	O
She	O
behaves	O
her	O
Self	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
forever	O
will	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
conclude	O
without	O
leting	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
love	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
period	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
--	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
Sepr	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
Sist	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
:	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
Washing	O
--	O
4-5	O
Cambric	O
3-3	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
10-10	O
Cloth	O
2-12	O
Lottery	O
Tu	O
2-5	O
Powder	O
&	O
c	O
4-7	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gl——	I-pers
--	O
0-6	O
F	O
0-7	O
Hopkins	B-pers
--	O
0-5	O
Chaise	O
--	O
0-	O
7	O
6	O
Webb	O
--	O
3-9	O
Box	O
--	O
1-14-6	O
Dartrey	B-pers
Maid	O
0-5-0	O
Lace	O
--	O
8-10-0	O
174	O
85	O
47-1	O
14	O
61	O
10	O
