TOKEN	NE
Boston	B-place
August	O
26	O
th	O
1768	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
bellieve	O
it	O
will	O
always	O
give	O
me	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
regreate	O
receiveing	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
instead	O
of	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
because	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
yr	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
was	O
so	O
disagreeable	O
a	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
to	O
You	O
--	O
asure	O
her	O
we	O
are	O
extreamly	O
Sorry	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
Indisposed	O
but	O
hope	O
the	O
Rhumatism	O
has	O
left	O
her	O
long	O
beffore	O
this	O
can	O
reach	O
You	O
&	O
heartily	O
wish	O
yr	O
next	O
may	O
bring	O
more	O
Comfortable	O
accounts	O
of	O
both	O
her	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
whose	O
Goutish	O
Complaints	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
sympathizes	O
with	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
double	O
Capacity	O
being	O
still	O
far	O
from	O
free	O
from	O
them	O
himself	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
all	O
this	O
sooner	O
but	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
well	O
myself	O
&	O
often	O
so	O
much	O
distrest	O
that	O
I	O
'm	O
quite	O
incap	O
a	O
ble	O
to	O
hold	O
a	O
Pen	O
--	O
I	O
write	O
with	O
pain	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
entitled	O
to	O
Speedy	O
good	O
Acts	O
:	O
of	O
You	O
all	O
as	O
You	O
Young	O
Lady	O
's	O
are	O
not	O
Lyable	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Interuptions	O
of	O
correspondance	O
we	O
married	O
ones	O
often	O
meet	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
want	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
information	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
fine	O
Buck	O
is	O
on	O
its	O
way	O
from	O
Risby	B-place
to	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
Us	O
so	O
beg	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
will	O
look	O
out	O
sharp	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
eat	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
Healths	O
'twould	O
be	O
a	O
thousand	O
pity	O
's	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
lost	O
had	O
we	O
been	O
there	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
eat	O
it	O
together	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
great	O
Comfort	O
to	O
Us	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
wt	O
we	O
imagine	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
of	O
its	O
kind	O
--	O
.	O
We	O
still	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
You	O
about	O
the	O
midle	O
of	O
Octr	O
:	O
I	O
therefore	O
hope	O
when	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
sees	O
Mr	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
he	O
'll	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
&	O
yt	O
the	O
Moment	O
the	O
route	O
arrives	O
I	O
shall	O
sett	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
find	O
every	O
thing	O
read	O
y	O
for	O
our	O
Reception	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
it	O
wont	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
people	O
here	O
can	O
prevent	O
it	O
or	O
keep	O
us	O
amongst	O
them	O
--	O
so	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
litle	O
certainty	O
falls	O
to	O
the	O
Lott	O
of	O
us	O
Millitary	O
People	O
--	O
one	O
thing	O
however	O
is	O
certain	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
ever	O
esteem	O
ourselves	O
Happy	O
in	O
an	O
Oportunity	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
yr	O
Neighbourhood	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
other	O
things	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
cause	O
to	O
regreate	O
yr	O
Babylonians	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
Civill	O
or	O
Sociable	O
than	O
the	O
people	O
here	O
--	O
't	O
is	O
one	O
constant	O
round	O
of	O
Invitations	O
for	O
us	O
&	O
those	O
we	O
are	O
most	O
Intimate	O
with	O
to	O
Partake	O
of	O
Venison	O
&	O
all	O
good	O
things	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
Collected	O
together	O
&	O
no	O
Vaills	O
nor	O
Card	O
Money	O
alow	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
regreate	O
finding	O
Loo	O
abolisht	O
amongst	O
You	O
--	O
as	O
its	O
a	O
Game	O
I	O
never	O
will	O
make	O
one	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
for	O
yr	O
Sake	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
dont	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Races	O
but	O
perhaps	O
your	O
party	O
may	O
Muster	O
more	O
forces	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Acts	O
of	O
my	O
Br	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Pappers	O
since	O
he	O
Sailled	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
from	O
London	B-place
he	O
was	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
beffore	O
he	O
sett	O
out	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
joins	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
&	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
compts	O
:	O
to	O
You	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mam	O
ma	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Most	O
faithfully	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wont	O
make	O
you	O
pay	O
double	O
by	O
putting	O
this	O
in	O
a	O
Cover	O
the	O
Venison	O
is	O
a	O
present	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mostyne	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
half	O
the	O
Estate	O
of	O
Risby	B-place
bellongs	O
--	O
