TOKEN	NE
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
August	O
1786	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
Letter	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
of	O
answering	O
a	O
Letter	O
you	O
wrote	O
me	O
from	O
Warwickshire	B-place
--	O
Now	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
angry	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
supposing	O
me	O
so	O
negligent	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
concluding	O
that	O
your	O
Letter	O
has	O
miscarried	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
fact	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
pretty	O
opinion	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Correspondent	O
,	O
by	O
writing	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Answer	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
mention	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Brace	O
of	O
Grouse	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
his	O
Letter	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
reach	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
by	O
mistake	O
had	O
it	O
directed	O
to	O
Taxall	B-place
,	O
Cheshire	B-place
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Derbyshire	B-place
--	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
that	O
Letter	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
remove	O
to	O
N	O
o	O
:	O
248	O
Oxford-Street	O
.	O
I	O
correspond	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
telling	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
considerably	O
better	O
this	O
Summer	O
than	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
Letter	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mother	O
(	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
)	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Person	O
receive	O
more	O
benefit	O
than	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
,	O
from	O
James	O
's	O
Powders	O
--	O
her	O
complaint	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
bilious	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
pity	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
ever	O
be	O
indispos	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
clever	O
and	O
most	O
amiable	O
young	O
Woman	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
whose	O
friendship	O
may	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
were	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
expected	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
affliction	O
they	O
had	O
sustain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
shock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
's	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
her	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pleasing	O
a	O
Woman./	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
sister	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
ago	O
--	O
She	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
(	O
who	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
)	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
also	O
--	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Party	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
were	O
here	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
to	O
celebrate	O
his	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
:	O
Inst	O
.	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
always	O
have	O
Music	O
of	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
forget	O
either	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
great	O
favourites	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
is	O
building	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Oxford	O
Street	O
looking	O
into	O
Hyde-Park	O
--	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
is	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
growing	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Situation	O
.	O
We	O
remove	O
tomorrow./	O
I	O
am	O
fonder	O
than	O
ever	O
of	O
Music	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	O
all	O
this	O
Summer	O
taking	O
Leſsons	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
yours	O
affectionately	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
London	B-place
.	O
August	O
25	O
th	O
:	O
1786	O
.	O
