TOKEN	NE
Jan	O
:	O
29	O
th	O
1786	O
I	O
hasten	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
most	O
impatiently	O
and	O
constantly	O
expected	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
certainly	O
receive	O
great	O
pleasure	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
kind	O
and	O
affectionate	O
things	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
unreasonable	O
enough	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
satisfied	O
with	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
yourself	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
hardly	O
understood	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
Do	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
does	O
he	O
,	O
stay	O
at	O
Courteenhall	B-place
all	O
the	O
winter	O
?	O
when	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
or	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
Cheshire	B-place
?	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
all	O
Day	O
?	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
question	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
Town	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
supposes	O
her	O
Friend	O
can	O
not	O
poſsibly	O
find	O
occupation	O
to	O
vary	O
a	O
dull	O
country	O
life	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
mistake	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
follow	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
about	O
&	O
what	O
engages	O
you	O
--	O
do	O
you	O
draw	O
or	O
paint	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
leisure	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
this	O
amusement	O
&	O
to	O
indulge	O
your	O
geniuses	O
--	O
All	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
my	O
dejection	O
is	O
so	O
true	O
,	O
just	O
and	O
unanswerable	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
reply	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
dined	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Selwyn	I-pers
's	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
when	O
I	O
arrived	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensberry	I-pers
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
Ganganelli	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
par	O
un	O
hazard	O
at	O
the	O
letter	O
--	O
read	O
it	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
who	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
asks	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
dejection	O
--	O
it	O
had	O
no	O
ostensible	O
one	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
says	O
what	O
is	O
true	O
&	O
what	O
I	O
feel	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
depend	O
on	O
so	O
many	O
external	O
causes	O
independant	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
mercy	O
we	O
are	O
that	O
who	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
--	O
?	O
Or	O
rather	O
I	O
have	O
(	O
in	O
this	O
respect	O
certainly	O
)	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
weak	O
mind	O
,	O
subservient	O
to	O
the	O
airy	O
,	O
influences	O
,	O
&	O
easily	O
distracted	O
&	O
discomposed	O
by	O
every	O
trifling	O
circumstance	O
--	O
or	O
to	O
speak	O
more	O
kindly	O
of	O
mysel	O
f	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sensibility	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
not	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
vexations	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
certainly	O
the	O
misfortune	O
&	O
misery	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
creastures	O
,	O
alter	O
my	O
happineſs	O
considerably	O
--	O
The	O
great	O
features	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
strike	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
speak	O
against	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
,	O
faint	O
touches	O
which	O
appear	O
only	O
on	O
a	O
nearer	O
view	O
,	O
paſs	O
unnoticed	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
a	O
bad	O
cough	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
heavy	O
&	O
oppreſsive	O
,	O
need	O
you	O
go	O
further	O
for	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
bad	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
complain	O
or	O
murmur	O
--	O
God	O
knows	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
contented	O
&	O
resigned	O
,	O
nay	O
I	O
enjoy	O
life	O
,	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
amusements	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
moments	O
&	O
I	O
suppose	O
few	O
people	O
can	O
deny	O
having	O
experienced	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
mind	O
has	O
lost	O
its	O
elasticity	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
spirits	O
have	O
fled	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
disgusts	O
&	O
tires	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
drinking	O
aſses	O
Milk	O
for	O
this	O
week	O
past	O
and	O
my	O
cough	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elisabeth	I-pers
is	O
recoveri	O
n	O
g	O
very	O
fast	O
they	O
say	O
--	O
but	O
looks	O
very	O
pale	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
fat	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
bad	O
sign	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
all	O
surprised	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
a	O
consumption	O
after	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
been	O
quite	O
miserable	O
about	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
frequent	O
relapses	O
have	O
kept	O
me	O
in	O
continual	O
agitation	O
--	O
Their	B-pers
Maj	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
the	O
two	O
elder	O
P	O
.	O
are	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
where	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
since	O
Friday	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Town	O
&	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
airing	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
ancient	O
musick	O
begins	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
the	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Oratorios	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
old	O
train	O
again	O
--	O
3	O
Days	O
in	O
the	O
week	O
entirely	O
given	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
like	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
of	O
my	O
Friend	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
re	O
where	O
th	O
a	O
nk	O
God	O
I	O
have	O
dined	O
but	O
9	O
times	O
since	O
th	O
e	O
14	O
th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
the	O
Opera	O
's	O
are	O
begun	O
--	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
go	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Ticket	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
power	O
to	O
judge	O
myself	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
merit	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsing	I-pers
since	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
asked	O
me	O
since	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
regret	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
never	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
--	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
are	O
all	O
her	O
children	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
how	O
does	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
grow	O
up	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
your	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
,	O
who	O
returns	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
gout	O
before	O
he	O
is	O
rather	O
better	O
but	O
looks	O
deplorably	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
Ly	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
--	O
dont	O
'	O
you	O
wish	O
me	O
joy	O
?	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
--	O
ever	O
affec	O
:	O
&	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
MGunning	B-pers
--	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
How	O
Mr	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
puts	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
patience	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
allowed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
like	O
a	O
tame	O
Cat	O
without	O
any	O
bodies	O
minding	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gives	O
himself	O
the	O
airs	O
of	O
being	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
Friend	O
!	O
he	O
is	O
intimate	O
with	O
everybo	O
dy	O
Gamekeeper	O
,	O
Groom	O
,	O
farmers	O
&	O
servants	O
&	O
pries	O
into	O
every	O
body	O
's	O
affairs	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
matter	O
for	O
making	O
himself	O
acceptable	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
goſsiping	O
house	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northamton	B-place
