TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
Sept	O
.	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
kind	O
letter	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
has	O
made	O
us	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
it	O
found	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Father	O
better	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
alarmingly	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
letter	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
unhappy	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
have	O
wrote	O
you	O
word	O
of	O
his	O
illneſs	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
made	O
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
myself	O
very	O
miserable	O
,	O
Friday	O
Yesterday	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
he	O
is	O
thank	O
God	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
eat	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
yesterday	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
dinner	O
&	O
with	O
a	O
relish	O
,	O
to	O
day	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
haunch	O
of	O
Venison	O
,	O
&	O
before	O
I	O
seal	O
my	O
letter	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
plays	O
his	O
part	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
arrived	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
month	O
to	O
day	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
disappointed	O
,	O
for	O
by	O
his	O
letters	O
to	O
us	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Chariot	O
&	O
our	O
own	O
horses	O
,	O
&	O
arrived	O
here	O
a	O
day	O
sooner	O
than	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
his	O
joy	O
&	O
surprize	O
at	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
after	O
an	O
absense	O
of	O
two	O
months	O
quite	O
overcame	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
eat	O
no	O
dinner	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
sheding	O
tears	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
wan	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
thin	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
eat	O
his	O
dinner	O
with	O
an	O
appetite	O
,	O
for	O
near	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
this	O
day	O
fortnight	O
we	O
thought	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
tour	O
:	O
We	O
therefore	O
went	O
;	O
&	O
our	O
first	O
stage	O
was	O
to	O
Wells	B-place
which	O
is	O
about	O
nineteen	O
miles	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
,	O
Clean	O
&	O
small	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
repair	O
&	O
order	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
&	O
presev	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
Glaſsonberry	B-place
Abbey	I-place
;	O
it	O
shows	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
moon	O
&	O
planets	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
are	O
s	O
ix	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
touching	O
a	O
spring	O
they	O
Gallop	O
round	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
reckon	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
peice	O
of	O
workmanship	O
&	O
is	O
about	O
seven	O
hundred	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
puppet	O
show	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
so	O
solemn	O
a	O
place	O
as	O
a	O
Cathedral	O
.	O
The	O
Bishop	O
's	O
palace	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
dismal	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
surrounded	O
by	O
a	O
high	O
stone	O
wall	O
&	O
a	O
moat	O
all	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
deanary	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
houses	O
in	O
Wells	B-place
&	O
some	O
very	O
Capital	O
ones	O
,	O
particularly	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tudway	I-pers
's	O
who	O
is	O
their	O
present	O
member	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Wookey	B-place
hole	I-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
miles	O
from	O
Wells	B-place
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Subteraneous	O
place	O
,	O
&	O
runs	O
for	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
und	O
a	O
mountain	O
,	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
it	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
quater	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
is	O
very	O
dangerous	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
along	O
a	O
path	O
in	O
some	O
places	O
not	O
a	O
foot	O
wide	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
a	O
precipice	O
,	O
of	O
at	O
leat	O
thirty	O
feet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
rapid	O
river	O
which	O
iſsues	O
from	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
can	O
better	O
feel	O
the	O
horror	O
I	O
felt	O
&	O
my	O
Dear	O
mother	O
least	O
his	O
foot	O
should	O
slip	O
than	O
I	O
discribe	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
guide	O
&	O
William	B-pers
,	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
hole	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
damp	O
&	O
therefore	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
yr	O
.	O
hum	O
ble	O
.	O
Sert	O
.	O
William	B-pers
&	O
our	O
guide	O
had	O
Candles	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
wonderful	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
water	O
as	O
it	O
drops	O
from	O
the	O
rocks	O
which	O
hung	O
over	O
our	O
heads	O
petrifies	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
spar	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
fine	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
they	O
Call	O
,	O
the	O
Witch	O
es	O
Chaldron	O
&	O
Furnace	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
bason	O
of	O
Water	O
two	O
feet	O
deep	O
&	O
about	O
fourteen	O
wide	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
is	O
the	O
Chaldron	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
vase	O
form	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
petrifaction	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
is	O
the	O
Furnace	O
;	O
their	O
are	O
other	O
petrifactions	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
the	O
old	O
Witch	O
herself	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
)	O
you	O
can	O
really	O
make	O
out	O
a	O
face	O
very	O
tolerably	O
,	O
their	O
is	O
another	O
which	O
forms	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
lion	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
Slippery	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
&	O
got	O
safe	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Father	O
setting	O
down	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
timber	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
an	O
Idea	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
so	O
dangerous	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
have	O
let	O
us	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
Wells	B-place
,	O
&	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
went	O
to	O
Bridgewater	B-place
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
ugly	O
dirty	O
Town	O
,	O
we	O
the	O
went	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
beautiful	O
Country	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
B.water	B-place
to	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
we	O
were	O
unlucky	O
in	O
the	O
weather	O
therefore	O
lost	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prospect	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
within	O
four	O
miles	O
of	O
Bristol	B-place
it	O
clear	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
discribe	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
prospect	O
,	O
the	O
City	B-place
of	I-place
Bristol	I-place
,	O
Clifton	B-place
the	O
hot	O
wells	O
&	O
the	O
river	O
runing	O
between	O
the	O
rocks	O
,	O
was	O
quite	O
inchanting	O
;	O
Bristol	B-place
is	O
a	O
very	O
populous	O
but	O
dirty	O
City	O
;	O
we	O
spent	O
one	O
very	O
pleasant	O
day	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Weare	I-pers
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
&	O
her	O
two	O
fine	O
children	O
.	O
Monday	O
Morn	O
:	O
My	O
Dear	O
Father	O
eat	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
dinner	O
yesterday	O
therefore	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
need	O
not	O
make	O
themselves	O
uneasy	O
about	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
perfect	O
recovery	O
than	O
ever	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
my	O
Father	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
paſs	O
'd	O
through	O
Bath	B-place
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Lime	B-place
in	O
Dorcetshire	B-place
not	O
meaning	O
to	O
stay	O
above	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
liked	O
my	O
Father	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
stay	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
a	O
fortnight	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
their	O
very	O
amiable	O
society	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Roman	O
Catholic	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
many	O
years	O
older	O
than	O
Her	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
sweet	O
temper	O
'd	O
man	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
your	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
;	O
but	O
so	O
Chearful	O
,	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
&	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
natural	O
lively	O
disposition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
an	O
interest	O
in	O
all	O
our	O
hearts	O
;	O
their	O
is	O
one	O
thing	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
after	O
your	O
marriage	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
your	O
very	O
affectionate	O
style	O
of	O
writing	O
brought	O
tears	O
into	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
s	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
that	O
very	O
letter	O
Now	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
&	O
shall	O
for	O
ever	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
yes	O
believe	O
me	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
must	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
for	O
ever	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
affectionate	O
remembrance	O
of	O
your	O
friends	O
,	O
our	O
happineſs	O
is	O
compleat	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
doubted	O
it	O
your	O
being	O
the	O
very	O
happy	O
woman	O
you	O
are	O
;	O
pray	O
tell	O
your	O
worthy	O
Father	O
&	O
sisters	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
mother	O
look	O
forward	O
With	O
pleasure	O
to	O
the	O
knowing	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Father	O
is	O
in	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
but	O
a	O
journey	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
will	O
make	O
him	O
very	O
happy	O
;	O
We	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
a	O
journey	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
,	O
since	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
uncertain	O
how	O
long	O
we	O
shall	O
stay	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
As	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
my	O
old	O
complaints	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
trying	O
the	O
waters	O
&	O
have	O
found	O
very	O
great	O
benefit	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
certainly	O
stay	O
this	O
month	O
out	O
;	O
&	O
in	O
our	O
return	O
home	O
shall	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
.	O
Our	O
Amiable	O
society	O
is	O
broke	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
have	O
left	O
us	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
a	O
very	O
amiable	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
us	O
to	O
morrow	O
;	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
General	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
who	O
came	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
reported	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
great	O
personal	O
courage	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
more	O
for	O
his	O
agreeableneſs	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good-	O
naturd	O
,	O
very	O
tall	O
,	O
&	O
next	O
to	O
a	O
degree	O
to	O
of	O
being	O
very	O
ugly	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
brother	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Harborough	I-pers
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Prattenton	I-pers
the	O
Miſstreſs	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
birth	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
pleasing	O
rather	O
pretty	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
&	O
person	O
&	O
equally	O
so	O
in	O
her	O
manners	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
universally	O
belov	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
who	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
delighted	O
with	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
should	O
like	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
our	O
Town	O
house	O
&	O
live	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
;	O
sin	O
ce	O
you	O
are	O
gone	O
,	O
their	O
is	O
no	O
one	O
I	O
should	O
regret	O
leaving	O
but	O
my	O
Dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
&	O
even	O
her	O
we	O
should	O
hope	O
to	O
tempt	O
&	O
come	O
&	O
be	O
wth	O
..	O
us	O
;	O
My	O
Father	O
has	O
many	O
old	O
friends	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
settled	O
,	O
particularly	O
Mr.	B-pers
Melmoth	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
schoolfellow	O
&	O
General	B-pers
Parsloe	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
polite	O
charming	O
man	O
,	O
his	O
age	O
is	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
eighty	O
seven	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
tour	O
with	O
his	O
daughter	O
&	O
grand	O
daughter	O
this	O
summer	O
,	O
of	O
five	O
hundred	O
miles	O
&	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
settled	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
which	O
is	O
says	O
is	O
the	O
nursery	O
for	O
old	O
age	O
,	O
their	O
is	O
likewise	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
yr	O
.	O
letter	O
likewise	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
&	O
mother	O
unite	O
their	O
kindest	O
&	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
our	O
dear	O
Ly	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
,	O
&	O
pray	O
remember	O
us	O
most	O
respectfully	O
to	O
Painshills	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
from	O
their	O
very	O
kind	O
behaviour	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
&	O
ever	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
we	O
have	O
already	O
a	O
great	O
affection	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
here	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
pump	O
room	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
for	O
sisters	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
leſs	O
than	O
twenty	O
six	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
am	O
taken	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
maid	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
be	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
unalterable	O
Affection	O
of	O
your	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickensons	I-pers
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
--	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
reasonable	O
long	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
&	O
tried	O
in	O
vain	O
for	O
a	O
frank	O
,	O
tell	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
think	O
letter	O
was	O
very	O
saucy	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
very	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
writes	O
so	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
beg	O
he	O
will	O
add	O
some	O
lines	O
in	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
write	O
,	O
he	O
boasts	O
of	O
preserving	O
his	O
dignity	O
,	O
his	O
letter	O
made	O
us	O
smile	O
,	O
I	O
declare	O
yrs	O
made	O
us	O
almost	O
cry	O
for	O
joy	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
M.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
Novr	O
:	O
12	O
th	O
1785	O
E.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
Septr	O
.	O
1785	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
Chesterfield	B-place
,	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
single	O
Sheet	O
