TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
only	O
attempt	O
adding	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
yours	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
's	O
safe	O
arrival	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sincerely	O
rejoice	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
deliver	O
the	O
enclosed	O
for	O
her	O
Royl	O
.	O
Hſs	O
.	O
from	O
whom	O
you	O
will	O
hear	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
CFinch	B-pers
Deal	B-place
Castle	I-place
June	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
