TOKEN	NE
October	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
1806	O
.	O
The	O
Hill	O
Top	O
--	O
near	O
Weobley	B-place
Herefordshire	B-place
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
ashamed	O
to	O
addreſs	O
you	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
account	O
in	O
various	O
ways	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
silence	O
,	O
by	O
explaining	O
plans	O
and	O
prospects	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
communicate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
instead	O
of	O
affording	O
matter	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
While	O
I	O
deferred	O
deferred	O
from	O
day	O
to	O
day	O
(	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
worst	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
)	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
took	O
place	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
notice	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
a	O
change	O
of	O
plan	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
,	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
engagement	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
is	O
renewed	O
for	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
remaining	O
there	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
transacted	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
England	B-place
;	O
but	O
on	O
reflection	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
over	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
busineſs	O
relative	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
we	O
wished	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
tenant	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
having	O
accepted	O
theatrical	O
engagements	O
,	O
made	O
it	O
uncertain	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
arrange	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
--	O
Now	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
chapter	O
of	O
grievances	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
the	O
former	O
period	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
fauſse	O
couche	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
ventured	O
upon	O
the	O
journey	O
and	O
voyage	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
succeeded	O
in	O
finding	O
a	O
tenant	O
;	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
,	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Dublin	B-place
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
firm	O
expectation	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
other	O
uneasineſses	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
you	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
is	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
separated	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
Pour	O
comble	O
de	O
malheur	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
lose	O
Mann	B-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
shortly	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
.	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
eligibly	O
established	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
rejoice	O
;	O
but	O
parting	O
from	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
eleven	O
years	O
'	O
tried	O
attachment	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
damps	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
I	O
should	O
otherwise	O
feel	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
kept	O
silence	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
,	O
as	O
write	O
such	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
lamentation	O
and	O
egotism	O
.	O
To	O
speak	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
entertaining	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
quite	O
lowered	O
by	O
one	O
croſs	O
circumstance	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
is	O
now	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
:	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
home	O
about	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
:	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
We	O
only	O
came	O
over	O
in	O
August	O
;	O
so	O
his	O
vacation	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
one	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
high	O
time	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
(	O
where	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
was	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
)	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
therefore	O
flatter	O
myself	O
your	O
health	O
has	O
not	O
needed	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
got	O
tired	O
of	O
Cheltenham	B-place
,	O
and	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
Do	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
recollect	O
they	O
shewed	O
no	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
Kindneſs	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
.	O
However	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
subjects	O
better	O
discuſsed	O
verbally	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
letter	O
--	O
if	O
worth	O
discuſsing	O
,	O
any	O
how	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
agree	O
,	O
admits	O
of	O
doubt	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
soon	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
my	O
seeming	O
negligence	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
here	O
some	O
months	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
movements	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
so	O
extremely	O
uncertain	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
surprised	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
arrangement	O
.	O
One	O
consolation	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
can	O
be	O
so	O
disagreeable	O
as	O
the	O
present	O
;	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
easily	O
understand	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
while	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
please	O
you	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
affectionately	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
practises	O
her	O
singing	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
almost	O
hesitate	O
sending	O
you	O
this	O
dull	O
scrawl	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
is	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
continued	O
appearance	O
of	O
inattention	O
.	O
Hoping	O
very	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
containing	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
most	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
senr	I-pers
:	I-pers
?	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
well	O
.	O
