TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1807	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
29	O
th	O
-	O
Janry	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
forgotten	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
replied	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
delay	O
in	O
answering	O
it	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
hope	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
whether	O
Ministerial	O
punishment	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
inflicted	O
on	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
on	O
my	O
Vanity	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
into	O
that	O
Secret	O
,	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
has	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
h	O
I	O
was	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
honoured	O
with	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Commands	O
,	O
as	O
Commiſsioner	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
Aſsembly	O
,	O
next	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
off	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
Febry-	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
your	O
s	O
L	O
reached	O
me	O
.	O
Several	O
Lords	O
are	O
talked	O
of	O
f	O
,	O
as	O
likely	O
to	O
get	O
that	O
Appointment	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Earls	O
of	O
Errol	B-pers
,	O
Leven	B-pers
,	O
Selkirk	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Semphill	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Lord	B-pers
Leven	I-pers
has	O
applied	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
both	O
conversed	O
&	O
corresponded	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
Enquiries	O
have	O
,	O
likewise	O
,	O
been	O
made	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
State	O
Liveries	O
are	O
shaped	O
,	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
discover	O
,	O
whether	O
this	O
Curiosity	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
Anxiety	O
of	O
the	O
Taylor	O
,	O
who	O
applied	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
a	O
Superior	O
.	O
Thus	O
far	O
I	O
have	O
lear	O
n't	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Taylor	O
who	O
called	O
on	O
my	O
Clothier	O
,	O
was	O
Foreman	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
employed	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Errol	I-pers
.	O
This	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
proves	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Report	O
circulated	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
ask	O
to	O
be	O
re-appointed	O
,	O
presuming	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
offended	O
at	O
the	O
manner	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
driven	O
from	O
Parliament	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
Childish	O
in	O
me	O
to	O
revenge	O
their	O
ill	O
treatment	O
on	O
myself	O
,	O
by	O
voluntarily	O
relinquishing	O
£1000	O
pr	O
Ann	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
Ministers	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
full	O
Credit	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
Me	O
.	O
The	O
Chequered	O
Votes	O
,	O
are	O
explained	O
thus	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
General	O
Election	O
,	O
Sixteen	O
Votes	O
to	O
give	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
thirty	O
Candidates	O
.	O
My	O
political	O
Inclinations	O
lean	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
Party	O
,	O
while	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
from	O
private	O
friendship	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
Individuals	O
of	O
the	O
Opposite	O
Party	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
This	O
disposes	O
of	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Votes	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
fourteen	O
,	O
or	O
fifteen	O
,	O
I	O
give	O
to	O
Candidates	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
party	O
.	O
Other	O
Peers	O
act	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
puts	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
knowing	O
how	O
a	O
General	O
Election	O
may	O
turn	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Votes	O
are	O
actually	O
given	O
.	O
Five	O
Votes	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
secured	O
my	O
Election	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Earls	O
of	O
Elgin	B-pers
,	O
Stair	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Roseberry	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Lords	O
Forbes	B-pers
,	O
Somerville	B-pers
&	O
Rollo	B-pers
deserted	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
carried	O
my	O
Election	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Opposition	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Ministers	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
's	O
name	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
having	O
aſsisted	O
at	O
the	O
demolition	O
of	O
a	O
Fort	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coast	O
of	O
his	O
France	B-place
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Imperieuse	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Cochrane	I-pers
.	O
They	O
have	O
lately	O
returned	O
from	O
their	O
Cruize	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Ship	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
docked	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
condole	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Cathcarts	O
have	O
put	O
on	O
their	O
Sables	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Event	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
equally	O
silent	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
They	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
Us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
mutually	O
exchange	O
Dinners	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
allow	O
any	O
Letters	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
ever	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Frank	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
numerous	O
Correspondence	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Franks	O
are	O
limited	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Parliament	O
,	O
can	O
conceive	O
the	O
Annoyance	O
of	O
being	O
tormented	O
with	O
Letters	O
inclosed	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
constant	O
source	O
of	O
trouble	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Servants	O
,	O
besides	O
having	O
very	O
frequently	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
paying	O
for	O
these	O
Packages	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
overweight	O
.	O
The	O
Lay	O
of	O
the	O
Last	O
Minstrel	O
must	O
please	O
Me	O
,	O
“	O
Ready	O
,	O
ay	O
Ready	O
”	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
Walter	O
Scott	O
(	O
1805	O
)	O
The	O
Lay	O
of	O
the	O
Last	O
Minstrel	O
,	O
Canto	O
IV	O
,	O
stanza	O
VIII	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
your	O
Goſsips	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
worst	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
Cathcart	O
Girls	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
handsome	O
,	O
&	O
four	O
Boys	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Greville	O
Mansfields	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
Stock	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
no	O
Questions	O
.	O
A	O
deputy	O
Grand	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Hatton	B-pers
,	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
's	O
,	O
General	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
's	O
by	O
his	O
third	O
Wife	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
is	O
perfectly	O
right	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
Exercise	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
neither	O
ride	O
,	O
nor	O
keep	O
riding	O
Horses	O
,	O
my	O
Miſses	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
tramp	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
seeming	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
particular	O
relish	O
for	O
going	O
an	O
Airing	O
in	O
the	O
Carriage	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
keep	O
Horses	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
are	O
hardly	O
ever	O
used	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
your	O
old	O
friend	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Beauvoir	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
is	O
defunct	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
no	O
more	O
come	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
than	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Japan	B-place
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
everything	O
kind	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
My	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
friend	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
