TOKEN	NE
Curzon	O
Street	O
--	O
Jany	O
.	O
12	O
--	O
1790	O
--	O
Both	O
your	O
last	O
Letters	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
have	O
been	O
round	O
to	O
Wherwell	B-place
,	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
came	O
very	O
succeſsfully	O
near	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
And	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
things	O
to	O
enclose	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
Frank	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
expecting	O
my	O
Uncle	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
However	O
as	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
immediately	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
delay	O
any	O
further	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
shall	O
travel	O
to	O
Him	O
at	O
Uppark	O
for	O
his	O
Signature	O
.	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Father	I-pers
still	O
continues	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
Prescription	O
with	O
great	O
Constancy	O
,	O
&	O
imputes	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
relief	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
Rhumatic	O
Twinges	O
&	O
Spasms	O
will	O
return	O
&	O
remind	O
him	O
during	O
this	O
damp	O
weather	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
still	O
so	O
helpleſs	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
lifting	O
his	O
Leg	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
rising	O
from	O
his	O
Chair	O
without	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
one	O
man	O
&	O
a	O
crutch	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Medical	O
People	O
persist	O
in	O
promising	O
a	O
certain	O
Recovery	O
,	O
tho	O
a	O
slow	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
nothing	O
now	O
has	O
been	O
recommended	O
or	O
applied	O
since	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
except	O
a	O
Bandage	O
.	O
His	O
Health	O
is	O
unimpaired	O
&	O
his	O
Spirits	O
rather	O
better	O
.	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Watkin	I-pers
attends	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
every	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
benefit	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
hoped	O
,	O
tho	O
her	O
Eyes	O
are	O
certainly	O
materially	O
better	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
gone	O
thro̅	O
much	O
Discipline	O
in	O
Blisters	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
Relapses	O
of	O
the	O
Complaint	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
does	O
not	O
trust	O
herself	O
to	O
read	O
or	O
write	O
&	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
considerate	O
in	O
You	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
temptation	O
of	O
answering	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
write	O
in	O
most	O
heartily	O
congratulating	O
you	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
instance	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
affectionate	O
generosity	O
in	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
present	O
poſeſsion	O
of	O
Taxal	B-place
Estate	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
imagine	O
the	O
great	O
agrément	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
&	O
the	O
Sensations	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
Parent	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
will	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
Reward	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
ever	O
be	O
carried	O
into	O
your	O
Neighborhood	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
inquire	O
You	O
out	O
.	O
A	O
Cottage	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Situation	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
You	O
describe	O
Your	O
's	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
my	O
delight	O
.	O
The	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Buxton	B-place
Baths	O
is	O
sometimes	O
urged	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
as	O
what	O
He	O
would	O
find	O
an	O
effectual	O
Restorative	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
Your	O
Abode	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
distant	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
doubt	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
unlikely	O
we	O
should	O
go	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
has	O
no	O
little	O
pleasure	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Place	O
except	O
Wherwell	B-place
.	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
has	O
indeed	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
tedious	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
suspect	O
an	O
alarming	O
Illneſs	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
given	O
out	O
as	O
a	O
Rhumatic	O
fever	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Dr-	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
has	O
all	O
along	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
;	O
But	O
two	O
other	O
Conjectures	O
have	O
spread	O
,	O
the	O
Insanity	O
which	O
you	O
mention	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Scrophulous	O
Nature	O
in	O
the	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
is	O
more	O
believed	O
than	O
the	O
former	O
because	O
only	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
&	O
Dr-	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
attend	O
;	O
&	O
an	O
Old	O
Apothecary	O
whom	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Wal	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
employed	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
is	O
not	O
suffered	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
never	O
quits	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
every	O
way	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
pitied	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
her	O
once	O
,	O
&	O
found	O
her	O
divided	O
between	O
Hope	O
&	O
Fear	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
particulars	O
.	O
Lately	O
,	O
our	O
Daily	O
answers	O
to	O
Enquiries	O
have	O
said	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
mending	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
way	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
It	O
was	O
altered	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
expreſs	O
that	O
She	O
continued	O
without	O
alteration	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
was	O
here	O
one	O
evening	O
,	O
lively	O
&	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
Entertainments	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
Ladies	O
.	O
The	O
Young	O
Montagues	O
have	O
three	O
Children	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs-	B-pers
I——	I-pers
can	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
arrival	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
notion	O
it	O
was	O
lately	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
You	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Quipos	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Louisa	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
who	O
is	O
still	O
at	O
Weymouth	B-place
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
expect	O
her	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
well	O
again	O
since	O
this	O
series	O
of	O
damp	O
weather	O
.	O
--	O
How	O
good	O
You	O
are	O
,	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
too	O
to	O
remember	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Stomach	O
too	O
so	O
kindly	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
been	O
remarkably	O
well	O
,	O
more	O
free	O
from	O
Heartburn	O
&	O
it	O
's	O
attendants	O
than	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
;	O
owing	O
I	O
think	O
to	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
's	O
perseverence	O
in	O
Lua	O
&	O
seltzer	O
Water	O
.	O
If	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
wants	O
to	O
grow	O
Strong	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
confidence	O
in	O
my	O
Skill	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
owe	O
him	O
some	O
advice	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
whenever	O
He	O
likes	O
to	O
apply	O
.	O
--	O
Your	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
is	O
married	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
your	O
account	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
other	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
prospect	O
for	O
permanent	O
Happineſs	O
;	O
Not	O
so	O
,	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Mornington	I-pers
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Fitzroy	I-pers
,	O
now	O
;	O
He	O
is	O
Lord	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
's	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Son	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
quite	O
£400	O
p	O
ann	O
.	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
worse	O
than	O
all	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mauvais	O
Sujet	O
.	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
&	O
Duch	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
have	O
been	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
Knowle	B-place
,	O
entertaining	O
200	O
Poor	O
People	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
their	O
Hall	O
;	O
the	O
best	O
sort	O
of	O
Féte	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
fine	O
example	O
.	O
--	O
London	B-place
is	O
full	O
of	O
French	O
Fugitives	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
Madame	B-pers
De	I-pers
Boufleurs	I-pers
,	O
Mistreſs	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
de	I-pers
Conti	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Ducheſse	B-pers
de	I-pers
Beron	I-pers
&	O
many	O
more	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Duc	I-pers
d'Orlean	I-pers
's	I-pers
has	O
bro't	O
over	O
with	O
him	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Buffon	I-pers
,	O
Daughter	O
in	O
law	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Naturalist	O
;	O
It	O
is	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
has	O
made	O
her	O
great	O
offers	O
,	O
but	O
She	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
Contempt	O
.	O
We	O
lead	O
a	O
quiet	O
Country	O
life	O
in	O
Curzon	O
Street	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
come	O
to	O
us	O
every	O
evening	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
suffered	O
much	O
Rhumatic	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
Vellum	O
Writing	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
advised	O
I	O
bought	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
famous	O
for	O
making	O
it	O
.	O
Little	O
Catharine	B-pers
grows	O
monstrously	O
fast	O
,	O
has	O
just	O
now	O
got	O
a	O
Sneezing	O
Cold	O
,	O
otherwise	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
She	O
sends	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
remembers	O
her	O
perfectly	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
You	O
many	O
happy	O
returns	O
of	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Janry	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
Yrs-	O
Sincerely	O
obliged	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
E.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
Midhurst	B-place
January	O
thirteen	O
1790	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Free	O
BLethieullier	B-pers
