TOKEN	NE
Weymouth	B-place
Jany	O
:	O
28	O
th	O
:	O
1787	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Sir	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
,	O
Myself	O
&	O
all	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
congratulate	O
you	O
&	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
(	O
&	O
ourselves	O
)	O
most	O
sincerely	O
on	O
the	O
good	O
News	O
,	O
this	O
Post	O
has	O
brought	O
us	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
safely	O
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
&	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Dr	O
:	O
little	O
Infant	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
:	O
I	O
pray	O
,	O
They	O
may	O
continue	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
Line	O
soon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
They	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
intreat	O
as	O
an	O
Old	O
Nurse	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
will	O
keep	O
herself	O
quiet	O
.	O
Our	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
pray	O
kiſs	O
your	O
little	O
Daughter	O
for	O
Me	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
your	O
Dear	O
Wife	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
:	O
Sir	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
(	O
with	O
sincere	O
Regard	O
)	O
&	O
rejoicing	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
present	O
Happineſs	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
much	O
Obliged	O
PCremorne	B-pers
I	O
wd	O
:	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
fly	O
&	O
just	O
peep	O
at	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
little	O
One	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
my	O
Julia	B-pers
is	O
rather	O
better	O
to	O
Day	O
;	O
In	O
one	O
point	O
,	O
materially	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
--	O
but	O
if	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
recd	O
.	O
it	O
my	O
Letter	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
might	O
make	O
her	O
low	O
just	O
now	O
--	O
pray	O
Dr	O
:	O
Sir	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
one	O
Line	O
soon	O
.	O
M	O
I	O
too	O
must	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
heartily	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
happineſs	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
addition	O
to	O
your	O
Family	O
;	O
&	O
upon	O
the	O
favourable	O
state	O
I	O
hope	O
this	O
will	O
find	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
slobber	O
h	O
er	O
Baby	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
most	O
hearty	O
wishes	O
for	O
her	O
safe	O
&	O
early	O
Recovery	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
every	O
species	O
of	O
happineſs	O
you	O
wish	O
for	O
I	O
remain	O
sincerely	O
Your	O
's	O
W.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
begs	O
his	O
best	O
respects	O
,	O
&	O
flatters	O
himself	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
leading	O
up	O
a	O
Country-Dance	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
amiable	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
about	O
this	O
day	O
fourteen	O
years	O
--	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Esqr=	I-pers
Post	O
House	O
WEYMOUTH	B-place
Viscounteſs	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
28	O
th	O
Janry	O
1787	O
