TOKEN	NE
20	O
July	O
1789	O
--	O
Bath	B-place
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
to	O
Lincom	B-place
Spa	I-place
where	O
we	O
drank	O
Tea	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
with	O
your	O
dear	O
friends	O
every	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
--	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
You	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
mentioned	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
before	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
Miſs	O
Basta	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
an	O
Irishman	O
--	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
Match	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
that	O
turned	O
out	O
better	O
--	O
he	O
poſseſses	O
enormous	O
merit	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
his	O
attentions	O
are	O
delightful	O
&	O
seem	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
heart	O
--	O
She	O
doats	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
their	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
married	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
gives	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
Caracter	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Square	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
intimate	O
wh-	O
this	O
family	O
--	O
21/	O
I	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
Drank	O
Tea	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
(	O
who	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
sent	O
her	O
Cards	O
of	O
Thanks	O
)	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
relapse	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
the	O
next	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
enquiries	O
--	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
talkg	O
to	O
the	O
Servant	O
Miſs	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
heard	O
my	O
Voice	O
&	O
sent	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
my	O
admittance	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
contrive	O
it	O
--	O
She	O
seemed	O
greatly	O
distreſsed	O
as	O
She	O
had	O
given	O
up	O
all	O
expectations	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
's	O
recovery	O
who	O
's	O
disorder	O
is	O
an	O
inflammation	O
upon	O
her	O
Lungs	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
constantly	O
&	O
has	O
scarce	O
ever	O
taken	O
her	O
clothes	O
off	O
--	O
&	O
seems	O
quite	O
worn	O
to	O
a	O
Shadow	O
--	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
she	O
will	O
suffer	O
materially	O
in	O
her	O
health	O
whether	O
her	O
Mother	O
dies	O
or	O
recovers	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
20	O
minutes	O
&	O
left	O
a	O
Lady	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
(	O
She	O
sent	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
)	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	I-pers
where	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
9	O
oClock	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
have	O
taken	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
Season	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
call	O
it	O
Summer	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
&	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Methuen	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
promised	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Methuen	I-pers
's	O
--	O
22/	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
by	O
appointment	O
&	O
found	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
ye-	B-pers
2d	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Isted	I-pers
--	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
10	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Tete	O
a	O
tete	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
eleven	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
Jellies	O
&	O
biscuits	O
for	O
our	O
supper	O
--	O
She	O
spoke	O
of	O
young	O
Mr.	B-pers
Locke	I-pers
s	O
extraordinary	O
Genius	O
for	O
painting	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
sketches	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Master	O
--	O
but	O
had	O
had	O
very	O
great	O
advantages	O
from	O
his	O
Eye	O
being	O
accustomed	O
from	O
his	O
earliest	O
infancy	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
Models	O
&	O
the	O
finest	O
paintings	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Locke	I-pers
told	O
her	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Rome	B-place
&	O
only	O
4	O
Year	O
's	O
old	O
he	O
shewed	O
a	O
predilection	O
for	O
fine	O
statues	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
stood	O
gazing	O
at	O
for	O
hours	O
--	O
his	O
Taste	O
was	O
formed	O
so	O
early	O
that	O
every	O
figure	O
he	O
draws	O
is	O
beautiful	O
from	O
its	O
perfect	O
symmetry	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
young	O
his	O
natural	O
turn	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
horrid	O
subjects	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
described	O
--	O
the	O
subject	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
invention	O
entirely	O
--	O
a	O
witch	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
killed	O
a	O
woman	O
&	O
her	O
two	O
Children	O
in	O
a	O
Cottage	O
--	O
the	O
poor	O
Husband	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
home	O
is	O
suffered	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
each	O
arm	O
which	O
hang	O
in	O
delightful	O
attitudes	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
agonies	O
grasps	O
his	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
seems	O
totally	O
insensible	O
of	O
&	O
he	O
appears	O
to	O
stand	O
petrified	O
with	O
horror	O
or	O
grief	O
--	O
the	O
Witch	O
was	O
finely	O
described	O
with	O
a	O
bloody	O
dagger	O
in	O
each	O
hand	O
seeming	O
to	O
tread	O
on	O
Air	O
and	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
horrid	O
Scenes	O
with	O
an	O
Air	O
of	O
Diabolical	O
Exultation	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
so	O
exquisitely	O
finished	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
made	O
an	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
his	O
mind	O
&	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
luckily	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
violently	O
agitated	O
Spirits	O
--	O
for	O
he	O
fancied	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Scene	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
described	O
paſs	O
before	O
him	O
in	O
reality	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
to	O
raise	O
his	O
Spirits	O
&	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
till	O
he	O
he	O
fell	O
aſleep	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
that	O
his	O
Fancy	O
,	O
Taste	O
&	O
Execution	O
can	O
hardly	O
be	O
equalled	O
--	O
She	O
mentioned	O
several	O
little	O
anecdotes	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
recollect	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
expelling	O
ye-	O
Ennui	O
when	O
yr-	O
pauvre	O
mari	O
returns	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
23/	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
this	O
morning	O
with	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
&	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
delight	O
of	O
receiving	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
Yes	O
my	O
dearest	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
's	O
--	O
&	O
go	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
you	O
desire	O
or	O
can	O
wish	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
&	O
how	O
dear	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
--	O
best	O
of	O
Women	O
What	O
a	O
Gadabout	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
is	O
become	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
amused	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
admire	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
attention	O
to	O
her	O
Dormouse	O
with	O
what	O
eagerneſs	O
she	O
will	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
papa	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
her	O
something	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
most	O
acceptable	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Tho	O
the	O
conduct	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
W——	I-pers
may	O
appear	O
unkind	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
on	O
many	O
Accts	O
.	O
justifiable	O
&	O
even	O
right	O
--	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
shew	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
zealous	O
friend	O
to	O
government	O
without	O
exerting	O
his	O
influence	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
in	O
its	O
behalf	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
supposed	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
firmness	O
of	O
Character	O
--	O
but	O
in	O
weak	O
minds	O
there	O
is	O
generally	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
the	O
greatest	O
degree	O
of	O
opiniatrete	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
mean	O
entirely	O
to	O
direct	O
that	O
Idea	O
to	O
him	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
sense	O
&	O
parts	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Levity	O
&	O
some	O
thing	O
Hamiltonian	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
the	O
expreſsion	O
--	O
in	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
a	O
complete	O
Medley	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
an	O
attachment	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
should	O
receive	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
an	O
opporty	O
of	O
manifesting	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
generally	O
liked	O
--	O
which	O
a	O
proud	O
,	O
reserved	O
Man	O
can	O
never	O
be	O
--	O
if	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
acts	O
from	O
patriotism	O
he	O
is	O
right	O
--	O
or	O
if	O
he	O
looks	O
forwards	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Children	O
's	O
interest	O
he	O
is	O
right	O
to	O
shew	O
himself	O
an	O
active	O
friend	O
--	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
acts	O
from	O
personal	O
resentment	O
or	O
caprice	O
I	O
should	O
condemn	O
him	O
--	O
How	O
perfectly	O
I	O
see	O
our	O
dear	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
looking	O
&	O
talking	O
over	O
the	O
alterations	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
&	O
how	O
busy	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
Idea	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
love	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
dont	O
wonder	O
that	O
my	O
Mary	B-pers
is	O
the	O
first	O
upon	O
her	O
List	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
24/	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Masters	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
for	O
reasons	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
explain	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
writing	O
Italian	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
7	O
hours	O
without	O
intermiſsion	O
except	O
a	O
visit	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
½	O
hour	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
at	O
7	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye-	B-pers
Vanbrughs	I-pers
,	O
&	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
large	O
party	O
of	O
Humdrums	O
&	O
tittering	O
Miſses	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyed	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
invited	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
--	O
also	O
Lord	B-pers
Scarborō	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Bosnet	B-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
seems	O
to	O
have	O
drank	O
his	O
senses	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
talked	O
an	O
abundance	O
of	O
Nonsense	O
,	O
in	O
so	O
low	O
a	O
tone	O
of	O
Voice	O
&	O
so	O
slow	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
kept	O
alive	O
all	O
one	O
's	O
attention	O
to	O
gueſs	O
even	O
at	O
his	O
meaning	O
but	O
his	O
engroſsing	O
all	O
the	O
conversation	O
made	O
me	O
wiſh	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
wont	O
say	O
where	O
--	O
but	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
--	O
our	O
conversation	O
was	O
stupid	O
--	O
at	O
ten	O
une	O
Table	O
service	O
avec	O
une	O
tres	O
jolie	O
petite	O
Soupe	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
--	O
upon	O
Castors	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
was	O
wheeled	O
to	O
it	O
&	O
we	O
all	O
took	O
our	O
places	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
seized	O
upon	O
the	O
Leg	O
of	O
chicken	O
than	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
began	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
ridiculous	O
story	O
about	O
his	O
refusing	O
to	O
say	O
Goose	O
when	O
a	O
Child	O
&	O
his	O
punishment	O
for	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
disobedience	O
--	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
changes	O
of	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
spelling	O
Go-go-Goo-goo-Goose-	O
D	O
oose	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
on	O
with	O
Do-D	O
:	O
oo	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
burst	O
&	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
Table	O
--	O
&	O
give	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
violent	O
fit	O
of	O
laughing	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
could	O
hardly	O
support	O
her	O
herself	O
&	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
made	O
faces	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
sat	O
staring	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
Sang	O
froid	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
clenched	O
except	O
one	O
solitary	O
finger	O
which	O
was	O
alternately	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
one	O
Eye	O
or	O
his	O
mouth	O
--	O
this	O
ridiculous	O
story	O
continued	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
eleven	O
we	O
all	O
came	O
away	O
&	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
usual	O
custom	O
--	O
w	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
sober	O
--	O
25/	O
I	O
am	O
all	O
alive	O
&	O
in	O
excellent	O
Spirits	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
lea	O
f	O
v	O
e	O
to	O
conclude	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
me	O
lately	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
back	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
--	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
that	O
Bathing	O
increased	O
my	O
Irritation	O
&	O
shattered	O
my	O
Nerves	O
my	O
appetite	O
was	O
gone	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tightneſs	O
&	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
from	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
inferred	O
that	O
my	O
health	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
retrograde	O
Motion	O
--	O
I	O
hastened	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
resolution	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
to	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
Fothergills	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
luckily	O
found	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
thrō	O
the	O
Cerimony	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
&	O
pulse	O
&	O
c	O
questions	O
&	O
Answers	O
--	O
The	O
Dr	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
Antemonials	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
so	O
well	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
Acids	O
which	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
try	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
degree	O
of	O
heat	O
of	O
the	O
Bath	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
properly	O
regulated	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
heat	O
of	O
the	O
Atmosphere	O
--	O
the	O
water	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
bathed	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
many	O
degrees	O
too	O
warm	O
--	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
&	O
take	O
an	O
Emetic	O
directly	O
which	O
I	O
d	O
id	O
but	O
no	O
Bile	O
appeared	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Acid	O
--	O
which	O
had	O
almost	O
an	O
immediate	O
Effect	O
--	O
for	O
since	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
Itching	O
which	O
was	O
become	O
intolerable	O
has	O
to	O
almost	O
totally	O
been	O
asleep	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
Complaisance	O
to	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
friendly	O
Adieu	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
Bath	O
--	O
my	O
appetite	O
returned	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
&	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
thank	O
the	O
Dr	O
.	O
for	O
having	O
made	O
me	O
so	O
happy	O
--	O
I	O
may	O
use	O
that	O
Expreſsion	O
--	O
as	O
lowneſs	O
of	O
Spirits	O
creates	O
real	O
Misery	O
--	O
for	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Martyr	O
--	O
sees	O
Devils	O
of	O
all	O
Colors	O
&	O
shapes	O
dancing	O
before	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
such	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
en	O
train	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
to	O
Fo-	B-pers
thergill	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
persuade	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Fee	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
“	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
attribute	O
to	O
old	O
Freindship	O
”	O
--	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Thursday	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Now	O
for	O
another	O
matter	O
--	O
p	O
b	O
ut	O
first	O
I	O
must	O
kiſs	O
your	O
fair	O
hand	O
&	O
lead	O
you	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
Monday	O
when	O
a	O
Gnat	O
had	O
the	O
impertinence	O
to	O
feast	O
upon	O
my	O
Leg	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
other	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
presumption	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
resolution	O
not	O
to	O
touch	O
the	O
polluted	O
part	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
wore	O
my	O
Boots	O
all	O
day	O
&	O
at	O
night	O
found	O
my	O
Leg	O
violently	O
inflamed	O
&	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
swelling	O
rubbed	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
applied	O
spirits	O
of	O
Wine	O
&	O
water	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
without	O
Effect	O
--	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morng	O
Dr.	B-pers
F——	I-pers
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
&	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Aperient	O
&	O
to	O
save	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Kind	O
of	O
Salt	O
,	O
very	O
powerful	O
in	O
the	O
Diuretic	O
way	O
--	O
&	O
thrō	O
the	O
whole	O
proceſs	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
unpleasant	O
of	O
any	O
operation	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
I	O
ever	O
experienced	O
--	O
The	O
Dr	O
.	O
said	O
--	O
the	O
inflammation	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
's	O
having	O
forced	O
the	O
Bile	O
to	O
the	O
Surface	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
--	O
on	O
weds	O
Dr.	B-pers
F——	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
poultice	O
to	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
&	O
kept	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Leg	O
till	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
place	O
healed	O
--	O
Now	O
Madam	O
you	O
may	O
Acct	O
.	O
for	O
my	O
poor	O
Legs	O
having	O
a	O
Holliday	O
,	O
&	O
may	O
also	O
suppose	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
returned	O
to	O
their	O
usual	O
occupation	O
of	O
capering	O
&	O
kicking	O
at	O
every	O
obstacle	O
--	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
kind	O
note	O
to	O
say	O
“	O
the	O
Gates	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
should	O
be	O
thrown	O
open	O
to	O
receive	O
so	O
renowned	O
a	O
Knight	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Vanity	O
to	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
disappointment	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Thursday	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
go	O
to	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
the	O
first	O
day	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Boot	O
--	O
I	O
repeated	O
the	O
offer	O
of	O
a	O
Fee	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
which	O
he	O
again	O
refused	O
--	O
however	O
I	O
will	O
tender	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
which	O
he	O
probably	O
will	O
not	O
accept	O
--	O
he	O
seems	O
pleased	O
with	O
being	O
consulted	O
by	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
scribble	O
to	O
you	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
happy	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
--	O
I	O
fancy	O
that	O
my	B-pers
dearest	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
often	O
visits	O
“	O
Iza	O
's	O
own	O
pitty	O
vole	O
”	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
often	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
feild	O
with	O
Grandpapa	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
one	O
fair	O
day	O
day	O
since	O
monday	O
,	O
&	O
enjoy	O
ourselves	O
every	O
Evening	O
over	O
a	O
snug	O
fire	O
--	O
pray	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
recipe	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Chartreuse	O
pie	O
--	O
in	O
return	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
pie	O
that	O
will	O
please	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Now	O
dont	O
be	O
figitty	O
about	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
every	O
day	O
complimented	O
upon	O
my	O
good	O
Looks	O
&	O
never	O
felt	O
my	O
self	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
agreeably	O
employed	O
in	O
subscribing	O
myself	O
,	O
my	O
charming	O
wife	O
's	O
affectionate	O
&	O
faithful	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Kiſses	O
in	O
abundance	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
J——D——	B-pers
--	O
&	O
Love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
25	O
th	O
July	O
Saturday	O
My	O
return	O
must	O
now	O
depend	O
upon	O
Ampa	B-pers
--	O
My	O
leg	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
To	O
Dr.	B-pers
F——	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	O
le	O
frith	O
X	O
post	O
}	O
Derbyshire	O
