TOKEN	NE
December	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Dickenson	B-pers
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
a	O
common	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
having	O
called	O
on	O
you	O
or	O
receiving	O
you	O
&	O
Gl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
when	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
Cold	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
forms	O
&	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
deigned	O
to	O
retire	O
back	O
in	O
dignified	O
leisure	O
.	O
however	O
my	O
light	O
Spirits	O
annoy	O
his	O
rear	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
no	O
vestige	O
of	O
the	O
Enemy	O
will	O
long	O
remain	O
--	O
As	O
to	O
dining	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
relapse	O
wch	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
apprehend	O
I	O
shall	O
dine	O
Saturday	O
with	O
my	O
Family	O
near	O
Southn	B-place
.	I-place
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
my	O
Sister	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
thought	O
myself	O
ill.	O
--	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
otherwise	O
I	O
should	O
most	O
gladly	O
have	O
accepted	O
your	O
Invitation	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
congratulate	O
you	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
on	O
the	O
happy	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
speedy	O
prospect	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
united	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
such	O
as	O
a	O
wise	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
indulgent	O
Parent	O
would	O
desire	O
as	O
a	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
Pray	O
aſsure	O
Gl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
that	O
I	O
regret	O
very	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
miſs	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
fail	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
The	O
American	O
news	O
was	O
indeed	O
most	O
unexpected	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
gave	O
the	O
despicable	O
nation	O
any	O
Credit	O
their	O
unworthy	O
vain	O
boasting	O
(	O
knowing	O
what	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
)	O
would	O
have	O
anihilated	O
it	O
fully	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
too	O
much	O
liberty	O
to	O
plague	O
us	O
again	O
.	O
With	O
best	O
Afft	O
.	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Daughter	O
I	O
am	O
Always	O
yours	O
Warwick	B-pers
J.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
