TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
May	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
or	O
25	O
th	O
instant	O
at	O
furthest	O
so	O
if	O
you	O
get	O
no	O
other	O
letter	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
me	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
when	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
well	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
dinner	O
you	O
'll	O
excuse	O
me	O
ſaying	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
most	O
Affctly-	O
Napier	B-pers
