TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
30	O
th	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1780	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
very	O
readily	O
have	O
obeyed	O
your	O
Orders	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
your	O
books	O
had	O
your	O
letter	O
reached	O
me	O
before	O
my	O
departure	O
from	O
Welwyn	B-place
.	O
They	O
are	O
however	O
safely	O
locked	O
up	O
at	O
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
&	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
Quarters	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
pleased	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
I	O
expect	O
You	O
will	O
summons	O
him	O
to	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
devouring	O
your	O
hot	O
Rolls	O
when	O
I	O
next	O
pay	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
admiring	O
your	O
presumption	O
in	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
You	O
stood	O
very	O
high	O
in	O
my	O
Esteem	O
.	O
Indeed	O
Miſs	O
I	O
never	O
recollect	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
so	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Sisters	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
preparing	O
Caps	O
&	O
Frocks	O
for	O
a	O
Young	O
Gentleman	O
or	O
Young	O
Lady	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
its	O
appearance	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Months	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Miſs	B-pers
L——	I-pers
.	O
The	O
meeting	O
was	O
unexpected	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
tenth	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Minute	O
I	O
felt	O
more	O
ridiculo	O
us	O
than	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Wheth	O
er	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
howev	O
er	O
I	O
was	O
received	O
with	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
regard	O
which	O
I	O
confeſs	O
pleased	O
me	O
greatly	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
Girl	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
probability	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
introduce	O
you	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
happiest	O
day	O
s	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
affectionate	O
Wishes	O
ever	O
attend	O
You	O
N——	B-pers
The	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
has	O
declared	O
himself	O
a	O
Candidate	O
at	O
our	O
Election	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
talked	O
of	O
as	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
received	O
any	O
application	O
from	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Duke	O
makes	O
a	O
figure	O
in	O
Parliament	O
,	O
no	O
man	O
need	O
despair	O
--	O
