TOKEN	NE
9	O
th	O
May	O
1782	O
Thursday	O
Morng	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
me	O
my	O
dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
look	O
exactly	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Poland	O
Hens	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
why	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
first	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
once	O
a	O
Friend	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
I	O
trust	O
an	O
Angel	O
in	O
Heaven	O
.	O
)	O
who	O
in	O
the	O
simplicity	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
began	O
a	O
Letter	O
once	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
by	O
the	O
“	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
my	O
merciful	O
God	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
very	O
“	O
great	O
comfort	O
&	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
“	O
continued	O
he	O
,	O
how	O
happy	O
this	O
News	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
&	O
c	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
like	O
my	O
good	O
Friend	O
in	O
thinking	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
Cold	O
as	O
makes	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
now	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
minded	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
Cold	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
has	O
vexed	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
hinders	O
me	O
from	O
paying	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
One	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
would	O
wish	O
to	O
shew	O
every	O
Respect	O
--	O
this	O
Respect	O
,	O
as	O
Madme	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
says	O
,	O
of	O
outward	O
form	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
that	O
Respect	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
--	O
which	O
those	O
must	O
feel	O
,	O
who	O
honor	O
&	O
respect	O
revere	O
Virtue	O
&	O
goodneſs	O
:	O
this	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
better	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
herself	O
for	O
the	O
reason	O
s	O
Madme	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
gives	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
must	O
remember	O
.	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
seeing	O
those	O
Virtues	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
without	O
being	O
impreſsed	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
profiting	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
by	O
them	O
--	O
My	O
cold	O
lies	O
in	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
dreſsed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
feather	O
Tippet	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
warmest	O
of	O
all	O
warm	O
things	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
aſsured	O
will	O
cure	O
me	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
that	O
make	O
my	O
Resemblance	O
to	O
my	O
prety	O
poland	O
Hen	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
She	O
becomes	O
her	O
bustling	O
feathers	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
Evg	O
:	O
&	O
only	O
Mrs.-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
some	O
very	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
so	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
look	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
sd	O
:	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
--	O
believe	O
me	O
Yrs	O
..	O
sincerely	O
PDartrey	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	B-place
:	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
--	O
