TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
just	O
add	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
has	O
a	O
Rash	O
,	O
since	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
his	B-pers
Royl	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
is	O
perfectly	O
well	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
Hawkins	B-pers
says	O
it	O
will	O
rather	O
be	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
otherwise	O
.	O
The	O
Uneasineſs	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Friday	O
was	O
probably	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Rash	O
being	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
Ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
I	O
made	O
out	O
all	O
my	O
News	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
for	O
her	O
Letter	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
.	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
Decbr	O
:	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
1780	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
