TOKEN	NE
My	O
Drst	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Charity	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
this	O
Eveng	O
:	O
Ld.-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Richd	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
&	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
--	O
we	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
why	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
--	O
only	O
come	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
--	O
tell	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
I	O
entreat	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
Favor	O
--	O
never	O
mind	O
dreſs	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
my	O
Dormeuse	O
--	O
in	O
haste	O
Yrs	O
:	O
most	O
truly	O
PD	B-pers
you	O
shall	O
not	O
stay	O
late	O
--	O
pray	O
come	O
if	O
you	O
poſsibly	O
can	O
--	O
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
&	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
sad	O
Cold	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
James	O
St	O
:	O
Wesm	B-place
:	I-place
