TOKEN	NE
Friday	O
23	O
d	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Got	O
up	O
early	O
&	O
had	O
my	O
head	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
read	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
in	O
Horace	B-pers
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
&	O
an	O
a	O
few	O
extracts	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
her	O
mother	O
in	O
law	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
was	O
a	O
farewell	O
visit	O
as	O
she	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
set	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
She	O
said	O
many	O
friendly	O
things	O
--	O
hop	O
'd	O
to	O
share	O
my	O
friendship	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
visit	O
them	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
made	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
flying	O
visits	O
--	O
At	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
besides	O
us	O
.	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
lively	O
&	O
sensible	O
--	O
--	O
Severe	O
strictures	O
were	O
paſs	O
'd	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
s	O
conduct	O
--	O
many	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
the	O
follies	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Affronts	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
in	O
her	O
Canvaſs	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
A	O
judgement	O
was	O
also	O
paſs	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
Verses	O
wch	O
were	O
pronounced	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
indifferent	O
&	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
to	O
merit	O
ye	O
.	O
applause	O
some	O
people	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
Lady	B-pers
Rushworth	I-pers
came	O
in	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
wth	O
..	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Napiers	O
then	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
where	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
join	O
them	O
.	O
Met	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dumfries	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bland	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hervey	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Peachals	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Johnston	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hervey	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Radnor	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Georgiana	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bulkley	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
past	O
9	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
too	O
much	O
engaged	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
&	O
expected	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
.	O
many	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
speeches	O
from	O
&	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
&	O
me	O
--	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
private	O
audience	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
day	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Leveé	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Majesty	O
sometime	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
gracious	O
--	O
he	O
represented	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
advanced	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Army	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
s	O
before	O
10	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
followed	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
&	O
Preſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hand	O
at	O
parting	O
&	O
said	O
many	O
truly	O
affectionate	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
heard	O
she	O
w	O
as	O
better	O
.	O
My	O
servt	O
.	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Chair	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
numerous	O
party	O
of	O
Belle	O
&	O
Beaux	O
Esprits	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Aſaph	I-pers
--	O
(	O
Shipley	B-pers
)	O
relative	O
to	O
Hume	B-pers
&	O
his	O
opinions	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Bishop	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Hume	B-pers
took	O
pains	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Atheist	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
an	O
English	O
Divine	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
--	O
Publish	O
'd	O
a	O
Book	O
against	O
ye	O
.	O
probability	O
of	O
Hell	O
torments	O
--	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
had	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Book	O
&	O
was	O
so	O
impatient	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
England	B-place
for	O
it	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
times	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
printed	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
this	O
shew	O
how	O
anxious	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
future	O
punishment	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Conversation	O
with	O
other	O
People	O
.	O
Voltaire	B-pers
invited	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
a	O
Visit	O
this	O
Summer	O
at	O
Farnborough	B-place
--	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
way	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
s	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
alone	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
.	O
Saturday	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
had	O
Breakfasted	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
s	O
late	O
Housekeeper	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
meſsage	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
time	O
to	O
converse	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
sometime	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cowslade	I-pers
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
Bishopstone	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
after	O
him	O
she	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
serious	O
&	O
religious	O
Conversation	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Brighouse	I-pers
s	O
Steward	O
came	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Rent	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
had	O
Sr-	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
her	O
father	O
s	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
enclosed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Diary	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
ye	O
.	O
Painter	O
to	O
bring	O
home	O
Opie	B-pers
s	O
Portrait	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
retouch	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Opie	B-pers
would	O
sit	O
once	O
more	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Opie	B-pers
made	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
above	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
&	O
amused	O
myself	O
with	O
observing	O
ye	O
.	O
various	O
countenances	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Paſsengers	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
their	O
House	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
next	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
stay	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
return	O
to	O
Town	B-place
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
days	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Son	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Abroad	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
early	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
us	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
till	O
near	O
6	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
room	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
wrote	O
notes	O
of	O
excuse	O
for	O
my	O
engagements	O
from	O
next	O
Wed	O
:	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
enquired	O
how	O
his	O
affairs	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
commiſsions	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Saw	O
Wm.Benn	B-pers
--	O
(	O
ye	O
.	O
political	O
Apothecary	O
)	O
--	O
whom	O
we	O
employ	O
--	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
our	O
Housemaid	O
who	O
is	O
ill	O
&	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
had	O
gain	O
'd	O
18	O
Votes	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
sad	O
riotous	O
doings	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Hustings	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
--	O
is	O
a	O
violent	O
opposer	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
Brother	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Poet	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
8	O
oClock	O
Churchill	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
came	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
trio	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Characters	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
ye	O
.	O
Shipley	O
's	O
--	O
Queen	B-pers
made	O
very	O
sensible	O
remarks	O
on	O
the	O
Conduct	O
Parents	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
towards	O
their	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
vice	O
versa	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
interesting	O
Conversation	O
after	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
left	O
us	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
after	O
12	O
Sunday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Curzon	O
Street	O
Chappel	O
--	O
After	O
Church	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
dear	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Wakes	O
--	O
Julia	B-pers
was	O
not	O
quite	O
recoverd	O
from	O
her	O
late	O
indisposition	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
paid	O
my	O
first	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
as	O
she	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
Tomorrow	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
as	O
other	O
Company	O
came	O
in	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
reluctantly	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
opportunity	O
of	O
paſsing	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
--	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Chappel	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
word	O
we	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
there	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
..	O
James	O
Place	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
sat	O
some	O
time	O
wth	O
.	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
us	O
--	O
she	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
wch	O
..	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
back	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
therefore	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
téte	O
a	O
tête	O
with	O
this	O
excellent	O
Woman	O
.	O
the	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
.	O
and	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
humanity	O
&	O
care	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
treat	O
servants	O
with	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
I	O
meant	O
to	O
sit	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
s	O
and	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Wind	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
courage	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
&	O
back	O
again	O
before	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
dismiſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Servt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
he	O
came	O
&	O
chatted	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
join	O
us	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cloud	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
lively	O
party	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
.	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
--	O
made	O
her	O
drink	O
some	O
tea	O
--	O
had	O
mine	O
brought	O
up	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
alone	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
been	O
agitated	O
--	O
I	O
reason	O
'd	O
soothed	O
&	O
remonstrated	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
treated	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
tenderneſs	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
came	O
up	O
after	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
handed	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Coach	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
was	O
somewhat	O
disconcerted	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Sert	O
.	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
particular	O
invitation	O
to	O
join	O
a	O
family	O
party	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
long	O
jumble	O
to	O
Wimpole	O
Street	O
increased	O
a	O
head	O
ach	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
.	O
however	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
myself	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
sat	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
next	O
Wednesday	O
for	O
reasons	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
little	O
Cousin	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
had	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Monday	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
At	O
11	O
oClock	O
took	O
my	O
Work	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
--	O
Parlour	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Exhibition	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Academy	O
it	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
open	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Crowd	O
.	O
&	O
heat	O
was	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
intend	O
going	O
again	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
now	O
remark	O
those	O
pictures	O
&	O
drawings	O
wch	O
.	O
pleased	O
me	O
most	O
.	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
Northampton	B-place
.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Beavers	O
--	O
An	O
agreeable	O
modest	O
young	O
Man	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bouverie	I-pers
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Blackstone	B-pers
was	O
very	O
useful	O
attentive	O
&	O
civil	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
some	O
Booksellers	O
shops	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
alter	O
my	O
dreſs	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
only	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
dind	O
there	O
--	O
a	O
pleasant	O
party	O
--	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
--	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
half	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
8	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
only	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
quiet	O
working	O
Party	O
&	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Company	O
&	O
Card	O
Tables	O
in	O
two	O
rooms	O
--	O
many	O
people	O
I	O
did	O
&	O
many	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
--	O
conversed	O
chiefly	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
(	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
)	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
J	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
:	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
At	O
10	O
Lady	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
were	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
After	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
ye	O
.	O
Conversation	O
was	O
chiefly	O
relative	O
to	O
poor	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
of	O
whose	O
health	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
very	O
melancholy	O
accounts	O
Tuesday	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
a	O
sleepleſs	O
night	O
--	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
low	O
from	O
my	O
thoughts	O
having	O
wander	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
past	O
events	O
--	O
&	O
Living	O
&	O
Dead	O
friends	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
came	O
&	O
consulted	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
writing	O
to	O
consult	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
physician	O
abt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Noah	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
wch	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
left	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Nosegay	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
were	O
out	O
--	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
wth	O
a	O
Mob	O
round	O
her	O
canvaſsing	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Strand	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
--	O
What	O
a	O
Pity	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
our	O
Sex	O
should	O
ever	O
forget	O
what	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
female	O
delicacy	O
--	O
the	O
Scenes	O
this	O
Dſs	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
lately	O
were	O
they	O
noted	O
down	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
gain	O
gain	O
credit	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
London	B-place
at	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
Election	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
&	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
a	O
hour	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
&	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Spencer	O
House	O
--	O
enquired	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Lucans	O
&	O
then	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Reading	O
Glaſs	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
purchase	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
wch	O
was	O
reckond	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Father	O
s	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
in	O
reading	O
writing	O
&	O
working	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
7	O
.	O
--	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
After	O
dinner	O
at	O
7	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
ye.Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
(	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Rochester	I-pers
Exeter	I-pers
)	O
&	O
Roſs	B-pers
after	O
tea	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
fine	O
Prints	O
Portraits	O
chiefly	O
wch	O
..	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
had	O
lent	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
sooner	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
D	B-pers
had	O
invited	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Mackonichie	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
were	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Whist	O
table	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
's	O
eyes	O
were	O
bad	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
spirits	O
--	O
the	O
Company	O
went	O
away	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Wednesday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
finished	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
open	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
transcribed	O
Verses	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
her	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
paid	O
us	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
her	O
Father	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
set	O
out	O
for	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
this	O
morng	O
.	O
At	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
his	O
eldest	O
Son	O
&	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
s	O
conduct	O
and	O
ye	O
.	O
Westminster	B-place
Election	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
subject	O
of	O
conversation	O
--	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
after	O
dinner	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
in	O
my	O
letter	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
added	O
before	O
I	O
closed	O
it	O
some	O
comical	O
speeches	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
ode	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
Mason	B-pers
s	O
on	O
Hope	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
reading	O
it	O
aloud	O
wch	O
she	O
did	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
himself	O
)	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
delighted	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
his	O
verses	O
so	O
read	O
by	O
her	O
--	O
--	O
little	O
Mason	B-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
cold	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
her	O
supper	O
time	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
Child	O
--	O
if	O
form	O
'd	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
Mother	O
she	O
will	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
if	O
she	O
lives	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
and	O
amiable	O
character	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
great	O
gentleneſs	O
of	O
temper	O
--	O
vivacity	O
of	O
spirits	O
--	O
a	O
lively	O
apprehension	O
to	O
.	O
learn	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
there	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
charming	O
,	O
nature	O
to	O
work	O
upon	O
.	O
After	O
Coffee	O
only	O
Julia	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
remain	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Men	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
indeed	O
staid	O
wth	O
us	O
.	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
came	O
as	O
early	O
as	O
7	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
agreeable	O
little	O
conversation	O
party	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
alone	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
when	O
ye	O
:	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
went	O
away	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
advantage	O
of	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
real	O
good	O
People	O
.	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
--	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
10	O
had	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
found	O
only	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
--	O
sat	O
&	O
chatted	O
with	O
her	O
sometime	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
reading	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Sent	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
Thursday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
which	O
was	O
before	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
as	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
our	O
party	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Coach	O
&	O
dismiſs	O
'd	O
her	O
own	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
famous	O
Automaton	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
invited	O
.	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
bespoke	O
a	O
private	O
Exhibition	O
,	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
Admiral	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
most	O
highly	O
pleased	O
with	O
seeing	O
this	O
very	O
surprising	O
piece	O
of	O
Mechanism	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
at	O
cheſs	O
wth	O
ye	O
.	O
Automaton	O
&	O
lost	O
ye	O
.	O
game	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
people	O
affirm	O
yt	O
.	O
the	O
movements	O
of	O
this	O
Machine	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
motion	O
were	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Magnet	O
therefore	O
I	O
desired	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
ask	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
whether	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Magnet	O
near	O
the	O
Automaton	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
derange	O
the	O
proper	O
movements	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
if	O
a	O
Magnet	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
strongest	O
powers	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
even	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
its	O
hands	O
rested	O
upon	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
effect	O
.	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
constructed	O
this	O
machine	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
family	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
German	O
or	O
Heſsian	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recal	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
bred	O
&	O
communicative	O
--	O
speaks	O
English	O
tolerably	O
indeed	O
very	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
England	B-place
only	O
8	O
months	O
.	O
he	O
converses	O
wth	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
&	O
Monsieur	B-pers
Anthon	I-pers
is	O
ye	O
.	O
person	O
who	O
attends	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Machine	O
--	O
winds	O
it	O
up	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
they	O
make	O
ye	O
.	O
Automaton	O
give	O
very	O
sensible	O
answers	O
--	O
for	O
example	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
questions	O
were	O
“	O
Wch	O
Party	O
are	O
You	O
of	O
'	O
”	O
&	O
it	O
reply	O
'd	O
by	O
pointing	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
.	O
Pour	O
m	O
Je	O
suis	O
pour	O
mon	O
Sultan	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Anthon	I-pers
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
2	O
Years	O
contriving	O
this	O
wonderful	O
piece	O
of	O
Machinery	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
generally	O
thought	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
night	O
time	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
ye	O
.	O
principles	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
Paper	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
work-men	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
who	O
made	O
ye	O
.	O
Springs	O
--	O
wheels	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
prided	O
himself	O
much	O
more	O
upon	O
fire	O
engine	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
invented	O
(	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
patent	O
for	O
)	O
as	O
that	O
wd	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
Mankind	O
,	O
this	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
show	O
or	O
describe	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
the	O
speaking	O
Machine	O
cost	O
him	O
much	O
trouble	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
brought	O
to	O
its	O
highest	O
perfection	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
8	O
years	O
contriving	O
it	O
.	O
this	O
seems	O
seems	O
a	O
leſs	O
complicated	O
machine	O
but	O
is	O
worthy	O
of	O
admiration	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
please	O
me	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Automaton	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
left	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
—	I-pers
s	O
--	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
curious	O
inventions	O
&	O
fine	O
Harpsicords	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
shew	O
'd	O
of	O
us	O
everything	O
worth	O
observing	O
.	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
another	O
oportunity	O
of	O
mentioning	O
Merlin	B-pers
&	O
his	O
inventions	O
more	O
fully	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
Merlin	B-pers
how	O
her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
did	O
(	O
she	O
writes	O
to	O
her	O
every	O
day	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
both	O
in	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
inform	O
Dowgr	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
my	O
enquiry	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
.	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
been	O
ill	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
night	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
&	O
ear-	O
ach	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
found	O
Julia	B-pers
going	O
out	O
with	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Extract	O
Book	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
below	O
--	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
continued	O
my	O
Extracts	O
I	O
read	O
letters	O
I	O
recd	O
by	O
days	O
Post	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
--	O
sad	O
melancholy	O
accounts	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Headach	O
with	O
seeing	O
sights	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
&	O
no	O
inclination	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
s	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
Lady	O
)	O
Aſsembly	O
therefore	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
ashamed	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
invited	O
above	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
carried	O
my	O
Papers	O
down	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
parlour	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
--	O
Genr	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
sent	O
over	O
to	O
invite	O
us	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
went	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
extracts	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
continued	O
writing	O
till	O
12	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
heard	O
yt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
was	O
better	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Friday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
came	O
before	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
s	O
Govenor	O
--	O
he	O
stopt	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
so	O
.	O
from	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
we	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
Place	O
--	O
she	O
paſs	O
'd	O
us	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
Carriage	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
airing	O
--	O
she	O
stopt	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
saw	O
us	O
&	O
sent	O
her	O
servt	O
.	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
return	O
home	O
to	O
receive	O
our	O
visit	O
,	O
this	O
we	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
allow	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
's	O
how	O
he	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
did	O
--	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
but	O
indifferent	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
&	O
I	O
then	O
parted	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Spencer	O
House	O
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
then	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
--	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Kings	O
--	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lose	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
her	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
who	O
is	O
shortly	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
(	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
Service	O
--	O
bears	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
--	O
is	O
the	O
present	O
Captain	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
s	O
youngest	O
Uncle	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
a	O
suitable	O
&	O
proper	O
match	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
her	O
friends	O
can	O
object	O
to	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
live	O
chiefly	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
--	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
wish	O
her	O
every	O
happineſs	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
my	O
good	O
old	O
friend	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
often	O
when	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
was	O
married	O
&	O
gone	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
paſs	O
some	O
time	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
they	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Place	O
near	O
London	B-place
.	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
went	O
to	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
(	O
who	O
also	O
lives	O
in	O
Dover	O
Street	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
)	O
&	O
her	O
little	O
girl	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
Mrs.	B-pers
(	I-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
was	O
there	O
she	O
soon	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
stay	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
intended	O
--	O
&	O
hear	O
d	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
abt	O
.	O
Politics	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
warm	O
politicians	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mulsgrave	I-pers
is	O
a	O
great	O
Foxite	O
--	O
heard	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
were	O
at	O
variance	O
--	O
yt	O
.	O
his	O
Majesty	O
behaved	O
wth	O
great	O
coolneſs	O
towards	O
&	O
took	O
indeed	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
supposed	O
to	O
arise	O
from	O
Prince	B-pers
interfering	O
in	O
Politicks	O
&	O
being	O
in	O
opposition	O
:	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
some	O
Musick	O
&	O
to	O
invite	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
was	O
esteem	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
finest	O
Singer	O
of	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
England	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
voice	O
has	O
not	O
lost	O
all	O
its	O
powers	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
thorough	O
knowledge	O
of	O
music	O
&	O
a	O
fine	O
taste	O
.	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
wth	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
s	O
--	O
enquired	O
after	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
who	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
took	O
his	O
leave	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
expecting	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
extracts	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
employment	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
me	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
--	O
she	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
'd	O
below	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Afternoon	O
&	O
Eveg	O
--	O
writing	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
extracts	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
home	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
wch	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
interest	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
employ	O
'd	O
herself	O
in	O
writing	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
morng	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachell	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Shoemaker	O
whom	O
Thonfield	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachell	I-pers
had	O
recommended	O
came	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
Shoes	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
German	O
&	O
appears	O
civil	O
.	O
lives	O
in	O
South	O
Moulton	O
Rd	O
.	O
May	O
1	O
st	O
1784	O
--	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Day	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
employ	O
myself	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
had	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
for	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
got	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
some	O
unpleasant	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
relative	O
to	O
politicks	O
between	O
her	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
Cousins	O
.	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
was	O
with	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harry	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
Brother	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
was	O
getting	O
better	O
--	O
that	O
however	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
yet	O
venture	O
out	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
promise	O
to	O
send	O
Notes	O
&	O
meſsages	O
wch	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
servts	O
.	O
as	O
our	O
poor	O
Man	O
has	O
still	O
ye	O
.	O
Ague	O
.	O
Col.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Shells	O
to	O
sort	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
.	O
B	O
Room	O
--	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
--	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
at	O
tea	O
time	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
7	O
oClock	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
going	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
as	O
the	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
Richard	B-pers
whom	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
wth	O
.	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
little	O
else	O
than	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
&	O
converse	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
she	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
melancholy	O
account	O
of	O
poor	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Health	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
little	O
supper	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
conversed	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
after	O
supper	O
I	O
sorted	O
shells	O
--	O
sat	O
up	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
harpsicord	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
near	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
had	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
in	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
woud	O
carry	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Wm.Benn	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
May	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Church	O
we	O
could	O
both	O
get	O
ready	O
therefore	O
I	O
read	O
prayers	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Wrote	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
excuse	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
others	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Noseley	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
Girl	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
)	O
made	O
me	O
visits	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
yesterday	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
had	O
a	O
Visit	O
from	O
my	O
Dear	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bland	I-pers
--	O
he	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
are	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
's	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
excellent	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
Man	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
he	O
&	O
his	O
wife	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
--	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Vis	O
a	O
Vis	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
above	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
meet	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
family	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
but	O
promised	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
sat	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
where	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
(	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
reads	O
lectures	O
on	O
Natural	O
Philosophy	O
)	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
also	O
--	O
Many	O
stories	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
--	O
&	O
election	O
matters	O
were	O
treated	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
turn	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Automaton	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
exhausted	O
a	O
general	O
conversation	O
on	O
different	O
topics	O
was	O
agreeable	O
kept	O
up	O
--	O
After	O
tea	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
Book	O
she	O
has	O
lately	O
bought	O
wch-	O
seems	O
a	O
curious	O
&	O
interesting	O
work	O
--	O
I	O
sld	O
.	O
like	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
but	O
my	O
pocket	O
money	O
wont	O
allow	O
of	O
such	O
indulgencies	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Quarto	O
&	O
is	O
unbound	O
a	O
guinea	O
&	O
half	O
.	O
the	O
subject	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
Origin	O
&	O
Progreſs	O
of	O
Writing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
wth	O
.	O
engravings	O
of	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
different	O
kinds	O
of	O
writing	O
Cyphers	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
earliest	O
times	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Progreſs	O
&	O
origin	O
of	O
Printing	O
.	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Esqr	O
.	O
keeper	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Records	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Tower	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Astle	I-pers
told	O
us	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
distreſsd	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
by	O
receiving	O
an	O
anonymous	O
letter	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
penny	O
Post	O
--	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
written	O
in	O
a	O
evidently	O
disguised	O
hand	O
--	O
the	O
contents	O
were	O
to	O
accuse	O
her	O
of	O
having	O
sent	O
some	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
named	O
letters	O
sign	O
'd	O
Argyll	O
--	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Idea	O
was	O
truly	O
Mahometan	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pitty	O
the	O
Black	O
drop	O
in	O
her	O
heart	O
was	O
not	O
squeezed	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
&	O
ended	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
threat	O
ening	O
if	O
she	O
sent	O
more	O
letters	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Words	O
Addio	O
Adieu	O
.	O
farewell	O
.	O
without	O
any	O
signature	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Astle	I-pers
told	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
anxious	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
could	O
poſsibly	O
torment	O
her	O
by	O
so	O
false	O
&	O
shameful	O
an	O
aspersion	O
--	O
&	O
gave	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Cover	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
&	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
penny	O
Post	O
offices	O
&	O
endeavour	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
to	O
trace	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
came	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
hardly	O
poſsible	O
,	O
not	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
things	O
equally	O
mysterious	O
being	O
dectedted	O
--	O
Before	O
8	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W—	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Concert	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
my	O
Chair	O
I	O
got	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
play	O
his	O
Hymn	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
Celestini	O
Stop	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsichord	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
servt	O
.	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
home	O
as	O
our	O
Man	O
is	O
ill	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
Staid	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
then	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
met	O
there	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Inchiquin	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Staid	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
Supper	O
but	O
I	O
declin	O
'd	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
chatted	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	O
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
&	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
diſsip	O
t	O
a	O
te	O
reflections	O
wch	O
.	O
this	O
conversation	O
obtruded	O
upon	O
my	O
mind	O
by	O
beginning	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
&	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
May	O
3	O
d	O
..	O
1784	O
What	O
art	O
thou	O
memory	O
of	O
our	O
former	O
days	O
That	O
dost	O
so	O
subtly	O
touch	O
ye	O
.	O
feeling	O
heart	O
?	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
'Ode	O
'	O
,	O
Essays	O
on	O
Various	O
Subjects	O
in	O
Prose	O
and	O
Verse	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
reflections	O
for	O
every	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
(	O
Dublin	O
:	O
Thomas	O
Ewing	O
,	O
1773	O
)	O
.	O
these	O
thoughts	O
made	O
me	O
I	O
paſsed	O
a	O
sleepleſs	O
night	O
--	O
but	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
Morng	O
.	O
Duty	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Supreme	O
disposer	O
of	O
all	O
things	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
mind	O
refresh	O
'd	O
&	O
my	O
Heart	O
much	O
lighter	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
s	O
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
who	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
picture	O
,	O
I	O
spent	O
near	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
this	O
agreeable	O
employment	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
came	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
good	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
was	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
Julia	B-pers
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
footman	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
invitation	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
excuses	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
both	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
time	O
enough	O
to	O
dreſs	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
therefore	O
was	O
obliged	O
also	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
read	O
in	O
different	O
books	O
till	O
past	O
7	O
wrote	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
was	O
in	O
short	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
settle	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
--	O
the	O
Watchmaker	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Watches	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
order	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Shoemaker	O
brought	O
my	O
Shoes	O
Betty	B-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
profusion	O
of	O
very	O
beautiful	O
flowers	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
ornamented	O
my	O
little	O
apartment	O
wth-	O
them	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
better	O
tho	O
'	O
still	O
an	O
invalid	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
only	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
began	O
to	O
read	O
one	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Plays	O
read	O
a	O
scene	O
or	O
two	O
aloud	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
well	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
heavy	O
&	O
unnatural	O
therefore	O
soon	O
shut	O
ye	O
.	O
book	O
--	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Haley	B-pers
s	O
in	O
Stratford	O
Place	O
--	O
a	O
Card	O
aſsembly	O
--	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachell	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wheeller	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachell	I-pers
s	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
done	O
Supper	O
--	O
but	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
something	O
being	O
brought	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
till	O
near	O
12	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Finch	O
's	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
May	O
4	O
th	O
..	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
enquired	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
&	O
left	O
a	O
Nosegay	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
congratulated	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
on	O
her	O
approaching	O
Marriage	O
--	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
fortune	O
was	O
£	O
700	O
a	O
Year	O
--	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
profeſsion	O
&	O
great	O
connexions	O
his	O
was	O
an	O
improving	O
fortune	O
.	O
From	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
of	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
--	O
sent	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
saw	O
her	O
3	O
fine	O
little	O
Girls	O
--	O
William	B-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
went	O
to	O
shops	O
--	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
wth	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
company	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
Katherine	B-pers
I	O
left	O
them	O
&	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
plagued	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
not	O
settling	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Rent	O
so	O
long	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
House	O
my	O
Mother	O
had	O
.	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
promised	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
--	O
after	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
came	O
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
were	O
going	O
out	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
to	O
say	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
this	O
Eveg	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggin	I-pers
s	O
aſsembly	O
therefore	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
going	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
excuse	O
myself	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
from	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
arran	O
g	O
ing	O
my	O
little	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
placing	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
manner	O
&	O
fatigued	O
myself	O
so	O
much	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
power	O
to	O
stir	O
when	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
12	O
&	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
alterations	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
that	O
it	O
repaid	O
me	O
for	O
all	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
to	O
be	O
denied	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
5	O
th	O
:	O
May	O
1784	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
wth	O
..	O
me	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
At	O
12	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
distreſs	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
had	O
got	O
ye	O
.	O
small	O
pox	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
he	O
sat	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
Sub	O
:	O
Governor	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Elder	O
Princes	O
This	O
man	O
's	O
manners	O
are	O
so	O
cold	O
&	O
formal	O
that	O
it	O
quite	O
freezes	O
one	O
neamoins	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
trimming	O
a	O
Cloak	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
brought	O
little	O
Coll.Hotham	B-pers
to	O
see	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
At	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
a	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
also	O
--	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
who	O
is	O
upon	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
s	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
sometime	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Kings	O
--	O
&	O
myself	O
Miſs	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
took	O
me	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
before	O
dinner	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
talkd	O
of	O
her	O
youngest	O
Daughter	O
s	O
Marriage	O
--	O
ask	O
me	O
questions	O
(	O
kindly	O
ones	O
abt	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
)	O
desired	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
I	O
would	O
introduced	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
interested	O
in	O
my	O
happineſs	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
quite	O
ungrateful	O
not	O
to	O
love	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
ingenius	O
works	O
--	O
particularly	O
two	O
screens	O
of	O
Philagree	O
2	O
paper	O
1	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
lately	O
done	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
¼	O
before	O
8	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
visit	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
her	O
every	O
happineſs	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
married	O
state	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
only	O
interrupted	O
for	O
ten	O
minutes	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
calling	O
to	O
settle	O
an	O
Engagement	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
fatigued	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
came	O
upstairs	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
Son	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
week	O
how	O
anxious	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
his	O
going	O
abroad	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Character	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
an	O
amiable	O
one	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
many	O
ar	O
traits	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
character	O
--	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
my	O
Cousin	O
ye	O
.	O
more	O
she	O
rises	O
in	O
my	O
esteem	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
likewise	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
respecting	O
our	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
--	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
late	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
to	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
those	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
found	O
adreſs	O
'd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
after	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
he	O
informs	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
strong	O
&	O
avow	O
'd	O
partiality	O
he	O
ever	O
entertain	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
wch	O
Time	O
itself	O
has	O
with	O
difficulty	O
conquer	O
'd	O
prevents	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
requests	O
me	O
to	O
excuse	O
this	O
liberty	O
,	O
&	O
distinguish	O
it	O
by	O
whatever	O
disgraceful	O
Epithet	O
I	O
please	O
either	O
of	O
folly	O
or	O
impertinence	O
but	O
not	O
for	O
one	O
moment	O
to	O
imagine	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
be	O
wanting	O
to	O
me	O
either	O
in	O
respect	O
or	O
esteem	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
grieved	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
friend	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
esteem	O
.	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
friend	O
without	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
and	O
lover	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
separated	O
I	O
must	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
an	O
agreeable	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
proper	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
an	O
answer	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
Sr.Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
--	O
I	O
ate	O
my	O
Supper	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
generally	O
a	O
little	O
bread	O
&	O
cheese	O
&	O
read	O
the	O
news	O
papers	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
.	O
May	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
..	O
me	O
.	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
finishing	O
my	O
dreſs	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Cousin	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Millener	O
as	O
she	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
bought	O
a	O
Cap	O
&	O
Balloon	O
Hat	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Inchiquin	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
he	O
ever	O
friendly	O
&	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
wishing	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
married	O
&	O
happily	O
settled	O
for	O
life	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
real	O
sentiments	O
&	O
read	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
that	O
affair	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
that	O
matter	O
could	O
be	O
finally	O
adjusted	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
he	O
approved	O
of	O
my	O
Conduct	O
&	O
thought	O
that	O
if	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
I	O
imagined	O
&	O
if	O
circumstances	O
wd	O
.	O
reasonably	O
admit	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
happier	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
came	O
he	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
indifferent	O
subjects	O
.	O
--	O
till	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
filld	O
up	O
my	O
time	O
in	O
working	O
&	O
being	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
whilst	O
s	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
then	O
my	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ernst	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
ye	O
.	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
had	O
said	O
many	O
handsome	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
praise	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
(	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Inchiquin	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
My	O
Cousin	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
my	O
Lady	B-pers
Ern	I-pers
&	O
self	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
company	O
--	O
Chs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
Uncle	B-pers
s	O
tutor	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
also	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
boys	O
ye	O
.	O
two	O
youngest	O
have	O
been	O
settled	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
some	O
days	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
is	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
left	O
us	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
St—	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
--	O
she	O
only	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
go	O
to	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
Cousin	B-pers
Chas	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Coach	O
--	O
we	O
set	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
down	O
at	O
her	O
Mothers	O
Lady	B-pers
Ern	I-pers
s	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Ern	I-pers
's	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
yet	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
an	O
Invalid	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Mothers	O
(	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
)	O
My	O
Uncle	O
staid	O
to	O
tea	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
early	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Ern	I-pers
&	O
then	O
left	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Concert	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
remain	O
'd	O
wth	O
..	O
us	O
almost	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
time	O
we	O
staid	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
s	O
political	O
principles	O
&	O
Conducts	O
&	O
other	O
common	O
topicks	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
&	O
read	O
in	O
my	O
little	O
Boudoir	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
now	O
very	O
comfortable	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
home	O
before	O
11.	O
they	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
little	O
cabin	O
Boudoir	O
wch	O
is	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Size	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
we	O
ate	O
our	O
petit	O
soupeé	O
there	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
soon	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Poem	O
to	O
me	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
3	O
years	O
ago	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Poem	O
is	O
a	O
Satire	O
(	O
a	O
gentle	O
one	O
)	O
on	O
learned	O
Women	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
merit	O
in	O
it	O
has	O
merit	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Master	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
her	O
usual	O
hour	O
of	O
going	O
home	O
(	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
came	O
home	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
to	O
sup	O
wth	O
,	O
us	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
Fête	O
.	O
My	O
good	O
friends	O
the	O
Dartreys	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
next	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
I	O
hope	O
sometime	O
at	O
their	O
Villa	O
near	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
they	O
kindly	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
expect	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
their	O
Coach	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
sent	O
the	O
servts	O
.	O
to	O
bed	O
sat	O
up	O
sometime	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
Sunday	O
May	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
servts	O
.	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Service	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
&	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
New	O
Testament	O
--	O
wrote	O
parts	O
of	O
letters	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
note	O
of	O
reproach	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
for	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
--	O
Burkitt	B-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
kindest	O
aſsurances	O
of	O
her	O
affection	O
&	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
her	O
future	O
happineſs	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
wth	O
a	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
hair	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
William	B-pers
Burkitt	I-pers
s	O
as	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
great	O
friends	O
&	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
presented	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
smelling	O
Bottle	O
in	O
an	O
ivory	O
silver	O
filagree	O
case	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
as	O
a	O
little	O
gage	O
d'amitie	O
we	O
settled	O
our	O
correspondence	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
journey	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Perthshire	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
spirits	O
affected	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
a	O
regret	O
when	O
we	O
part	O
from	O
those	O
for	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
regard	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
that	O
the	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
perhaps	O
we	O
may	O
never	O
meet	O
again	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
obtrude	O
itself	O
upon	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
they	O
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
&	O
sung	O
a	O
few	O
songs	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
young	O
companions	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
young	O
Miſs	B-pers
H—	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
one	O
yt	O
.	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
Service	O
went	O
to	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
very	O
poorly	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
night	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
indifferent	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
usual	O
cheerfulneſs	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
woman	O
this	O
is	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
happineſs	O
to	O
have	O
known	O
such	O
true	O
excellence	O
!	O
We	O
walk	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Gate	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Mall	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
prudent	O
a	O
Chaperon	O
to	O
lead	O
my	O
young	O
people	O
to	O
the	O
fluttering	O
Crowd	O
we	O
there	O
turn	O
'd	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
again	O
the	O
Heat	O
was	O
quite	O
oppressive	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
her	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
(	O
not	O
ye	O
fine	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
)	O
a	O
very	O
opposite	O
character	O
has	O
this	O
good	O
lady	O
ever	O
borne	O
to	O
hers	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
--	O
too	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
woman	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
these	O
Ladys	O
by	O
meeting	O
them	O
in	O
partys	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bouvrie	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
&	O
then	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
in	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
Antient	O
Poetry	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
after	O
8	O
oClock	O
she	O
is	O
got	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
very	O
weak	O
&	O
low	O
.	O
as	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
Lady	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sing	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sung	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
some	O
Italian	O
songs	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
fine	O
voice	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H—	I-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
&	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Wakes	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Servants	O
early	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
oClock	O
.	O
Monday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1784	O
.	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
dress	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Woman	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Warehouse	O
came	O
&	O
tried	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Corsets	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Shoemaker	O
brought	O
home	O
my	O
clogs	O
&	O
c.	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
alwa	O
ys	O
keep	O
to	O
the	O
custom	O
of	O
paying	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
m	O
transacted	O
my	O
own	O
affairs	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
great	O
advantage	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
one	O
is	O
never	O
in	O
any	O
diſtreſs	O
,	O
besides	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
principle	O
with	O
me	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
ones	O
debt	O
.	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
morning	O
wth	O
.	O
reading	O
writing	O
&	O
working	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
,	O
his	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lively	O
,	O
clever	O
,	O
pleasant	O
Man	O
.	O
&	O
has	O
ye	O
.	O
art	O
putting	O
every	O
one	O
in	O
good	O
humour	O
&	O
if	O
people	O
ever	O
laugh	O
they	O
must	O
do	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
chuses	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
lately	O
been	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
--	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
some	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Court	O
of	O
France	B-place
&	O
characters	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
great	O
Ministers	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
was	O
half	O
affronted	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
she	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
early	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
till	O
she	O
did	O
--	O
drank	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G——	I-pers
came	O
in	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
--	O
as	O
did	O
the	O
young	O
Sea	O
Officer	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
I	O
askd	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Smelts	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
went	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
be	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
were	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Town	B-place
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
.	O
King	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
to	O
Handcock	B-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
saucy	O
one	O
--	O
&	O
another	O
.	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
undressing	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
her	O
time	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
May	O
12	O
th	O
:	O
1784	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
two	O
very	O
smart	O
answers	O
to	O
my	O
Notes	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
:	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
:	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
stay	O
'd	O
sometime	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
for	O
whom	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Vote	O
&	O
went	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
had	O
gain	O
'd	O
his	O
Election	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Daughter	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
long	O
visit	O
from	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
who	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
manuscript	O
poems	O
written	O
by	O
different	O
people	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
copy	O
--	O
he	O
spoke	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Statford	I-pers
--	O
his	O
great	O
Abilities	O
&	O
c.	O
said	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
ten	O
years	O
older	O
than	O
him	O
therefore	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
70	O
.	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
wth-	O
Lord	B-pers
Monboddo	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Manfield	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpscord	O
after	O
dinner	O
some	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
leſsons	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
wrote	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Poems	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
--	O
Vento	B-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
6	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charm	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
little	O
Boudoir	O
&	O
whilst	O
she	O
staid	O
sat	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
Scarlati	B-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
After	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
whilst	O
I	O
wrote	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
doors	O
open	O
so	O
we	O
could	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
talk	O
'd	O
occasionally	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
who	O
was	O
deep	O
in	O
newpapers	O
&	O
politicks	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
last	O
letter	O
At	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
pass	O
'd	O
a	O
sociably	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
only	O
themselves	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
goes	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Brightlmstone	B-place
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
the	O
servts	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
10	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
inquired	O
if	O
I	O
lived	O
here	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
his	O
name	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
message	O
he	O
replied	O
--	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
himself	O
--	O
what	O
was	O
still	O
more	O
singular	O
he	O
knockd	O
only	O
gave	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
knock	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
--	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
commented	O
on	O
this	O
adventure	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
May	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Thursday	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
friendly	O
note	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
(	O
who	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
be	O
married	O
tomorrow	O
a	O
lock	O
of	O
her	O
Hair	O
&	O
a	O
hand	O
some	O
Diamond	O
pin	O
for	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
--	O
I	O
answerd	O
her	O
note	O
repeated	O
my	O
wishes	O
for	O
her	O
future	O
happineſs	O
&	O
thank	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
presents	O
as	O
they	O
deserved	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
terrible	O
cold	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
wch	O
.	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
as	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
they	O
sat	O
talking	O
of	O
Elections	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
After	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
goes	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
tomorrow	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pressing	O
invitation	O
to	O
Horton	O
&	O
I	O
promised	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
when	O
Frederick	B-pers
went	O
.	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
wth-	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
Hip	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
&	O
gone	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
.	O
At	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
sister	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
,	O
a	O
modest	O
pleasing	O
woman	O
.	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fix	O
an	O
afternoon	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
next	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
provided	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Company	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
At	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
confin	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
therefore	O
she	O
sent	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
to	O
beg	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
it	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
&	O
read	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ernst	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Poem	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
beautiful	O
prints	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
bought	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Dryden	B-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Twins	O
Sisters	O
--	O
Prior	B-pers
's	O
Neice	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Clarendon	I-pers
Daughter	O
--	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
--	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Villars	I-pers
s	O
next	O
Brother	O
C	B-pers
--	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
fortune	O
of	O
near	O
£5000	O
a	O
year	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
Uncle	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
for	O
this	O
Estate	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
name	O
--	O
Admiral	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
is	O
to	O
give	O
Lord	B-pers
Mornington	I-pers
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
£1500	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
&	O
a	O
£1000	O
to	O
buy	O
Clothes	O
--	O
&	O
her	O
jointure	O
to	O
be	O
2000	O
there	O
was	O
much	O
talk	O
of	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
species	O
of	O
Robbery	O
--	O
wch	O
was	O
that	O
one	O
Lady	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Pins	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
ladies	O
heads	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
aſsemblies	O
were	O
getting	O
into	O
their	O
Carriages	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
Eveg	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Poole	I-pers
was	O
coming	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
Assembly	O
--	O
a	O
Man	O
hit	O
her	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
temple	O
&	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Earing	O
quite	O
through	O
her	O
Ear	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
handing	O
her	O
was	O
suprised	O
to	O
hear	O
her	O
scream	O
out	O
&	O
turning	O
round	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
pouring	O
down	O
her	O
neck	O
for	O
the	O
Ear	O
was	O
torn	O
quite	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
in	O
Ad	B-pers
:	I-pers
Forbes	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
sat	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Friday	O
2	O
1	O
4	O
th	O
May	O
1784	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
I	O
borrow	O
'd	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Douglaſs	O
Cause	O
--	O
the	O
language	O
is	O
extremely	O
good	O
&	O
there	O
seems	O
so	O
much	O
justice	O
due	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
that	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
condemn	O
Stewart	B-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
&	O
brought	O
her	O
2	O
eldest	O
Girls	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
visit	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
since	O
ye	O
.	O
death	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
.	O
recd	O
.	O
&	O
answerd	O
several	O
notes	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
before	O
4	O
--	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
to	O
leave	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
watch	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
Met	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
the	O
celebrated	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
is	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
's	O
guest	O
every	O
winter	O
½	O
year	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
party	O
,	O
I	O
regret	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
every	O
thing	O
Dr.	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Johnston	I-pers
said	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
just	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Illneſs	O
&	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
75	O
th	O
.	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
&	O
very	O
infirm	O
his	O
faculties	O
are	O
bright	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
He	O
glories	O
in	O
being	O
esteem	O
'd	O
a	O
sincere	O
Christian	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
ever	O
an	O
unbeliever	O
that	O
had	O
ever	O
taken	O
pains	O
to	O
investigate	O
ye	O
.	O
evidence	O
He	O
aſsured	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
fact	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
never	O
read	O
those	O
writings	O
wch	O
he	O
so	O
profanely	O
attack	O
'd	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	O
)	O
House	O
one	O
day	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
do	O
you	O
ever	O
read	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
--	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Hume	B-pers
gave	O
us	O
--	O
an	O
other	O
instance	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
--	O
most	O
harden	O
'd	O
Infidels	O
he	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
(	I-pers
Cummings	I-pers
a	O
great	O
Mathematician	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
Clever	O
Man	O
--	O
indeed	O
uncommonly	O
so	O
--	O
He	O
boasted	O
to	O
Hume	B-pers
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Scriptures	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
taught	O
to	O
read	O
in	O
it	O
at	O
school	O
--	O
but	O
one	O
day	O
finding	O
no	O
other	O
book	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
Bible	O
&	O
read	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
story	O
of	O
Joseph	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
thought	O
really	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
saying	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
--	O
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
happiness	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
Sincere	O
Christian	O
--	O
Madam	O
say	O
's	O
he	O
then	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
never	O
forget	O
it	O
or	O
let	O
others	O
be	O
unacquainted	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
Johnston	B-pers
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
provoked	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
incouragement	O
given	O
to	O
People	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
their	O
talents	O
who	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
unbelievers	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
foreigners	O
who	O
came	O
over	O
wth	O
.	O
no	O
other	O
title	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
unbelief	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
highly	O
encouraged	O
&	O
she	O
instanced	O
in	O
particular	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Mention	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
had	O
a	O
pension	O
from	O
this	O
country	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Abbè	B-pers
Raynal	I-pers
added	O
that	O
unbelievers	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
propagate	O
their	O
pernicious	O
doctrines	O
--	O
Johnstone	B-pers
replied	O
she	O
could	O
urge	O
nothing	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
.	O
under	O
that	O
restraint	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
equally	O
good	O
for	O
their	O
being	O
banish	O
'd	O
from	O
all	O
societies	O
who	O
profeſs	O
'd	O
Christianity	O
,	O
he	O
added	O
he	O
would	O
banish	O
them	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
&	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
where	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
recd-	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Rouſseau	B-pers
said	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
a	O
Head	O
so	O
unfurnished	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
credit	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Classical	O
scholar	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
learnt	O
at	O
school	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
any	O
subject	O
he	O
ever	O
wrote	O
upon	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
abilities	O
were	O
equal	O
to	O
any	O
mans	O
he	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
application	O
.	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
common	O
subjects	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ignorant	O
--	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
many	O
&	O
daily	O
proofs	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
faculty	O
habit	O
of	O
lying	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
degree	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Club	O
to	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
belonged	O
that	O
and	O
ye	O
.	O
society	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
never	O
scrupled	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
they	O
wanted	O
faith	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
advanced	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
envious	O
of	O
Men	O
--	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
praise	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
nay	O
even	O
ye	O
.	O
Beauty	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
being	O
praised	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
indure	O
.	O
Johnstone	B-pers
having	O
been	O
succeſs	O
suceſsfull	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
publications	O
it	O
greatly	O
irritated	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
--	O
after	O
talking	O
of	O
him	O
one	O
day	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
acrimony	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Glaſs	O
&	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
ugly	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
neither	O
.	O
Kelly	B-pers
said	O
that	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
was	O
a	O
very	O
vulgar	O
man	O
&	O
vastly	O
conceited	O
--	O
Kelly	B-pers
told	O
us	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
had	O
lived	O
much	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
during	O
Dr.	B-pers
Go	I-pers
s	O
life	O
time	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
happy	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
gain	O
ye	O
.	O
attention	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
company	O
to	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
sometimes	O
utter	O
ye	O
.	O
groſsest	O
nonsense	O
--	O
but	O
&	O
talk	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
common	O
sense	O
--	O
the	O
laugh	O
against	O
him	O
however	O
was	O
never	O
so	O
painful	O
as	O
the	O
not	O
being	O
attended	O
to	O
in	O
preference	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
many	O
good	O
qualities	O
he	O
chief	O
failings	O
were	O
want	O
of	O
veracity	O
.	O
envy	O
vanity	O
&	O
want	O
of	O
oeconomy	O
.	O
one	O
striking	O
instance	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
mention	O
'd	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
introduced	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Club	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
,	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
c	O
were	O
Members	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
dean	O
of	O
Durham	O
+	O
thinking	O
to	O
impose	O
on	O
the	O
Company	O
--	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
mentioned	O
Johnstone	B-pers
exclaim	O
'd	O
surely	O
The	O
Red	O
Book	O
would	O
have	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
better	O
--	O
O	O
say	O
's	O
Burke	B-pers
he	O
was	O
so	O
ignorant	O
of	O
common	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Book	O
.	O
Though	O
he	O
wrote	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
histry	O
.	O
of	O
England	B-place
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
turning	O
over	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
English	O
Historians	O
&	O
abridging	O
them	O
--	O
his	O
Natural	O
Histry	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
work	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
kind	O
taken	O
from	O
Reynolds	B-pers
--	O
wd	O
.	O
he	O
otherwise	O
have	O
assured	O
us	O
that	O
Cows	O
shed	O
their	O
Horns	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
?	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
when	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
wrote	O
was	O
not	O
liked	O
that	O
it	O
proceeded	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Envy	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Public	O
&	O
their	O
malice	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
mortify	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
owe	O
his	O
pretty	O
Novel	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Vicar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
plunged	O
in	O
debt	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
&	O
wrote	O
that	O
book	O
to	O
extricate	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
finish	O
'd	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
Boswell	B-pers
who	O
would	O
only	O
give	O
him	O
20	O
L	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Copy	O
--	O
upon	O
which	O
ye	O
.	O
neceſsitous	O
Author	O
withdrew	O
ye	O
.	O
his	O
Publication	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
&	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
his	O
generous	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
acquainting	O
him	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
melancholy	O
situation	O
.	O
Johnstone	B-pers
--	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Guinea	O
&	O
ordering	O
a	O
Coach	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
drove	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
drown	O
his	O
cares	O
with	O
Maderia	O
--	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
use	O
he	O
made	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Guinea	O
was	O
to	O
procure	O
this	O
liquor	O
--	O
Buffon	B-pers
seiz	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Bottle	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
emptied	O
half	O
&	O
corking	O
it	O
declard	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
taste	O
another	O
drop	O
.	O
he	O
then	O
comforted	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
aſsurance	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
his	O
Novel	O
to	O
good	O
advantage	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
&	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
70	O
L	O
:	O
after	O
this	O
Dodsley	B-pers
--	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
ever	O
run	O
in	O
debt	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Dr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Gold-	B-pers
smith	I-pers
in	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
Johnstone	B-pers
told	O
us	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
Dr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
in	O
her	O
happier	O
days	O
.	O
she	O
meant	O
when	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
was	O
living	O
--	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
happies	O
t	O
couple	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
they	O
hardly	O
ever	O
were	O
separated	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
day	O
&	O
never	O
for	O
one	O
night	O
during	O
28	O
or	O
29	O
years	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
has	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
was	O
her	O
lover	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
most	O
tender	O
Husband	O
to	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
also	O
inform	O
'd	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
s	O
4	O
Sisters	O
who	O
keep	O
the	O
School	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
that	O
the	O
5	O
Sisters	O
were	O
all	O
different	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
characters	O
but	O
equally	O
amiable	O
&	O
clever	O
--	O
gave	O
many	O
striking	O
instances	O
of	O
their	O
genius	O
,	O
benevolence	O
&	O
excellent	O
principles	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
goes	O
always	O
first	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
found	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
2	O
Pottles	O
of	O
fine	O
Strawberries	O
--	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
sent	O
them	O
Saturday	O
1	O
5	O
6	O
th	O
May	O
1784	O
Walk	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
oClock	O
till	O
11	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
&	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
short	O
Visit	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
working	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
belonging	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
it	O
was	O
her	O
Morning	O
for	O
having	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Coach	O
--	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Cavendish	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
visit	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
the	O
Painters	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sit	O
for	O
her	O
Picture	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
wth	O
whom	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
came	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
at	O
dinner	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
s	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
many	O
handsome	O
things	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Romney	B-pers
took	O
me	O
wth	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Chariot	O
to	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
sometime	O
saw	O
him	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
&	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Aunt	O
to	O
her	O
daughter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
from	O
her	O
House	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
French	B-pers
Ambaſsador	I-pers
--	O
we	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
with	O
her	O
--	O
after	O
staying	O
there	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
my	O
Aunt	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
dinner	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
heated	O
&	O
tired	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
walk	O
that	O
we	O
made	O
her	O
eat	O
a	O
Sandwich	O
&	O
drink	O
some	O
wine	O
&	O
water	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
agreeable	O
party	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
said	O
she	O
always	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
sign	O
when	O
Men	O
liked	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
of	O
virtuous	O
&	O
amiable	O
Women	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
accidentaly	O
this	O
Morng	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
at	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
House	O
.	O
&	O
having	O
talk	O
'd	O
o	O
f	O
ye	O
.	O
exhibition	O
,	O
by	O
chance	O
mention	O
'd	O
my	O
name	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Somerset	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	O
H	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
&	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
had	O
been	O
dangerously	O
Ill	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
recovering	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
's	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveng	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
a	O
Numerous	O
Bas	O
Bleu	O
party	O
.	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
since	O
her	O
coming	O
to	O
London	B-place
,	O
she	O
was	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
herself	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
sincere	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
she	O
told	O
me	O
was	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Standart	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
very	O
entertaining	O
told	O
us	O
some	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cs	I-pers
s	O
lively	O
strokes	O
of	O
wit	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Natural	O
fool	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
inspirations	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
slept	O
from	O
home	O
at	O
her	O
friend	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
Lambeth	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
China	O
flower	O
pot	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
nosegay	O
.	O
May	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mayfair	O
Chapel	O
.	O
the	O
Text	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
George	I-pers
Selwyn	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Paul	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Philipians	O
--	O
'let	O
Your	O
Conversation	O
be	O
in	O
Heaven	O
'	O
Philippians	O
3:20	O
,	O
KJV	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
delivery	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
compose	O
a	O
discourse	O
his	O
sermons	O
are	O
never	O
interesting	O
.	O
After	O
Chapel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Selwyn	I-pers
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
is	O
always	O
at	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Mornings	O
to	O
receive	O
visits	O
from	O
her	O
scholars	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
famous	O
Drawing	O
Mistreſs	O
.	O
from	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
saw	O
Dr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
congratulated	O
on	O
her	O
Sister	O
s	O
Marriage	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Highgate	B-place
when	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
that	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Dr	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
as	O
was	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
at	O
her	O
door	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
taken	O
me	O
to	O
Master	B-pers
Blackwood	I-pers
but	O
I	O
was	O
heated	O
&	O
tired	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
walk	O
&	O
excusd	O
myself	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
was	O
come	O
home	O
we	O
chatted	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
4	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
only	O
her	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
before	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
dining	O
Room	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
7	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
Shells	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
amuse	O
her	O
:	O
ye.Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
managed	O
her	O
Money	O
transactions	O
&	O
advised	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
ye	O
.	O
Banker	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Interest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
--	O
but	O
go	O
myself	O
ever	O
½	O
year	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
others	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Drawing	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
doing	O
&	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
.	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
we	O
separated	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
Monday	O
17	O
th	O
..	O
May	O
1784	O
Recd	O
.	O
&	O
answerd	O
Notes	O
--	O
arranged	O
my	O
Porte	O
feulles	O
sorted	O
out	O
prints	O
,	O
sent	O
back	O
those	O
I	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
wrote	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Gown	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
park	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
her	O
two	O
eldest	O
Girls	O
recd	O
.	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
of	O
Taplow	B-place
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
)	O
were	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
the	O
whole	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Grand	O
Proceſsion	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
said	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
conducted	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
sight	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
were	O
standing	O
on	O
Ladders	O
set	O
against	O
ye	O
.	O
Walls	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Court	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
House	O
.	O
wearing	O
Laurels	O
Fox	O
tails	O
in	O
their	O
hats	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
this	O
Hero	O
paſs	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
triumphal	O
Car	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
longest	O
Poll	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Westminster	B-place
election	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
known	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
the	O
streets	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
through	O
were	O
crowded	O
wth	O
.	O
people	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
seem	O
'd	O
peaceably	O
inclined	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
upstairs	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
employ	O
'd	O
herself	O
in	O
translating	O
Italian	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
lights	O
in	O
the	O
windows	O
as	O
all	O
our	O
street	O
was	O
illuminated	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
tired	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
up	O
any	O
longer	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
indeed	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Neighbours	O
put	O
out	O
their	O
lights	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Met	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
People	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
House	O
they	O
seemd	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
18	O
th	O
:	O
May	O
1784	O
--	O
went	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
woman	O
,	O
&	O
but	O
tho	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
a	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honor	O
is	O
unpolishd	O
her	O
language	O
is	O
ungram̄atical	O
&	O
very	O
Slip-Slop	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
advantages	O
of	O
living	O
wth	O
.	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
polished	O
.	O
from	O
her	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
her	O
Brother	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
high	O
spirits	O
wth	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
triumph	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Papendick	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
from	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
Dover	O
Street	O
--	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stilingfleet	I-pers
who	O
look	O
'd	O
wretchedly	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
state	O
of	O
Health	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
nothing	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
but	O
Fox	B-pers
.	O
&	O
the	O
entertainments	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
.	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
are	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
chaird	O
Yesterday	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
