TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
ye	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
By	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
ye	O
25	O
th	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
and	O
agreeable	O
situation	O
at	O
Eastbourne	B-place
.	O
When	O
you	O
reflect	O
on	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
our	O
laſt	O
correſpondence	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
appriſ	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
final	O
iſsue	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
been	O
waiting	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
in	O
your	O
laſt	O
:	O
I	O
sincerely	O
congratulate	O
you	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
as	O
for	O
Catherine	B-pers
&	O
Nanny	B-pers
--	O
let	O
them	O
excuſe	O
themſelves	O
;	O
no	O
juſtification	O
shall	O
they	O
have	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
the	O
confidence	O
to	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
regular	O
scolding	O
in	O
your	O
behalf	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
little	O
thought	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
guilty	O
themſelves	O
without	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
a	O
plea	O
.	O
Excepting	O
Nanny	B-pers
's	O
face	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
complains	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
affirm	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
indiſpoſitio	O
n	O
among	O
us	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
taking	O
the	O
bark	O
for	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
hope	O
with	O
succeſs	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
affectionate	O
father	O
R	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
M	O
L	O
eonidas	O
Septr	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
-	O
1780	O
