TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
14	O
th	O
:	O
July	O
1785	O
My	O
Dr	O
..	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
bids	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
is	O
disappointed	O
in	O
not	O
seeing	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
here	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
one	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
says	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
all	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
says	O
that	O
parting	O
is	O
painful	O
,	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
us	O
in	O
Town	B-place
as	O
it	O
is	O
really	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
s	O
power	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
&	O
inde	O
d	O
e	O
d	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
w	O
h	O
ere	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
sleep	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
mother	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
disturb	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
is	O
poor	O
woman	O
too	O
infirm	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
bustle	O
,	O
which	O
our	O
coming	O
to	O
London	B-place
would	O
do	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
painful	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
those	O
we	O
love	O
,	O
had	O
we	O
not	O
every	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
I	O
believe	O
nothing	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
us	O
our	O
coming	O
&	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Grasty	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
,	O
since	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
you	O
must	O
excuse	O
our	O
taking	O
leave	O
by	O
letter	O
&	O
accept	O
the	O
sincere	O
wishes	O
My	O
Dr	O
Friends	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
&	O
myself	O
for	O
your	O
health	O
&	O
happineſs	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
other	O
day	O
She	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
sincere	O
congratulations	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
wishing	O
you	O
many	O
many	O
happy	O
years	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
with	O
every	O
happineſs	O
,	O
she	O
gives	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
my	O
Dr	O
friend	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
wishes	O
much	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
poſsession	O
of	O
some	O
worthy	O
mans	O
heart	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
sure	O
that	O
that	O
only	O
can	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
Dr-	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
Town	B-place
by	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
who	O
will	O
put	O
in	O
into	O
the	O
penny	O
post	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
present	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
&	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
will	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
make	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
your	O
Dr	O
..	O
friend	O
next	O
winter	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
shall	O
look	O
forward	O
with	O
pleasure	O
to	O
the	O
Winter	O
in	O
the	O
happy	O
hopes	O
&	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
set	O
my	O
heart	O
on	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
..	O
of	O
June	O
how	O
have	O
I	O
long	O
'd	O
&	O
depended	O
on	O
your	O
spending	O
some	O
happy	O
days	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
alas	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
quite	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
for	O
good	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
Dr	O
Mr	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
very	O
sincere	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
unites	O
in	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
.	O
