TOKEN	NE
May	O
19	O
1807	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Love	O
A	O
friend	O
has	O
procur	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
an	O
aperture	O
for	O
sending	O
to	O
Engd	B-place
:	I-place
but	O
has	O
confin	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
avoid	O
bulk	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
that	O
even	O
two	O
words	O
from	O
me	O
will	O
be	O
acceptable	O
to	O
so	O
affectionate	O
a	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
endeavour	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
in	O
so	O
limited	O
a	O
space	O
You	O
may	O
easily	O
imagine	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
was	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
interruption	O
of	O
our	O
correspondence	O
;	O
particularly	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
you	O
all	O
remain	O
happily	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
uncertain	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
miserably	O
anxious	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
also	O
for	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Father	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
Augt	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
fully	O
explain	O
the	O
deplorable	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
nevertheleſs	O
rather	O
alarming	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
console	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
hope	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Timmins	I-pers
might	O
have	O
perform	O
'd	O
his	O
promise	O
of	O
making	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
confort	O
you	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
who	O
cou	O
'd	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
acct	O
:	O
of	O
yr	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	O
&	O
her	O
children	O
.	O
The	O
providential	O
supply	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
belov	O
'd	O
Parent	O
sent	O
to	O
restore	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
was	O
perhaps	O
the	O
means	O
with	O
the	O
bleſsing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
to	O
preserve	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
enabled	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
underwent	O
a	O
course	O
of	O
medicines	O
,	O
which	O
purified	O
my	O
blood	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
,	O
&	O
served	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
alive	O
for	O
the	O
winter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
horror	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
that	O
I	O
fortunately	O
took	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
near	O
the	O
Casino	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
warm	O
;	O
&	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
rigours	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
cold	O
,	O
wet	O
,	O
confortleſs	O
winter	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Casino	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
place	O
wherein	O
I	O
can	O
enjoy	O
tollerable	O
health	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
air	O
of	O
the	O
sea	O
is	O
so	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
my	O
existence	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
omit	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
recd	O
.	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
medicines	O
&	O
c	O
safe	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
have	O
made	O
me	O
pay	O
very	O
dear	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
custom	O
house	O
at	O
Rome	B-place
,	O
rejoiced	O
my	O
heart	O
in	O
procuring	O
me	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
reading	O
your	O
dear	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
two	O
Friends	O
'	O
just	O
a	O
year	O
after	O
their	O
date	O
.	O
Good	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sydall	I-pers
s	O
'	O
presents	O
were	O
highly	O
acceptable	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
kind	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
return	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
can	O
better	O
imagine	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
have	O
room	O
here	O
to	O
explain	O
:	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
goods	O
is	O
yet	O
at	O
Meſsina	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
world	O
suffers	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
must	O
be	O
content	O
with	O
what	O
pleases	O
God	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
my	O
wish	O
that	O
the	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
drawn	O
for	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
interest	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
adjust	O
the	O
sum	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
's	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
if	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
any	O
means	O
of	O
sending	O
me	O
anything	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
over	O
&	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
all	O
remain	O
well	O
including	O
all	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
family	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
gratefully	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
&	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
yr	O
most	O
affect	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
E	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
to	O
Miss	B-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
19	O
May	O
1807	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch-Hall	B-place
Near	O
Manchester	B-place
