TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
two	O
friends	O
have	O
read	O
her	O
obliging	O
letter	O
with	O
the	O
moſt	O
cordial	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Her	O
pictures	O
of	O
the	O
various	O
objects	O
environing	O
her	O
preſent	O
reſidence	O
merit	O
high	O
admiration	O
;	O
but	O
much	O
higher	O
pleaſure	O
--	O
reſults	O
from	O
the	O
conſideration	O
of	O
her	O
preſent	O
unconſtrain	O
'd	O
felicity	O
:	O
more	O
pleaſing	O
,	O
more	O
heart-felt	O
still	O
were	O
the	O
paternal	O
senſations	O
,	O
which	O
affected	O
the	O
writer	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
learn	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
reply	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
to	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
important	O
diſpatches	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
quarter	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
preceding	O
her	O
departure	O
from	O
London	B-place
.	O
Among	O
many	O
vexations	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
lately	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
peculiar	O
embarraſsment	O
of	O
your	O
situation	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
child	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
leaſt	O
of	O
my	O
sufferings	O
.	O
I	O
truſt	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
set	O
free	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
truly	O
thankful	O
at	O
my	O
releaſe	O
from	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
anxiety	O
.	O
Paſs	O
'd	O
experience	O
will	O
befriend	O
you	O
better	O
,	O
than	O
any	O
advice	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
in	O
future	O
keep	O
a	O
strict	O
watch	O
over	O
the	O
unſuſpecting	O
generoſity	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
heart	O
is	O
the	O
fervent	O
wiſh	O
of	O
your	O
affectionate	O
RGlover	B-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
unites	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
love	O
&	O
sentiments	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
July	O
15	O
:	O
1780	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
