TOKEN	NE
15	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
1785	O
Albemarle	O
Str	O
London	B-place
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
kind	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mother	O
made	O
us	O
both	O
weep	O
,	O
how	O
soothing	O
&	O
affectionate	O
;	O
indeed	O
our	O
loſs	O
is	O
irreparable	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
reflect	O
on	O
his	O
character	O
&	O
many	O
virtues	O
,	O
&	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
happier	O
than	O
this	O
world	O
ever	O
made	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
rather	O
reconciles	O
one	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
his	O
loſs	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
his	O
long	O
&	O
tedious	O
illneſs	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
fortitude	O
&	O
resignation	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
apprehended	O
himself	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
&	O
Docr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
both	O
thought	O
so	O
,	O
o	O
O	O
wing	O
to	O
the	O
laudanum	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
his	O
senses	O
quite	O
forsook	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
seldom	O
knew	O
my	O
mother	O
or	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Friday	O
fortnight	O
before	O
we	O
loſs't	O
him	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
senses	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
knowing	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
interrested	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
paſs	O
'd	O
I	O
will	O
copy	O
a	O
written	O
paper	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
down	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
.	O
“	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
..	O
of	O
Novr	O
:	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
rather	O
delirious	O
“	O
for	O
Some	O
days	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
day	O
awoke	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
chair	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
“	O
sleep	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
sitting	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
great	O
diſtreſs	O
calling	O
for	O
his	O
“	O
child	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
in	O
tears	O
,	O
grasp	O
'd	O
my	O
“	O
hand	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
my	O
own	O
my	O
dearest	O
child	O
,	O
he	O
addreſs	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
Virtue	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
“	O
Oh	O
virtue	O
virtue	O
,	O
God	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
who	O
is	O
truly	O
virtuous	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
“	O
walkd	O
in	O
her	O
paths	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
live	O
my	O
sweet	O
child	O
&	O
be	O
the	O
admiration	O
“	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
--	O
After	O
a	O
pause	O
he	O
addreſs	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
“	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
reason	O
to	O
approve	O
of	O
her	O
conduct	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
“	O
always	O
been	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
“	O
hour	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
spoke	O
of	O
truth	O
,	O
&	O
calld	O
on	O
God	O
&	O
looking	O
“	O
upwards	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
clasp	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
meet	O
his	O
maker	O
“	O
face	O
to	O
face	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
mother	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
mistrusted	O
”	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
asur	O
'd	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
justice	O
“	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
injured	O
him	O
;	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
“	O
was	O
very	O
composed	O
&	O
desired	O
no	O
one	O
might	O
be	O
permitted	O
to	O
come	O
“	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
his	O
son	O
coming	O
in	O
rather	O
abruptly	O
he	O
“	O
said	O
Richd	B-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Richd	B-pers
..	I-pers
,	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
complain	O
;	O
his	O
son	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
“	O
to	O
explain	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
mind	O
has	O
been	O
“	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
great	O
perterbation	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
“	O
explain	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
spoke	O
from	O
his	O
feeling	O
;	O
Richd	B-pers
..	I-pers
left	O
“	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Father	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
from	O
that	O
day	O
“	O
his	O
faculties	O
quite	O
forsook	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
will	O
weep	O
as	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
above	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
Idea	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
a	O
scene	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
his	O
countenance	O
,	O
his	O
tears	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
words	O
are	O
deeply	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
once	O
he	O
said	O
“	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
womens	O
tears	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
”	O
The	O
dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
comfort	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
constant	O
&	O
kind	O
attention	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
has	O
provided	O
amply	O
for	O
Richd	B-pers
..	I-pers
,	O
&	O
left	O
him	O
his	O
library	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
already	O
disposed	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
debt	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
miſstress	O
of	O
six	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
is	O
far	O
more	O
valuable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
than	O
money	O
,	O
are	O
his	O
manuscripts	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
greatest	O
proof	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
affection	O
;	O
my	O
excellent	O
mother	O
is	O
amply	O
provided	O
for	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
£800	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
disposal	O
the	O
plate	O
excepted	O
which	O
is	O
only	O
hers	O
for	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
goes	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
£800	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
perhaps	O
when	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
settl	O
'd	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Richd	B-pers
..	I-pers
comes	O
in	O
for	O
£11.000	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
behaviour	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
's	O
illneſs	O
was	O
very	O
faulty	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
almost	O
say	O
shocking	O
.	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tell	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
were	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
kind	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
esteem	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
your	O
sincere	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
my	O
Father	O
has	O
left	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lenton	I-pers
£200	O
..	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
with	O
our	O
dearest	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
busy	O
putting	O
up	O
some	O
books	O
,	O
she	O
looks	O
remarkably	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
well	O
;	O
She	O
desires	O
he	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
