TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1806	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
You	O
certainly	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
intelligence	O
I	O
sent	O
You	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
perceive	O
something	O
like	O
contrition	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
neglected	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
line	O
of	O
your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
very	O
condescendingly	O
grant	O
You	O
a	O
free	O
pardon	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
returns	O
You	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Poetry	O
you	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
lines	O
do	O
credit	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
was	O
was	O
true	O
of	O
old	O
Bet	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
old	O
Slut	O
,	O
though	O
bearing	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
resemblance	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
more	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
fat	O
Priest	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
than	O
of	O
an	O
English	O
Gentlewoman	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Melville	I-pers
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
replaced	O
on	O
the	O
List	O
of	O
Privy	O
Counsellors	O
,	O
the	O
moment	O
his	O
Peers	O
had	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Charges	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
Sovereign	O
having	O
wished	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
his	O
present	O
Advisers	O
seem	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
hasty	O
in	O
acknowledging	O
the	O
injury	O
They	O
have	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Lord	B-pers
Melville	I-pers
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
being	O
absent	O
from	O
Edinburgh	B-place
when	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
suited	O
my	O
convenience	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
North	O
as	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Duneira	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
situated	O
in	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
subject	O
to	O
Earthquakes	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Thunder	O
&	O
Lightning	O
have	O
rather	O
been	O
prevalent	O
this	O
Season	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
trusted	O
myself	O
where	O
Volcanic	O
Appearances	O
abound	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
entirely	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
Storms	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
travelling	O
twelve	O
Miles	O
in	O
the	O
Thunder	O
Storm	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
dreadful	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
so	O
much	O
mischief	O
was	O
done	O
both	O
in	O
England	B-place
&	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
Remember	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
answerable	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
B.	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Fleet	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
's	O
post	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
dated	O
off	O
Barbadoes	B-place
the	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
the	O
arrived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
sail	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
been	O
at	O
Newfoundland	B-place
.	O
Where	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
portion	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Sight	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
is	O
the	O
most	O
injured	O
Woman	O
,	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Britain	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prince	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
soon	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
A	O
credit	O
from	O
Meſsrs-	B-pers
Coutts	I-pers
has	O
been	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
Banks	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Clarence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
believe	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
penetrate	O
so	O
far	O
North	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
little	O
.	O
His	O
Lordship	O
&	O
his	O
Son	O
Frederick	B-pers
only	O
arrived	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
today	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
behave	O
properly	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
Invitation	O
to	O
a	O
Haunch	O
of	O
Venison	O
,	O
this	O
day	O
Week	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
are	O
with	O
Admiral	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Mounteviot	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
will	O
remain	O
till	O
his	O
Lordship	O
has	O
fixed	O
on	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
Residence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
its	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
,	O
is	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
prefer	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
be	O
difficult	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
procure	O
I	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
as	O
will	O
hold	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
our	O
being	O
very	O
cordial	O
here	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
on	O
me	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
his	O
arrival	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
previous	O
steps	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
Kings	O
&	O
Queens	O
,	O
or	O
Windsor	O
's	O
hereabout	O
,	O
and	O
We	O
are	O
as	O
Great	O
as	O
themselves	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
seeing	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
sitting	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
vastly	O
enjoy	O
such	O
a	O
Meeting	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
could	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
quite	O
delightful	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
such	O
happineſs	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
destined	O
for	O
Me	O
.	O
Pray	O
dont	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
your	O
Husband	O
s	O
shooting	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
really	O
been	O
a	O
Sportsman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
have	O
bent	O
his	O
steps	O
to	O
the	B-place
Highlands	I-place
to	O
shoot	O
.	O
With	O
best	O
Love	O
&	O
kind	O
wishes	O
from	O
all	O
here	O
to	O
all	O
at	O
Leighton	O
House	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Yourself	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
I	O
ever	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
September	O
1806	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
