TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
November	O
21	O
st	O
1785	O
.	O
/	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
./	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
your	O
friendly	O
Letter	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
--	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
whenever	O
I	O
had	O
leisure	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
my	O
not	O
having	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
b	O
een	O
much	O
agitated	O
lately	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
expectation	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
--	O
She	O
arriv	O
'd	O
in	O
London	B-place
last	O
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
to	O
conceive	O
my	O
joy	O
upon	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
after	O
an	O
absence	O
of	O
upwards	O
of	O
3	O
years	O
&	O
a	O
half	O
--	O
my	O
joy	O
is	O
much	O
embitter	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
being	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
I	O
fear	O
not	O
a	O
Week	O
longer	O
--	O
it	O
breaks	O
my	O
Heart	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
our	O
separation	O
,	O
for	O
Heaven	O
knows	O
when	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
again	O
--	O
we	O
may	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
we	O
expect	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
was	O
a	O
chance./	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
last	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Brumpton	B-place
to	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
this	O
Morning	O
to	O
Wandsworth-Hill	B-place
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
are	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
uneasy	O
about	O
little	O
Charles	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Cold	O
that	O
occasions	O
a	O
swelling	O
in	O
his	O
Throat./	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
he	O
also	O
bids	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Gyfardière	I-pers
's	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
saw	O
not	O
long	O
ago./	O
Poor	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
is	O
likely	O
to	O
die	O
very	O
soon	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
pity	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
!	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
--	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
very	O
little	O
as	O
yet	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Play	O
--	O
not	O
on	O
a	O
Night	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
perform	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
expects	O
to	O
be	O
confin	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
yet	O
goes	O
on	O
performing	O
still	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
better	O
than	O
ever	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Creature	O
is	O
she	O
not	O
?	O
--	O
Is	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
yet	O
?	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
pray	O
prese	O
nt	O
my	O
Compliments	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
Are	O
your	O
Caves	O
and	O
Grottoes	O
finish	O
'd	O
yet	O
?	O
--	O
London	B-place
is	O
not	O
yet	O
near	O
full	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
--	O
the	O
Parliament	O
sat	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
that	O
people	O
are	O
glad	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Summer	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
they	O
can	O
,	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
Town./	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
practising	O
Music	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
some	O
improvement	O
this	O
last	O
Summer	O
;	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
so	O
--	O
Are	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
musical	O
?	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
is	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
Music./	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
visit	O
London	B-place
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
not	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
your	O
present	O
situation./	O
My	O
Brother	O
was	O
much	O
gratified	O
by	O
your	O
writing	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
affectionate	O
--	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
forget	O
those	O
who	O
show	O
friendship	O
to	O
him./	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
I	O
look	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
stronger	O
for	O
having	O
spent	O
the	O
Summer	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
I	O
bath	O
'd	O
pretty	O
constantly	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
believe	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
me./	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
stupid	O
Letter	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
news	O
to	O
tell	O
you./	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
Accept	O
their	O
best	O
Wishes	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
yours	O
affectionately./	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
/	O
P	O
:	O
S	O
:	O
Make	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
and	O
Mother	O
's	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel-le-Frith	B-place
Cheshire	B-place
