TOKEN	NE
Chelsea	B-place
3	O
d	O
.	O
Apl	O
1785	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Any	O
point	O
relative	O
to	O
your	O
Happyneſs	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatterd	O
in	O
being	O
referrd	O
to	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
every	O
Confidence	O
you	O
place	O
in	O
me	O
shall	O
remain	O
unreveald	O
=	O
Delicacy	O
,	O
the	O
characteristic	O
of	O
yourself	O
,	O
naturally	O
makes	O
me	O
attentive	O
to	O
that	O
point	O
--	O
but	O
in	O
such	O
eſsential	O
matters	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
relief	O
to	O
your	O
friends	O
that	O
;	O
more	O
or	O
leſs	O
M.r	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dickeson	I-pers
's	O
father	O
s	O
fortune	O
(	O
for	O
present	O
maintenance	O
as	O
usual	O
I	O
shd	O
understand	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
after	O
any	O
debts	O
or	O
provisions	O
for	O
his	O
younger	O
Children	O
shoud	O
be	O
mentiond	O
&	O
your	O
provision	O
in	O
proportion	O
thereto	O
as	O
to	O
Remainder	O
be	O
such	O
as	O
this	O
liberality	O
consistent	O
with	O
the	O
Means	O
--	O
naturally	O
woud	O
dictate	O
--	O
Any	O
adventious	O
incidents	O
out	O
of	O
Question	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
whenever	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickeson	I-pers
intended	O
in	O
meeting	O
me	O
at	O
Chester	B-place
&	O
his	O
Confidence	O
placed	O
in	O
my	O
Character	O
,	O
The	O
circumstances	O
attending	O
my	B-pers
family	I-pers
prevents	O
my	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
avail	O
my	O
self	O
thereof	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsurd	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
Candid	O
consideration	O
&	O
privacy	O
in	O
any	O
point	O
you	O
may	O
Communicate	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Ms	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
affte	O
frd	O
.	O
&	O
obt	O
servt	O
Dartrey	B-pers
