TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Sund	O
a	O
y	O
Night	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Tho	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
most	O
likely	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
yet	O
to	O
convince	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
ke	O
p	O
e	O
p	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
Pen	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
I	O
can	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
with	O
&	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
in	O
due	O
time	O
spend	O
some	O
comfortable	O
hours	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
this	O
day	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
happy	O
one	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
that	O
no	O
unlucky	O
expreſsion	O
has	O
embittered	O
it	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
most	O
heartily	O
&	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
you	O
happineſs	O
,	O
thorns	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
every	O
state	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
contented	O
mind	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
experience	O
gathers	O
the	O
Roses	O
notwithstand	O
in	O
g	O
&	O
such	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
yours	O
is	O
.	O
We	O
arrived	O
safe	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Seven	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
spent	O
the	O
Evg	O
till	O
9	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
this	O
Morg	O
at	O
eight	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
after	O
breakfasted	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
s	O
new	O
Room	O
with	O
Genl	B-pers
Fritag	I-pers
Genl	B-pers
Budé	I-pers
Col	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Arnald	I-pers
,	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
Princes	O
&	O
all	O
their	O
Gentlemen	O
afterwards	O
took	O
their	O
walk	O
,	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
read	O
us	O
a	O
Sermon	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Egremont	I-pers
attending	O
,	O
nothing	O
worth	O
relating	O
paſsed	O
from	O
that	O
hour	O
till	O
nine	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
&	O
dined	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
that	O
you	O
remember	O
,	O
I	O
often	O
thought	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
wished	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
dont	O
die	O
,	O
but	O
Baron	B-pers
Albrlaben	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
morrow	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
go	O
to	O
Eton	B-place
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Boys	O
deliver	O
their	O
Speeches	O
,	O
I	O
scarcely	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
as	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
does	O
not	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
add	O
another	O
line	O
but	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Afftly	O
Yr	O
MCG——	B-pers
we	O
do	O
not	O
set	O
out	O
till	O
6	O
o	O
Clock	O
Tuesd	O
a	O
y	O
Evg	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	B-place
Prince	I-place
Ernest	I-place
House	I-place
Kew	B-place
