TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
-	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
Febry-	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
be	O
informed	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
safe	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
found	O
my	O
Landlord	O
determined	O
to	O
die	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
fulfilled	O
his	O
purpose	O
by	O
departing	O
this	O
Life	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
&	O
still	O
lies	O
in	O
State	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
over	O
my	O
Bedchamber	O
.	O
Monday	O
next	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
is	O
fixed	O
for	O
his	O
funeral	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
your	O
Note	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
The	B-pers
Counteſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accept	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
's	I-pers
Majesty	I-pers
has	O
been	O
indisposed	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
Yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	I-pers
Majesty	I-pers
has	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Concert	O
of	O
Antient	O
Musick	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
folks	O
say	O
all	O
is	O
right	O
;	O
others	O
,	O
maintain	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
opinion	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
everything	O
kind	O
from	O
Me	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
may	O
be	O
believed	O
and	O
,	O
That	O
I	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
M	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
remaining	O
ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
's	O
Very	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
