TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
pt	O
one	O
Monday	O
A	O
Thousand	O
thanks	O
my	O
Dearest	O
for	O
yr-	O
kind	O
Notes	O
,	O
as	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
not	O
yet	O
to	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
her	O
Answer	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
the	O
Dear	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
Dressages	O
Literaires	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
certain	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
seize	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
kindly	O
I	O
feel	O
yr-	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
poor	O
Beale	B-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
yr-	O
account	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
much	O
better	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
seriosly	O
alarmed	O
about	O
her	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
imagine	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
all	O
distreſsed	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
Pascal	B-pers
does	O
my	O
Hair	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
it	O
my	O
Head	O
being	O
in	O
order	O
is	O
of	O
consequence	O
here	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
eſsential	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
my	O
Dear	O
be	O
alarmed	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
yesterday	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
differente	O
reprises	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
well	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
fine	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
with	O
P	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
feel	O
the	O
Sun	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
exceſsively	O
sharp	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
heard	O
Mr	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
&	O
me	O
dispute	O
about	O
Sr	B-pers
C	I-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
an	O
excellent	O
Politician	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Believe	O
me	O
very	O
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Since	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
above	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
pleased	O
their	O
R	O
Hs	O
have	O
continued	O
their	O
writing	O
,	O
but	O
does	O
not	O
think	O
Pſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
so	O
well	O
as	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
either	O
the	O
Sense	O
or	O
Handwriting	O
,	O
wishes	O
Mr	B-pers
Guiffardier	I-pers
would	O
when	O
he	O
corrects	O
the	O
the	O
false	O
spelling	O
likewise	O
correct	O
or	O
rather	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
write	O
the	O
extract	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
correct	O
manner	O
or	O
to	O
use	O
her	O
own	O
Words	O
in	O
better	O
Sense	O
.	O
my	O
Love	O
and	O
Duty	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
little	O
Dears	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizth	I-pers
&	O
P	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
Swelling	O
in	O
their	O
Face	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
further	O
consequence	O
--	O
P	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
