TOKEN	NE
27	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
29	O
th	O
-	O
Janry-	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
told	O
that	O
when	O
a	O
Lady	O
writes	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
She	O
never	O
explains	O
her	O
meaning	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Postscript	O
.	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
Inst-	O
seems	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
observation	O
,	O
for	O
after	O
commanding	O
Me	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
You	O
stick	O
in	O
a	O
scrap	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
“	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
“	O
this	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
”	O
Without	O
this	O
latitude	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
have	O
sent	O
my	O
Servant	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
's	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
although	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
odd	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
enquiries	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Beds	B-place
,	O
&	O
not	O
in	O
Town	B-place
to	O
receive	O
the	O
answer	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
inclosed	O
Notes	O
of	O
enquiry	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
,	O
or	O
for	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
should	O
have	O
delivered	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
They	O
,	O
would	O
probably	O
have	O
sent	O
You	O
an	O
Answer	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
entire	O
Stranger	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
somewhat	O
surprised	O
at	O
receiving	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Consequently	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
none	O
.	O
Your	O
three	O
packets	O
have	O
not	O
reached	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
me	O
Manuscript	O
papers	O
?	O
I	O
sent	O
You	O
a	O
paper	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
Queries	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
to	O
You	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
Graciously	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
marked	O
the	O
Answers	O
,	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
s	O
paper	O
,	O
the	O
full	O
purpose	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
answered	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Manuscripts	O
might	O
have	O
remained	O
in	O
perfect	O
security	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
.	O
It	O
is	O
lucky	O
for	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
your	O
Hub	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
scolded	O
You	O
for	O
running	O
the	O
Risque	O
of	O
losing	O
your	O
Papers	O
.	O
Major	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
not	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
,	O
is	O
at	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Moore	I-pers
's	O
Aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
,	O
Anderson	B-pers
,	O
is	O
not	O
her	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
.	O
With	O
best	O
affections	O
to	O
Yourself	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
With	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
no	O
good	O
Apples	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
--	O
London	B-place
,	O
Thirtieth	O
January	O
1809	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
.	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
