TOKEN	NE
1782	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
to	O
Decbr	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
&	O
Jan	O
7.	O
to	O
Feb	O
6	O
'	O
178	O
2	O
3	O
Novr	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
to	O
Decbr	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
1782	O
Wedn	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1782	O
came	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
at	O
--	O
2	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
at	O
3	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
28	O
Thursday	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
go	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
from	O
12	O
--	O
till	O
1	O
oClock	O
To	O
Lady	B-pers
CFinch	I-pers
at	O
3	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Dine	O
there	O
Ld	B-pers
Bellemont	I-pers
--	O
call	O
upon	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
7	O
--	O
come	O
home	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
E	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Friday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
xxx	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
e	O
t	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
8	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Satry	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
at	O
10	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
to	O
see	O
ye	O
Pictures	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
came	O
,	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
till	O
near	O
4	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyêres	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Coach	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
dr	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
only	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
--	O
had	O
my	B-pers
U	I-pers
.	I-pers
C	O
.	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
alone	O
ye	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
Sunday	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1782	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Doctr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
Madm	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
La	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
(	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
)	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
home	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
.	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
came	O
there	O
to	O
Tea	O
)	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
8	O
at	O
Dr	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
10	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
Monday	O
2	O
d	O
..	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
AMClarke	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
from	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
at	O
12	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
&	O
paid	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
&	O
Madle	B-pers
.	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
.	I-pers
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
&	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schewelenberg	I-pers
.	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Cates	O
Mrs	B-pers
E	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
&	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
--	O
went	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
from	O
8	O
till	O
10.	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Wedn	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Col.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
my	O
Uncle	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Patoon	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Coll	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
staid	O
sometime	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Tuffnell	I-pers
s	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
Din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
their	O
Coach	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
11	O
oClock	O
5	O
th	O
Decbr	O
1782	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
came	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
--	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
sat	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
saw	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
staid	O
some	O
time	O
and	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
at	O
4	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
dined	O
wth	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Aunt	O
.	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
Had	O
his	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mry	I-pers
..	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
there	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
(	O
Company	O
there	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Beauvoir	I-pers
s	O
door	O
.	O
&	O
at	O
Ld	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
staid	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10.	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
6	O
th	O
Decbr	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
came	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
some	O
time	O
to	O
talk	O
abt	O
her	O
affairs	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
at	O
11	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
Atholl	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
My	O
Uncle	O
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym	O
Call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
to	O
ye	O
Queens	O
House	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
wth	O
Miſs	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
--	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
.	O
Ldy-	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
&	O
c	O
there	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
3	O
books	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
pattern	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ha	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
back	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
--	O
met	O
Col	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Lite	I-pers
.	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Majendie	I-pers
Col.	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schelenbergen	I-pers
s	O
Servt	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
from	O
5	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
at	O
7	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
¾	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
th	O
Decbr	O
..	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
for	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
Houses	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
him	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
from	O
2	O
till	O
3	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
ye	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
alone	O
to	O
arrange	O
my	O
things	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
commiſsion	O
abt	O
ye	O
.	O
picture	O
I	O
Sent	O
in	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schelenbergen	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
.	I-pers
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
4	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
only	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
taken	O
Ill	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
N	I-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
came	O
home	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
th	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
better	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Vandergutch	I-pers
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
made	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schwellengberg	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
drawings	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Picture	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
4	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
.	O
at	O
7.	O
went	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
for	O
10	O
Min	O
:	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
there	O
.	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Decbr	O
10	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
staid	O
2	O
Hours	O
.	O
settled	O
abt	O
Goodyar	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaneys	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
came	O
--	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
did	O
not	O
See	O
him	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
came	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
s	O
sat	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Swinburne	I-pers
)	O
Mr	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
there	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
I	O
calld	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
House	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
there	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
to	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
(	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
sent	O
me	O
his	O
Papers	O
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
11	O
Decbr	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vandergutch	I-pers
who	O
took	O
away	O
39	O
Pictures	O
for	O
200	O
£	O
.	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
paid	O
2	O
Months	O
from	O
this	O
date	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
4	O
dined	O
&	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
I	O
am	O
settled	O
--	O
only	O
ourselves	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
1782	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
sat	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
her	O
room	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
Accounts	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Claude	I-pers
Crespinny	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
then	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
D.	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
sat	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
.	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
American	O
Phamplet	O
call	O
'd	O
common	O
Sense	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Cards	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
workd	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Reevely	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Deveyanes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
Friday	O
13	O
Debr	O
.	O
--	O
Whilst	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
from	O
Richmond	B-place
came	O
in	O
.	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
12.	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
one	O
oClock	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Son	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
saw	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
20	O
Min	O
after	O
1	O
--	O
sat	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
min	O
.	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
sat	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Phamplet	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
--	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
&	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
near	O
ten	O
.	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Postscript	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Phamplet	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
.	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Palmerston	I-pers
14	O
th	O
.	O
Satry	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mee	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Book	O
Adele	O
et	O
Theodore	O
--	O
his	O
disapprobation	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Work	O
--	O
Mde	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Luton	I-pers
s	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
Glover	B-pers
came	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
Call	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Aufreres	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
--	O
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
D.	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Schelenberg	I-pers
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Picture	O
--	O
About	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chetwynd	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
what	O
they	O
said	O
Kindly	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
P	B-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Phamplet	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Day	I-pers
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
American	O
War	O
--	O
+	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
--	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
a	O
B	O
ag	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
+	O
she	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
Sunday	O
15	O
th	O
:	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
--	O
read	O
Prayers	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
G——	I-pers
--	O
had	O
my	O
Hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Goodyar	B-pers
s	O
Room	O
--	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
Lord	B-pers
Fitzmorris	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye-	O
Tutor	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
.	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Read	O
ye	O
Bible	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
8	O
Mast	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Dawson	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
acroſs	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
s	O
sat	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
--	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Supper	O
Monday	O
1	O
7	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
about	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
of	I-pers
Germany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hotchkinsons	O
&	O
she	O
bought	O
gowns	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Set	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
down	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
with	O
her	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
with	O
her	O
staid	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
at	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
had	O
been	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
gave	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
lines	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
after	O
Supper	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Verses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Tuesday	O
17	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
did	O
not	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Aunt	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
ye	O
2	O
Pictures	O
&	O
paid	O
me	O
100	O
£	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
staid	O
till	O
1	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
A	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
at	O
2	O
she	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
4	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
J	O
.	O
Palace	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
s	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
Dreſsden	O
China	O
Brought	O
there	O
to	O
shew	O
ym	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
to	O
rem	O
ain	O
there	O
till	O
it	O
is	O
valued	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
s	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
sat	O
there	O
till	O
supper	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
wth	O
us	O
Wedn	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
Isabella	O
of	O
ye	O
fatal	O
Marriage	O
I	O
workd	O
her	O
some	O
Shoes	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
call	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
have	O
ye	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Pictures	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
went	O
out	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
came	O
back	O
unexpectedly	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Reevely	I-pers
a	O
Bride	O
&	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Jason	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
staid	O
supper	O
.	O
Decbr	O
19	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
little	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
wth	O
.	O
K.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Educ	O
t	O
a	O
tion	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
our	O
future	O
Plan	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
offer	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
A.M.C	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
visit	O
me	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
4	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
&	O
Dowg	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
also	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Millsington	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
after	O
supper	O
talkd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Character	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
amp	O
;	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Friday	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
sat	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Portman	I-pers
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
talkd	O
over	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Mar̄iage	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
Did	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
MrColl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
introduced	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
as	O
did	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Note	O
from	O
Frederick	B-pers
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
Dinner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
excused	O
myself	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
together	O
--	O
ab.t	O
.	O
8	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Card	O
's	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
them	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
9	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
staid	O
Supper	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
read	O
one	O
Scene	O
of	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Tragedy	O
he	O
wrote	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
16	O
--	O
and	O
wch	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
for	O
50	O
years	O
Ethelmond	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
Saturday	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.M.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Vandergutch	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
just	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Reevely	I-pers
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
Mrs	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
again	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
Houses	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
AM	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
Room	O
We	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
had	O
been	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Reevely	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Reevely	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
Sunday	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1782	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
little	O
Daughter	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Sr	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
there	O
--	O
So	O
Is	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
Garden	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
from	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
to	O
ye	O
Q	O
House	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
too	O
Ill	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schewellenberg	I-pers
--	O
met	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Guiffadiere	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bab	I-pers
Planta	I-pers
--	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
--	O
met	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stephens	I-pers
who	O
walk	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Door	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lyte	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
c	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
at	O
4	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
only	O
their	O
own	O
family	O
&	O
a	O
Col.	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
--	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
in	O
our	O
return	O
home	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
Decbr-	O
23	O
d	O
Monday	O
--	O
had	O
been	O
indisposed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Night	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
Spendlove	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
her	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
12	O
to	O
see	O
Houses	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
dreſs	O
till	O
after	O
dinner	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
the	O
2	O
M	O
r	O
Grevilles	O
--	O
Dowg	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
Supper	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
f	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Pliny	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
Decbr	O
.	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
sent	O
notes	O
to	O
Cicero	B-pers
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
F.	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.e	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Conduit	O
Street	O
.	O
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
sister	O
into	O
ye	O
City	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
went	O
on	O
&	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
Marriage	O
--	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
Supper	O
time	O
&	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
25	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Weday	O
Xmaſs	O
Day	O
was	O
disappointed	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
(	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
alone	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
She	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
letting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
become	O
Pensioner	O
at	O
2	O
£	O
2	O
S	O
pr	O
.	O
Year	O
--	O
after	O
+	O
12	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Is	B-pers
:	I-pers
there	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
.	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Mr.Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
Both	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
death	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
my	B-pers
Mother	I-pers
read	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
Book	O
&	O
read	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Lycidas	O
--	O
Milton	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Young	O
Canary	O
Bird	O
in	O
a	O
present	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
before	O
Supper	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
some	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Gray	B-pers
26	O
th	O
Decbr	O
Thursday	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
ask	O
my	O
advice	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
private	O
altercation	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Winter	O
Quarters	O
at	O
Shaftsbury	B-place
Dorset	B-place
:	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
&	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Do	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
enquired	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
she	O
was	O
better	O
Mrs	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
Do	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Egertons	O
--	O
to	O
thank	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chartaris	I-pers
for	O
my	O
Cap	O
.	O
they	O
sat	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
s	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
s	O
staid	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
D.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
pictures	O
55	O
£	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
in	O
May	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vandergutch	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
home	O
before	O
Supper	O
--	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
staid	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
talking	O
over	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
affairs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Decbr	O
27	O
th	O
..	O
Friday	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
Claude	I-pers
Crespiny	I-pers
till	O
12	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
her	O
Chaise	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
at	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
saw	O
her	O
3	O
little	O
Boys	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
in	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
different	O
Subjects	O
We	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
2	O
.	O
Met	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
W.H	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
My	O
Uncle	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Frederick	B-pers
of	O
Hannover	O
Street	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
not	O
knowing	O
I	O
was	O
remov	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
tragedy	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
for	O
50	O
years	O
--	O
it	O
uncorrected	O
.	O
Ethelmond	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
Spendlove	I-pers
at	O
supper	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
Saturday	O
After	O
B——	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Harley	O
Street	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
sometime	O
saw	O
her	O
little	O
Boy	O
.	O
she	O
sat	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s.	O
saw	O
Dg	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
met	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
.	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
½	O
an	O
Hour	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
staid	O
sometime	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schewllenberg	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Effingham	I-pers
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
met	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
L	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
&	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
Uncle	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
:	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
all	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
at	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
a	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
Il	O
n	O
'	O
y	O
a	O
rien	O
de	O
plus	O
vî	O
te	O
oublié	O
,	O
qu'une	O
personne	O
qui	O
veut	O
l'être	O
;	O
son	O
recueillement	O
est	O
la	O
nouvelle	O
du	O
jour	O
,	O
&	O
le	O
lendemain	O
on	O
n'en	O
parle	O
plus	O
.	O
Quand	O
on	O
n'est	O
joyeux	O
que	O
par	O
étourderie	O
ou	O
par	O
occasion	O
,	O
le	O
cœur	O
demeure	O
livré	O
aux	O
remords	O
ou	O
au	O
dégoût	O
.	O
L'amour	O
de	O
nos	O
devoirs	O
nous	O
aſsocie	O
à	O
tous	O
les	O
gens	O
de	O
bien	O
,	O
&	O
l'amour	O
du	O
vice	O
nous	O
mets	O
en	O
société	O
avec	O
tous	O
les	O
méchants	O
.	O
Votre	O
ame	O
ne	O
s'agrandira	O
qu'autant	O
que	O
,	O
fermes	O
sans	O
rudeſse	O
;	O
économes	O
,	O
sans	O
avarice	O
;	O
généreux	O
,	O
sans	O
prodigalité	O
,	O
vous	O
ennoblirez	O
toutes	O
vos	O
actions	O
.	O
Prenez	O
garde	O
de	O
vous	O
de	O
dedommager	O
en	O
secret	O
de	O
la	O
réserve	O
que	O
vous	O
ferez	O
paroître	O
:	O
il	O
ne	O
faut	O
pas	O
perdre	O
de	O
vue	O
qu'on	O
doit	O
être	O
vertueux	O
pour	O
soi-même	O
&	O
pour	O
le	O
Ciel	O
,	O
&	O
que	O
l'Honnête	O
homme	O
est	O
celui	O
qui	O
ne	O
craint	O
ni	O
la	O
critique	O
,	O
ni	O
l'examen	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
Mr	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Louis-Antoine	B-pers
Caraccioli	I-pers
's	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
left	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
Georges	O
Church	O
.	O
After	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
I	O
went	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
&	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
&	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
bedside	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
walkd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
found	O
him	O
better	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hatham	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
was	O
introduced	O
to	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
Din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
2	O
Grevilles	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
Loan	O
Decbr	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
Monday	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Clarkes	B-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
walk	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
terms	O
--	O
partly	O
agree	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
whom	O
we	O
met	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
ym	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
told	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
what	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
&	O
dictated	O
to	O
me	O
an	O
agreement	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
.	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
written	O
in	O
1753	O
in	O
6	O
weeks	O
--	O
Nadir	O
Shaw	O
.	O
he	O
finish	O
'd	O
it	O
after	O
Supper	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
ye	O
.	O
agreement	O
to	O
sign	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Dr.	B-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
a	O
moment	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
Lodgings	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
for	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
CFinch	I-pers
.	O
went	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
s	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
they	O
were	O
all	O
,	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Key	O
's	O
of	O
ye	O
Apartments	O
.	O
a	O
Man	O
from	O
Mde	B-pers
..	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
--	O
abt	O
.	O
Moddeling	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vunder	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Humes	O
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym-	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
a	O
Mry	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
--	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
M	I-pers
Burdieu	I-pers
--	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveng	O
there	O
a	O
Mary	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
drunk	O
tea	O
there	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sang	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
leſsons	O
Concluded	O
ye	O
.	O
Year	O
very	O
happily	O
1	O
st	O
Janry	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
The	O
Glovers	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
&	O
gave	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
a	O
locket	O
of	O
my	O
Hair	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
a	O
locket	O
for	O
her	O
Han	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
5	O
oClock	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
2	O
Grevilles	O
--	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
read	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
Glover	O
s	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Genl	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
there	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryuyeres	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
8	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
a	O
Ball	O
for	O
her	O
Young	O
Scholars	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
Miſs	O
3	O
rd	O
.	O
Friday	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Sisters	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
to	O
dinner	O
&	O
Supper	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
tea	O
&	O
Supper	O
.	O
singing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Saturday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
there	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
.	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
WKing	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
brought	O
5	O
th	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
read	O
Prayers	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
c	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Manners	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
WKing	I-pers
at	O
Supper	O
.	O
Sunday	O
Mrs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
Do	O
..	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
read	O
prayers	O
to	O
Clarkes	B-pers
&	O
c.	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
's	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
abt	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
came	O
at	O
4	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Whitemore	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Tea	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Monday	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hallifax	I-pers
who	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Adam	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
)	O
at	O
7	O
had	O
a	O
Chair	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
came	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
had	O
a	O
Chair	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
s	O
to	O
Supper	O
met	O
there	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Reveleys	B-pers
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Clarks	B-pers
.	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
ye	O
Morning	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
¼	O
after	O
9	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Spendlove	I-pers
s	O
&	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
.	O
walkd	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
told	O
him	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
locks	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schewellenberg	I-pers
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brighouse	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
we	O
read	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
9	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
8	O
th	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
over	O
my	O
leaving	O
Court	O
.	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ed	I-pers
.	I-pers
Bentink	I-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Study	O
abt	O
.	O
corre	O
cting	O
his	O
Poem	O
for	O
Publication	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
Exerter	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
we	O
read	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
.	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriage	O
w	O
ith	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
found	O
only	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
shopping	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
met	O
us	O
we	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
-	O
Pauls	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
out	O
After	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
we	O
workd	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
after	O
to	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
after	O
Suppe	O
r	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
American	O
book	O
Hist	O
:	O
Nantucket	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Son	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
10	O
Tuesday	O
10	O
th	O
after	O
B	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
G	I-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
Dſs	B-pers
Rutland	I-pers
Portland	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
ym	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Do	O
Met	O
Ldy	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
Park	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
She	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
we	O
parted	O
=	O
Lord	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
after	O
Dinner	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Col	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
s	O
Ldy	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
there	O
Ldy	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
&	O
we	O
all	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
Satry	O
11	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
came	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
his	O
Poem	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
F	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
&	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
found	O
only	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
at	O
home	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
--	O
D	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
Young	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
their	O
2	O
daughters	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Pery	I-pers
2	O
M	O
r	O
Wartons	O
Sup	O
'd	O
--	O
there	O
at	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
2	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
Sunday	O
12	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
staid	O
alone	O
with	O
Dr	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
till	O
12	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
s	O
only	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
went	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
Jacksons	B-pers
--	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
as	O
did	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
ye	O
Banker	O
to	O
Supper	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Monday	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
Janry	O
After	O
B——	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
ye	O
Workmen	O
went	O
on	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
AMClarke	I-pers
sat	O
wth-	O
him	O
sometime	O
(	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
went	O
on	O
Satry	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
stay	O
till	O
Wedn——	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
Edmund	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Gel	B-pers
'	I-pers
Budé	I-pers
s	O
to	O
visit	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
of	O
Taplow	B-place
--	O
she	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
at	O
her	O
Door	O
conversed	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
little	O
Girl	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
went	O
Lord	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
s	O
Man	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
came	O
at	O
3	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
My	O
Uncle	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
had	O
his	O
Coach	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
his	O
Son	O
ye	O
Page	O
of	O
Honor	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
--	O
Genl	B-pers
Freytag	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bryuyeres	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
--	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
had	O
the	O
Coach	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
Young	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
sat	O
up	O
wth	O
Coll	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
after	O
ye	O
rest	O
retired	O
talk	O
of	O
America	B-place
Tuesday	O
14	O
Jan	O
Ducheſs	O
of	O
&	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Friday	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Cath	O
cart	O
Sat	O
14	O
Call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
together	O
15	O
Met	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
in	O
Clarges	O
Str	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
D	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
16	O
Go	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
dinner	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
read	O
--	O
17	O
th	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
go	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
18	O
th	O
Sat	O
wth	O
Dr	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
King	I-pers
at	O
My	O
Uncle	O
calld	O
sat	O
wth	O
him	O
dind	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
G——	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
R	B-pers
Wa	I-pers
8	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
Supper	O
19	O
Read	O
Prayers	O
at	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
&	O
Dr	B-pers
Ma	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
brought	O
me	O
his	O
Poem	O
Nobility	O
as	O
a	O
present	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Mulso	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
1	O
2	O
sat	O
with	O
him	O
sometime	O
.	O
I	O
walkd	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
--	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Came	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
7	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
Staid	O
at	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tattridge	I-pers
--	O
I	O
read	O
out	O
frm	O
.	O
7	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
An	O
Oriental	O
Comedy	O
written	O
30	O
years	O
ago	O
in	O
16	O
days	O
--	O
ye	O
Brattling	O
Barber	O
an	O
uncorrected	O
Manuscript	O
Copy	O
.	O
--	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Monday	O
.	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
house	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Sorted	O
my	O
Clothes	O
&	O
linnen	O
.	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
with	O
Mr	B-pers
--	O
they	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
us	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
oClock	O
--	O
21	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
staid	O
sometime	O
with	O
Col	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Private	O
Phamplet	O
relative	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
interesting	O
Anecdotes	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
came	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Whist	O
wth	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
22	O
d	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
had	O
Sr-	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
paid	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
ye	B-pers
late	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
CFinch	I-pers
went	O
for	O
¼	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Macke	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Athol	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Murry	I-pers
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
sometime	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
2.	O
went	O
to	O
Md	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
abt	O
Peace	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
--	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Whist	O
--	O
Schewlengberg	B-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth-	O
Coll	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
dau	O
ghter	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
Thursday	O
.	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
arra	O
n	O
ged	O
my	O
Books	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
calld	O
there	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
came	O
&	O
fetchd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
go	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
--	O
they	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
with	O
us	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
--	O
we	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
past	O
10	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
Peace	O
was	O
concluded	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Party	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
talk	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Peace	O
&	O
.	O
24	O
Friday	O
--	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
all	O
Morning	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
out	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
,	O
just	O
to	O
give	O
some	O
some	O
orders	O
Came	O
back	O
by	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
to	O
tea	O
&	O
Cards	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
Sent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
G	I-pers
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Do	O
.	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
not	O
to	O
dine	O
Sunday	O
--	O
2	O
nd	O
..	O
Febry	O
.	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
Morng	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
we	O
had	O
Mr	B-pers
read	O
parts	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
&	O
slept	O
there	O
for	O
ye	O
1	O
st	O
time	O
--	O
parted	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
day	O
--	O
Monday	O
3	O
d	O
Febry	O
all	O
day	O
Tuesday	O
4	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
&	O
Glover	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
5	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
--	O
Goodyar	B-pers
--	O
went	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
breakfasted	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
afternoon	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
A	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
&	O
Sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
my	O
Birthday	O
spent	O
very	O
happily	O
--	O
every	O
one	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
sent	O
something	O
for	O
Supper	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
provide	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
Bed	O
till	O
2.	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
Punch	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
6	O
th	O
Thursday	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
3	O
Waistcoats	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
's	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
She	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
for	O
Court	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
went	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
to	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Harpur	O
Street	O
in	O
ye	B-place
City	I-place
--	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
Sup	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
ye	O
Stoloffs	O
&	O
Burgeſs	O
's	O
&	O
c.	O
singing	O
after	O
Supper	O
7	O
th	O
Friday	O
Had	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
2	O
hours	O
whilst	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Egertons	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
s	O
at	O
7	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
¼	O
to	O
9.	O
went	O
to	O
Argyle	O
House	O
saw	O
ye	O
Prince	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Colonade	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
sitting	O
&	O
reading	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
P	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
Devanys	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W.	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
parted	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
North	I-pers
had	O
been	O
&	O
Coll	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Fite	I-pers
s	O
--	O
dine	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
--	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
coach	O
--	O
made	O
a	O
Cap	O
for	O
Is	B-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
out	O
at	O
8	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
she	O
read	O
one	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Plays	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
.	O
13	O
Friday	O
March	O
1783	O
Thursday	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
her	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
therefore	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
excuse	O
myself	O
dining	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
s	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Thompson	B-pers
s	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
with	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
.	O
staid	O
with	O
ym	O
.	O
till	O
8	O
.	O
Goodyar	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
out	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Miniatures	O
&	O
c.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
8	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
11	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
scene	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Belamont	I-pers
out	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
Sigismunda	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
Friday	O
14	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
Walpole	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Thompson	B-pers
&	O
their	O
Daughters	O
Compte	B-pers
Marshalle	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
M	O
air	O
d	O
read	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
read	O
Mr	B-pers
s	O
C	O
o	O
riolanus	O
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Satry	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
at	O
Breakfast	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Is	B-pers
:	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym	O
..	O
.	O
Thompson	B-pers
came	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
up	O
whilst	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
.	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
9	O
had	O
Dr	B-pers
carriage	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kenient	I-pers
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
s	O
Aſsembly	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
12.	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
c	O
Sunday	O
16	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
french	O
Chappel	O
--	O
heard	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
preach	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
A.	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Str	O
.	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
there	O
)	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
&	O
Mons	B-pers
Rustan	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
ca	O
me	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
staid	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
we	O
read	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Seasons	O
.	O
16	O
March	O
Monday	O
17	O
th	O
March	O
1783	O
at	O
12	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
calld	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
s	O
Do	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Nosegay	O
&	O
c	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Whist	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
went	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
calld	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Egertons	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
died	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
left	O
Names	O
a	O
t	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Col	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
B.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Durham	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
s	O
&	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Son	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
Supper	O
only	O
themselves	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
Tuesday	O
18	O
th	O
went	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s	O
drawings	O
--	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
not	O
up	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
the	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
My	O
Uncle	O
at	O
2	O
to	O
meet	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
they	O
settled	O
about	O
my	O
Cousins	O
going	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Geneva	B-place
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
near	O
4	O
oClock	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
wrote	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
10	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
's	O
Aſsembly	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11.	O
went	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
there	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
12	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Wedn	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
Mrs	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
left	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
came	O
we	O
read	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
2	O
hours	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chetwynd	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
Lecture	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
Sheridan	B-pers
Thursday	O
March	O
20	O
th	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
came	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
met	O
there	O
ye	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Frytag	I-pers
&	O
ye-	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
ye	O
Painter	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
Picture	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Salomons	I-pers
there	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Whole	O
day	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Opie	B-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscript	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Leonidas	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
.	O
March	O
20	O
1783	O
Sat	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
picture	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
Rose	O
tree	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mac'Konochie	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Ticket	O
for	O
Almacks	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
Friday	O
March	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Lecture	O
&	O
engaged	O
to	O
take	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
instead	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
¼	O
past	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
Sheridan	B-pers
drank	O
Coffee	O
&	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Tea	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
show	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
drawings	O
.	O
had	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
home	O
.	O
Satry	O
.	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
he	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Child	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
met	O
her	O
Brother	O
there	O
--	O
then	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
in	O
Hyde	O
park	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
who	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
in	O
their	O
Coach	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldworthy	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
10	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Sund	O
.	O
2	O
2	O
th	O
3	O
d	O
--	O
in	O
ye-	O
Morng	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
langers	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Argill	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
after	O
Dinner	O
my	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
us	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
came	O
away	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
11	O
Monday	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
.	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Solis	I-pers
there	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
there	O
calld	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Butlers	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
Commiſsion	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
there	O
calld	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chetwynd	I-pers
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
my	O
Uncle	O
walkd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
who	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Guilford	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dyer	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
took	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
staid	O
there	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
Company	O
ye	O
.	O
Strothoffs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
R	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
--	O
Maria	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
there	O
--	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
went	O
&	O
Sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Boscawen	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
HMore	I-pers
only	O
them	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Carter	B-pers
at	O
supper	O
--	O
Burney	B-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
25	O
th	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
found	O
me	O
going	O
out	O
walkd	O
wit	O
h	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
s	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s.	O
I	O
breakfas	O
ted	O
at	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
room	O
--	O
saw	O
some	O
drawings	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Laurens	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burdieu	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
in	O
James	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
calld	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mc	I-pers
.	I-pers
Konichie	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Burdieu	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
Ldy	B-pers
H	I-pers
lent	O
me	O
her	O
Coach	O
went	O
to	O
2	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catter	I-pers
lookd	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Mills	I-pers
s	O
Prints	O
&	O
c.	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Whitbread	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
Supper	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
sat	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
Dowr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
till	O
12	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
for	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
Wedn	O
.	O
26	O
March	O
1783	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
had	O
Hollar	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
,	O
show	O
'd	O
ym	O
.	O
Prints	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
2	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
ye	O
Young	O
People	O
.	O
we	O
set	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
home	O
then	O
Miſs	B-pers
L.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
wth	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
.	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
did	O
not	O
dine	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Thursday	O
March	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
not	O
dining	O
there	O
.	O
went	O
at	O
7	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
sup	O
'd	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
we	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
Friday	O
28	O
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
breakfasted	O
there	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
pas	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
walkd	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
met	O
there	O
ye	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
.	O
we	O
walkd	O
together	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
&	O
then	O
parted	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
ye	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
there	O
.	O
Met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
calld	O
upon	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
Mr	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
wth	O
her	O
on	O
busi	O
n	O
eſs	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
call	O
upon	O
Sr	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Is	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Ernst	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
s	O
D	O
r	O
Du	O
Chair	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
Benefit	O
Concert	O
.	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
Satry	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
.	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
's	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Egertons	I-pers
staid	O
sometime	O
with	O
each	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
he	O
read	O
Some	O
Manuscripts	O
--	O
we	O
lookd	O
over	O
his	O
Box	O
of	O
papers	O
&	O
c.	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
Sunday	O
30	O
.	O
Dor	B-pers
Ldy	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
May	O
fair	O
Chappel	O
--	O
Brought	O
me	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
to	O
excuse	O
myself	O
dining	O
there	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
4	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
only	O
her	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
Dumb	O
Waiter	O
--	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
Library	O
after	O
dinner	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
Prints	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
8	O
Mrs	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
there	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
Uncle	O
at	O
½	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
.	O
found	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Clarendon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
staid	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
had	O
spent	O
ye	O
day	O
.	O
out	O
sat	O
&	O
talkd	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
Monday	O
31	O
st	O
March	O
1783	O
Mr	B-pers
Skeffington	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Dean	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
from	O
8	O
till	O
9	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
Poem	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
V	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
past	O
3	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
.	O
writing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
April	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
where	O
I	O
pleased	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Gunnings	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ancaster	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
¼	O
past	O
two	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Strand	O
.	O
&	O
after	O
to	O
his	O
Sons	O
--	O
saw	O
there	O
a	O
fine	O
bust	O
of	O
Mercury	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
his	O
Picture	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
of	O
Belvedere	O
Isabella	O
--	O
very	O
finely	O
executed	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
tete	O
a	O
tete	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bolye	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
7	O
Flaxman	B-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
w	O
h	O
e	O
nt	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
Hamilton	B-pers
ye	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Gunnings	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
convers	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Wedn	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
-	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
from	O
11	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
calld	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
while	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Chaperon	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Concert	O
sent	O
back	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
ticket	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
at	O
4	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Strothoff	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
as	O
did	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burgeſs	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughters	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Knowseley	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abingdon	I-pers
s	O
wth	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
&	O
workd	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
Dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
Boyle	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bendycke	I-pers
found	O
ym	O
.	O
at	O
Whist	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
there	O
I	O
staid	O
supper	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Taxier	B-pers
not	O
come	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
--	O
on	O
horseback	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
bow	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
Thursday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
from	O
11	O
till	O
12	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
at	O
1	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
M'Konichie	I-pers
came	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
5	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
there	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
Chs	B-pers
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
Tea	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Templetown	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
at	O
8.	O
went	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
Mry	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
a	O
Card	O
Party	O
.	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Coach	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fiztmaurice	I-pers
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
's	O
a	O
Concert	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
Compte	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
next	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
11.	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
12	O
.	O
Friday	O
April	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
&	O
her	O
children	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
12.	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
(	O
Julia	O
went	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
pictures	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
there	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Picture	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
other	O
places	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
s	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
s	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
met	O
me	O
--	O
saw	O
Hamilton	B-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
7.	O
met	O
Col	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
walkd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
read	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
Lady	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Satry	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1783	O
Mr	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mr	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
&	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Kings	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s.	O
had	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Ticket	O
for	O
her	O
Box	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
took	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Frederick	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
ye-	O
Character	O
of	O
Calista	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
fair	O
Penitent	O
--	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
entertaintment	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
staid	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
till	O
11	O
Sunday	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Church	O
went	O
to	O
May	O
fair	O
Chapp	O
el	O
came	O
home	O
after	O
Church	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
&	O
her	O
2	O
eldest	O
Girls	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Compte	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
only	O
ourselves	O
+	O
+	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
carried	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
home	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
V	O
April	O
7	O
th	O
Monday	O
1783	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
again	O
at	O
2	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
Maria	B-pers
--	O
at	O
4	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
she	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
he	O
staid	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
near	O
8	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs.-	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Knowsley	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
at	O
10	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
Carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
--	O
An	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
lent	O
me	O
his	O
Vis-à-Vis	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mistake	O
about	O
my	O
Chair	O
.	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
begun	O
a	O
Novel	O
&	O
c	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
April	O
8	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
before	O
10	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
breakfasted	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
from	O
3	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
they	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
c.	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
April	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
settled	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Affairs	O
--	O
gave	O
her	O
from	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
her	O
7	O
£	O
4	O
.	O
6.	O
buy	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
near	O
20	O
£	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
11.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Do	O
.	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
saw	O
ye	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Kings	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Picture	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
b	O
y	O
u	O
y	O
in	O
Oils	O
--	O
a	O
Maddalen	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
,	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
met	O
their	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
(	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
)	I-pers
King	I-pers
staid	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
then	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hulse	I-pers
met	O
there	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
dreſsing	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
me	O
his	O
drawings	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Balstrode	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Gunnings	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
tea	O
&	O
c	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
April	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
A	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
after	O
4	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
2	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
for	O
us	O
at	O
6	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Bruyyeres	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hammerley	I-pers
my	O
Cousin	O
&	O
self	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
character	O
o	O
f	O
ye	O
Isabella	O
in	O
ye	O
fatal	O
Marriage	O
.	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
entertainment	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
lobby	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
James	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
/2	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
out	O
--	O
drew	O
&	O
read	O
--	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
Monday	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
April	O
1783	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Town	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
Stop	O
'd	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Cone	O
Hat	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Lord	B-pers
Loughborough	I-pers
staid	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
read	O
Mr.	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
s	O
Prize	O
Poem	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
came	O
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Germany	B-place
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
him	O
alone	O
an	O
hour	O
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
out	O
.	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
Madan	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
--	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
&	O
sat	O
below	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
read	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
s	O
Hist	O
:	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Reign	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
.	O
at	O
10	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
ym	O
.	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Tuesday	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
April	O
1783	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Milbanke	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Rapin	B-pers
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
tea	O
&	O
Supper	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
read	O
letters	O
.	O
Work	O
'd	O
&	O
c.	O
Till	O
1	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
23	O
d	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
KnowSley	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Miſsrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
person	O
for	O
Governeſs	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
eldest	O
Daughter	O
--	O
Staid	O
only	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Rapin	B-pers
to	O
tea	O
we	O
sat	O
all	O
together	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Ethelmond	O
--	O
we	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
ye	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Athol	I-pers
s	O
Screen	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
went	O
at	O
10	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
11	O
Thursday	O
24	O
th	O
April	O
1783	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
busy	O
about	O
Mr	B-pers
Screen	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
m	O
e	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
she	O
din	O
'd	O
out	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
dinner	O
read	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
Vesey	B-pers
s	O
rape	O
of	O
ye	O
Lock	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Devaynes	B-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
J-	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
Bell	B-pers
Pope	B-pers
ye	B-pers
:	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
came	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
in	O
after	O
Supper	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
alone	O
to	O
finish	O
ye	O
.	O
Screen	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
.	O
Friday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1783	O
.	O
Buller	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
after	O
having	O
set	O
ym	O
.	O
down	O
at	O
several	O
places	O
came	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
had	O
calld	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
7	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wat	I-pers
.	I-pers
Thursby	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
went	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
company	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Bell	B-pers
--	O
they	O
went	O
at	O
10	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
home	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
together	O
after	O
supper	O
Maria	O
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
some	O
ridiculous	O
lines	O
on	O
ye	O
loſs	O
of	O
ye	O
Knocker	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Satry	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
Lady	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
&	O
their	O
little	O
Girl	O
--	O
who	O
staid	O
alone	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Bell	B-pers
Mr	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Sorrel	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
--	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
L.	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
we	O
wrote	O
verses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sunday	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
after	O
Church	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ham̄ersley	I-pers
.	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
3.	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
.	O
--	O
calld	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
s	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
went	O
&	O
told	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
would	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
paid	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
(	O
her	O
Mother	O
)	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
only	O
