TOKEN	NE
I	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Walk	O
this	O
fine	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
profit	O
by	O
It	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
London	B-place
on	O
Busineſs	O
.	O
Do	O
They	O
go	O
to	O
Strawberry-Hill	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Evening	O
?	O
&	O
can	O
I	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
Use	O
to	O
carry	O
or	O
bring	O
back	O
?	O
Their	O
Obedient	O
FBoscawen	B-pers
Rosedale	O
Friday	O
Night	O
July	O
18	O
th	O
1788	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
July	O
1788	O
