TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
Street	O
23	O
July	O
1781	O
my	O
Dear	O
Willm	B-pers
King	I-pers
it	O
has	O
given	O
us	O
,	O
very	O
real	O
concern	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Your	O
illneſs	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Your	O
letter	O
aſsured	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
was	O
got	O
well	O
;	O
Yet	O
am	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
You	O
continue	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
nervous	O
complaints	O
are	O
very	O
bad	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
:	O
especialy	O
this	O
Hot	O
Weather	O
;	O
could	O
say	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
clear	O
,	O
if	O
You	O
shew	O
letters	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
enter	O
too	O
deeply	O
in	O
Your	O
case	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
suposed	O
a	O
Quack	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Weymouth	B-place
,	O
Dorset	B-place
.	O
as	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
that	O
place	O
next	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
invalids	O
,	O
and	O
travelling	O
with	O
our	O
own	O
horses	O
,	O
we	O
intend	O
to	O
make	O
Easy	O
days	O
and	O
sunday	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
shall	O
Stop	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
Dorchester	B-place
and	O
visit	O
a	O
friend	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
arrive	O
at	O
Weymouth	B-place
till	O
Monday	O
:	O
where	O
we	O
shall	O
most	O
likely	O
rest	O
a	O
fortnight	O
and	O
then	O
proceed	O
to	O
Yarty	B-place
in	O
Devonshire	B-place
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
s	O
Joynture	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Sprights	O
and	O
Goblins	O
in	O
which	O
that	O
country	O
abounds	O
,	O
these	O
thirty	O
Year	O
so	O
a	O
dismal	O
old	O
Mansion	O
among	O
the	O
Hills	O
--	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
shall	O
paſs	O
our	O
time	O
agreably	O
as	O
nothing	O
is	O
more	O
conducive	O
to	O
that	O
than	O
good	O
Humor	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
intend	O
to	O
take	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
:	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
anticipate	O
as	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
send	O
You	O
particulars	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Ghosts	O
were	O
troublesome	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
..	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
inform	O
You	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
is	O
got	O
very	O
stout	O
again	O
,	O
a	O
proof	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
Hillingdon	B-place
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
last	O
Thursday	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
15	O
mile	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Elize	I-pers
:	I-pers
Worsley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Smalbury	O
Green	O
;	O
and	O
believe	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
Royal	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
to	O
catch	O
a	O
glimpse	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
vain	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
far	O
to	O
see	O
.	O
as	O
she	O
bore	O
the	O
fatigue	O
of	O
it	O
without	O
any	O
inconvenience	O
flatter	O
myself	O
the	O
Journey	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
.	O
my	O
Sister	O
I	O
fear	O
will	O
find	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
is	O
very	O
restorative	O
we	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
how	O
clever	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
,	O
could	O
You	O
make	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
Sir	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Banks	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
;	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
extraordinary	O
?	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
officers	O
might	O
ask	O
who	O
they	O
pleas	O
:	O
d	O
:	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
surprised	O
me	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
Yr	O
letter	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
seemed	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
extraordinary	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
and	O
spent	O
my	O
time	O
very	O
agreably	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Old	B-place
Windsor	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Galatee	O
Barge	O
,	O
and	O
sail	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
Isleworth	B-place
25	O
mile	O
:	O
another	O
d	O
ay	O
we	O
went	O
of	O
a	O
fishing	O
party	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
h	O
t	O
o	O
ca	O
tch	O
Eels	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
a	O
pond	O
was	O
so	O
full	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
were	O
seen	O
,	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
a	O
Mans	O
Arm	O
:	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
loaded	O
with	O
fishing	O
tackle	O
,	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Catch	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
fish	O
in	O
that	O
pond	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
:	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
those	O
parties	O
always	O
turn	O
out	O
croſs	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
proved	O
whet	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Evening	O
was	O
fine	O
the	O
fish	O
would	O
not	O
bite	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
out	O
of	O
patience	O
,	O
flung	O
in	O
the	O
net	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
:	O
but	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
usual	O
fate	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
weeds	O
!	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
fish	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
.	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
entertained	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
mortified	O
about	O
the	O
disapointment	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
fisher	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
charming	O
House	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
fine	O
pictures	O
&	O
variety	O
of	O
Virtū	O
which	O
was	O
too	O
great	O
an	O
Amusement	O
,	O
to	O
regret	O
the	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
conclude	O
this	O
,	O
without	O
enquiring	O
after	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Banks	I-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
is	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
able	O
to	O
retake	O
her	O
usual	O
attendance	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
my	O
agreable	O
friend	O
will	O
Shine	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
department	O
;	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
in	O
every	O
other	O
She	O
undertakes	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
leſs	O
attendance	O
(	O
if	O
poſsible	O
)	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
regain	O
her	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
Spirits	O
--	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
they	O
feel	O
obliged	O
,	O
for	O
Your	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
;	O
and	O
joyn	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
,	O
for	O
Your	O
Health	O
and	O
Happineſs	O
:	O
and	O
hope	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
Your	O
pen	O
:	O
which	O
always	O
gives	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
s	O
Sincere	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Wil	B-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
