TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
May	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1794	O
Thursday	O
continued	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
packet	O
for	O
you	O
inclosing	O
a	O
lettr	O
.	O
from	O
Grandpapa	O
&	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
&	O
arrived	O
in	O
proper	O
time	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
s	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Falmouth	I-pers
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
act	O
of	O
franking	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
later	O
he	O
wou	O
ld	O
I	O
suppose	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
act	O
of	O
dreſsing	O
for	O
dinner	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
Gazette	O
containing	O
news	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Victory	O
;	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
found	O
my	O
Beau	O
arrived	O
,	O
&	O
Harriet	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
well	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
dinner	O
&	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
charm	O
'd	O
with	O
ye	O
:	O
engaging	O
lively	O
Hosteſs	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
4	O
oClock	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
her	O
play	O
fellow	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
Morrison	B-pers
to	O
superintend	O
them	O
,	O
upstairs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
uninterruptedly	O
enjoy	O
a	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
with	O
the	O
good	O
Man	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
reap	O
much	O
entertainment	O
from	O
his	O
conversation	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
least	O
ye	O
.	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
perceiving	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
pleased	O
wth-	O
his	O
visit	O
&	O
my	O
attentions	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
6	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
on	O
busineſs	O
--	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
learnt	O
that	O
Richardson	B-pers
Author	O
of	O
Pamela	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
had	O
4	O
daughters	O
&	O
yt	O
a	O
Maiden	O
one	O
still	O
living	O
abt	O
.	O
20	O
miles	O
from	O
London	B-place
(	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
Woman	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
one	O
)	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
poſseſsion	O
a	O
large	O
collection	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
s	O
manuscripts	O
&	O
letters	O
wh	O
.	O
she	O
intend	O
ing	O
ed	O
leaving	O
as	O
a	O
legacy	O
to	O
a	O
numerous	O
progeny	O
of	O
Nephews	O
&	O
Nieces	O
--	O
Richardson	B-pers
left	O
his	O
daughters	O
5000	O
£	O
each	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wt	O
:	O
me	O
&	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Ireland	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
is	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
400	O
£	O
Pr	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
to	O
his	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Son	O
who	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
of	O
good	O
family	O
&	O
connexions	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
to	O
pay	O
30	O
Guineas	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
who	O
's	O
rect	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
sufficient	O
,	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
leave	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
s	O
House	O
wth	O
.	O
their	O
Cook	O
who	O
will	O
remain	O
at	O
their	O
ho	O
use	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
is	O
to	O
divide	O
her	O
time	O
between	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
&	O
Walsh	B-pers
during	O
their	O
absence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
,	O
paſs	O
'd	O
an	O
agreeable	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
who	O
appears	O
amiable	O
&	O
interesting	O
--	O
we	O
filled	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
with	O
working	O
&	O
reading	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
papers	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Lounger	O
to	O
ym	O
..	O
I	O
was	O
invite	O
d	O
to	O
supper	O
by	O
Ly	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
thinking	O
yt	O
.	O
this	O
was	O
to	O
continue	O
consented	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Supper	O
Room	O
Mr.	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
made	O
his	O
appearance	O
,	O
&	O
soon	O
after	O
enterd	O
ye	O
.	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Tullibardine	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Tutor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
from	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
reserve	O
a	O
communication	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Manners	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
remarks	O
till	O
we	O
meet	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
so	O
galant	O
as	O
to	O
croſs	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
knock	O
up	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
civil	O
speech	O
about	O
calling	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
gave	O
a	O
broad	O
hint	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
by	O
not	O
having	O
already	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
&	O
ccccc	O
Friday	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
May	O
1794	O
I	O
went	O
early	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
&	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
she	O
is	O
certainly	O
in	O
an	O
alarming	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
aware	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
have	O
medical	O
aſsistance	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
writing	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Price	I-pers
&	O
I	O
helpd	O
her	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
her	O
letter	O
by	O
meſsages	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
informing	O
him	O
of	O
your	O
Hunting	O
Royal	O
Stags	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
humble	O
dwellings	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
In	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pigotts	I-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
Portrait	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
of	O
their	O
Mother	O
--	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
quit	O
Bath	B-place
without	O
seeing	O
it	O
.	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
credit	O
this	O
picture	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
in	O
after	O
ages	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
instead	O
of	O
receiving	O
their	O
money	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
your	O
shabby	O
little	O
letter	O
from	O
Chorleywood	B-place
--	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
somewhat	O
affectionate	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
first	O
lines	O
wch	O
.	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
disappointment	O
of	O
a	O
more	O
circumstantial	O
letter	O
from	O
thence	O
--	O
poor	O
Morrison	B-pers
look	O
'd	O
very	O
blank	O
,	O
but	O
consoled	O
herself	O
with	O
hopes	O
that	O
tomorrows	O
post	O
would	O
,	O
agre	O
eable	O
to	O
your	O
promise	O
,	O
make	O
full	O
amends	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Marquis	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
during	O
my	O
absence	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
fine	O
day	O
for	O
excursions	O
but	O
the	O
Gardeners	O
are	O
praying	O
for	O
rain	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Irelands	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
the	O
Eldest	O
is	O
a	O
well	O
bred	O
,	O
very	O
modest	O
,	O
&	O
sensible	O
Young	O
Woman	O
,	O
her	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
Wine	O
Merchant	O
,	O
&	O
lives	O
near	O
Bristol	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
when	O
we	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
therefore	O
shall	O
not	O
repeat	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
repeated	O
from	O
her	O
father	O
during	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
last	O
year	O
,	O
his	O
paſsing	O
thro	O
'	O
ye	O
:	O
allied	O
armies	O
&	O
other	O
equally	O
interesting	O
subjects	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
came	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
time	O
this	O
week	O
Louisa	B-pers
however	O
danc	O
'd	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Abbé	I-pers
Rudemare	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
hour	O
since	O
you	O
went	O
--	O
I	O
now	O
regret	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
advantage	O
since	O
his	O
first	O
attendance	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
has	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
but	O
is	O
again	O
able	O
to	O
mount	O
the	O
Hill	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Green	I-pers
has	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
times	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
Louisa	B-pers
had	O
no	O
mercy	O
on	O
the	O
Shrubs	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
being	O
determined	O
Master	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
Leveson	I-pers
Gower	I-pers
should	O
have	O
a	O
fine	O
May	O
Nosegay	O
--	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
amiable	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
bleſsed	O
her	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
night	O
I	O
gratified	O
her	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
accompanied	O
by	O
Squire	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
bearer	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
fragrant	O
present	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
large	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
hours	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Chat	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
Lord	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Evelyn	I-pers
were	O
playing	O
at	O
cards	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bos	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
not	O
pleased	O
with	O
our	O
paying	O
ye	O
.	O
K	B-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
so	O
liberally	O
&	O
seems	O
averse	O
to	O
our	O
being	O
engaged	O
in	O
ye	O
:	O
War	O
;	O
Was	O
shewn	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Regimentals	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
taste	O
.	O
I	O
calld	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Rundells	B-pers
before	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
they	O
have	O
wth-	O
ym	O
.	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Trevanion	I-pers
--	O
/	O
who	O
's	O
husband	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Ruſsian	O
Service/	O
&	O
her	O
child	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
soon	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Ruſsia	B-place
--	O
the	O
Empreſs	B-pers
allows	O
her	O
a	O
pension	O
of	O
150	O
£	O
Pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
Saturday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
May	O
--	O
After	O
Rudemare	B-pers
went	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
Louisa	B-pers
improves	O
both	O
in	O
her	O
french	O
&	O
english	O
,	O
I	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
as	O
attentive	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
attention	O
she	O
fails	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Morrison	B-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Miſs	B-pers
S	I-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
--	O
She	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
broiling	O
hot	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
besides	O
ye	O
.	O
Town	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Bustle	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Election	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
saw	O
Sr.	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
seated	O
in	O
his	O
triumphal	O
Car	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
the	O
Cook	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
&	O
aſsist	O
Smith	B-pers
she	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Town	O
Hall	O
early	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Cold	O
dinner	O
--	O
but	O
Charles	B-pers
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
shew	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
our	O
Surprise	O
we	O
had	O
roast	O
veal	O
,	O
--	O
a	O
made	O
dish	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
--	O
hot	O
Vegetables	O
,	O
Butter	O
Well	O
Melted	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Cooking	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
letting	O
us	O
see	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
set	O
off	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
cold	O
in	O
ye	O
:	O
Larder	O
was	O
produced	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
five	O
&	O
fives	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
lucky	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
longer	O
bilious	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
doubtleſs	O
have	O
been	O
mortifying	O
to	O
a	O
high	O
degree	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
done	O
honor	O
to	O
his	O
dinner	O
.	O
Morrison	B-pers
said	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
eat	O
out	O
of	O
vexation	O
to	O
day	O
having	O
been	O
terribly	O
disappo	O
inted	O
in	O
not	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
wch	O
:	O
you	O
promised	O
in	O
your	O
last	O
faithfully	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Mind	O
to	O
punish	O
you	O
&	O
not	O
send	O
this	O
large	O
proof	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
gave	O
Louisa	B-pers
a	O
good	O
leſson	O
to	O
day	O
and	O
I	O
encounterd	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
his	O
fragrances	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
dance	O
her	O
minute	O
minuet	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Bigge	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
&	O
c	O
were	O
there	O
--	O
spent	O
two	O
pleasant	O
hours	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bigge	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
kept	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
of	O
conversation	O
very	O
agreeably	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
much	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
&	O
sup	O
with	O
them	O
telling	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
set	O
his	O
heart	O
upon	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
prefer	O
r	O
ing	O
eating	O
a	O
few	O
Radishes	O
quietly	O
wth-	O
Meg	B-pers
.	O
I	O
debat	O
declined	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Sunday	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
I	O
think	O
venture	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
letters	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
directed	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rich	O
enough	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
surprised	O
you	O
--	O
Pray	O
send	O
for	O
Money	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
for	O
so	O
poor	O
am	O
I	O
at	O
this	O
present	O
writing	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
borrow	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
postage	O
of	O
your	O
next	O
letter	O
whenever	O
it	O
arrives	O
.	O
Well	O
I	O
have	O
borrowd	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
&	O
paid	O
postage	O
for	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
fuſs	O
myself	O
about	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
satisfied	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
mention	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
or	O
ill	O
--	O
with	O
whole	O
limbs	O
or	O
broken	O
bones	O
,	O
pleased	O
or	O
displeas	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
paſsion	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
paſsion	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
forth	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
true	O
few	O
are	O
the	O
families	O
where	O
reign	O
domestic	O
harmony	O
&	O
peace	O
equal	O
to	O
our	O
own	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
hasten	O
to	O
close	O
this	O
letter	O
&	O
not	O
indulge	O
myself	O
by	O
a	O
full	O
reply	O
to	O
yours	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Falmouth	I-pers
&	O
enclose	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Stockport	B-place
--	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
time	O
I	O
will	O
avail	O
write	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
cover	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
depend	O
on	O
Your	O
saying	O
every	O
thing	O
expreſsive	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
true	O
affection	O
I	O
bear	O
her	O
.	O
Comet	O
is	O
well	O
&	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
pranks	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
a	O
guineas	O
worth	O
of	O
mischief	O
to	O
some	O
apple	O
trees	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
almost	O
eaten	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
pasture	O
of	O
the	O
Orchard	O
,	O
--	O
his	O
palate	O
is	O
grown	O
too	O
nice	O
to	O
relish	O
his	O
once	O
favorite	O
treat	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
he	O
disdainfully	O
refusd	O
even	O
from	O
the	O
affectionate	O
hands	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
this	O
Morning	O
;	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
has	O
so	O
gain	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
attach	O
hearts	O
of	O
Dash	O
&	O
Sancho	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
his	O
inseparable	O
companions	O
--	O
the	O
former	O
carries	O
his	O
stick	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
later	O
has	O
been	O
taught	O
to	O
be	O
delighted	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
carrying	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
Doll	O
fastened	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
is	O
taking	O
pains	O
with	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
learns	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
loves	O
you	O
dearly	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
The	O
Nightingales	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Grove	O
behind	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
sing	O
D	O
ay	O
&	O
Night	O
most	O
harmoniously	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
my	O
letters	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
dates	O
