TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
town	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
your	O
Card	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
given	O
your	O
self	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
I	O
beleive	O
I	O
shall	O
goe	O
out	O
of	O
town	B-place
again	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
nixt	O
Saturday	O
,	O
to	O
mr	B-pers
Irby	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
I	O
hope	O
wee	O
shall	O
meet	O
often	O
which	O
will	O
allways	O
give	O
me	O
pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
spent	O
your	O
Summer	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
knoting	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
of	O
town	B-place
,	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
thing	O
to	O
doe	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
send	O
it	O
without	O
puting	O
your	O
Self	O
to	O
much	O
inconveince	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
likewise	O
taken	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Majesty	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
my	O
Netting	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Shall	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
with	O
my	O
most	O
respectful	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
aſsured	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
affectionat	O
regard	O
and	O
am	O
your	O
much	O
obliged	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Maddox	O
Street	O
Janr	O
2	O
th	O
1782	O
Many	O
happy	O
years	O
attend	O
you	O
adieu	O
