TOKEN	NE
Visit	O
to	O
Dowger	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
Bulstrode	O
Journals	O
of	O
from	O
to	O
Jany	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
Dec	O
5	O
1783	O
--	O
1784	O
at	O
Falmer	B-place
.	O
a	O
Woman	O
saw	O
a	O
Cuckow	O
cheat	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Hedge	O
Sparrow	O
off	O
her	O
nest	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
had	O
3	O
Eggs	O
in	O
it	O
after	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Cuckow	O
was	O
gone	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hedge	O
Sparrow	O
's	O
Eggs	O
'd	O
&	O
y	O
e	O
spotted	O
C.	O
Egg	O
lain	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
Sorr	O
Sorry	O
,	O
I	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
shot	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
4	O
2	O
400	O
2400	O
fallow	O
deer	O
.	O
ye	O
Queen	O
6	O
w	O
th	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
--	O
17	O
People	O
were	O
employed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
Larkins	O
China	O
Shop	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
--	O
ye	O
only	O
Shop	O
for	O
Lisle	O
Thread	O
a	O
tea	O
Spoonful	O
Plants	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Peak	O
of	O
Derbyshire	O
1763	O
1	O
Giant	O
throatwort	O
2	O
Shining	O
downfoot	O
Cranes-	O
bill	O
3	O
Great	O
yellow	O
Heartsease	O
4	O
Climbing	O
fumitory	O
5	O
Stags	O
Horn	O
Moſs	O
6	O
Myrtle	O
leaved	O
Cranberry	O
7	O
Apple	O
Rose	O
8	O
Scarlet	O
cup	O
moſs	O
1766	O
1	O
Knotted	O
Parsley	O
2	O
Purple	O
&	O
Yellow	O
Hearts	O
ease	O
3	O
Great	O
tufted	O
wood	O
vetch	O
4	O
Brittle	O
Fern	O
5	O
Lancashire	O
Asphodel	O
6	O
Mountain	O
Averna	O
7	O
Cloud	O
Berries	O
8	O
Bloody	O
Cranes	O
bill	O
Marsh	O
Saxifrage	O
The	O
Blue	O
Iris	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Bedford	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Woburn	O
Road	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
ditches	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
Race	O
Ground	O
*	O
My	O
first	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
terror	O
Of	O
ye	O
.	O
weak	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
My	O
second	O
disgraces	O
the	O
heart	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
tongue	O
When	O
join	O
'd	O
together	O
ye	O
.	O
grave	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Wise	O
Are	O
gain	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
charms	O
&	O
allow	O
me	O
a	O
prize	O
Made	O
by	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
My	O
first	O
is	O
allowed	O
to	O
have	O
Charms	O
without	O
end	O
My	O
2	O
d	O
is	O
either	O
a	O
foe	O
or	O
a	O
friend	O
When	O
join	O
'd	O
far	O
&	O
near	O
to	O
mischief	O
I	O
tend	O
Bullstrode	O
Decbr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Went	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
extremely	O
happy	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
&	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
by	O
my	O
consent	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
Repeated	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
seeing	O
ye	O
.	O
affection	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
taken	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
how	O
much	O
they	O
both	O
loved	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
certain	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
&	O
ever	O
should	O
merit	O
ye	O
.	O
Affection	O
of	O
every	O
one	O
who	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
ever	O
really	O
merit	O
,	O
&	O
endeavour	O
to	O
deserve	O
such	O
encomiums	O
!	O
how	O
truly	O
flattering	O
the	O
praises	O
of	O
this	O
venerable	O
and	O
most	O
amiable	O
of	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
soon	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
day	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
(	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
me	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Admiral	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Chalfont	O
--	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Fog	O
did	O
not	O
disperse	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
s	O
sent	O
her	O
pretty	O
meſsenger	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
enquire	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
slept	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
&	O
invited	O
m	O
e	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
brought	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
papers	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
paragraphs	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
then	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
10	O
minutes	O
&	O
then	O
hoped	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Housekeeper	O
came	O
&	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
Store	O
Rooms	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
delighted	O
--	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
her	O
China	O
Closets	O
--	O
Linnen	O
Preſses	O
,	O
her	O
Stores	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
eat	O
of	O
Cakes	O
,	O
Sweetmeats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
orange	O
cakes	O
to	O
please	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
flowers	O
--	O
a	O
Peacocks	O
feather	O
to	O
keep	O
&	O
use	O
as	O
a	O
mark	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
to	O
remember	O
her	O
by	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
&	O
all	O
Servants	O
lik	O
'd	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
s	O
had	O
prevaild	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
lengthen	O
my	O
stay	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
thousand	O
civil	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
also	O
ye	O
.	O
Steward	O
s	O
room	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
large	O
--	O
here	O
ye	O
.	O
upper	O
servts	O
.	O
dine	O
--	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
hung	O
round	O
with	O
pictures	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
--	O
where	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
little	O
spinning	O
Wheel	O
&	O
table	O
&	O
I	O
my	O
little	O
table	O
&	O
fringe	O
knotting	O
&	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Burlington	I-pers
--	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
lovely	O
,	O
unfortunate	O
Daughter	O
.	O
who	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Euston	I-pers
--	O
son	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Grafton	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Mother	O
was	O
infamous	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
horrid	O
wretches	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
--	O
his	O
conduct	O
towards	O
his	O
beautiful	O
amiable	O
wife	O
being	O
brutal	O
,	O
beyond	O
imagination	O
brutal	O
--	O
this	O
wretch	O
had	O
an	O
intrigue	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
s	O
wife	O
--	O
Kill	O
'd	O
his	O
own	O
--	O
&	O
ruin	O
'd	O
a	O
lady	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
particulars	O
are	O
too	O
long	O
for	O
to	O
note	O
down	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
About	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
busineſs	O
to	O
transact	O
could	O
not	O
remain	O
with	O
us	O
long	O
she	O
made	O
us	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
flying	O
visits	O
before	O
dinner	O
at	O
2	O
o	O
Clock	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
(	I-pers
née	I-pers
Cosby	I-pers
)	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
&	O
eat	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
heart	O
laugh	O
&	O
ran	O
a	O
Race	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
gain	O
'd	O
her	O
point	O
however	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Siesta	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
remaind	O
together	O
till	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
read	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
miscelaneous	O
Manuscripts	O
--	O
--	O
chiefly	O
remarks	O
on	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
History	O
written	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
Barnet	B-pers
s	O
grandfather	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
to	O
transcribe	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
original	O
--	O
these	O
remarks	O
proved	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
was	O
influenced	O
too	O
often	O
by	O
a	O
party	O
spirit	O
--	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
she	O
read	O
me	O
were	O
two	O
anecdotes	O
relating	O
to	O
Barnet	B-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Czar	I-pers
paid	O
him	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
unfortunately	O
a	O
favorite	O
Monkey	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
ye	I-pers
.	I-pers
2d	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
who	O
took	O
in	O
it	O
his	O
head	O
to	O
be	O
vastly	O
affronted	O
because	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Czar	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
revenge	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
affront	O
,	O
by	O
grinning	O
&	O
jumping	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
--	O
so	O
the	O
whole	O
visit	O
conversation	O
that	O
paſs	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
making	O
apologies	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
had	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
see	O
The	B-pers
Czar	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
&	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
Speeches	O
--	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
--	O
he	O
therefore	O
went	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
leads	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Windows	O
--	O
he	O
soon	O
caught	O
the	O
eyes	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Lords	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
resist	O
laughing	O
at	O
the	O
ridiculous	O
figure	O
he	O
made	O
,	O
--	O
he	O
soon	O
retired	O
.	O
--	O
At	O
7	O
tea	O
,	O
during	O
tea	O
I	O
contrived	O
to	O
finish	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Dear	O
ye	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
After	O
tea	O
I	O
read	O
Evelina	O
which	O
I	O
finishd	O
at	O
ten	O
oClock	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
finish	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
E	O
:	O
ye	O
Book	O
she	O
had	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
Dst	O
:	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
--	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
if	O
she	O
wishd	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
little	O
Catherine	B-pers
was	O
ill	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
parted	O
¼	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
limbs	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
ride	O
yesterday	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
conversation	O
after	O
Supper	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
Fanny	B-pers
.	O
her	O
manners	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Bullstrode	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
oClock	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
F——ding	I-pers
s	O
room	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
found	O
2	O
letters	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
table	O
one	O
,	O
frm	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
contain	O
'd	O
more	O
comfortable	O
accounts	O
of	O
little	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
one	O
from	O
Fanny	B-pers
.	O
soon	O
after	O
10	O
left	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
&	O
desird	O
me	O
to	O
accompany	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
alas	O
!	O
her	O
eyes	O
would	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
felt	O
much	O
honor	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
confidence	O
she	O
placed	O
in	O
me	O
my	O
heart	O
ach	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
she	O
no	O
longer	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
mine	O
I	O
read	O
her	O
letters	O
--	O
in	O
one	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
from	O
her	O
eldest	O
Nephew	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lately	O
spent	O
a	O
week	O
here	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
these	O
lines	O
--	O
“	O
my	O
best	O
reſpects	O
“	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
“	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
,	O
her	O
sprightlineſs	O
“	O
will	O
chase	O
away	O
those	O
any	O
“	O
lowness	O
of	O
spirits	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
“	O
wherever	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
sorrow	O
can	O
surely	O
make	O
no	O
long	O
abode	O
.	O
”	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
his	O
remembrance	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
worthy	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
read	O
the	O
news	O
papers	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
,	O
I	O
obey	O
'd	O
--	O
for	O
is	O
it	O
poſsibly	O
to	O
refuse	O
obeying	O
her	O
dictates	O
?	O
the	O
weather	O
was	O
remarkably	O
fine	O
--	O
no	O
fog	O
--	O
the	O
sun	O
shone	O
bright	O
.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
wind	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
South	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Grotto	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
the	O
calm	O
serenity	O
of	O
the	O
scene	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
around	O
me	O
.	O
here	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
all	O
those	O
whom	O
I	O
loved	O
,	O
of	O
every	O
one	O
whose	O
friendship	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
happy	O
to	O
enjoy	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
fed	O
the	O
Peacocks	O
&	O
Guinea	O
fowls	O
who	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
--	O
every	O
Bird	O
&	O
animal	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
variety	O
are	O
tame	O
&	O
sociable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
walk	O
&	O
c.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
began	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
whilst	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
her	O
friend	O
had	O
received	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.......	O
Soon	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
B——	B-pers
came	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
order	O
the	O
servts	O
.	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Oysters	O
wch	O
:	O
she	O
eats	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
as	O
did	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
said	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
upper	O
Servts-	O
dine	O
at	O
2	O
--	O
Betty	B-pers
left	O
me	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
Oysters	O
laid	O
ye	O
Napkin	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
receive	O
Betty	B-pers
en	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
our	O
Gouté	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
Betty	O
came	O
dinner	O
&	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
dinner	O
Bell	O
rang	O
--	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
right	O
not	O
to	O
intrude	O
before	O
the	O
Dſs	O
had	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
(	O
her	O
daughter	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
expected	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
5	O
oClock	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Met	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
found	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
attentive	O
&	O
polite	O
towards	O
me	O
&	O
always	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
the	O
common	O
chit	O
chat	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
World	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
&	O
read	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
might	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
together	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
went	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
¼	O
before	O
7	O
&	O
sat	O
wth-	O
me	O
--	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
at	O
7	O
the	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chambers	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
)	O
came	O
&	O
told	O
us	O
tea	O
was	O
ready	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
our	O
little	O
Table	O
&	O
Candles	O
&	O
work	O
.	O
conversed	O
upon	O
the	O
News	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
fashions	O
--	O
dreſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
¼	O
before	O
10	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
leave	O
ye	O
.	O
ladies	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
talk	O
without	O
restraint	O
--	O
for	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
nothing	O
for	O
judicious	O
for	O
younger	O
people	O
taught	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
nothing	O
marks	O
ignorance	O
or	O
want	O
due	O
propriety	O
&	O
respect	O
more	O
than	O
for	O
a	O
younger	O
Person	O
many	O
years	O
younger	O
than	O
the	O
society	O
she	O
happens	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
not	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
proper	O
deference	O
&	O
respect	O
,	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
shew	O
she	O
knows	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
right	O
to	O
appear	O
an	O
intruder	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
ten	O
ye	O
.	O
G	O
.	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
C	O
:	O
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
supper	O
was	O
ready	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
Room	O
--	O
we	O
soon	O
after	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
12.	O
conversation	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
melancholy	O
situation	O
of	O
Poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
Corke	I-pers
retired	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
ye	O
.	O
excuse	O
of	O
attending	O
her	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Mother	O
together	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
they	O
probably	O
wd	O
.	O
set	O
talking	O
till	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
--	O
receivd	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Woman	O
s	O
bleſsing	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
bed	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
1	O
oClock	O
to	O
write	O
Decbr	O
.	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Bullstrode	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
the	O
Servt	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
s	O
room	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
breakfasting	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
)	O
so	O
our	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
interrupted	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
appear	O
'd	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
this	O
Morning	O
--	O
but	O
her	O
spirits	O
were	O
better	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
beloved	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
&	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
comfort	O
of	O
being	O
aſsured	O
by	O
her	O
that	O
little	O
Katherine	B-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
&	O
that	O
her	O
own	O
health	O
&	O
&	O
spirits	O
were	O
restored	O
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Fanny	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
11	O
&	O
proposed	O
a	O
walk	O
--	O
I	O
readily	O
attended	O
her	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
was	O
mild	O
&	O
pleasant	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Greenhouse	O
wch	O
.	O
forms	O
one	O
Wing	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
in	O
an	O
inclosure	O
it	O
are	O
many	O
beautiful	O
Birds	O
--	O
some	O
fine	O
Peacocks	O
--	O
remarkable	O
pretty	O
Bantam	O
's	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
two	O
Grews	O
or	O
Numedian	O
Cranes	O
--	O
these	O
Cranes	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
Years	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
tame	O
that	O
came	O
hopping	O
to	O
us	O
&	O
eat	O
bread	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
hands	O
--	O
these	O
birds	O
have	O
a	O
singular	O
method	O
d	O
of	O
jumping	O
&	O
dancing	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
pleased	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
really	O
quite	O
laughable	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
ir	O
odd	O
capers	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
cut	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Grotto	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
told	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
soarce	O
of	O
amusement	O
the	O
forming	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
it	O
being	O
entirely	O
form	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
--	O
she	O
began	O
it	O
just	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
loved	O
Sister	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
ye-	O
year	O
1759	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
our	O
walk	O
we	O
separated	O
--	O
I	O
begun	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
sheet	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Window	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
our	O
walk	O
she	O
pursued	O
hers	O
alone	O
--	O
I	O
again	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
upstairs	O
as	O
she	O
heard	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
the	O
Chaplain	O
was	O
come	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
for	O
sometime	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
:	O
Room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
:	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
--	O
about	O
1	O
oClock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Chapel	O
--	O
the	O
Chapel	O
is	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
preach	O
'd	O
a	O
sensible	O
discourse	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
please	O
me	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
--	O
it	O
grew	O
tedious	O
&	O
was	O
spun	O
out	O
too	O
long	O
.	O
After	O
Chapel	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
&	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
in	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Gallery	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
in	O
London	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
absent	O
all	O
the	O
Week	O
.	O
he	O
soon	O
took	O
leave	O
.	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
their	O
rooms	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
detain	O
'd	O
me	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
her	O
Mother	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
added	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
--	O
was	O
beginning	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
illneſs	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
conduct	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
coming	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
our	O
conversation	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
desired	O
I	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
alter	O
my	O
Dreſs	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
eat	O
oysters	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
always	O
does	O
between	O
breakfast	O
&	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
3	O
oClock	O
--	O
say	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
again	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
my	O
letters	O
--	O
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
at	O
4	O
ye	O
.	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chambers	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ring	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
already	O
there	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
famous	O
Automaton	O
ye	O
.	O
Cheſs	O
Player	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
London	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
ladies	O
to	O
their	O
coffee	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
own	O
converse	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
went	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
&	O
enclosed	O
my	O
letters	O
to	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
library	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Book	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wanted	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
something	O
in	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Memoirs	O
--	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Temple	I-pers
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
dinner	O
tea	O
was	O
ready	O
--	O
met	O
William	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
housekeeper	O
who	O
said	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
civil	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
terrible	O
slip-slop	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
that	O
one	O
is	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
ones	O
countenance	O
.	O
after	O
tea	O
till	O
supper	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
our	O
little	O
Table	O
&	O
candles	O
--	O
Books	O
of	O
Prints	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
very	O
agreeable	O
--	O
“	O
from	O
Grave	O
,	O
to	O
Gay	O
”	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
also	O
,	O
as	O
ye	O
Poet	O
adds	O
--	O
“	O
from	O
lively	O
to	O
severe	O
”	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Converse	O
during	O
2	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
--	O
former	O
Actors	O
&	O
Actreſs	O
's	O
--	O
anecdotes	O
concerning	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
attachment	O
of	O
Dogs	O
--	O
some	O
stories	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
&	O
I	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Boileau-Despreaux	I-pers
½	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
attended	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Soame	I-pers
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
undreſ	O
'd	O
sent	O
John	B-pers
Dryden	I-pers
to	O
bed	O
--	O
sat	O
up	O
&	O
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddon	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
Pilgrim	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
..	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Bullstrode	O
Before	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
the	O
sert	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
E	O
gerton	O
family	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
said	O
how	O
cautious	O
Young	O
women	O
should	O
be	O
what	O
society	O
they	O
enterd	O
into	O
&	O
particularly	O
wth	O
.	O
whom	O
they	O
appeared	O
in	O
public	O
.	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
an	O
anecdote	O
of	O
herself	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Young	O
&	O
first	O
married	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Hell-Fire	O
club	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
consisted	O
of	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
dozen	O
Persons	O
of	O
fashion	O
of	O
both	O
sexes	O
--	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
females	O
were	O
unmarried	O
--	O
the	O
horrid	O
impieties	O
these	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
ridicule	O
ye	O
.	O
scriptures	O
&	O
their	O
conversation	O
was	O
blasphemous	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
degree	O
--	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
act	O
plays	O
--	O
some	O
represented	O
ye	O
.	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
wth	O
.	O
Child	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Members	O
of	O
this	O
Club	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Betty	B-pers
&	O
an	O
his	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
wch	O
.	O
Bishop	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
who	O
attended	O
him	O
gave	O
Simon	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
day	O
he	O
died	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
s	O
who	O
had	O
apartments	O
at	O
Somerset	O
house	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Sy	O
House	O
dining	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Aunt	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Pendarves	I-pers
the	O
Physician	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
quite	O
overcome	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
horrid	O
scene	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
quitted	O
--	O
said	O
he	O
left	O
this	O
miserable	O
wretch	O
expiring	O
--	O
uttering	O
the	O
most	O
horrid	O
imprecations	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
denying	O
his	O
belief	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
sacred	O
--	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
burn	O
in	O
Hell	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
then	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
a	O
sister	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Virtue	O
&	O
good	O
principles	O
but	O
unfortunately	O
for	O
her	O
conceived	O
a	O
violent	O
attachment	O
to	O
a	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
--	O
one	O
the	O
handsomest	O
men	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
times	O
--	O
but	O
a	O
perfect	O
Lothario	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
oportunities	O
of	O
being	O
much	O
together	O
&	O
he	O
attach	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
her	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
plain	O
young	O
Woman	O
--	O
but	O
his	O
vanity	O
was	O
gratified	O
in	O
having	O
raised	O
so	O
strong	O
a	O
paſsion	O
in	O
her	O
breast	O
.	O
She	O
thought	O
her	O
love	O
returned	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
paſsionate	O
letters	O
paſs	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
&	O
their	O
pictures	O
exchanged	O
&	O
he	O
at	O
length	O
grew	O
tired	O
of	O
&	O
neglected	O
her	O
&	O
openly	O
addreſsed	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
the	O
wretched	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
after	O
having	O
used	O
every	O
endeavour	O
to	O
recall	O
his	O
affection	O
became	O
almost	O
frantic	O
with	O
despair	O
--	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
one	O
morning	O
from	O
Hampton	O
Palace	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Court	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honour	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
)	O
(	O
afterwards	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
)	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
herself	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
house	O
in	O
Pall	O
Mall	O
acting	O
a	O
thousand	O
wild	O
extravagancies	O
,	O
this	O
of	O
course	O
soon	O
attracted	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
spectators	O
--	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
an	O
opposite	O
house	O
saw	O
this	O
unhappy	O
woman	O
,	O
&	O
knowing	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
he	O
humanely	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
ye	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
--	O
here	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
colvu	O
convulsions	O
&	O
soon	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
her	O
reason	O
wch	O
.	O
now	O
was	O
totally	O
gone	O
,	O
her	O
friends	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
--	O
&	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
she	O
died	O
raving	O
Mad	O
.	O
notwithstanding	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
to	O
whom	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
paid	O
his	O
addreſses	O
was	O
made	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
this	O
story	O
--	O
she	O
married	O
him	O
soon	O
after	O
Miſs	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
s	O
Death	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
received	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
daily	O
Message	O
of	O
Kind	O
inquiring	O
--	O
wrote	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
--	O
but	O
finding	O
Lady	O
Weymouth	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
--	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Grotto	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
cold	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
sun	O
gave	O
no	O
sign	O
of	O
appearing	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lengthen	O
my	O
walk	O
.	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Window	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Queen	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
come	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
till	O
these	O
M——	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
some	O
verses	O
wch	O
.	O
her	O
Maid	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
written	O
upon	O
her	O
last	O
Birth-day	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
without	O
merit	O
&	O
seem	O
'd	O
written	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
heart	O
.	O
When	O
Queen	B-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
staid	O
sometime	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
--	O
to	O
practice	O
Spinning	O
--	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
proficiency	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
one	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
s	O
footman	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
at	O
I	O
then	O
begun	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
pasteboard	O
for	O
a	O
Chinese	O
Paper	O
Lant	O
h	O
ern	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
imitate	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
pst	O
d	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
their	O
M——	O
went	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
eat	O
oysters	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
excuse	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
eat	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
some	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
late	O
before	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
hers	O
(	O
NB	O
her	O
room	O
is	O
abt	O
.	O
80	O
feet	O
from	O
mine	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
straight	O
line	O
indeed	O
--	O
but	O
so	O
often	O
does	O
she	O
trot	O
to	O
&	O
fro	O
that	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
84	O
that	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
often	O
blush	O
at	O
my	O
lazyineſs	O
)	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
news	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
--	O
wt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
wt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
much	O
ye	O
.	O
better	O
for	O
this	O
visit	O
for	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
fatigued	O
&	O
heated	O
--	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
sent	O
me	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
not	O
waiting	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
me	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
fatigued	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
excuse	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
conversation	O
after	O
dinner	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
Coffee	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
--	O
to	O
leave	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
together	O
--	O
attended	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
she	O
was	O
I	O
thought	O
much	O
exhausted	O
&	O
had	O
exerted	O
herself	O
too	O
much	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
repose	O
.	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
7	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
all	O
our	O
tables	O
&	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Epistle	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
conversed	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Wilmots	O
--	O
were	O
our	O
topics	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
apartments	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
as	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
private	O
converse	O
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
wrote	O
my	O
Journal	O
.	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
curious	O
Fungus	O
's	O
this	O
afternoon	O
--	O
one	O
particularly	O
so	O
wch	O
.	O
came	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Bois	O
de	O
Boulonge	O
--	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
is	O
dying	O
--	O
they	O
say	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sincere	O
Penitent	O
--	O
her	O
mother	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
is	O
in	O
great	O
affliction	O
.	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
England	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
great	O
distreſs	O
of	O
many	O
who	O
formerly	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
quitted	O
her	O
Baron	O
--	O
her	O
Character	O
&	O
c	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
--	O
Groom	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
Nice	B-place
--	O
they	O
think	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
recover	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
in	O
great	O
affliction	O
--	O
her	O
only	O
Daughter	O
Lady	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
being	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Physician	O
at	O
Nice	B-place
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Holderneſse	I-pers
ill	O
&	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
accompany	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
otherwise	O
to	O
have	O
staid	O
with	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
at	O
St.	B-place
Albans	I-place
till	O
her	O
Child	O
was	O
wean	O
'd	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
next	O
March	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Legge	I-pers
is	O
to	O
mourn	O
two	O
years	O
&	O
remain	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
has	O
added	O
a	O
1000	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
to	O
her	O
joynture	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
4000	O
pr	O
..	O
An	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
in	O
consequence	O
given	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Personals	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Late	O
Lord	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
ye	O
Ducheſs	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
to	O
invite	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
here	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
conversation	O
afterwards	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
that	O
wicked	O
wretch	O
Lady	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
detection	O
of	O
his	O
Guilt	O
--	O
a	O
former	O
trial	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
an	O
accusation	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
upon	O
his	O
F	O
:	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
wld	O
.	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
oClock	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
left	O
y	O
e	O
Dſs	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
Gallery	O
met	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
--	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
to	O
enqu	O
ire	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
&	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
s	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
poor	O
old	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
was	O
dead	O
he	O
died	O
2	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
her	O
Room	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
Bleſsing	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Book	O
--	O
sent	O
Lord	B-pers
Denbigh	I-pers
to	O
Bed	O
&	O
sat	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Bulstrode	O
Tuesday	O
Decbr	O
.	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
3	O
letters	O
one	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
one	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
little	O
Weaver	B-pers
--	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
read	O
some	O
paſsages	O
from	O
ym	O
.	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
--	O
let	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Breakfast	O
was	O
over	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
Packett	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
as	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
a	O
Stage	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
usual	O
Kind	O
meſsage	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
Fan̄y	B-pers
y	O
e	O
.	O
House	O
Steward	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
Chimney	O
board	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
to	O
cover	O
wth	O
.	O
Prints	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
Medly	O
stile	O
.	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
his	O
drawings	O
some	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
day	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
being	O
a	O
thick	O
fog	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
repair	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Chimney	O
board	O
of	O
her	O
doing	O
in	O
Colord	O
Paper	O
--	O
Vases	O
,	O
Antique	O
figures	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
I	O
painted	O
12	O
til	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
took	O
her	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Town	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
meſsages	O
&	O
c	O
Betty	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
set	O
out	O
had	O
her	O
reel	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wound	O
of	O
her	O
yarn	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
repairing	O
ye	O
Screen	O
Mr.	B-pers
Levoes	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
housekeeper	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
a	O
Maid	O
sleep	O
in	O
ye	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
now	O
Betty	O
was	O
gone	O
&	O
other	O
civil	O
offers	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Maid	O
came	O
&	O
we	O
ma	O
id	O
de	O
her	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Newspapers	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
left	O
me	O
.	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
come	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
famous	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Dews	I-pers
--	O
among	O
others	O
,	O
one	O
striking	O
anecdote	O
that	O
though	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
affected	O
in	O
highest	O
degree	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
grand	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
she	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
after	O
she	O
died	O
for	O
the	O
Jewels	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
--	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
lent	O
ym	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
answer	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
never	O
demand	O
those	O
jewels	O
again	O
except	O
she	O
danced	O
at	O
Court	O
--	O
her	O
answer	O
was	O
then	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
D——	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
dance	O
at	O
Court	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
behaved	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
extravagant	O
manner	O
--	O
her	O
grief	O
notwithstanding	O
most	O
violent	O
in	O
appearance	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
one	O
day	O
laying	O
prostrate	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
ground	O
&	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
(	O
who	O
told	O
this	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
)	O
had	O
liked	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
over	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
being	O
dark	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
said	O
she	O
was	O
praying	O
--	O
for	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
thus	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Ground	O
being	O
too	O
Wicked	O
to	O
Kneel	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
died	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
promising	O
youth	O
at	O
the	O
University	O
--	O
her	O
grief	O
was	O
unbounded	O
--	O
her	O
Vanity	O
was	O
wounded	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
hopes	O
of	O
an	O
ambitious	O
Mind	O
was	O
destroy	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
used	O
by	O
way	O
mortification	O
&	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
affliction	O
to	O
dreſs	O
herself	O
like	O
a	O
beggar	O
&	O
sit	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
miserable	O
wretches	O
in	O
the	O
Cloisters	O
at	O
Westminster	O
Abbey	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
said	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Dk	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
her	O
during	O
this	O
mourning	O
of	O
hers	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
at	O
Westminster	O
School	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
certain	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Heaven	O
&	O
as	O
her	O
ambition	O
went	O
even	O
beyond	O
ye	O
.	O
Grave	O
--	O
That	O
she	O
Knew	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
highest	O
seats	O
--	O
many	O
other	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
were	O
told	O
&	O
the	O
hat	O
Ducheſs	O
show	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
original	O
letters	O
written	O
to	O
her	O
Grandfather	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Marlbrough	I-pers
(	O
Reign	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
by	O
the	O
Famous	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
of	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
those	O
of	O
her	B-pers
Son	I-pers
were	O
witty	O
&	O
impious	O
&	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
gr	O
flattering	O
encomiums	O
&	O
c	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
said	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
s	O
Person	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
handsome	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
fine	O
addreſs	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
drinker	O
&	O
swore	O
terribly	O
--	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
his	O
coming	O
once	O
to	O
her	O
Uncle	O
Q	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
s	O
at	O
North	O
End	O
--	O
his	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
--	O
&	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Greenhouse	O
where	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
upon	O
a	O
Couch	O
--	O
a	O
meſsage	O
arrived	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
waited	O
for	O
by	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Counsal	O
--	O
he	O
rous	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
snach	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Green	O
bag	O
of	O
Paper	O
&	O
flew	O
to	O
Busineſs	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Bolingbroke	I-pers
told	O
us	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
people	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
no	O
Man	O
ever	O
was	O
so	O
early	O
so	O
active	O
,	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
M——	I-pers
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Place	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
truth	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
drinking	O
all	O
night	O
&	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
--	O
to	O
put	O
wet	O
napkin	O
g	O
s	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
&	O
Eyes	O
to	O
cool	O
the	O
heat	O
&	O
head	O
achs	O
occasiond	O
by	O
his	O
intemperance	O
&	O
then	O
appears	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
Busineſs	O
wth	O
.	O
as	O
much	O
ease	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
lived	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
temperate	O
life	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
who	O
died	O
a	O
few	O
month	O
ago	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
aged	O
83	O
wth	O
.	O
all	O
her	O
faculties	O
unimpaird	O
--	O
gave	O
us	O
her	O
Character	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
anecdote	O
--	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Levee	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
Lord	B-pers
Bolingbroke	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Stanley	I-pers
s	O
Heir	O
(	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
abroad	O
)	O
--	O
was	O
talking	O
there	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
stood	O
next	O
him	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Quarrel	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Viger	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Irish	O
house	O
--	O
&	O
said	O
--	O
't	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
it	O
can	O
end	O
so	O
they	O
must	O
fight	O
--	O
Oh	O
says	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Coalition	O
&	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
secretaries	O
of	O
state	O
.	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
was	O
next	O
talk	O
of	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
men	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
3000	O
feet	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Air	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
went	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
eating	O
Oysters	O
wth	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
finish	O
'd	O
Lord	B-pers
N——	I-pers
s	O
screen	O
&	O
begun	O
ye	O
.	O
Medley	O
one	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Flood	I-pers
reposd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
room	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
Prints	O
in	O
a	O
Folio	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
out	O
for	O
my	O
the	O
Board	O
I	O
am	O
doing	O
.	O
Gratten	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
Windsor	B-place
he	O
had	O
been	O
wth	O
.	O
y	O
Dſs	O
.	O
us	O
u	O
al	O
enquiries	O
after	O
their	O
M——	O
After	O
tea	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
began	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
account	O
Memoirs	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
written	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
course	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
to	O
first	O
abt	O
a	O
plan	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Vincent	I-place
&	O
c	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
Goldsworthy	B-pers
Cousin	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
separated	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
one	O
doing	O
my	O
screen	O
10	O
th	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Marlbrough	I-pers
came	O
&	O
assisted	O
me	O
in	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensbury	I-pers
found	O
her	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Uncle	O
to	O
say	O
--	O
he	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
ye	O
.	O
King	O
was	O
to	O
invite	O
him	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
c	O
Conversation	O
at	O
B	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
education	O
&	O
c.	O
soon	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Astley	I-pers
--	O
wish	O
him	O
to	O
marry	O
--	O
said	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
too	O
well	O
understood	O
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
meſsage	O
soon	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
lookd	O
at	O
my	O
Work	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
screen	O
&	O
c	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
works	O
of	O
her	O
doing	O
--	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
Prayers	O
Bell	O
was	O
rung	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
notice	O
there	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
Sacrament	O
next	O
Sunday	O
--	O
After	O
C	O
Lady	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
came	O
up	O
.	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
--	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
new	O
Fungus	O
's	O
ye	O
Gardener	O
had	O
found	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
sreen	O
therefore	O
she	O
orderd	O
ye	O
.	O
Oysters	O
brought	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
herself	O
--	O
said	O
an	O
awful	O
time	O
was	O
approaching	O
that	O
all	O
she	O
felt	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
leaving	O
those	O
that	O
loved	O
her	O
to	O
mourn	O
her	O
loſs	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
meet	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
her	O
house	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
Prints	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
her	O
Md	O
.	O
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
in	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
when	O
she	O
expaitiatded	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
s	O
goodneſs	O
wept	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
how	O
extremely	O
--	O
sensible	O
,	O
&	O
grateful	O
she	O
appears	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
began	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
--	O
at	O
4	O
went	O
up	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
together	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dg	O
room	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
joind	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
lively	O
conversation	O
--	O
after	O
D	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
remaind	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dining	O
room	O
--	O
till	O
near	O
7	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
conduct	O
--	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Character	O
--	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
dear	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
After	O
tea	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
added	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
was	O
chid	O
for	O
running	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
had	O
his	O
table	O
&	O
Papers	O
Mr	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
prayers	O
while	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Copy	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
mistakes	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
read	O
till	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
therefore	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
before	O
Supper	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
recd	O
.	O
her	O
Bleſsing	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
D	O
.	O
room	O
--	O
whilst	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
a	O
visit	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
Q	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
liv	O
'd	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lively	O
altercation	O
abt	O
.	O
paying	O
a	O
Compn	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
us	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
&	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
heard	O
a	O
Curious	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
Halifax	B-place
--	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
Candles	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
sent	O
me	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prayers	O
.	O
11	O
th	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
came	O
&	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
B	O
--	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
B	O
room	O
.	O
we	O
B	O
upstairs	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
Letters	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bollin	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
--	O
converse	O
at	O
B	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eaton	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
begun	O
to	O
write	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
soon	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
found	O
herself	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
as	O
she	O
had	O
intended	O
to	O
visit	O
Mr	B-pers
L——	I-pers
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
I	O
persuaded	O
her	O
agst	O
.	O
it	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
foggy	O
&	O
cold	O
.	O
Rcd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Meſsage	O
--	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Journal	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
busy	O
transcribing	O
--	O
I	O
began	O
transcribing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Prayers	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
is	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
Copy	O
.	O
Sat	O
in	O
ye	O
D	O
room	O
till	O
dinner	O
did	O
not	O
alter	O
my	O
Dreſs	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
--	O
the	O
Dſs	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
looking	O
over	O
Books	O
--	O
China	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
turning	O
room	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
tea	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
read	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
foundling	O
Hospital	O
for	O
Wit	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
read	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
Memoires	O
--	O
&	O
contrived	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
spent	O
a	O
Peaceful	O
Eveg	O
.	O
sat	O
up	O
til	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
reading	O
in	O
ye	O
ye	O
Lady	B-pers
L	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
Mann	O
12	O
th	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
dreſs	O
--	O
breakfasted	O
upstairs	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
Queen	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
Airing	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
&	O
ye	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
found	O
Prior	B-pers
from	O
Windsor	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
--	O
he	O
staid	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
many	O
particulars	O
of	O
ye	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
&	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
at	O
Eaton	O
--	O
ye	O
shameful	O
manner	O
in	O
wh	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
behaved	O
to	O
ye	O
Gentleman	O
Aſsistants	O
--	O
some	O
laughable	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
boys	O
destroying	O
ye	O
Whipping	O
Post	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
fixture	O
time	O
immemorial	O
--	O
their	O
selling	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
s	O
son	O
--	O
not	O
being	O
permitted	O
by	O
his	O
tutor	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
destruction	O
of	O
it	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
Lady	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
great	O
triumph	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
w	O
d	O
.	O
carry	O
London	B-place
to	O
Gordon	O
Castle	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
preserve	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
trophy	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
the	O
Boys	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
tool	O
to	O
divide	O
their	O
spoils	O
of	O
the	O
whipping	O
Post	O
that	O
red	O
hot	O
Pokers	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
No	O
prayers	O
to	O
day	O
as	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
.	O
book	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Morng	O
paſs	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
some	O
Shell	O
&	O
foſsils	O
--	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
ym	O
.	O
over	O
&	O
placed	O
them	O
in	O
drawers	O
&	O
c	O
Conversation	O
--	O
Air	O
Balloons	O
Dr	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
made	O
a	O
Drawing	O
of	O
one	O
--	O
&	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
Great	O
Meteor	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
saw	O
from	O
ye	O
Terrace	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marquis	I-pers
of	I-pers
Huntley	I-pers
went	O
away	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
together	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Medly	O
Chimney	O
Board	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Mr	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
writing	O
Dr	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
at	O
their	O
Work	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
Conversation	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
Words	O
Beautiful	O
--	O
Handsome	O
--	O
Agreeable	O
--	O
fine	O
Person	O
.	O
pretty	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
separated	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
Maid	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
came	O
&	O
insisted	O
upon	O
doing	O
my	O
Hair	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
Curling	O
Irons	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
dreſ	O
'd	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
submit	O
--	O
comb	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
out	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
After	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
past	O
one	O
reading	O
Decbr	O
.	O
13	O
Saturday	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
came	O
to	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
Dreſsing	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
went	O
upstairs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
only	O
in	O
ye	O
Breakfast	O
room	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
began	O
to	O
break	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
letters	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
--	O
one	O
comfortable	O
long	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
&	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
soon	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
:	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
read	O
ye	O
Man	O
:	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
prayers	O
yt	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
mine	O
correctly	O
.	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Clogs	O
&	O
c	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
delightful	O
Clear	O
day	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Warm	O
Sun	O
the	O
Air	O
frosty	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
long	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
Sh	O
ru	O
bbery	O
.	O
flower	O
Garden	O
.	O
botanick	O
Garden	O
&	O
c	O
fed	O
the	O
Grews	O
&	O
other	O
Birds	O
.	O
during	O
our	O
Walk	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
only	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
fortune	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
living	O
--	O
his	O
Character	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
form	O
our	O
walk	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
letter	O
Then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
,	O
staid	O
somet	O
ime	O
--	O
&	O
at	O
look	O
over	O
Papers	O
Q	B-pers
:	I-pers
Eliz	I-pers
:	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Manuscripts	O
to	O
copy	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
request	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
&	O
she	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
D——	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
eat	O
Oysters	O
--	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
together	O
many	O
fine	O
things	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
Miſsil	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
some	O
fine	O
Miniatures	O
2	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
a	O
Lord	O
&	O
Countess	O
of	O
Pembroke	O
,	O
ye	O
other	O
2	O
unknown	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
one	O
Large	O
Locket	O
black	O
&	O
Green	O
in	O
a	O
tortoishell	O
Case	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
his	O
son	O
in	O
an	O
Oldfashion	O
'd	O
Locket	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
ornamented	O
wth	O
.	O
Jewels	O
in	O
a	O
Large	O
Locket	O
Black	O
&	O
Green	O
enamel	O
.	O
it	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Cyphers	O
--	O
of	O
W.	O
R	O
.	O
&	O
E.	O
are	O
still	O
remaining	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
ye	O
.	O
enamel	O
is	O
damaged	O
.	O
a	O
Miſsal	O
very	O
inferior	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
former	O
bound	O
in	O
silver	O
of	O
a	O
smaller	O
size	O
given	O
to	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
by	O
ye	O
present	O
Queen	O
Edward	B-pers
ye	I-pers
.	I-pers
6th-	I-pers
at	O
her	O
spinning	O
wheel	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
at	O
her	O
Capert	O
Carpet	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
then	O
--	O
after	O
much	O
persuasion	O
&	O
our	O
taking	O
away	O
her	O
wosterds	O
left	O
off	O
Isaac	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
2	I-pers
by	I-pers
Oliver	I-pers
went	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
gown	O
.	O
he	O
&	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
I	O
aſsisted	O
y	O
e	O
Dſs	O
.	O
in	O
putting	O
up	O
ye	O
things	O
&	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
other	O
Curious	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
...	I-pers
Olivier	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſsal	O
&	O
c	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
ye	O
Dr	O
room	O
to	O
hunt	O
for	O
some	O
paper	O
covering	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
length	O
went	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
hands	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
near	O
6	O
oClock	O
.	O
Milton	B-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
tune	O
upon	O
ye	O
Organ	O
to	O
hasten	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
dinner	O
Sr.	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
Raliegh	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Raliegh	I-pers
was	O
sometime	O
settling	O
her	O
work	O
I	O
aſsisted	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
she	O
had	O
purchased	O
--	O
&	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
shameful	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
of	O
many	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
of	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
tea	O
time	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
ye	O
cramp	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
Manuscripts	O
for	O
me	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
to	O
Copy	O
&	O
read	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
begun	O
to	O
read	O
abt	O
.	O
8.	O
read	O
till	O
near	O
ten	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
I	O
then	O
left	O
off	O
&	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
a	O
droll	O
story	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
having	O
Papers	O
wch	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
Mr.	B-pers
West	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
s	O
Reign	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
,	O
his	O
treatment	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
living	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
after	O
his	O
marriage	O
to	O
her	O
neice	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
Marriage	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Shelburne	I-pers
.	O
Grandfather	B-pers
s	O
character	O
&	O
c	O
comments	O
upon	O
--	O
ye	O
Conversation	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
of	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Lord	B-pers
Shelburne	I-pers
told	O
me	O
one	O
anecdote	O
of	O
her	O
serving	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Granville	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
folly	O
of	O
a	O
Lady	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
El	O
abt	O
a	O
H	O
:	O
Coach	O
Lady	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
s	O
answer	O
.	O
we	O
separated	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
two	O
writing	O
reading	O
out	O
things	O
Lady	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
told	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Exeter	I-pers
--	O
his	O
courting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
traducing	O
his	O
memory	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
Sunday	O
Bullstrode	O
Mrs.	B-pers
GriffithsElstrope	I-pers
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
in	O
Dressing	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
room	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
upon	O
religious	O
subjects	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Delany	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
first	O
receiving	O
ye	O
.	O
sacrament	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
2	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Wesleys	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Methodist	O
Preachers	O
she	O
knew	O
ym	O
.	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Young	O
Men	O
--	O
they	O
lived	O
near	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
students	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
they	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
serious	O
turn	O
&	O
aſsociated	O
wth	O
.	O
such	O
as	O
were	O
so	O
--	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Evg	O
these	O
Brothers	O
joind	O
some	O
other	O
young	O
Men	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
&	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Eveg	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Scriptures	O
&	O
find	O
out	O
Objects	O
of	O
Charity	O
for	O
to	O
relieve	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
happy	O
beginning	O
--	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Vanity	O
of	O
being	O
singular	O
&	O
growing	O
Enthusiasts	O
made	O
them	O
endeavour	O
to	O
gain	O
proselytes	O
&	O
ad	O
d	O
opt	O
th	O
ose	O
at	O
system	O
of	O
Religious	O
doctrine	O
wch	O
.	O
many	O
reasonable	O
People	O
think	O
pernicious	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
letters	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Orrery	I-pers
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
remain	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
Chappel	O
time	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
Swift	B-pers
ye	O
.	O
House	O
Steward	O
came	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
large	O
Porte	O
Folio	O
of	O
his	O
Drawings	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
came	O
&	O
we	O
lookd	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
them	O
over	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
then	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
chapel	O
--	O
met	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Gallery	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
sermon	O
--	O
because	O
of	O
ye	O
sacrament	O
wch	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
made	O
ye	O
Service	O
too	O
long	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Levers	I-pers
has	O
an	O
other	O
Church	O
to	O
serve	O
.	O
When	O
ye	O
.	O
prayers	O
were	O
over	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
ye	O
Chapel	O
.	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Pew	O
next	O
ye	O
.	O
Altar	O
&	O
received	O
ye	O
Communion	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
abt	O
.	O
22	O
Servants	O
who	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
sacrament	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
After	O
Chapel	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
Abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
eat	O
Oysters	O
.	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
trinkets	O
gifts	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
Picture	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
done	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
when	O
she	O
was	O
young	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
neat	O
tortoishell	O
Box	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Medallion	O
of	O
her	O
hair	O
in	O
a	O
cypher	O
set	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
pearls	O
&	O
c	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Dreſs	O
Mr.	B-pers
Levers	I-pers
aſsisted	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
found	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
made	O
me	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
our	O
stile	O
of	O
living	O
--	O
our	O
house	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Repose	O
d	O
in	O
ye	O
D	O
:	O
R	O
:	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
apartments	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
ye	O
doors	O
were	O
shut	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
state	O
bedchamber	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
formerly	O
disposed	O
&	O
furnished	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
sat	O
conversing	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
alterations	O
made	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
head	O
Keeper	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
word	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
I	O
insisted	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
came	O
to	O
room	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Zincks	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
reproached	O
me	O
most	O
kindly	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
absent	O
--	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
writing	O
letters	O
that	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
so	O
soon	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
write	O
any	O
more	O
letters	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
Manuscripts	O
of	O
ye	O
Ducheſs	O
's	O
she	O
left	O
us	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
finish	O
letters	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
conversed	O
I	O
wrote	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
ducheſs	O
--	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
Portrait	O
Prints	O
&	O
related	O
anecdotes	O
relating	O
to	O
them	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
us	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brumpton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Manuscripts	O
to	O
copy	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Conversation	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
sore	O
throats	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
famous	O
rect	O
.	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
many	O
instances	O
of	O
the	O
cures	O
it	O
had	O
made	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
plaister	O
she	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
rect	O
.	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
ab	O
t	O
.	O
Education	O
.	O
we	O
parted	O
abt	O
¼	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
2	O
writing	O
16	O
15	O
th	O
Monday	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Key	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
papers	O
&	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
her	O
usual	O
meſsage	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Aunt	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
the	O
circumstance	O
's	O
attending	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
two	O
fine	O
Rosarys	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
left	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
D——	O
room	O
before	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
settled	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
work	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
soon	O
came	O
ye	O
.	O
Dss	O
.	O
found	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
was	O
quite	O
unhappy	O
abt	O
.	O
it	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
fine	O
things	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
wch	O
.	O
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
I	O
shall	O
notice	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
were	O
at	O
there	O
work	O
&	O
c	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
Broth	O
for	O
my	O
Cold	O
.	O
&	O
they	O
were	O
as	O
unhappy	O
abt	O
.	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
actually	O
in	O
a	O
consumption	O
.	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
as	O
also	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
Eaton	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
&	O
one	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Provost	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Pendarves	I-pers
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
aſsist	O
her	O
in	O
locking	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
shewn	O
me	O
.	O
then	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
&	O
c	O
no	O
time	O
for	O
dreſsing	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
brough	O
me	O
answers	O
to	O
my	O
notes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
alone	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
answer	O
to	O
her	O
note	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
various	O
topics	O
of	O
conversation	O
came	O
into	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
abt	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
reposed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
read	O
me	O
Manuscript	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Epicure	O
&	O
c	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
had	O
not	O
been	O
candid	O
nor	O
true	O
in	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
written	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
--	O
they	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
read	O
because	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
me	O
hoarse	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
cold	O
&	O
c	O
wanted	O
vastly	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
out	O
something	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
secretary	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
histy	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
times	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
read	O
many	O
interesting	O
anecdotes	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Man	O
.	O
Book	O
--	O
of	O
Pope	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
Johnston	B-pers
,	O
her	O
Character	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
--	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
,	O
a	O
laughable	O
Anecdote	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
Q	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
.	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ceremon	O
y	O
ie	O
s	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
aſsembly	O
she	O
ever	O
gave	O
his	O
throwing	O
down	O
a	O
tea	O
Kettle	O
in	O
paying	O
his	O
Compts	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
entrance	O
&	O
c.	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Society	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
B	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burnet	I-pers
--	O
Character	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
--	O
how	O
he	O
once	O
distreſsd	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
his	O
great	O
affection	O
for	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
description	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Character	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Present	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
s	O
mother	O
--	O
Vulgar	O
,	O
handsome	O
silly	O
--	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
once	O
to	O
her	O
footmen	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Chair	O
&	O
big	O
wth	O
.	O
child	O
--	O
John	O
John	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Belly	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
hoarse	O
voice	O
--	O
was	O
daughter	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
(	I-pers
when	I-pers
Widow	I-pers
to	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Pendarves	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
present	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pendarves	I-pers
.	O
y	O
e	O
present	O
their	O
days	O
of	O
Mourning	O
for	O
their	O
Wifes	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
well	O
together	O
.	O
ye	O
De	O
.	O
of	O
M	O
very	O
gay	O
&	O
had	O
miſtreſs	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
young	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
William	I-pers
's	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
famous	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
Jewel	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
&	O
tis	O
notorious	O
--	O
that	O
when	O
news	O
came	O
of	O
ye	O
Victory	O
of	O
Blenheim	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Picture	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
--	O
cover	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
flat	O
Diamond	O
wth	O
.	O
brilliant	O
edges	O
wch	O
.	O
cost	O
8000	O
Pounds	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
daughter	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
--	O
When	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
was	O
in	O
disgrace	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Holland	B-place
before	O
she	O
went	O
she	O
made	O
presents	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
--	O
&	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
QAnne	B-pers
Picture	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
had	O
given	O
her	O
--	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
round	O
with	O
Jewels	O
these	O
she	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
knowing	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
gave	O
her	O
this	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
value	O
for	O
it	O
&	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
mark	O
of	O
regard	O
sensibly	O
conscious	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
deserving	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
havng	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
poſseſsion	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
present	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Buccleugh	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Grandfather	O
--	O
who	O
in	O
a	O
genteel	O
way	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
100	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Welbeck	O
Mrs	B-pers
Higgen	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
had	O
upwards	O
of	O
90,000	O
Pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
in	O
Places	O
besides	O
Blenheim	O
&	O
all	O
their	O
family	O
&	O
Children	O
in	O
Places	O
.	O
they	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
even	O
pay	O
the	O
taxes	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
granted	O
them	O
at	O
Whitehal	O
--	O
&	O
whenever	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
made	O
a	O
Campain	O
he	O
was	O
alway	O
furnish	O
with	O
every	O
Material	O
of	O
Linnen	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
at	O
ye	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
expence	O
Lord	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
once	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
another	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
difficult	O
hand	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
person	O
said	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
puts	O
no	O
tittles	O
upon	O
the	O
i	O
's	O
--	O
O	O
says	O
ye	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
it	O
saves	O
his	O
Grace	O
ink	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
characters	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
Queen	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
after	O
supper	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
Eugene	I-pers
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Dunbar	O
that	O
was	O
--	O
her	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Marriage	O
--	O
her	O
character	O
--	O
of	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Vesey	O
--	O
her	O
Absenses	O
--	O
Of	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
--	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
E	I-pers
:	I-pers
Bentick	I-pers
--	O
of	O
ye	O
famous	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
sending	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
Busineſs	O
of	O
a	O
secret	O
Nature	O
to	O
ye	O
Post	O
wthout-	O
a	O
direction	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
Prince	O
s	O
affairs	O
--	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
y	O
e	O
hand	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
ye	O
Person	O
who	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
particulars	O
relating	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dowg	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Lytellton	I-pers
Late	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
--	O
we	O
separated	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
promise	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
12	O
tomorrow	O
but	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lytellon	I-pers
came	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
verses	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
beg	O
'd	O
she	O
found	O
me	O
writing	O
--	O
staid	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
told	O
me	O
many	O
things	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
her	O
conduct	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
2	O
oClock	O
writing	O
a	O
dark	O
foggy	O
day	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
Swift	B-pers
came	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
my	O
cold	O
was	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
.	I-pers
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
breakfast	O
in	O
bed	O
--	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dreſs	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
before	O
11	O
went	O
to	O
Vaneſsa	B-pers
--	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
slept	O
well	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
interesting	O
converse	O
--	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
what	O
time	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
again	O
repeated	O
that	O
she	O
looked	O
forward	O
to	O
my	O
being	O
a	O
Comfort	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
wish	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
give	O
her	O
when	O
that	O
period	O
arrived	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
--	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
loved	O
me	O
&	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
wld	O
.	O
give	O
her	O
comfort	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
my	O
character	O
--	O
O	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
ever	O
endeavour	O
to	O
act	O
up	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
character	O
&	O
be	O
from	O
my	O
heart	O
wt	O
.	O
she	O
thinks	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
settling	O
in	O
life	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
sort	O
of	O
Person	O
I	O
ought	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
happineſs	O
to	O
marry	O
--	O
plainly	O
very	O
plainly	O
she	O
drew	O
the	O
Picture	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
Wax	O
figures	O
of	O
Anatomy	O
in	O
ye	O
Museum	O
of	O
Dublin	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
her	O
paragraphs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
letters	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
After	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
as	O
had	O
letters	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
write	O
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Donan	I-pers
Donellan	I-pers
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
particulars	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
as	O
it	O
related	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
going	O
to	O
ye	B-place
West	I-place
indies	I-place
&	O
c.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
letter	O
of	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
make	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
D	O
.	O
uneasy	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
:	O
Dſs	O
.	O
kind	O
daily	O
Meſsage	O
of	O
enquiry	O
she	O
was	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
very	O
angry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
12	O
oClock	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
letters	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
room	O
wch	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
mentioned	O
in	O
her	O
letter	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
hea	O
d	O
r	O
d	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ben	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
's	O
son	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
room	O
found	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
there	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
her	O
own	O
Woman	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
fine	O
Miſsils	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
at	O
her	O
Wheel	O
we	O
conversed	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
character	O
ye	O
Miſs	O
J	O
who	O
does	O
ye	O
.	O
flowers	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.Peachey	B-pers
s	O
introduction	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
hoped	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
Sr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
mentions	O
in	O
her	O
letter	O
.	O
Talkd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
Ab	O
t	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
ye	O
..	O
Dſs	O
.	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
made	O
me	O
her	O
daily	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
nosegay	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
set	O
at	O
their	O
work	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
Miſsils	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miss	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
&	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Montagu	O
&	O
16	O
Decbr	O
1783	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
eat	O
Broth	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
left	O
us	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
read	O
my	O
letter	O
frm	O
Miſs	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
:	O
talked	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
--	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
dinner	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
ye	O
D	O
:	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
waiting	O
to	O
dreſs	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
talkd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
disappointment	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
in	O
his	O
application	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
plan	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
&	O
c	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Dr	O
.	O
room	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
alone	O
.	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
poſsible	O
to	O
her	O
this	O
winter	O
in	O
town	B-place
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
whenever	O
I	O
chose	O
that	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
always	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
but	O
never	O
take	O
it	O
ill	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
ſs	O
.	O
joind	O
us	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Horses	O
there	O
were	O
7	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
oClock	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
felt	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
having	O
given	O
her	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
D	O
reposed	O
in	O
ye	O
drawing	O
room	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
&	O
I	O
conversed	O
til	O
tea	O
time	O
&	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
porte	O
follio	O
of	O
drawings	O
Views	O
of	O
Spa	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
she	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
recd	O
from	O
a	O
M	O
rs	O
Walker	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
fetchd	O
some	O
original	O
letters	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astly	I-pers
s	O
--	O
to	O
her	O
Grandfather	O
&	O
ye	O
original	O
letter	O
she	O
wrote	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
upon	O
ye	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mr.	B-pers
Asford	I-pers
--	O
an	O
unaffected	O
sensible	O
letter	O
--	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
left	O
us	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
read	O
till	O
supper	O
time	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
supper	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
told	O
me	O
some	O
remarkable	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
of	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
--	O
his	O
reading	O
his	O
Satire	O
of	O
Attoſsa	O
--	O
his	O
conversations	O
wth	O
.	O
King	B-pers
William	I-pers
Queen	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
s	O
Secretary	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
s	O
Character	O
.	O
his	O
being	O
connected	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
getting	O
3000£	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
suppreſs	O
Atoſsa	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
published	O
it	O
after	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
parted	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Pope	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
talked	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
¼	O
after	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
2	O
oClock	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Bulstrode	O
1783	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
up	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
came	O
She	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
hair	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
10	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
--	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
Me	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Hooke	I-pers
--	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
ever	O
Chance	O
threw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
in	O
Life	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
her	O
sake	O
--	O
again	O
repeated	O
that	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
often	O
this	O
Winter	O
in	O
town	B-place
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
consult	O
me	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
look	O
over	O
Manuscrip	O
ts	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
to	O
Copy	O
,	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
drawing	O
's	O
&	O
obligingly	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
made	O
paper	O
Cases	O
for	O
the	O
Manuscripts	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
usual	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
Pope	B-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
&	O
read	O
ye	O
Papers	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
s	O
long	O
speech	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
upon	O
ye	O
East	O
India	O
tax	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
then	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
till	O
prayers	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
,	O
After	O
Prayers	O
we	O
all	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
room	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
at	O
his	O
table	O
&	O
Manuscripts	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
West	B-place
India	I-place
Shells	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Mr	B-pers
Liviers	I-pers
in	O
making	O
him	O
believe	O
these	O
were	O
oysters	O
coming	O
to	O
eat	O
this	O
occasion	O
'd	O
much	O
mirth	O
--	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
pronounced	O
ye	O
.	O
shells	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
--	O
afterwards	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
lookd	O
out	O
some	O
foſsils	O
&	O
shells	O
for	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
drawers	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
to	O
sort	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
begun	O
my	O
card	O
almanack	O
wch	O
..	O
Lord	B-pers
Abington	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
to	O
Copy	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
four	O
--	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
laugh	O
'd	O
so	O
once	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
form	O
table	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
choking	O
:	O
after	O
dinner	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
had	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Shells	O
brought	O
--	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
ym	O
.	O
over	O
together	O
&	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
Box	O
&	O
its	O
Contents	O
--	O
this	O
employ	O
'd	O
us	O
till	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
came	O
up	O
from	O
her	O
room	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
from	O
ye	O
Dining	O
room	O
.	O
At	O
7	O
tea	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
all	O
our	O
tables	O
&	O
I	O
finished	O
my	O
Almanack	O
&	O
wrote	O
ye	O
letter	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Papers	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
folded	O
&	O
seal	O
'd	O
ym	O
.	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
read	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
finished	O
ye	O
Book	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
curious	O
anecdotes	O
relative	O
to	O
those	O
times	O
--	O
a	O
singular	O
story	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Agnew	I-pers
receiving	O
an	O
Anonymous	O
letter	O
,	O
meeting	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
in	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
fields	O
&	O
what	O
paſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
having	O
him	O
a	O
fortnight	O
conceald	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
&	O
not	O
even	O
his	O
servants	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
--	O
he	O
learnt	O
many	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
Man	O
relative	O
d	O
to	O
Politic	O
's	O
--	O
when	O
got	O
to	O
L	O
:	O
Inn	O
:	O
fields	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
the	O
Man	O
Started	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
Graſs	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
hid	O
for	O
in	O
those	O
times	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
paved	O
&	O
c.	O
said	O
Sir	O
now	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
yes	O
I	O
am	O
says	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
injured	O
any	O
one	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
her	O
all	O
ye	O
:	O
Books	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
or	O
rather	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
past	O
ten	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
carried	O
ye	O
Voll	O
.	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
contains	O
his	O
Criticizm	O
on	O
Women	O
--	O
read	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
table	O
,	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
Attoſsa	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
meant	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbr	I-pers
'	I-pers
&	O
we	O
related	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harly	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
Prior	B-pers
--	O
we	O
parted	O
abt-	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Pope	B-pers
light	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Shells	O
&	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
came	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
things	O
--	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
her	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
to	O
leave	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
--	O
to	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
friendship	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Thursday	O
1783	O
M	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
my	O
papers	O
&	O
c	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Malbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
dreſsing	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
when	O
Breakfast	O
was	O
,	O
Pope	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
doing	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
dear	O
dear	O
Woman	O
.	O
Beg	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
hurry	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
soon	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
upstairs	O
--	O
Young	B-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
take	O
leave	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
my	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Shells	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
a	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
by	O
Voltaire	B-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
ye-	O
room	O
&	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
upon	O
paper	O
wht	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Lord	B-pers
Melcombe	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
separated	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
ready	O
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
housemaid	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
footman	O
came	O
&	O
put	O
up	O
carried	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
ye	O
Chaise	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
put	O
up	O
all	O
ye	O
books	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
most	O
tender	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
wept	O
&	O
said	O
kind	O
things	O
yt	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Heart	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
y	O
e	O
Dr	O
:	O
room	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
.	O
desird	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
care	O
of	O
keep	O
Company	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lighfoot	I-pers
.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
again	O
met	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
she	O
walk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
&	O
waited	O
till	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Housekeepers	O
Room	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
again	O
bid	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Adieu	O
.	O
went	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
Hall	O
.	O
ye	O
Bulter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
ye	O
Cook	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
waiting	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
set	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
door	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
11	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Morning	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
drive	O
.	O
We	O
paſs	O
,	O
a	O
Wedding	O
a	O
Burrial	O
&	O
an	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
told	O
me	O
many	O
circumstances	O
relative	O
to	O
her	O
family	O
--	O
&	O
particularly	O
a	O
sister	O
of	O
hers	O
who	O
lives	O
w	O
th	O
.	O
a	O
Mrs	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
their	O
manner	O
of	O
living	O
&	O
c.	O
talk	O
of	O
her	O
dear	O
&	O
worthy	O
Miſstreſs	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Talkd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mackay	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
arrived	O
in	O
Town	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Chaise	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
Decbr	O
1783	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Friday	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
was	O
welcomed	O
&	O
recd	O
.	O
by	O
dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
with	O
her	O
usual	O
tenderness	O
&	O
affection	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
after	O
a	O
separation	O
of	O
a	O
Month	O
&	O
2	O
days	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
Whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
too	O
seemd	O
happy	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
..	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
ye	O
West	B-place
India	I-place
affair	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
sent	O
notes	O
&	O
had	O
answers	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
ye	O
Kings	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
--	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
paſs	O
'd	O
away	O
pleasantly	O
.	O
except	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
wch	O
occasion	O
'd	O
us	O
some	O
uneasineſs	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
trace	O
from	O
whom	O
it	O
came	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
were	O
utterly	O
incomprehensible	O
.	O
we	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
talkd	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
the	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Papers	O
i	O
found	O
ym-	O
arrived	O
&	O
safe	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
s	O
custody	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
1783	O
My	O
Drst	O
Madam	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
quit	O
Your	O
Graces	O
Bulst	O
your	O
house	O
without	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
upon	O
Paper	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
full	O
heart	O
prevented	O
my	O
denied	O
me	O
power	O
of	O
utterance	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
indeed	O
I	O
could	O
bear	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
even	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
shall	O
meet	O
you	O
both	O
have	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
jointly	O
I	O
addreſs	O
you	O
for	O
my	O
heart	O
accept	O
Madam	O
the	O
acknowledgements	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Grateful	O
heart	O
wch	O
.	O
can	O
borrow	O
no	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
tender	O
proofs	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
received	O
of	O
your	O
tender	O
regard	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
shown	O
me	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
be	O
aſsured	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
you	O
have	O
conferred	O
upon	O
me	O
in	O
I	O
have	O
allowing	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
your	O
guest	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
in	O
Bulstrode	O
has	O
paſs	O
'd	O
too	O
profitibly	O
&	O
agreeably	O
ever	O
to	O
be	O
erased	O
from	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
your	O
Grace	O
's	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
,	O
respectful	O
&	O
Grateful	O
friend	O
M	O
H	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Friday	O
1783	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Isabbella	B-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
--	O
get	O
up	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
breakfast	O
sent	O
up	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
was	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
was	O
shewn	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
aſsemble	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
c	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
was	O
soon	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
she	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
then	O
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
at	O
Chamber	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Children	O
well	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawan	I-pers
calld	O
for	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
A	O
M	O
&	O
I	O
&	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
,	O
met	O
there	O
my	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
card	O
table	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
in	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
finding	O
me	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
--	O
&	O
would	O
not	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
tell	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
News	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
respecting	O
Politicks	O
&	O
answer	O
the	O
Questions	O
respecting	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
he	O
also	O
told	O
me	O
wch-	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
also	O
an	O
anecdote	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
of	O
Scraps	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
wth-	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
10.	O
as	O
did	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Macbride	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
late	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
soon	O
after	O
supper	O
..	O
Lord	B-pers
Lytelton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
ab	O
t	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Mackbride	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
parted	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
had	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
breakfast	O
,	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
Brea	O
kfast	O
room	O
&	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
many	O
interesting	O
matters	O
&	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
letters	O
.	O
little	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
&	O
was	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
room	O
he	O
was	O
vastly	O
pleased	O
wth	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
Child	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
they	O
staid	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
introduced	O
Mr	B-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
--	O
