TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
thō	O
I	O
miſs	O
'd	O
of	O
seeing	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
to	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
convinced	O
of	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
your	O
getting	O
some	O
Country	O
Air	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
intend	O
going	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
who	O
approves	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
orders	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
hopes	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
join	O
in	O
that	O
wish	O
.	O
The	O
Weather	O
is	O
soft	O
&	O
mild	O
&	O
the	O
Season	O
every	O
day	O
advancing	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
benefit	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
full	O
time	O
to	O
recover	O
yourself	O
compleetly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
found	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
quite	O
well	O
.	O
She	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
send	O
you	O
their	O
Love	O
.	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
with	O
the	O
truest	O
Affection	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
CFinch	B-pers
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
30	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
Monday	O
1778	O
--	O
