TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
There	O
now	O
remains	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
complete	O
your	O
work	O
of	O
friendship	O
&	O
compaſsion	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
indeed	O
been	O
bestowd	O
upon	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
valued	O
more	O
than	O
all	O
other	O
human	O
beings	O
;	O
&	O
saying	O
this	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
my	O
obligations	O
is	O
acknowledged	O
.	O
From	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
my	O
dearest	O
daughter	O
I	O
have	O
endeavord	O
if	O
poſsible	O
to	O
tranquillize	O
my	O
mind	O
respecting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
&	O
to	O
banish	O
every	O
rancorous	O
sentiment	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
written	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
here	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
wrong	O
in	O
my	O
desire	O
to	O
forgive	O
.	O
Shou	O
'd	O
he	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
propose	O
in	O
the	O
light	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
much	O
benefitted	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
extremely	O
gratified	O
in	O
being	O
no	O
longer	O
at	O
enmity	O
with	O
my	O
daughter	O
s	O
husband	O
.	O
The	O
result	O
of	O
this	O
meeting	O
shall	O
be	O
communicated	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
request	O
,	O
has	O
proposed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
deliver	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
certain	O
papers	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
communicate	O
the	O
sentiments	O
&	O
wishes	O
of	O
a	O
dying	O
friend	O
.	O
Knowing	O
what	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
has	O
sufferd	O
from	O
extreme	O
affliction	O
&	O
bodily	O
fatigue	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
critical	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
expose	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
chance	O
of	O
an	O
untoward	O
event	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
written	O
to	O
her	O
her	O
this	O
day	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
defer	O
her	O
visit	O
till	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
safely	O
undertaken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
meantime	O
she	O
will	O
consult	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
arrangement	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
affairs	O
;	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
more	O
able	O
aſsistant	O
nor	O
one	O
in	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
greater	O
confidence	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
poſseſs	O
'd	O
of	O
what	O
were	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
ideas	O
&	O
of	O
mine	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Shou	O
'd	O
an	O
agreement	O
take	O
place	O
between	O
me	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
there	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
contest	O
upon	O
inferior	O
objects	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
view	O
but	O
his	O
interest	O
,	O
preserving	O
myself	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
from	O
dupery	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
extremely	O
haughty	O
&	O
acts	O
too	O
much	O
through	O
the	O
influence	O
of	O
paſsion	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
knowing	O
what	O
turn	O
things	O
may	O
take	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
experiment	O
I	O
shall	O
consider	O
myself	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
acquitted	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
dear	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
,	O
&	O
one	O
no	O
leſs	O
so	O
from	O
the	O
enchanting	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Halliday	I-pers
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
still	O
unanswerd	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
has	O
notified	O
to	O
me	O
his	O
surprize	O
&	O
concern	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
's	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
no	O
information	O
of	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
illneſs	O
previous	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
death	O
.	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
the	O
answer	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
adding	O
that	O
my	O
daughter	O
after	O
having	O
experienced	O
a	O
total	O
neglect	O
for	O
so	O
many	O
years	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
betray	O
'd	O
an	O
abject	O
mind	O
by	O
attempting	O
to	O
attract	O
the	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
relations	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
hours	O
.	O
She	O
might	O
excuse	O
them	O
for	O
not	O
giving	O
her	O
their	O
patronge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
aſsert	O
that	O
so	O
excellent	O
a	O
mind	O
cou	O
'd	O
never	O
merit	O
contempt	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
regards	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
grateful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
June	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
PS	O
.	O
Pray	O
inform	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Whalley	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
negligent	O
,	O
grief	O
&	O
anxiety	O
having	O
absorbed	O
my	O
whole	O
mind	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
single	O
18	O
June	O
1810	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
