TOKEN	NE
Lodge	O
Decr	O
.	O
8	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
I	O
must	O
write	O
to	O
Expreſs	O
my	O
Gratitude	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Solicitude	O
respecting	O
my	O
Health	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
indeed	O
been	O
very	O
ill.	O
for	O
the	O
short	O
time	O
it	O
lasted	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
Severe	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
consolation	O
.	O
that	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
quite	O
at	O
my	O
ease	O
&	O
when	O
compar	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Situation	O
this	O
day	O
time	O
12	O
Months	O
it	O
was	O
realy	O
a	O
Bed	O
of	O
roses	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
free	O
from	O
all	O
complaints	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
still	O
reasonably	O
Weak	O
however	O
I	O
increase	O
in	O
Strength	O
hourly	O
--	O
&	O
begin	O
to	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
week	O
to	O
undertake	O
my	O
Journey	O
.	O
to	O
paſs	O
my	O
xmaſs	O
at	O
Newsells	O
and	O
Audley	O
End	O
--	O
there	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
find	O
pleasant	O
Society	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
will	O
.	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
it	O
shortens	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
take	O
your	O
kind	O
advice	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
--	O
being	O
aſsure	O
'd	O
of	O
yr	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
certainly	O
shall	O
not	O
venture	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
.	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
Cold	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
billious	O
Seizure	O
.	O
&	O
attended	O
with	O
great	O
fever	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Cough	O
--	O
What	O
I	O
go	O
upon	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Situation	O
I	O
like	O
Society	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
abroad	O
amongst	O
the	O
French	O
Emigrants	O
--	O
&	O
heard	O
of	O
Dukes	O
&	O
Ducheſses	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
luxury	O
far	O
beyond	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
--	O
when	O
old	O
Comte	O
Montbrison	O
at	O
81.	O
could	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Richmond	O
steps	O
morning	O
&	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
if	O
these	O
people	O
could	O
confer	O
&	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Situation	O
.	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
try	O
hard	O
viz	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
life	O
easy	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
pleasant	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
making	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
grieve	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
s	O
complaint	O
:	O
be	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Advice	O
I	O
give	O
comes	O
fr	O
Sir	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Milman	I-pers
--	O
every	O
morning	O
take	O
a	O
sponge	O
into	O
the	O
Coldest	O
Water	O
.	O
(	O
if	O
Ice	O
so	O
much	O
the	O
better	O
)	O
&	O
bathe	O
that	O
part	O
--	O
it	O
gives	O
immediate	O
ease	O
.	O
&	O
certainly	O
frees	O
that	O
part	O
which	O
is	O
diseas	O
'd	O
for	O
relaxation	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Pill	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
body	O
open	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Wretched	O
painful	O
disorder	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
certainly	O
not	O
a	O
dangerous	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
sitters	O
during	O
my	O
confinement	O
the	O
best	O
News	O
is	O
.	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
told	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
--	O
who	O
told	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
which	O
last	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
my	O
Nephew	O
.	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
preſent	O
Sessions	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
repeal	O
of	O
that	O
Inquisitorial	O
power	O
Sir	O
--	O
a	O
Great	O
friend	O
of	O
Addington	B-pers
s	O
--	O
told	O
my	O
Aunt	O
St	O
Leger	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
please	O
--	O
as	O
that	O
Inquisitor	O
did	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
leading	O
story	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
eloped	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
leaving	O
his	O
nine	O
Children	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
Unsuspected	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
.	O
&	O
seized	O
her	O
departure	O
--	O
her	O
poor	O
husband	O
Husband	O
has	O
investigated	O
her	O
Conduct	O
.	O
&	O
finds	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
three	O
are	O
his	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
are	O
doubtful	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
Woman	O
I	O
ever	O
should	O
have	O
suspected	O
.	O
so	O
Modest	O
.	O
so	O
Gentle	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
respected	O
as	O
a	O
pattern	O
for	O
a	O
Wife	O
&	O
Mother	O
--	O
neither	O
her	O
Father	O
(	O
Sir	B-pers
Richd	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
)	O
or	O
the	O
Arch	O
Bishop	O
s	O
family	O
will	O
contribute	O
a	O
sixpence	O
to	O
her	O
support	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
story	O
goes	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
has	O
taken	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
Protection	O
.	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Leathes	I-pers
has	O
paid	O
dear	O
for	O
the	O
invitation	O
to	O
these	O
Theatricals	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
representation	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
Sir	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
Edmonstone	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
being	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Mrs	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Leathes	I-pers
s.	O
Just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
Bushy	B-place
Park	I-place
Miſs	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hired	O
Post	O
Horses	O
drew	O
furiously	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Coachman	O
drove	O
a	O
turn	O
at	O
the	O
round	O
Pond	O
in	O
Bushy	B-place
Park	I-place
.	O
the	O
Chaise	O
took	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
&	O
ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
Chariot	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Unfortunately	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
The	O
Carriages	O
entangled	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
went	O
several	O
yards	O
together	O
.	O
at	O
last	O
Lady	B-pers
C——	I-pers
s	O
Coachman	O
with	O
an	O
Effort	O
extricated	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
carriage	O
.	O
was	O
thrown	O
off	O
his	O
Box	O
.	O
&	O
broken	O
two	O
bones	O
&	O
one	O
leg	O
--	O
the	O
Horses	O
finding	O
themselves	O
without	O
a	O
driver	O
ran	O
thro	O
'	O
all	O
the	O
gates	O
.	O
&	O
came	O
into	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
Palace	O
yard	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
loose	O
stones	O
--	O
they	O
however	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
C——	I-pers
s	O
door	O
.	O
2	O
Centinels	O
seeing	O
them	O
without	O
a	O
driver	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
--	O
whilst	O
these	O
poor	O
Women	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
difficulty	O
they	O
could	O
keep	O
them	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Animals	O
were	O
work	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
phrenzy	O
--	O
the	O
Ladies	O
were	O
unhurt	O
.	O
but	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Mud	O
.	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
Glaſses	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Leathes	I-pers
has	O
been	O
ill	O
with	O
seizures	O
and	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
surpris	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Escape	O
--	O
Harry	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
has	O
been	O
at	O
Hastings	B-place
--	O
&	O
my	O
sister	O
writes	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
gives	O
a	O
most	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
every	O
body	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
at	O
Wing	B-place
--	O
so	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
dependance	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
plac	O
'd	O
upon	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
after	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
(	O
but	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
never	O
knew	O
nor	O
ever	O
will	O
hear	O
--	O
)	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
write	O
her	O
yr	O
kind	O
remembrances	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
will	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
Mrs	B-pers
J	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
--	O
they	O
give	O
a	O
most	O
comfortable	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
venerable	O
friend	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
coming	O
soon	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
come	O
quietly	O
in	O
a	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
--	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
offer	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
sole	O
useful	O
reading	O
--	O
Consul	O
at	O
Cairo	O
so	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
must	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
much	O
Information	O
.	O
Useful	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
interesting	O
--	O
one	O
feels	O
surpris	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Country	O
from	O
where	O
all	O
Arts	O
Sciences	O
had	O
their	O
beginning	O
.	O
is	O
now	O
Escaped	O
from	O
a	O
hoard	O
of	O
Ruffians	O
,	O
who	O
cd	O
have	O
destroy	O
'd	O
any	O
vestiges	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
destroying	O
the	O
Authenticity	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
my	O
best	O
remembrances	O
ever	O
attend	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
most	O
affect	O
&	O
obliged	O
Friend	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
