TOKEN	NE
just	O
before	O
leaving	O
for	O
Naples	B-place
allusion	O
to	O
satisfactory	O
post	O
they	O
leave	O
Mary	B-pers
in	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
incapable	O
of	O
the	O
neglect	O
you	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
resist	O
thanking	O
you	O
immediately	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
enquiry	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
ulcerated	O
Sore	O
throat	O
but	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
of	O
so	O
gentle	O
a	O
kind	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
over	O
.	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
full	O
intention	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
Kingston	B-place
,	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Philipps	I-pers
's	I-pers
proposed	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
visiting	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
day	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
bad	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
friend	O
was	O
ill	O
which	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
our	O
scheme	O
,	O
but	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
determined	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
before	O
we	O
go	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
will	O
be	O
about	O
Saturday	O
Se'enight	O
--	O
he	O
takes	O
leave	O
of	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
on	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
we	O
both	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
Their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
on	O
Thursday	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
melancholy	O
ceremony	O
for	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
thoroughly	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Italian	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
intimacy	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
shall	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
therefore	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
deprived	O
of	O
the	O
Sweets	O
of	O
Society	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
of	O
life	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
most	O
relish	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
once	O
more	O
left	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
private	O
resources	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
small	O
I	O
might	O
perhaps	O
satisfy	O
myself	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
not	O
obliged	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
measure	O
to	O
give	O
myself	O
now	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
hurry	O
of	O
the	O
Great	O
World	O
which	O
I	O
abhor	O
.	O
--	O
if	O
Hamilton	B-pers
had	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
of	O
think	O
ing	O
I	O
am	O
inclined	O
to	O
think	O
believe	O
we	O
should	O
give	O
up	O
every	O
thing	O
&	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
Estate	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
much	O
more	O
comfortable	O
Scheme	O
than	O
our	O
present	O
situation	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
more	O
lucrative	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bad	O
Courtier	O
,	O
&	O
perhaps	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
all	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
my	O
Spirit	O
of	O
independency	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
myself	O
&	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
rejoice	O
infinitely	O
in	O
the	O
happy	O
situation	O
we	O
leave	O
you	O
in	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
protection	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Queens	O
whom	O
I	O
respect	O
&	O
honour	O
,	O
most	O
sincerely	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
any	O
Sovereign	O
upon	O
Earth	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
--	O
but	O
all	O
this	O
is	O
between	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
.	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
&	O
is	O
vastly	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
reception	O
there	O
--	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
declare	O
himself	O
Candidate	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
election	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
left	O
all	O
that	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
represent	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
desired	O
it	O
but	O
wish	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
act	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
their	O
wishes	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
a	O
re	O
almost	O
universal	O
,	O
they	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
great	O
impatience	O
at	O
our	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
abroad	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
desirous	O
we	O
should	O
live	O
among	O
them	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
struggle	O
who	O
should	O
receive	O
him	O
best	O
--	O
the	O
Estate	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
prosperous	O
way	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
w	O
a	O
i	O
s	O
a	O
reall	O
pleasure	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
memory	O
w	O
a	O
i	O
s	O
still	O
dear	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
knowing	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
curious	O
about	O
his	O
transactions	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
begging	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Strongest	O
terms	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
how	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
not	O
be	O
prevaild	O
upon	O
she	O
says	O
her	O
little	O
boy	O
grows	O
fat	O
&	O
lively	O
,	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Poor	O
Monsr	B-pers
.	I-pers
D'Ajincourt	I-pers
is	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
little	O
disapointed	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
really	O
intollerable	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
tagging	O
after	O
us	O
in	O
our	O
Journey	O
,	O
tho	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
)	O
he	O
is	O
really	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
general	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
them	O
bearable	O
before	O
they	O
are	O
compleat	O
Sixty	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
my	O
old	O
Knights	O
of	O
Malta	B-place
when	O
I	O
visited	O
that	O
Island	O
--	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
however	O
were	O
old	O
enough	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
ye	I-pers
14th-	I-pers
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
reign	O
'd	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
in	O
my	O
airing	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
calld	O
on	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
paint	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
notice	O
she	O
will	O
make	O
herself	O
sick	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
unleſs	O
she	O
can	O
be	O
prevaild	O
upon	O
to	O
sleep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
but	O
be	O
aſsured	O
we	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
the	O
t	O
Sincere	O
friendship	O
Yr	O
Most	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
CHamilton	B-pers
you	O
must	O
put	O
on	O
Mourning	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensbury	I-pers
Friday	O
--	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
July	O
1777	O
