TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
my	O
last	O
with	O
the	O
enclosed	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
after	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
returned	O
from	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
long	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
news	O
Papers	O
of	O
this	O
week	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
still	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
wrong	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
too	O
rough	O
&	O
stormy	O
for	O
sea	O
bathing	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Papers	O
also	O
mention	O
an	O
horrid	O
catastrophe	O
by	O
lightning	O
close	O
to	O
your	O
quarters	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
terribly	O
alarmed	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
universally	O
understood	O
here	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
is	O
very	O
soon	O
to	O
succeed	O
our	O
Lord	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
reminding	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
opportunity	O
was	O
now	O
come	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
agreed	O
an	O
application	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
with	O
greater	O
probability	O
of	O
succeſs	O
than	O
it	O
coud	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
last	O
winter	O
.	O
I	O
entreated	O
her	O
to	O
use	O
her	O
interest	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
second	O
my	O
hopes	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
most	O
agreeable	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hinted	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
memorial	O
she	O
permitted	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
in	O
her	O
hands	O
coud	O
be	O
presented	O
under	O
his	O
patronage	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
hopes	O
that	O
the	O
truths	O
contained	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
might	O
procure	O
it	O
a	O
favorable	O
acceptance	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
however	O
however	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sanguine	O
in	O
my	O
expectations	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
perceived	O
any	O
decided	O
symptoms	O
of	O
zeal	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
in	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
alone	O
able	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
wish	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
is	O
certainly	O
proper	O
,	O
&	O
woud	O
do	O
credit	O
to	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
argument	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
become	O
me	O
to	O
pursue	O
further	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
availed	O
yourself	O
of	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
bathing	O
in	O
the	O
sea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
your	O
friend	O
Doctor	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
recommended	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
House	O
in	O
Sackville	O
Street	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
week	O
of	O
next	O
month	O
for	O
storms	O
and	O
bad	O
weather	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
set	O
in	O
earlier	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
during	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
summer	O
in	O
making	O
considerable	O
improvements	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
which	O
may	O
now	O
be	O
called	O
a	O
very	O
complete	O
Villa	O
.	O
When	O
your	O
are	O
settled	O
in	O
your	O
winter	O
quarters	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
is	O
well	O
&	O
has	O
lately	O
added	O
a	O
Daughter	O
to	O
her	O
family	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
was	O
here	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
School	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
other	O
respects	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Latour	O
--	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
October	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
