TOKEN	NE
Brough	B-place
,	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
detained	O
here	O
till	O
a	O
Road	O
is	O
cut	O
through	O
the	O
Snow	O
on	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
impaſsable	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
off	O
tomorrow	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
gueſs	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
only	O
arrived	O
here	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
since	O
Tuesday	O
&	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
The	O
Mail	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
forwarded	O
on	O
Horseback	O
&	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
Hope	O
,	O
carry	O
away	O
this	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Stapleford	O
Hall	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
proposed	O
calling	O
on	O
A.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
&	O
at	O
Leighton	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
despair	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
execute	O
this	O
plan	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
If	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
figuring	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
Birthday	O
)	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
Newport	O
Pagnel	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
try	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
,	O
if	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
Napier	B-pers
Brough	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Fifth	O
Janry-	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
