TOKEN	NE
21	O
family	O
Canterbury	B-place
Apl-	O
26	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
Since	O
I	O
got	O
yours	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
mostly	O
confinded	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
my	O
old	O
Bowel	O
complaint	O
&	O
indeed	O
every	O
uneaſineſs	O
I	O
have	O
sends	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
the	O
Hurry	O
at	O
first	O
upon	O
My	O
Father	O
s	O
death	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
greatest	O
friends	O
who	O
died	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
after	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
keeped	O
my	O
thoughts	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
I	O
really	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
&	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
ordered	O
without	O
giving	O
myself	O
any	O
trouble	O
than	O
reflection	O
&	O
a	O
sensibility	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
nature	O
began	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
distu	O
r	O
bance	O
&	O
was	O
confined	O
really	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
for	O
four	O
days	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
getting	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
as	O
My	O
Phiſician	O
only	O
n	O
ow	O
says	O
he	O
visits	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
so	O
hope	O
from	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thinks	O
all	O
the	O
bad	O
is	O
over	O
--	O
You	O
do	O
me	O
but	O
justice	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
when	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
writing	O
to	O
Col	B-pers
or	I-pers
Ld	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
you	O
think	O
the	O
ſame	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
regard	O
&	O
friendſhip	O
will	O
ever	O
contin	O
u	O
e	O
the	O
ſame	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
espicially	O
as	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
ever	O
act	O
up	O
to	O
those	O
ſentiments	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
are	O
Miſstriſs	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
every	O
body	O
of	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
must	O
be	O
happy	O
in	O
your	O
friendſhip	O
.	O
You	O
ask	O
much	O
abt	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
made	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
most	O
distant	O
manner	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
present	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
amiable	O
Young	O
Lady	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
more	O
surprised	O
at	O
her	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
should	O
a	O
proper	O
match	O
be	O
proposed	O
than	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
settled	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Young	O
Ladys	O
grown	O
up	O
dont	O
yeild	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
to	O
their	O
eldest	O
Sister	O
as	O
they	O
likeways	O
most	O
amiable	O
young	O
Ladys	O
and	O
as	O
handſome	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
wish	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
conſidering	O
my	O
partiality	O
for	O
my	O
Neices	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
I	O
'll	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
against	O
any	O
family	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
ſame	O
number	O
for	O
every	O
accomplishment	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
The	O
youngest	O
little	O
Kitty	B-pers
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
children	O
I	O
ever	O
ſay	O
as	O
likeways	O
the	O
youngest	O
Son	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
eldest	O
Gentlemen	O
are	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
himself	O
I	O
think	O
looks	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Ruſsia	B-place
&	O
in	O
better	O
spirits	O
,	O
He	O
goes	O
ſome	O
time	O
next	O
Month	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Character	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
&	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
paſsing	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
where	O
I	O
still	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
changed	O
my	O
motions	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
from	O
my	O
old	O
deſigns	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
may	O
anſwer	O
me	O
one	O
question	O
,	O
You	O
ſeem	O
to	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
about	O
your	O
Uncle	O
Cathcart	B-pers
s	O
family	O
&	O
I	O
thou	O
ght	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
know	O
as	O
little	O
about	O
you	O
or	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
are	O
there	O
any	O
dryneſs	O
between	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
them	O
concerning	O
yourself	O
or	O
Mama	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
reaſon	O
for	O
your	O
dryneſs	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
family	O
but	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
nothing	O
to	O
My	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
that	O
should	O
make	O
a	O
shyneſs	O
between	O
them	O
&	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
an	O
anſwer	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
post	O
as	O
I	O
dont	O
propose	O
staying	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
longer	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
whatever	O
you	O
say	O
shall	O
be	O
confined	O
entirely	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
breast	O
nor	O
shall	O
any	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
Adieu	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
Remember	O
me	O
most	O
affctly	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
your	O
most	O
Affct	O
Guardian	O
Napier	B-pers
Let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
&	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
