TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
Saturday	O
10	O
th	O
Feb	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
Bell	B-pers
who	O
arrived	O
last	O
night	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
made	O
me	O
nicely	O
&	O
sincerely	O
happy	O
by	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
comfortable	O
account	O
poſsible	O
of	O
your	O
situati	O
on	O
health	O
and	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
wanted	O
this	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
seen	O
you	O
three	O
times	O
since	O
you	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
only	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
accidentally	O
met	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
about	O
you	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
without	O
any	O
circumstances	O
or	O
particulars	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
feel	O
comfortable	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickn	I-pers
was	O
I	O
conclude	O
too	O
much	O
engaged	O
in	O
communicati	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
information	O
to	O
all	O
your	O
Friends	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
hoped	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
one	O
line	O
--	O
&	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
this	O
event	O
,	O
so	O
happily	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
your	O
happineſs	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expreſsed	O
in	O
having	O
a	O
dear	O
little	O
child	O
to	O
love	O
and	O
to	O
cherish	O
&	O
educate	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
delightful	O
task	O
!	O
what	O
a	O
continual	O
source	O
of	O
happineſs	O
!	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
love	O
&	O
anxiety	O
&	O
attentio	O
n	O
&	O
a	O
continued	O
return	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
sentiments	O
it	O
inspires	O
you	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
ask	O
whether	O
you	O
nurse	O
it	O
yoursel	O
f	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
sentiments	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
--	O
well	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
happiest	O
being	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
does	O
me	O
good	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
for	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
answerd	O
ere	O
now	O
--	O
I	O
answered	O
&	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
mentally	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
my	O
heart	O
--	O
did	O
you	O
feel	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
continue	O
very	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
occupied	O
constantly	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
deeply	O
engaged	O
in	O
Euclid	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
induced	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
long	O
neglected	O
study	O
by	O
a	O
present	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Elliott	I-pers
has	O
made	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
edition	O
of	O
that	O
Book	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
once	O
accidentally	O
discovered	O
(	O
in	O
an	O
aſsembly	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
understood	O
somethi	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
one	O
word	O
which	O
betrayed	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
to	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
interested	O
him	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
made	O
him	O
desirin	O
g	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
I	O
cultivated	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
for	O
the	O
meeti	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
P	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
twice	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
read	O
of	O
that	O
&	O
other	O
things	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
&	O
certainly	O
with	O
mor	O
e	O
pleasure	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
advantage	O
too	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
sensible	O
well	O
informed	O
good	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gentleneſs	O
&	O
elegance	O
of	O
manners	O
that	O
particularly	O
please	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
reading	O
too	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
recreation	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
set	O
of	O
french	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
now	O
publishing	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
century	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
language	O
&	O
manners	O
of	O
that	O
early	O
age	O
extremely	O
pleasing	O
from	O
their	O
great	O
simplicity	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
interested	O
in	O
this	O
lecture	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
expected	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
now	O
attending	O
Mr	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
's	O
lectures	O
,	O
my	O
view	O
was	O
merely	O
that	O
of	O
accompanyi	O
n	O
g	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
Daughter	O
who	O
goes	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
recollect	O
in	O
g	O
what	O
I	O
formerly	O
new	O
,	O
&	O
fixi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
knowledge	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
by	O
fresh	O
experiments	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
ask	O
how	O
a	O
fine	O
London	O
Lady	O
finds	O
time	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
(	O
besides	O
musick	O
masters	O
4	O
times	O
per	O
week	O
)	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
th	O
at	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
fine	O
Lady	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
before	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
secret	O
--	O
my	O
Evenings	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
are	O
all	O
engaged	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
twice	O
a	O
week	O
&	O
the	O
others	O
sitti	O
n	O
g	O
with	O
my	O
Friend	O
's	O
,	O
oftenest	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
sometimes	O
the	O
opera	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
life	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
infor	O
mation	O
about	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
Nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
inquiries	O
&	O
observations	O
--	O
when	O
has	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
shall	O
write	O
you	O
word	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
God	O
in	O
heaven	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
interrupt	O
ed	O
&	O
stopped	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
you	O
--	O
adieu	O
--	O
adieu	O
!	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
No	O
2	O
Abbey	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
Honble-	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Feby	O
.	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
