TOKEN	NE
3	O
d	O
.	O
sent	O
letter	O
&	O
diary	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
4	O
th	O
.	O
Sent	O
Print	O
Air	O
B	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
6	O
th	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
a	O
Son	O
10	O
th	O
..	O
sent	O
diary	O
&	O
letter	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
Do	O
.	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
17	O
.	O
th	O
.	O
Letter	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Do	O
--	O
21	O
Do.-	O
}	O
recd	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Do	O
.	O
}	O
24	O
Do	O
.	O
&	O
Diary	O
&	O
c	O
25	O
Do	O
.	O
&	O
Diary	O
.	O
Lady	O
W.	O
better	O
--	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
Letter	O
“	O
Good	O
unexpected	O
,	O
Evil	O
unforeseen	O
,	O
“	O
Appear	O
by	O
turns	O
as	O
fortune	O
shifts	O
ye	O
.	O
scene	O
,	O
“	O
some	O
raised	O
aloft	O
,	O
come	O
tumbling	O
down	O
amain	O
,	O
“	O
And	O
fall	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
they	O
bound	O
&	O
rise	O
again	O
.	O
Dryden	O
,	O
The	O
Eleventh	O
Book	O
of	O
the	O
Aeneis	O
ll.656-9	O
.	O
Dryden	B-pers
London	B-place
(	O
1	O
Decbr	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
all	O
I	O
felt	O
&	O
thought	O
when	O
we	O
parted	O
last	O
Night	O
--	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
wept	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
releived	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
sat	O
alone	O
in	O
my	O
breakfast	O
Room	O
this	O
Morng	O
that	O
the	O
friendly	O
aid	O
of	O
tears	O
easd	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
the	O
oppreſsion	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
--	O
I	O
check	O
'd	O
every	O
melancholy	O
presage	O
whilst	O
I	O
saw	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
You	O
were	O
hastening	O
on	O
Your	O
Road	O
from	O
me	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
future	O
happineſs	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
abandon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
taking	O
myself	O
severely	O
to	O
task	O
--	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
erase	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
--	O
shall	O
I	O
ever	O
hide	O
a	O
thought	O
from	O
You	O
?	O
--	O
shall	O
I	O
ever	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
making	O
You	O
believe	O
me	O
more	O
worthy	O
of	O
Your	O
approbation	O
than	O
I	O
really	O
am	O
?	O
No	O
No	O
You	O
shall	O
see	O
my	O
heart	O
as	O
through	O
a	O
transparent	O
Mirror	O
.	O
The	O
dear	O
Sister	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
whole	O
day	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Wifes	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Widowd	O
Sister	O
--	O
I	O
denied	O
myself	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
&	O
sat	O
alone	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
duty	O
to	O
employ	O
myself	O
&	O
keep	O
my	O
up	O
my	O
spirits	O
The	B-pers
perverse	I-pers
one	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
,	O
who	O
left	O
me	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
Good	O
Dowager	O
cheer	O
'd	O
my	O
spirits	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
You	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
will	O
in-	O
interest	O
You	O
--	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
&	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
always	O
ye	O
.	O
King	O
of	O
Poland	O
“	O
We	O
hope	O
ye	O
King	O
of	O
Poland	O
will	O
stay	O
till	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
day	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
Yo	O
.	O
will	O
“	O
be	O
Queen	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
feasted	O
him	O
about	O
so	O
much	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
“	O
Condescend	O
to	O
a	O
vulgar	O
Beef-	O
stake	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
relish	O
“	O
he	O
knows	O
he	O
shall	O
meet	O
with	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
my	O
Dear	O
“	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
ordered	O
a	O
poor	O
Rook	O
to	O
be	O
shot	O
to	O
death	O
&	O
a	O
whole	O
“	O
Colony	O
frightened	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
wits	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
starving	O
,	O
for	O
“	O
picking	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
grains	O
of	O
Corn	O
frm	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Hares	O
,	O
whilst	O
ye	O
.	O
screaming	O
“	O
Peacocks	O
,	O
squalling	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
Cackling	O
Bantams	O
gobbled	O
it	O
“	O
all	O
up	O
wth	O
.	O
impunity	O
?	O
We	O
dont	O
doubt	O
Yo	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
merry	O
Xmaſs	O
&	O
“	O
Return	O
Yor	O
.	O
kind	O
wishes	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
warmth	O
--	O
the	O
Friend	O
says	O
that	O
(	O
2	O
“	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
acceptable	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
sufficient	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
word	O
“	O
warmth	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
We	O
dont	O
know	O
wht	O
Your	O
fashions	O
are	O
in	O
London	B-place
“	O
but	O
ours	O
are	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
;	O
four	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
hoods	O
to	O
the	O
“	O
tip	O
of	O
our	O
Nose	O
,	O
besides	O
Spectacles	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
impatient	O
to	O
meet	O
our	O
my	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
dinner	O
“	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
set	O
down	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
on	O
Wedn-	O
“	O
&	O
go	O
home	O
directly	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
may	O
every	O
thing	O
happen	O
tend	O
“	O
to	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
King	O
of	O
Poland	O
“	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
make	O
my	O
Compts	O
acceptable	O
--	O
”	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
also	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
a	O
very	O
saucy	O
one	O
--	O
You	O
shall	O
judge	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
frank	O
I	O
will	O
enclose	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
A	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairy	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
The	B-pers
D.D.P	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Baroneſs	O
&	O
Pieta	B-pers
(	O
whom	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
we	O
will	O
call	O
Baron	B-pers
were	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
attractions	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
resisted	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
as	O
cheerful	O
a	O
countenance	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
aſsume	O
&	O
went	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
happy	O
by	O
seeing	O
my	O
beloved	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Baroneſs	O
delighted	O
me	O
by	O
saying	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
of	O
You	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fairy	O
she	O
fairly	O
own	O
'd	O
a	O
paſsion	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
--	O
Attica	B-pers
--	O
ye	O
verse	O
writer	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
civil	O
,	O
fair	O
looking	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
Cap	O
wd	O
.	O
become	O
him	O
vastly	O
--	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
we	O
will	O
call	O
him	O
Pieta	B-pers
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
tell	O
You	O
all	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
interesting	O
tho	O
'	O
as	O
conversation	O
tolerably	O
amusing	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
the	O
eldest	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
(	O
I	O
hate	O
ye	O
.	O
name	O
perverse	O
we	O
will	O
drop	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
scribbled	O
a	O
folio	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
of	O
A	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
friend	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
her	O
Servt	O
.	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
house	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
beleive	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
now	O
only	O
dictate	O
her	O
letters	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
her	O
Maid	O
writes	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
transcribe	O
it	O
.	O
“	O
Happy	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
kind	O
remembrances	O
I	O
“	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
made	O
doubly	O
precious	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
“	O
being	O
united	O
wth	O
.	O
those	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
&	O
inestimabl	O
y	O
e	O
friend	O
“	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
must	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
herself	O
--	O
most	O
“	O
sensibly	O
have	O
I	O
miſs	O
'd	O
my	O
amiable	O
Morning	O
companion	O
,	O
“	O
my	O
works	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
slow	O
&	O
sad	O
--	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
enlivening	O
hour	O
of	O
“	O
a	O
summons	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
check	O
3	O
“	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
sympathising	O
Lamentations	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
board	O
of	O
“	O
Croſs	O
Stitch	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
of	O
diligence	O
--	O
where	O
is	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
“	O
&	O
her	O
Manuscripts	O
?	O
says	O
our	O
Dear	O
Good	O
Dowager	O
.	O
“	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
exaltation	O
says	O
The	O
Chaplain	O
“	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
shift	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
of	O
regret	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
hope	O
&	O
console	O
“	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
Wedn	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
or	O
rather	O
ye	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
“	O
look	O
upon	O
You	O
to	O
be	O
incapable	O
of	O
failing	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
Your	O
engagets-	O
“	O
I	O
shall	O
depend	O
on	O
Your	O
eating	O
Beef	O
stakes	O
according	O
to	O
promise	O
,	O
“	O
but	O
shd	O
.	O
Yo	O
.	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
Friend	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
“	O
You	O
will	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
“	O
is	O
no	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
left	O
London	B-place
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
“	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
say	O
more	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
able	O
&	O
will	O
not	O
embar̅eſs	O
“	O
Yo	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
uneceſsary	O
Compts	O
.	O
&	O
wishes	O
to	O
those	O
friends	O
who	O
may	O
“	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
knowing	O
You	O
lose	O
no	O
opportunity	O
“	O
of	O
doing	O
justice	O
to	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
obliged	O
&	O
afft	O
.	O
“	O
Alas	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
reduced	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Cloak	O
myself	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
bear	O
“	O
in	O
mind	O
yt	O
.	O
kind	O
attention	O
&	O
many	O
others	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Guardian	O
s	O
Mr	B-pers
Jerningham	I-pers
“	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sorry	O
for	O
Florio	B-pers
.	O
if	O
Yo	O
.	O
send	O
to	O
enquire	O
“	O
after	O
him	O
be	O
so	O
generous	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
particular	O
enquiry	O
“	O
for	O
me	O
P	O
S.	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Dowager	B-pers
.	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
--	O
Your	O
Journals	O
“	O
are	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
infinite	O
value	O
continue	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
beseech	O
You	O
--	O
there	O
“	O
has	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
bustle	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
tables	O
that	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
“	O
thought	O
You	O
were	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
exalt	O
him	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
“	O
find	O
is	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
case	O
his	O
best	O
respects	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
.	O
Aſsure	O
“	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
of	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
that	O
health	O
&	O
happineſs	O
may	O
“	O
ever	O
attend	O
Yo	O
.	O
&	O
them	O
You	O
love	O
--	O
MCP	O
“	O
Our	O
dear	O
friend	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
”	O
The	O
Sister	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
conversed	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
were	O
You	O
thinking	O
of	O
us	O
?	O
for	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
You	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr-	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
pretty	O
M	B-pers
D	I-pers
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
You	O
were	O
pleased	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
reception	O
she	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Viscount	O
had	O
given	O
Yo	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
the	O
Baroneſs	O
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
In	O
Queen	O
Curzon	O
Street	O
Young	O
Marall	O
paſs	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
Company	O
wth	O
.	O
3	O
Gentlemen	O
--	O
he	O
smil	O
'd	O
,	O
kiſs	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
graceful	O
bow	O
--	O
the	O
Carriage	O
proceeded	O
&	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
--	O
presently	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
were	O
calld	O
to	O
stop	O
&	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
door	O
--	O
His	O
companions	O
waited	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
.	O
the	O
following	O
Dialogue	O
took	O
place	O
--	O
(	O
dont	O
look	O
Yellow	O
now	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
took	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
token	O
of	O
friendship	O
,	O
said	O
how	O
happy	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
“	O
I	O
thank	O
4	O
)	O
You	O
Sir	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
am	O
now	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
heard	O
You	O
were	O
ill	O
Sr	O
.	O
&	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
Your	O
R	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
speak	O
so	O
hoarse	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
Yr	O
.	O
relations	O
or	O
friends	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
enquire	O
after	O
You	O
&	O
send	O
You	O
meſsages	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
have	O
Sir	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
yor	O
.	O
kind	O
remembrances	O
”	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
“	O
Ought	O
I	O
to	O
congratulate	O
You	O
?	O
,	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
No	O
Sir	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
when	O
may	O
I	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
when	O
shall	O
You	O
change	O
Yor	O
.	O
Name	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
Sir	O
there	O
are	O
affairs	O
to	O
settle	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
place	O
soon	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
sometime	O
at	O
B	O
“	O
near	O
3	O
Months	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
made	O
particular	O
enquiries	O
when	O
You	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
Lady	O
my	O
Father	O
Mother	O
&	O
Sisters	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
You	O
&	O
am	O
was	O
much	O
provoked	O
&	O
shock	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
”	O
“	O
O	O
Sr	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
nor	O
does	O
it	O
signify	O
”	O
“	O
Where	O
are	O
You	O
going	O
”	O
?	O
“	O
To	O
dine	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
——	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Baroneſs	O
”	O
are	O
you	O
with	O
them	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
No	O
Sir	O
”	O
“	O
Do	O
You	O
still	O
live	O
“	O
in	O
C	O
.	O
Str	O
.	O
?	O
“	O
Yes	O
Sir	O
”	O
--	O
Farewell	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
You	O
,	O
“	O
I	O
bow	O
'd	O
in	O
reply	O
”	O
--	O
&	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
my	O
hand	O
ye	O
whole	O
time	O
wch	O
greatly	O
distreſsed	O
me	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
bye	O
Standards	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	I-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
who	O
din	O
'd	O
also	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Baron	O
s	O
--	O
the	O
American	O
Gentleman	O
whom	O
you	O
saw	O
,	O
&	O
whose	O
Story	O
the	O
Baroneſs	O
told	O
You	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
also	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
3	O
of	O
their	O
Children	O
--	O
a	O
Nephew	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
also	O
who	O
spends	O
his	O
Hol	O
l	O
idays	O
at	O
his	O
Uncle	O
s	O
--	O
a	O
fine	O
Youth	O
very	O
amiable	O
engaging	O
--	O
The	O
Baroneſs	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
thinking	O
of	O
You	O
&	O
hoped	O
You	O
wd	O
.	O
get	O
safe	O
home	O
--	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mirander	B-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
informd	O
her	O
King	B-pers
of	I-pers
Poland	I-pers
was	O
better	O
&	O
Pliny	B-pers
was	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
London	B-place
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
14	O
Miles	O
off	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
leave	O
Norfolk	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
for	O
Courteen	O
Hall	O
--	O
At	O
7	O
--	O
good	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
,	O
Baroneſs	O
,	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
Nephew	O
&	O
me	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
all	O
down	O
&	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriage	O
to	O
convey	O
me	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
s	O
(	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
call	O
her	O
Mirander	B-pers
)	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
ye	O
.	O
Eldest	O
&	O
the	O
Sister	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
was	O
there	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
You	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
denied	O
entrance	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
twice	O
he	O
should	O
venture	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
--	O
Gypsy	B-pers
's	O
eldest	O
Son	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Student	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
)	O
he	O
came	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
Dowager	O
s	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
strange	O
reports	O
had	O
reach	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
wch	O
.	O
kept	O
him	O
a	O
week	O
longer	O
there	O
from	O
going	O
to	O
Bull	O
.	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
said	O
ye	O
same	O
had	O
been	O
spread	O
all	O
over	O
London	B-place
--	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
explain	O
themselves	O
--	O
the	O
Good	O
Dowg	O
&	O
her	O
Friend	O
are	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
they	O
allude	O
to	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
on	O
Thursday	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
(	O
5	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
letter	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
disappointed	O
--	O
You	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
line	O
--	O
the	O
Sister	O
excused	O
You	O
&	O
said	O
that	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
to	O
Worbourn	B-place
too	O
late	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
Coaches	O
probably	O
&	O
he	O
must	O
suppose	O
I	O
should	O
28	O
th	O
Decbr	O
1784	O
continued	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
safe	O
so	O
far	O
.	O
I	O
tell	O
You	O
once	O
for	O
all	O
my	O
friend	O
that	O
You	O
must	O
either	O
be	O
very	O
attentive	O
to	O
these	O
kind	O
of	O
requests	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
must	O
learn	O
to	O
grow	O
more	O
indifferent	O
about	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Visit	O
from	O
the	O
Priest	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
consult	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
his	O
Son	O
whom	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
remove	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
for	O
his	O
education	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
&	O
he	O
descided	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
proposed	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
torment	O
You	O
with	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
He	O
was	O
particular	O
in	O
his	O
enquiries	O
after	O
You	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
much	O
solicitude	O
abt	O
.	O
Your	O
getting	O
safe	O
to	O
Your	O
Journeys	O
end	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
went	O
early	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
--	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
You	O
believe	O
it	O
the	O
Sister	O
seduced	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
aſsured	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
inform	O
You	O
how	O
well	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
all	O
You	O
had	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
this	O
Subject	O
.	O
Decbr	O
..	O
29	O
th	O
..	O
84	O
.	O
The	O
Sister	O
again	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
day	O
at	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
s	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
my	O
Brothers	O
Wife	O
(	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baron	I-pers
)	O
&	O
a	O
Pieta	B-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
common	O
chit-chat	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Eastrey	B-place
in	O
Kent	B-place
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
such	O
as	O
it	O
now	O
is	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
violent	O
Light	O
e	O
ning	O
&	O
heard	O
Loud	O
Thunder	O
The	O
Sky	O
too	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
terribly	O
flurry	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
this	O
Morng	O
in	O
making	O
Extracts	O
from	O
the	O
Friend	O
s	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
Mr	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
has	O
allowed	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
trusted	O
me	O
with	O
--	O
what	O
pleasure	O
shall	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
reading	O
them	O
with	O
You	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
hope	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Eldest	O
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
writing	O
&	O
was	O
agreeably	O
interrupted	O
by	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
forgive	O
me	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
begin̅ing	O
of	O
this	O
page	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
comfortleſs	O
Journey	O
have	O
You	O
had	O
,	O
yet	O
6	O
)	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
that	O
You	O
have	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
no	O
accident	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
Joy	O
&	O
comfort	O
of	O
hearing	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
safe	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
You	O
did	O
,	O
&	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
calling	O
upon	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baron	I-pers
she	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
&	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
every	O
attention	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
this	O
afte	O
r	O
noon	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
as	O
the	O
Friend	O
does	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
reading	O
,	O
“	O
that	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
love	O
society	O
a	O
day	O
sometimes	O
entirely	O
to	O
oneself	O
is	O
very	O
pleasant	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
wonder	O
at	O
people	O
who	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
melancholy	O
thing	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
alone	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
pause	O
in	O
music	O
wch	O
when	O
properly	O
introduced	O
gives	O
a	O
grace	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
piece	O
”	O
Apropos	O
as	O
to	O
Music	O
I	O
intreat	O
yt	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
cultivate	O
it	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
delight	O
in	O
Harmony	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
Your	O
Ear	O
is	O
too	O
nice	O
to	O
endure	O
discordant	O
sounds	O
therefore	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
You	O
will	O
arrive	O
at	O
perfection	O
--	O
if	O
You	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
“	O
more	O
meant	O
than	O
meets	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
Ear	O
”	O
perhaps	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Women	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
love	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
Riddles	O
--	O
What	O
dreadful	O
Weather	O
for	O
You	O
to	O
travel	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
almost	O
hate	O
to	O
feel	O
the	O
warmth	O
from	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
fire	O
when	O
I	O
reflect	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
shivering	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
air	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
Joy	O
of	O
hearing	O
You	O
are	O
got	O
safe	O
home	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
worse	O
for	O
Your	O
journey	O
how	O
light	O
will	O
my	O
spirits	O
be	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
--	O
remember	O
remember	O
what	O
consequence	O
Your	O
health	O
&	O
life	O
are	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
greatest	O
proof	O
You	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
of	O
Your	O
affection	O
is	O
being	O
careful	O
of	O
yourself	O
.	O
for	O
,	O
“	O
How	O
trifling	O
are	O
all	O
worldly	O
concerns	O
compared	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
life	O
of	O
a	O
beloved	O
friend	O
”	O
!	O
The	O
Sister	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Eldest	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairys	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
had	O
been	O
invited	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
Myself	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
your	O
request	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
my	O
pen	O
&	O
went	O
soberly	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
detirmined	O
that	O
I	O
wd-	O
shame	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Snow-ball	I-pers
a	O
pretty	O
Monitor	O
indeed	O
You	O
chose	O
to	O
enforce	O
Your	O
precepts	O
!	O
Here	O
am	O
I	O
finely	O
abused	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
allowed	O
to	O
read	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
against	O
me	O
I	O
believe	O
saucy	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
thinks	O
the	O
Sister	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
remember	O
that	O
People	O
do	O
not	O
boast	O
except	O
when	O
the	O
thing	O
is	O
uncommon	O
I	O
mean	O
her	O
early	O
hours	O
.	O
if	O
Brothers	O
will	O
set	O
examples	O
&	O
friends	O
will	O
be	O
agreeable	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
be	O
blamed	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
your	O
Journey	O
is	O
finished	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
space	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
affectionate	O
friend	O
&	O
Sister	O
(	O
7	O
I	O
stole	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
this	O
Paper	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
short	O
memories	O
people	O
have	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
C	O
Street	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
——	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
she	O
directed	O
it	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
the	O
Viscount	O
Times	O
have	O
altered	O
when	O
exact	O
&	O
punctual	O
people	O
are	O
inattentive	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
deserve	O
a	O
Postscript	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
malice	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
:	O
84	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
that	O
You	O
shall	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
packets	O
I	O
keep	O
writing	O
on	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
a	O
Frank	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Viscount	O
for	O
2.	O
one	O
for	O
this	O
days	O
post	O
&	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
I	O
will	O
wait	O
till	O
I	O
receive	O
an	O
answer	O
from	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
last	O
Night	O
&	O
heard	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Good	O
Dowgr	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
Friend	O
got	O
safe	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
This	O
Morng	O
the	O
Good	O
Dowr	O
.	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
thinks	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
sick	O
now	O
You	O
are	O
“	O
over	O
the	O
Hills	O
&	O
far	O
away	O
”	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
that	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
every	O
Affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
Your	O
Sisters	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
You	O
will	O
aſsure	O
Your	O
Father	O
that	O
I	O
both	O
respect	O
&	O
esteem	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baron	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
other	O
day	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wild	O
Man	O
very	O
lately	O
seen	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
--	O
the	O
severity	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
drove	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Woods	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
in	O
a	O
Savage	O
State	O
&	O
has	O
no	O
language	O
but	O
makes	O
a	O
barbarous	O
noise	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
but	O
and	O
fled	O
away	O
again	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
spent	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
with	O
Dear	O
Pieta	B-pers
,	O
but	O
a	O
heavy	O
fog	O
&	O
thaw	O
makes	O
me	O
afraid	O
to	O
to	O
to	O
take	O
cold	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
walk	O
even	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
distance	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
You	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
of	O
my	O
health	O
&	O
You	O
never	O
shall	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
reproach	O
me	O
with	O
failing	O
in	O
my	O
promises	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
mortified	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
was	O
to	O
miſs	O
seeing	O
You	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
requested	O
You	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
Your	O
journey	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
&	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
close	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Window	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
distinguish	O
one	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
so	O
horrid	O
a	O
a	O
Mist	O
but	O
comfortably	O
seated	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
S	I-pers
fire	O
side	O
8	O
)	O
The	O
darkneſs	O
increased	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
is	O
like	O
an	O
Eclipse	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
Candles	O
.	O
God	O
grant	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
on	O
Horseback	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Mist	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Toby	I-pers
Fret	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
that	O
I	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
borrow	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
we	O
a	O
re	O
lately	O
published	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
said	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
very	O
different	O
advice	O
to	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
what	O
Mrs	B-pers
S——	I-pers
had	O
done	O
to	O
his	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
says	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
endeavour	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
principle	O
&	O
Virtue	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
The	B-pers
Eldest	I-pers
recommends	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
right	O
to	O
conceal	O
&	O
aid	O
what	O
is	O
wrong	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
had	O
a	O
visit	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Brother	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
Officer	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
commands	O
for	O
W——	O
as	O
he	O
sets	O
out	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
s	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Janr	O
:	O
&	O
they	O
they	O
are	O
then	O
both	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
disappointed	O
of	O
the	O
Frank	O
for	O
this	O
post	O
--	O
The	O
good	O
Dowgr	O
.	O
has	O
Just	O
sent	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
shall	O
send	O
her	O
Coach	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
The	O
Friend	O
s	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
angry	O
if	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
drink	O
our	O
Heaths	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
not	O
in	O
fat	O
Ale	O
but	O
in	O
more	O
Nectarian	O
liquor	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
--	O
perhaps	O
You	O
may	O
just	O
now	O
be	O
wishing	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
well	O
comfort	O
Yourself	O
for	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
we	O
shall	O
drink	O
the	O
Pieta	B-pers
s	O
health	O
.	O
Thursday	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
aſsure	O
You	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
nervous	O
headach	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
but	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
feel	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
9	O
Thursday	O
30	O
th	O
Decbr-	O
continued	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
disappointed	O
of	O
the	O
frank	O
&	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
send	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
the	O
Pretty	O
Gypsy	O
wrote	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
kind	O
letter	O
--	O
the	O
Viscount	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
says	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
am	O
“	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
our	O
meeting	O
was	O
mutua	O
ble	O
lly	O
agreeable	O
&	O
“	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
”	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Friend	O
s	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
The	O
Good	O
Dowgr	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
dined	O
there	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
but	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
much	O
recovered	O
--	O
many	O
regrets	O
abt	O
.	O
Your	O
not	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Toby	I-pers
Fret	I-pers
thought	O
it	O
strange	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
drink	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
health	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
&	O
great	O
friend	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
worthy	O
ones	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
private	O
converse	O
&	O
as	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
I	O
slip	O
'd	O
away	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
credit	O
for	O
this	O
attention	O
--	O
more	O
than	O
it	O
deserved	O
for	O
I	O
only	O
did	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
what	O
an	O
avowed	O
ene	O
n	O
my	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
all	O
restraint	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Miranda	B-pers
Coach	O
--	O
the	O
Eldest	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
before	O
ten	O
--	O
Anne	B-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
You	O
chiefly	O
)	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
to	O
my	O
resolution	O
of	O
neither	O
reading	O
or	O
writing	O
or	O
sitting	O
up	O
after	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
so	O
make	O
Yourself	O
easy	O
on	O
that	O
head	O
.	O
Friday	O
31	O
st	O
..	O
Decbr	O
..	O
To	O
day	O
you	O
will	O
probably	O
get	O
home	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
uncommonly	O
oppreſsed	O
&	O
agitated	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
dread	O
that	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
recd	O
.	O
with	O
frowns	O
&	O
O	O
how	O
dreadful	O
are	O
ye	O
.	O
frowns	O
of	O
a	O
beloved	O
Parent	O
to	O
a	O
Mind	O
&	O
heart	O
like	O
Yours	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
of	O
as	O
it	O
diſsipated	O
my	O
thoughts	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
he	O
is	O
as	O
worthy	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
Sr	O
Toby	O
(	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
him	O
M	O
r	O
D	O
.	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
)	O
&	O
more	O
lively	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
inform	O
'd	O
or	O
has	O
read	O
so	O
much	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sensible	O
Man	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Visit	O
he	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
as	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
--	O
he	O
won	O
my	O
heart	O
by	O
talking	O
of	O
his	O
little	O
Daughter	O
a	O
sweet	O
Child	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
10	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
poor	O
Mans	O
heart	O
has	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
wound	O
no	O
time	O
can	O
heal	O
--	O
You	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
beautiful	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
Wife	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
abt	O
.	O
5	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
thought	O
he	O
intended	O
spending	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
when	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
rose	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
leave	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
this	O
polite	O
apology	O
for	O
ye	O
leng	O
ht	O
th	O
of	O
his	O
visit	O
--	O
that	O
't	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
fault	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Sister	O
has	O
again	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
day	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Wifes	O
House	O
to	O
comfort	O
the	O
Widow	O
--	O
the	O
Fairy	O
sent	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
for	O
My	O
Spirits	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
day	O
equal	O
to	O
any	O
exertion	O
.	O
The	O
Eldest	O
goes	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
following	O
note	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
(	O
for	O
ye	O
future	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
her	O
y	O
e	O
Lady	O
)	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
who	O
treat	O
one	O
with	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
affection	O
?	O
“	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
Yo	O
.	O
,	O
will	O
You	O
come	O
“	O
&	O
spend	O
a	O
Country	O
day	O
with	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
?	O
that	O
is	O
dine	O
&	O
“	O
stay	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
You	O
come	O
resume	O
Yor	O
.	O
old	O
excellent	O
custom	O
“	O
of	O
dining	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
&	O
continue	O
it	O
every	O
Sunday	O
“	O
when	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
interfere	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
“	O
do	O
whatever	O
is	O
most	O
convenient	O
to	O
Yourself	O
but	O
let	O
“	O
me	O
see	O
You	O
soon	O
Ever	O
very	O
Affly	O
Yors	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
Afternoon	O
for	O
as	O
my	O
Spirits	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
late	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
my	O
command	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
they	O
were	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ff	O
f	O
raid	O
of	O
trusting	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
support	O
too	O
far	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
that	O
others	O
should	O
perceive	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
perfectly	O
happy	O
.	O
Friday	O
Night	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
This	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
cheerleſs	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
idle	O
a	O
Moment	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tempting	O
meſsage	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairy	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
Pieta	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
rouse	O
my	O
spirits	O
sufficiently	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
peace	O
offering	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
some	O
fine	O
Potted	O
Lampreys	O
the	O
Friend	O
sent	O
me	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
Note	O
from	O
Pieta	B-pers
just	O
arrived	O
from	O
Nor'tonshire	B-place
&	O
dreſsing	O
obliged	O
to	O
dreſs	O
&	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
wth	O
.	O
Pieta	B-pers
she	O
is	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
her	O
on	O
Sunday	O
--	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
tomorrow	O
is	O
a	O
Court	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
11	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Snow-ball	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
quite	O
detirmined	O
abt	O
.	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Swaines	I-pers
can	O
go	O
perhaps	O
I	O
shall	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
stay	O
in	O
London	B-place
I	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
humour	O
for	O
doing	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
how	O
ungrateful	O
is	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
kind	O
friends	O
here	O
--	O
well	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
spirits	O
grow	O
better	O
I	O
wont	O
leave	O
them	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Snow	O
ball	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
come	O
early	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Spring	O
--	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
sitting	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
we	O
are	O
now	O
going	O
soberly	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
Bon	O
Soir	O
Mon	O
Amie	O
Dieu	O
vous	O
garde	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Janry	O
1785	O
Satry	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
a	O
New	O
Year	O
May	O
You	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Friend	O
begin	O
it	O
happily	O
&	O
may	O
every	O
future	O
Year	O
of	O
Your	O
life	O
be	O
still	O
Crown	O
'd	O
with	O
bleſsings	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
exchanged	O
Notes	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
She	O
aſsures	O
ME	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
&	O
has	O
sent	O
me	O
her	O
kind	O
kind	O
wishes	O
for	O
happiness	O
--	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
Dr	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Friend	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
engaged	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
pretty	O
Gypsy	O
&	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
&	O
will	O
now	O
amuse	O
myself	O
in	O
transcribing	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Attica	B-pers
friend	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
in	O
reply	O
to	O
one	O
I	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
after	O
we	O
dined	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Adelphi	O
“	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
fell	O
in	O
Love	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
“	O
did	O
we	O
?	O
For	O
ye	O
.	O
paſsion	O
You	O
say	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
conceived	O
for	O
“	O
us	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
interest	O
.	O
In	O
Lord	B-pers
Chesterfield	I-pers
You	O
will	O
have	O
“	O
a	O
most	O
formidable	O
rival	O
,	O
she	O
therefore	O
desires	O
You	O
“	O
may	O
be	O
told	O
of	O
Yor	O
.	O
danger	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
Generosity	O
“	O
not	O
very	O
usual	O
on	O
these	O
occasions	O
.	O
Seriously	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
“	O
are	O
delighted	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
unaffected	O
agreeable	O
manners	O
,	O
&	O
“	O
shd	O
think	O
him	O
very	O
interesting	O
--	O
even	O
without	O
that	O
desire	O
“	O
of	O
thinking	O
him	O
so	O
wch	O
.	O
his	O
connexion	O
wth	O
.	O
Yo	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
naturally	O
inspire	O
.	O
“	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
condole	O
wth	O
.	O
Yo	O
.	O
on	O
his	O
loſs	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
“	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
congratulate	O
Yo	O
.	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
arrival	O
of	O
Yor	O
.	O
other	O
dear	O
friends	O
(	O
12	O
“	O
whose	O
society	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
console	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
our	O
Dear	O
Atterbury	B-pers
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
“	O
prosperous	O
journey	O
,	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
spirits	O
;	O
pray	O
aſsure	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
“	O
most	O
affectionate	O
love	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
have	O
thank	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Good	O
Dowager	O
again	O
&	O
again	O
“	O
for	O
her	O
noble	O
bounty	O
to	O
my	O
poor	O
Poeteſs	O
,	O
rich	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
affairs	O
“	O
go	O
on	O
so	O
prosperously	O
.	O
When	O
Yo	O
.	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
Dowgrs	O
.	O
Friend	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
“	O
respectfully	O
offer	O
her	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
wishes	O
of	O
this	O
good	O
season	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
heartily	O
wish	O
“	O
every	O
new	O
Year	O
may	O
bring	O
wth	O
.	O
it	O
an	O
augmentation	O
of	O
bleſsings	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
If	O
You	O
“	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
White	O
's	O
(	O
Arabic	O
Profeſsor	O
)	O
Sermons	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
recommend	O
them	O
“	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
a	O
Parallel	O
between	O
ye	O
.	O
History	O
&	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
Christ	O
&	O
of	O
Mahomet	O
,	O
“	O
they	O
are	O
written	O
in	O
a	O
noble	O
stile	O
&	O
manly	O
strain	O
of	O
Piety	O
,	O
sense	O
,	O
&	O
intelligence	O
of	O
“	O
the	O
subject	O
;	O
they	O
unite	O
a	O
good	O
temper	O
with	O
a	O
warm	O
spirit	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
eloquent	O
without	O
“	O
affectation	O
--	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
I	O
am	O
charm	O
'd	O
with	O
'em	O
.	O
When	O
You	O
write	O
“	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
in	O
charity	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
soon	O
,	O
pray	O
mention	O
how	O
ye	O
.	O
Baroneſs	O
does	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
“	O
was	O
much	O
concerned	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
And	O
be	O
sure	O
tell	O
me	O
then	O
how	O
Mr-	B-pers
S	I-pers
“	O
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
it	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
Your	O
hands	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
You	O
.	O
The	O
Widow	O
unites	O
in	O
kind	O
love	O
wth	O
.	O
Yor	O
.	O
ever	O
Afft	O
.	O
&	O
faithful	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
have	O
You	O
had	O
“	O
any	O
comfortable	O
parties	O
yet	O
,	O
&	O
where	O
?	O
Hampton	B-place
last	O
day	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
new	O
Year	O
Heaven	O
“	O
send	O
us	O
a	O
happy	O
new	O
one	O
!	O
”	O
Saturday	O
night	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
fill	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
this	O
Sheet	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
am	O
I	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
quite	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
together	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
dined	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
's	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Her	O
Son	O
was	O
there	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
fashionable	O
Young	O
Man	O
--	O
but	O
his	O
sensible	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
&	O
well-bred	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
ye	O
.	O
case	O
wth	O
.	O
all	O
of	O
this	O
tribe	O
.	O
Who	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
joy	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Loves	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Toby	I-pers
Fret	I-pers
no	O
other	O
company	O
(	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Daughter	O
of	O
course	O
at	O
home	O
)	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
spent	O
an	O
afternoon	O
much	O
à	O
mon	O
gre	O
--	O
Wit	O
,	O
anecdote	O
,	O
sense	O
&	O
as	O
an	O
agreeable	O
variety	O
ye	O
.	O
Chit	O
Chat	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
have	O
I	O
been	O
entertained	O
with	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
sort	O
of	O
society	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
gains	O
so	O
much	O
knowledge	O
&	O
information	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
room	O
to	O
say	O
more	O
now	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
take	O
as	O
authentic	O
news	O
--	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
s	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
2	O
d	O
Daughter	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
Cousin	O
of	O
Denmark	O
.	O
Prince	O
said	O
this	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Table	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Son	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
&	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
King	B-pers
of	I-pers
Poland	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Library	O
at	O
Lutton	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
finest	O
&	O
largest	O
I	O
beleive	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
some	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
to	O
vex	O
his	O
eldest	O
Son	O
as	O
they	O
differ	O
in	O
Politics	O
.	O
AM	B-pers
did	O
not	O
ask	O
a	O
single	O
question	O
abt	O
.	O
You	O
but	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
enjoy	O
my	O
charming	O
society	O
this	O
Winter	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
would	O
hate	O
You	O
most	O
cordially	O
did	O
she	O
know	O
that	O
You	O
ever	O
intended	O
to	O
bur̅y	O
my	O
wonderful	O
self	O
in	O
retirement	O
.	O
I	O
send	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
viz	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
of	O
Janry	O
.	O
more	O
folio	O
sheets	O
in	O
a	O
frank	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Viscount	O
s.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
send	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
Are	O
all	O
safe	O
in	O
your	O
poſseſsion	O
do	O
you	O
like	O
I	O
should	O
write	O
thus	O
?	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
&	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
improve	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
our	O
dear	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
saucy	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
depend	O
on	O
my	O
constant	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Charge	O
I	O
am	O
bounded	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
--	O
accept	O
.	O
Sisters	O
wishes	O
for	O
many	O
happy	O
years	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
To	O
Mr	B-pers
B.ernard	I-pers
D.ewes	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Single	O
Sheet	O
Derbyshire	O
Sunday	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1785	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
The	O
Streets	O
are	O
in	O
too	O
bad	O
a	O
State	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
venture	O
out	O
except	O
in	O
a	O
Carriage	O
--	O
I	O
hate	O
dabbling	O
in	O
wet	O
,	O
&	O
dirt	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
aversion	O
to	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
You	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
like	O
I	O
should	O
adopt	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
fashion	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
half	O
boots	O
&	O
Great	O
Coat	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
my	O
walking	O
out	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Streets	O
are	O
perfectly	O
clean	O
--	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
neglect	O
ye	O
.	O
duties	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
--	O
If	O
I	O
remember	O
right	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
read	O
any	O
of	O
the	B-pers
dear	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
s	O
Sermons	O
it	O
is	O
therefore	O
allowable	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
transcribe	O
a	O
few	O
paſsages	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
it	O
pleased	O
me	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
our	O
opinions	O
&	O
tastes	O
are	O
similiar	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
approve	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Union	O
of	O
Piety	O
&	O
Morality	O
--	O
“	O
The	O
neglect	O
of	O
Piety	O
argues	O
depravity	O
“	O
of	O
heart	O
;	O
&	O
it	O
infers	O
an	O
irregular	O
discharge	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
duties	O
“	O
of	O
morality	O
”	O
--	O
It	O
argues	O
internal	O
depravity	O
for	O
it	O
discovers	O
a	O
“	O
cold	O
&	O
a	O
hard	O
heart	O
.	O
if	O
there	O
be	O
any	O
impreſsion	O
wch	O
.	O
man	O
is	O
“	O
formed	O
by	O
Nature	O
to	O
receive	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sense	O
of	O
religion	O
.	O
As	O
“	O
soon	O
as	O
his	O
Mind	O
opens	O
to	O
observation	O
&	O
reflection	O
,	O
he	O
“	O
discerns	O
innumerable	O
marks	O
of	O
his	O
dependant	O
state	O
.	O
He	O
“	O
finds	O
himself	O
placed	O
by	O
some	O
superior	O
power	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
vast	O
“	O
world	O
,	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
wisdom	O
&	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Creator	O
are	O
“	O
conspicous	O
on	O
every	O
side	O
,	O
The	O
magnificence	O
,	O
the	O
beauty	O
&	O
order	O
“	O
of	O
nature	O
excite	O
him	O
to	O
admire	O
&	O
adore	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
looks	O
“	O
up	O
to	O
that	O
invisible	O
hand	O
wch	O
.	O
operates	O
throughout	O
the	O
“	O
Universe	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
impreſsed	O
wth	O
.	O
reverence	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
receives	O
“	O
bleſsings	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
avoid	O
ascribing	O
to	O
divine	O
goodneſs	O
“	O
he	O
is	O
prompted	O
to	O
gratitude	O
.	O
The	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
those	O
“	O
forms	O
affections	O
under	O
the	O
various	O
forms	O
of	O
divine	O
“	O
religious	O
worship	O
,	O
are	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
native	O
effusions	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
human	O
heart	O
.	O
Ignorance	O
may	O
mislead	O
,	O
&	O
superstition	O
“	O
may	O
corrupt	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
origin	O
is	O
derived	O
from	O
“	O
sentiments	O
that	O
are	O
eſsential	O
to	O
Man	O
.	O
--	O
Whatever	O
“	O
either	O
from	O
reverence	O
or	O
from	O
gratitude	O
can	O
excite	O
Men	O
“	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
worship	O
of	O
God	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
Christian	O
Revelation	O
placed	O
“	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
shld	O
.	O
think	O
were	O
sufficient	O
to	O
“	O
overawe	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
thoughtleſs	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
melt	O
the	O
most	O
“	O
obdurate	O
mind	O
.	O
--	O
Where	O
religion	O
is	O
neglected	O
,	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
“	O
no	O
regular	O
nor	O
steady	O
practice	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
duties	O
of	O
morality	O
,	O
the	O
“	O
character	O
will	O
be	O
inconsistent	O
,	O
&	O
Virtue	O
placed	O
on	O
a	O
basis	O
“	O
too	O
narrow	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
always	O
loose	O
&	O
tottering	O
.	O
For	O
“	O
such	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
propensity	O
of	O
our	O
Nature	O
to	O
Vice	O
,	O
so	O
numerous	O
are	O
14/	O
“	O
are	O
the	O
temptations	O
to	O
a	O
relaxed	O
&	O
immoral	O
conduct	O
,	O
“	O
that	O
stronger	O
restraints	O
than	O
those	O
of	O
mere	O
reason	O
are	O
“	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
imposed	O
on	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
sense	O
of	O
right	O
&	O
wrong	O
,	O
the	O
“	O
principle	O
of	O
honor	O
,	O
or	O
ye	O
.	O
instinct	O
of	O
benevolence	O
,	O
are	O
“	O
barriers	O
too	O
feeble	O
to	O
withstand	O
ye	O
.	O
strength	O
of	O
paſsion	O
.	O
“	O
In	O
the	O
tranquil	O
Seas	O
Seasons	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
these	O
natural	O
“	O
principals	O
may	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
carry	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
ordinary	O
course	O
of	O
social	O
“	O
duties	O
with	O
some	O
regularity	O
.	O
But	O
wait	O
till	O
some	O
“	O
trying	O
emergence	O
come	O
.	O
Let	O
the	O
conflict	O
of	O
the	O
paſsions	O
“	O
arise	O
.	O
Let	O
the	O
heart	O
be	O
either	O
wounded	O
by	O
sore	O
“	O
distreſs	O
,	O
or	O
agitated	O
by	O
violent	O
emotions	O
;	O
&	O
You	O
shall	O
“	O
presently	O
see	O
that	O
virtue	O
without	O
religion	O
is	O
“	O
inadequate	O
to	O
the	O
government	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
destitute	O
“	O
of	O
its	O
proper	O
guard	O
,	O
of	O
its	O
firmest	O
support	O
,	O
of	O
its	O
“	O
chief	O
encouragement	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
sink	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
weight	O
“	O
of	O
misfortune	O
;	O
or	O
will	O
yield	O
to	O
the	O
solicitation	O
of	O
“	O
guilt	O
--	O
The	O
great	O
motives	O
that	O
produce	O
constancy	O
&	O
“	O
firmneſs	O
of	O
action	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
palpable	O
&	O
striking	O
“	O
kind	O
.	O
A	O
divine	O
Legislator	O
,	O
uttering	O
his	O
voice	O
from	O
“	O
Heaven	O
;	O
An	O
Omniscient	O
witneſs	O
,	O
beholding	O
us	O
in	O
“	O
all	O
our	O
retreats	O
;	O
An	O
Almighty	O
Governour	O
stretching	O
“	O
forth	O
his	O
arm	O
to	O
punish	O
or	O
reward	O
,	O
disclosing	O
the	O
“	O
secrets	O
of	O
the	O
invisible	O
world	O
,	O
informing	O
us	O
of	O
“	O
perpetual	O
rest	O
prepared	O
hereafter	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
righteous	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
“	O
indignation	O
&	O
wrath	O
awaiting	O
ye	O
.	O
wicked	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
“	O
the	O
considerations	O
wch	O
.	O
overawe	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
support	O
“	O
integrity	O
,	O
&	O
check	O
guilt	O
.	O
They	O
add	O
to	O
Virtue	O
that	O
“	O
solemnity	O
wch	O
.	O
should	O
ever	O
characterize	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
“	O
admonitions	O
of	O
Conscience	O
they	O
give	O
ye	O
.	O
authority	O
of	O
“	O
a	O
law	O
.	O
Co-operating	O
wth	O
.	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
dispositions	O
of	O
a	O
“	O
pious	O
Man	O
,	O
they	O
strengthen	O
&	O
insure	O
their	O
influence	O
.	O
“	O
On	O
his	O
Alms	O
you	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
certain	O
dependence	O
,	O
“	O
who	O
thinks	O
not	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
nor	O
has	O
joined	O
prayer	O
to	O
his	O
“	O
charitable	O
deeds	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
humanity	O
is	O
seconded	O
“	O
by	O
Piety	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Spring	O
from	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
flows	O
is	O
rendered	O
,	O
of	O
“	O
course	O
more	O
regular	O
&	O
constant	O
--	O
In	O
short	O
--	O
withdraw	O
“	O
Religion	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
shake	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
pillars	O
of	O
morality	O
,	O
in	O
“	O
every	O
heart	O
you	O
weaken	O
ye	O
.	O
influence	O
of	O
Virtue	O
:	O
&	O
“	O
among	O
the	O
Multitude	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
bulk	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
You	O
“	O
overthrow	O
its	O
power	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
who	O
fails	O
materially	O
either	O
“	O
in	O
Piety	O
or	O
in	O
Virtue	O
is	O
always	O
obnoxious	O
to	O
the	O
anguish	O
of	O
remorse	O
“	O
His	O
partial	O
goodneſs	O
may	O
flatter	O
him	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
superficial	O
“	O
observation	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
solitude	O
or	O
distreſs	O
awakens	O
the	O
powers	O
of	O
(	O
15	O
“	O
of	O
reflection	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
feel	O
that	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
duty	O
“	O
performed	O
,	O
atones	O
not	O
for	O
another	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
neglected	O
.	O
--	O
Where	O
“	O
Beneficence	O
&	O
devotion	O
are	O
united	O
,	O
they	O
pour	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
“	O
in	O
whom	O
they	O
meet	O
,	O
the	O
full	O
pleasures	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
&	O
pure	O
“	O
heart	O
.	O
His	O
alms	O
connected	O
him	O
wth	O
.	O
Men	O
;	O
his	O
prayers	O
“	O
with	O
God	O
.	O
He	O
looks	O
without	O
dismay	O
on	O
both	O
worlds	O
.	O
All	O
“	O
nature	O
has	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
bening	O
benign	O
aspect	O
.	O
If	O
engaged	O
in	O
active	O
“	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
friend	O
of	O
Man	O
;	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
happy	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
exertions	O
“	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
friendship	O
;	O
If	O
left	O
in	O
retirement	O
,	O
he	O
walks	O
among	O
“	O
ye	O
.	O
works	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
Every	O
object	O
is	O
enlivened	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
sense	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
divine	O
presence	O
.	O
Every	O
where	O
he	O
traces	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
beneficent	O
hand	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Author	O
of	O
nature	O
;	O
&	O
every	O
where	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
glowing	O
heart	O
“	O
he	O
hears	O
&	O
answers	O
his	O
secret	O
voice	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
looks	O
up	O
to	O
heaven	O
“	O
he	O
rejoices	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
thought	O
that	O
there	O
dwells	O
that	O
God	O
whom	O
he	O
“	O
Serves	O
&	O
honors	O
;	O
that	O
Saviour	O
in	O
whom	O
he	O
trusts	O
;	O
that	O
Spirit	O
of	O
“	O
grace	O
from	O
whose	O
inspiration	O
his	O
piety	O
&	O
his	O
charity	O
“	O
flow	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
looks	O
around	O
him	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
soothed	O
“	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasing	O
remembrance	O
of	O
good	O
offices	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
“	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
studied	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
many	O
who	O
dwell	O
there	O
.	O
How	O
“	O
comfortable	O
ye	O
.	O
reflection	O
,	O
that	O
him	O
no	O
poor	O
man	O
can	O
“	O
upbraid	O
for	O
having	O
withheld	O
his	O
due	O
;	O
him	O
no	O
unfortunate	O
“	O
Man	O
can	O
reproach	O
for	O
having	O
seen	O
&	O
despised	O
his	O
sorrows	O
;	O
“	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
are	O
descending	O
ye	O
.	O
prayers	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
needy	O
&	O
“	O
ye	O
.	O
aged	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
hands	O
of	O
those	O
whom	O
his	O
protection	O
has	O
“	O
supported	O
;	O
or	O
his	O
bounty	O
has	O
fed	O
,	O
are	O
lifted	O
up	O
in	O
secret	O
to	O
“	O
bleſs	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
To	O
this	O
Honor	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
bleſsedneſs	O
,	O
let	O
our	O
“	O
hearts	O
continually	O
aspire	O
&	O
throughout	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
“	O
let	O
those	O
solemn	O
&	O
sacred	O
words	O
sound	O
in	O
our	O
ears	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
the	O
“	O
directory	O
of	O
our	O
conduct	O
.	O
“	O
He	O
hath	O
shewed	O
thee	O
,	O
O	O
Man	O
,	O
“	O
what	O
is	O
good	O
;	O
&	O
what	O
doth	O
ye	O
.	O
Lord	O
thy	O
God	O
require	O
of	O
thee	O
“	O
but	O
--	O
to	O
do	O
justly	O
,	O
&	O
love	O
mercy	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
walk	O
humbly	O
wth-	O
“	O
thy	O
God	O
?	O
”	O
.	O
Micah	O
,	O
6:8	O
.	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
Mr	B-pers
B.D	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
has	O
has	O
had	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
night	O
--	O
is	O
however	O
better	O
now	O
.	O
Sunday	O
7	O
oClock	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
King	B-pers
of	I-pers
Poland	I-pers
(	O
Widow	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
)	O
sent	O
her	O
Carriage	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
B.D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
:	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
w	O
th	O
Lady	B-pers
Dowgrs	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Diary	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
because	O
her	O
little	O
grandson	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
this	O
seem	O
'd	O
quite	O
primitive	O
considering	O
the	O
present	O
dinner	O
hours	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
&	O
the	O
time	O
paſs	O
'd	O
agreeably	O
in	O
sensible	O
converse	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
us	O
some	O
curious	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
D.ewes	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
B.D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
for	O
she	O
lived	O
near	O
them	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
her	O
youth	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Litchfield	B-place
16	O
)	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
memory	O
will	O
retain	O
them	O
I	O
shall	O
reserve	O
them	O
for	O
our	O
future	O
conversations	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
expect	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
must	O
read	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
she	O
comes	O
Adieu	O
--	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
--	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
at	O
8	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
look	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
&	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
this	O
moment	O
gone	O
,	O
many	O
enquiries	O
she	O
made	O
abtt	O
.	O
You	O
--	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
prepared	O
to	O
love	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
good	O
telling	O
You	O
this	O
for	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
pretty	O
,	O
very	O
wise	O
&	O
much	O
accomplished	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
great	O
friends	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
7	O
ever	O
since	O
we	O
were	O
acquainted	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
abt	O
.	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
tired	O
wth	O
.	O
talking	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exert	O
myself	O
to	O
write	O
down	O
all	O
we	O
said	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
relate	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
secrets	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
you	O
must	O
never	O
imagine	O
I	O
shall	O
reveal	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
is	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
perhaps	O
we	O
shall	O
talk	O
of	O
You	O
--	O
Good	O
Night	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
.	O
Monday	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
Decbr	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
risen	O
from	O
being	O
under	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
(	O
Pieta	B-pers
s	O
Sister	O
)	O
hands	O
near	O
3	O
hours	O
what	O
a	O
waste	O
of	O
time	O
!	O
--	O
however	O
I	O
always	O
read	O
so	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
putting	O
my	O
hair	O
into	O
fashionable	O
order	O
--	O
cutting	O
,	O
curling	O
,	O
&	O
dreſsing	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
triffles	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
upon	O
_	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
saying	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
relating	O
to	O
those	O
we	O
love	O
is	O
interesting	O
so	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
finish	O
the	O
sentence	O
if	O
You	O
please	O
--	O
A	O
Note	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
friend	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
&	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
't	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
Baroneſs	O
's	O
Birth	O
day	O
&	O
I	O
always	O
dine	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
is	O
again	O
gone	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Wife	O
s	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
engaged	O
to	O
an	O
aſsembly	O
this	O
Eveg	O
at	O
Attica	B-pers
s	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
Humour	O
for	O
a	O
Croud	O
&	O
fine	O
folks	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
an	O
excuse	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
&	O
go	O
quietly	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairy	O
s	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
sent	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
favorites	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
17	O
Tuesday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1785	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
too	O
late	O
last	O
night	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
conversing	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
resolution	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
Your	O
wish	O
)	O
of	O
not	O
sitting	O
up	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
read	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
I	O
formerly	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Eldest	O
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
we	O
parted	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
pretty	O
Gypsy	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
You	O
some	O
extracts	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
..	O
reasons	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Delay	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
what	O
she	O
says	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
Mountagu	B-pers
s	O
Son	O
&	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
always	O
makes	O
enquiries	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
“	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Dialogue	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
shews	O
“	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
heart	O
,	O
&	O
friendship	O
&	O
then	O
one	O
is	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
“	O
any	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
provoked	O
wth	O
..	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
behaviour	O
of	O
“	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
quite	O
“	O
shameful	O
--	O
”	O
I	O
sincerely	O
return	O
your	O
good	O
wishes	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
beginning	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
Year	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
uncomfortable	O
situation	O
“	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
amply	O
made	O
amends	O
for	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
next	O
“	O
Year	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
imagine	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
being	O
exceſsively	O
vext	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
“	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
consider	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
of	O
Your	O
friends	O
who	O
now	O
“	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
will	O
protect	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
allow	O
“	O
that	O
this	O
delay	O
is	O
any	O
way	O
occasioned	O
by	O
him	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
“	O
natural	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
old	O
people	O
(	O
&	O
indeed	O
there	O
are	O
instances	O
“	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Young	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
old	O
)	O
to	O
like	O
there	O
own	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
except	O
“	O
ye	O
.	O
disappointment	O
of	O
having	O
an	O
Event	O
delay	O
'd	O
from	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
“	O
expects	O
so	O
much	O
happineſs	O
--	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
at	O
ease	O
.	O
I	O
“	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
tell	O
him	O
this	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
natural	O
Your	O
near	O
“	O
Relations	O
shd	O
.	O
often	O
be	O
question	O
'd	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
often	O
)	O
I	O
shall	O
“	O
take	O
care	O
that	O
no	O
suspicion	O
shall	O
fall	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
“	O
thing	O
unpleasant	O
wth	O
.	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
hinted	O
at	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
now	O
“	O
added	O
to	O
all	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
both	O
may	O
continue	O
encreasing	O
“	O
through	O
many	O
many	O
Years	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairy	O
s	O
last	O
night	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
there	O
--	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Charlotte	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mar-all	I-pers
(	O
her	O
Niece	O
)	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
AM	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
an	O
Irish	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
very	O
large	O
fortune	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
few	O
who	O
have	O
traveld	O
with	O
observation	O
--	O
such	O
observation	O
as	O
renders	O
him	O
an	O
entertaining	O
companion	O
&	O
a	O
useful	O
Member	O
of	O
society	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
&	O
is	O
aſsisting	O
ye	O
.	O
Irish	O
Manufactors	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
was	O
much	O
pleasant	O
conversation	O
--	O
the	O
Fairy	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
went	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
supper	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
drank	O
Your	O
health	O
&	O
the	O
Fairy	O
her	O
Husband	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
said	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
abt	O
.	O
You	O
.	O
18	O
)	O
Tuesday	O
Morng	O
.	O
/	O
Ah	O
how	O
unlucky	O
my	O
foolish	O
pate	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
miſs	O
'd	O
seeing	O
my	O
Love	O
Our	B-pers
Widows	I-pers
&	O
a	O
half	O
love	O
his	O
Brother	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
Alas	O
!	O
Perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
lost	O
Clasic	O
Verses	O
in	O
my	O
Praise	O
wch	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
might	O
have	O
charm	O
'd	O
posterity	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
angry	O
if	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
compositions	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
--	O
so	O
please	O
to	O
borrow	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Genius	O
&	O
writings	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
G.arrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
English	O
Poetry	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
Dodsleys	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Poetry	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
things	O
written	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
two	O
Brothers	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
reckon	O
'd	O
our	O
most	O
judicious	O
Critics	O
&	O
Pieta	B-pers
is	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
best	O
Scholars	O
--	O
&	O
who	O
enters	O
wth	O
..	O
true	O
spirit	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
genius	O
of	O
the	O
Antients	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
papers	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Adventurer	O
they	O
are	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
Z	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
writing	O
ye	O
.	O
name	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
H	O
.	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
Warton	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
also	O
Translated	O
Virgil	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
suppose	O
They	O
have	O
written	O
many	O
things	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Visit	O
from	O
good	O
Pliny	B-pers
--	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
friend	O
s	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
In	O
the	O
Eveg	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
--	O
H.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Visit	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
,	O
agreeable	O
,	O
pretty	O
Woman	O
Some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
will	O
talk	O
more	O
about	O
her	O
--	O
The	O
Lady	O
too	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
&	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
Compt	O
.	O
of	O
saying	O
--	O
how	O
difficult	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
quit	O
me	O
--	O
She	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
her	O
three	O
day	O
's	O
--	O
Thursday	O
--	O
Sunday	O
&	O
Monday	O
next	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
busy	O
cleaning	O
&	O
hanging	O
up	O
my	O
Dr.	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
s	O
Picture	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
placed	O
where	O
the	O
Print	O
of	O
ye	O
Royal	O
Children	O
was	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
hung	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
my	O
two	O
little	O
Rooms	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
perfect	O
order	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
again	O
tidy	O
&	O
comfortable	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
employ	O
myself	O
wth-	O
regularity	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
profit	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
--	O
work	O
--	O
draw	O
--	O
&	O
write	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
breakfasted	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
at	O
intervals	O
I	O
scribble	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
my	O
other	O
,	O
absent	O
friends	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
occupy	O
my	O
Mind	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
I	O
shall	O
begin	O
to	O
learn	O
Italian	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
slow	O
progreſs	O
I	O
fear	O
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth-	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
met	O
since	O
Yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
for	O
since	O
You	O
went	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
19	O
)	O
breakfasted	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
amiable	O
Baroneſs	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
remind	O
me	O
of	O
tomorrow	O
Tuesday	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
dining	O
Room	O
--	O
Mar	B-pers
all	I-pers
has	O
left	O
us	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sister	O
&	O
I	O
are	O
both	O
writing	O
--	O
can	O
not	O
You	O
or	O
rather	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
sometimes	O
transport	O
Yourself	O
in	O
idea	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
now	O
fancying	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
sitting	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
this	O
difference	O
only	O
excepted	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
write	O
without	O
interruptions	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
live	O
I	O
believe	O
You	O
have	O
engaged	O
a	O
Sylph	O
in	O
Your	O
service	O
&	O
the	O
little	O
invisible	O
spirit	O
I	O
suppose	O
seeing	O
the	O
characters	O
my	O
pen	O
had	O
just	O
traced	O
was	O
detirmin	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
no	O
distance	O
could	O
secure	O
me	O
from	O
being	O
interrupted	O
by	O
You	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
finished	O
that	O
word	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Post-mans	O
knock	O
made	O
me	O
start	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
You	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
reply	O
to	O
it	O
immediately	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
worse	O
for	O
Your	O
journey	O
&	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
safe	O
at	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Your	O
letter	O
is	O
dated	O
Sunday	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
of	O
Jany	O
&	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
You	O
got	O
to	O
Elvaston	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
ye	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
perhaps	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
wrong	O
--	O
&	O
You	O
may	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
unreasonable	O
well	O
I	O
wont	O
say	O
what	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
even	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
command	O
of	O
a	O
moment	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
when	O
friendship	O
&	O
affection	O
had	O
claims	O
upon	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
steal	O
either	O
an	O
early	O
or	O
late	O
hour	O
from	O
my	O
repose	O
to	O
satisfy	O
them	O
--	O
Busineſs	O
may	O
occupy	O
us	O
--	O
engagements	O
of	O
various	O
kinds	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
necessary	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
fulfill	O
--	O
but	O
even	O
a	O
first	O
Minister	O
of	O
State	O
will	O
find	O
one	O
½	O
Hour	O
in	O
ye	O
24	O
to	O
devote	O
to	O
friendship	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
satisfied	O
with	O
five	O
Minutes	O
had	O
You	O
bestowed	O
them	O
upon	O
me	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
poſseſs	O
Your	O
affection	O
&	O
that	O
You	O
love	O
me	O
entirely	O
--	O
how	O
comes	O
it	O
then	O
that	O
Your	O
heart	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
ease	O
&	O
Your	O
mind	O
at	O
rest	O
when	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
suffering	O
the	O
torture	O
20	O
of	O
suspence	O
,	O
put	O
Yourself	O
in	O
my	O
place	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
&	O
then	O
judge	O
how	O
anxious	O
I	O
was	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
Your	O
safety	O
.	O
forgive	O
me	O
this	O
reproach	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
from	O
my	O
heart	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
I	O
become	O
indifferent	O
abt	O
You	O
.	O
Your	O
little	O
Sylph	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
pen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
“	O
&	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
”	O
Alexander	O
Pope	O
,	O
The	O
Rape	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
Canto	O
1	O
,	O
l.26	O
remember	O
how	O
often	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
has	O
told	O
You	O
that	O
it	O
gives	O
him	O
pain	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
look	O
grave	O
&	O
that	O
smiles	O
become	O
You	O
best	O
--	O
the	O
gloom	O
that	O
overspread	O
my	O
countenance	O
vanished	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
--	O
the	O
Sylph	O
to	O
reward	O
me	O
placed	O
Your	O
image	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
ideal	O
view	O
of	O
You	O
composed	O
my	O
spirits	O
&	O
I	O
resumed	O
my	O
pen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
You	O
to	O
ask	O
The	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
admirers	O
--	O
had	O
he	O
become	O
one	O
indeed	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
pleased	O
because	O
You	O
think	O
him	O
worthy	O
of	O
Your	O
friendship	O
&	O
deserving	O
of	O
Your	O
esteem	O
,	O
however	O
upon	O
any	O
terms	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
place	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Yours	O
upon	O
the	O
list	O
&	O
for	O
Your	O
sake	O
I	O
will	O
overlook	O
the	O
humiliation	O
--	O
for	O
is	O
it	O
consistent	O
wth	O
.	O
that	O
proper	O
pride	O
wch	O
.	O
a	O
female	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
solicit	O
admiration	O
?	O
--	O
After	O
having	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
raise	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
Your	O
friend	O
s	O
character	O
You	O
most	O
imprudently	O
reveal	O
that	O
his	O
Heart	O
is	O
narrow	O
&	O
selfish	O
,	O
--	O
does	O
a	O
benevolent	O
one	O
ever	O
enquire	O
whether	O
ye	O
.	O
Object	O
of	O
there	O
charity	O
shall	O
return	O
the	O
alms	O
they	O
give	O
?	O
or	O
does	O
a	O
generous	O
Man	O
expect	O
more	O
than	O
thanks	O
&	O
gratitude	O
to	O
reward	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
liberality	O
?	O
You	O
will	O
stare	O
perhaps	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
this	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
Your	O
own	O
hand	O
that	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
declared	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
give	O
my	O
poor	O
Milkwoman	O
a	O
Crown	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
large	O
Collection	O
of	O
Sermons	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
writing	O
them	O
--	O
nay	O
more	O
he	O
expects	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
y	O
e	O
production	O
of	O
my	O
Brain	O
.	O
what	O
an	O
unconscionable	O
creature	O
!	O
--	O
&	O
how	O
inconsiderate	O
are	O
You	O
to	O
expose	O
Your	O
Friend	O
thus	O
!	O
If	O
You	O
continue	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
some	O
Sermons	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
my	O
bargain	O
,	O
viz	O
that	O
they	O
shall	O
take	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
delivery	O
&	O
ye	O
“	O
lapping	O
up	O
shall	O
be	O
a	O
full	O
½	O
hour	O
more	O
.	O
(	O
21	O
Tuesday	O
4	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
85	O
continued	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
Dowgrs	O
.	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
7	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
friends	O
house	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Dr-	O
Friend	O
so	O
much	O
recovered	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
flattered	O
myself	O
she	O
was	O
she	O
is	O
nevertheleſs	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
was	O
in	O
chearful	O
spirits	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hours	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
her	O
Niece	O
--	O
who	O
has	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
praises	O
wch	O
.	O
this	O
unworthy	O
woman	O
does	O
not	O
merit	O
--	O
God	O
grant	O
The	O
dear	O
Friend	O
may	O
never	O
be	O
undeceived	O
--	O
for	O
w	O
h	O
ere	O
she	O
even	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
suspected	O
of	O
doing	O
what	O
is	O
wrong	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
wld-	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
repent	O
having	O
employed	O
the	O
Husband	O
--	O
who	O
is	O
as	O
worthleſs	O
a	O
being	O
as	O
the	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
Dowgr	O
.	O
The	O
Friend	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
just	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
(	O
did	O
not	O
Your	O
cheek	O
burn	O
?	O
)	O
when	O
Miranda	B-pers
came	O
--	O
&	O
there	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
hour	O
I	O
always	O
quit	O
ye	O
.	O
friend	O
s	O
house	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
ye	O
.	O
trio	O
were	O
equally	O
chagrined	O
at	O
the	O
interruption	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
Cousin	O
justice	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
mood	O
.	O
From	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Friend	O
s	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
:	O
Wife	O
s	O
House	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
dismiſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Dowg	O
Coach	O
--	O
The	O
Husband	O
Was	O
from	O
home	O
--	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
Widow	O
Sister	O
&	O
A.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
composed	O
ye	O
:	O
party	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
tranquil	O
&	O
friendly	O
one	O
--	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Jun.r	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
sat	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
eldest	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1785	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Priest	O
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
confidential	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
he	O
enquired	O
very	O
kindly	O
after	O
You	O
--	O
the	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
her	O
Company	O
--	O
Abt	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Baron	O
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
Blair	B-pers
(	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
a	O
great	O
friend	O
of	O
ye	O
Baroneſs	O
's	O
&	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Carriage	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
son	O
a	O
smart	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
hair	O
in	O
ye	O
:	O
ton	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
those	O
Compts	O
.	O
I	O
daily	O
meet	O
wth	O
.	O
of	O
wishing	O
me	O
happineſs	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
those	O
questions	O
autho	O
r	O
ised	O
by	O
intimacy	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
soon	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
friendly	O
party	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Baron	O
s	O
,	O
viz	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dear	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bristol	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Son	O
)	O
hereafter	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Pieta	B-pers
,	O
his	O
Tutor	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
N——	I-pers
--	O
this	O
day	O
my	O
most	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
friend	O
the	O
Baroneſs	O
is	O
44	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
hearing	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
felt	O
as	O
if	O
22	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
her	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Year	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
few	O
like	O
her	O
--	O
Virtue	O
ought	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
life	O
for	O
such	O
as	O
promote	O
inculcate	O
her	O
precepts	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
You	O
my	O
friend	O
!	O
surely	O
if	O
the	O
Guardian	O
was	O
perfectly	O
acquai	O
n	O
ted	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
characters	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
to	O
be	O
intimate	O
with	O
his	O
parental	O
cares	O
for	O
Your	O
future	O
happineſs	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
his	O
writing	O
that	O
fatal	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
so	O
cruelly	O
dwelt	O
upon	O
my	O
Mind	O
.	O
I	O
refer	O
to	O
one	O
paſsage	O
only	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
“	O
Your	O
expectations	O
of	O
happineſs	O
will	O
be	O
disappointed	O
&	O
c	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
my	O
Chaperon	O
in	O
the	O
Baron	O
s	O
Coach	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
alone	O
,	O
we	O
chatted	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Thursday	O
6	O
th	O
janry	O
.	O
The	O
worthy	O
Baron	O
made	O
me	O
an	O
early	O
visit	O
--	O
he	O
whisper	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gueſsd	O
ye	O
.	O
subject	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
father	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
regretted	O
extremely	O
that	O
his	O
engagements	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
when	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
seeing	O
You	O
more	O
particularly	O
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
hours	O
of	O
her	O
company	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
spirits	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Lady	O
.	O
--	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Eveg-	O
Our	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
loves	O
You	O
as	O
a	O
Brother	O
,	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
6	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Wife	O
s	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
orders	O
to	O
be	O
denied	O
to	O
visitors	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
alone	O
--	O
I	O
try	O
to	O
amuse	O
myself	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
--	O
but	O
how	O
difficult	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
when	O
the	O
Mind	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
ease	O
--	O
Yet	O
when	O
I	O
reflect	O
how	O
rich	O
a	O
treasure	O
I	O
poſseſs	O
in	O
Your	O
love	O
&	O
esteem	O
&	O
how	O
bleſsed	O
I	O
am	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
sincere	O
affection	O
of	O
many	O
very	O
valuable	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
Friends	O
I	O
blush	O
at	O
repining	O
at	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
but	O
a	O
sensible	O
heart	O
will	O
fell	O
feel	O
pangs	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
always	O
properly	O
check	O
do	O
not	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Friend	O
Imagine	O
that	O
I	O
indulge	O
that	O
lowneſs	O
of	O
spirits	O
wch	O
.	O
now	O
oppreſses	O
me	O
--	O
when	O
that	O
Cloud	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
so	O
long	O
lour	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
is	O
diſsipated	O
I	O
shall	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
lively	O
chearfulneſs	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
natural	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
Dr.	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
wrote	O
this	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
“	O
it	O
is	O
salutary	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
checks	O
to	O
our	O
enjoyments	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
reflect	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
perfect	O
bliſs	O
--	O
how	O
(	O
23	O
otherwise	O
should	O
we	O
be	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
life	O
to	O
come	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
convinced	O
that	O
every	O
disappointment	O
we	O
meet	O
wth-	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
is	O
if	O
we	O
properly	O
discharge	O
our	O
great	O
duties	O
intended	O
as	O
a	O
bleſsing	O
”	O
wth	O
.	O
this	O
comfortable	O
Idea	O
I	O
bid	O
You	O
Adieu	O
for	O
to	O
night	O
--	O
May	O
God	O
of	O
his	O
infinite	O
mercy	O
protect	O
us	O
both	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
will	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
paſs	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
lives	O
together	O
May	O
we	O
so	O
live	O
to	O
his	O
Glory	O
here	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
united	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
to	O
come	O
Friday	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
Garrick	B-pers
left	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
early	O
they	O
were	O
engaged	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
summons	O
resolution	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
visits	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
s	O
daughter	O
accidentally	O
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
she	O
sat	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
Drawing	O
&	O
she	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Minstrel	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
&	O
had	O
taste	O
to	O
relish	O
it	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sensible	O
refin	O
'd	O
Young	O
Woman	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
will	O
acquit	O
herself	O
very	O
properly	O
through	O
life	O
.	O
Good	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
short	O
Visit	O
as	O
an	O
earnest	O
of	O
a	O
longer	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
Note	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
enquiries	O
after	O
You	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
I	O
have	O
finish	O
'd	O
Charlotte	B-pers
s	O
fan	O
--	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
with	O
working	O
&	O
thinking	O
of	O
You	O
.	O
The	O
Sisters	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
Saturday	O
8	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
:	O
Reading	O
--	O
writing	O
extracts	O
&	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
good	O
accts	O
.	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
this	O
Morg	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
At	O
1	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
(	O
M	O
d	O
of	O
Honor	O
)	O
came	O
she	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
O	O
how	O
my	O
Nerves	O
are	O
worn	O
with	O
questions	O
,	O
conjectures	O
&	O
reports	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
pity	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
I	O
shall	O
absolutely	O
break	O
wth	O
.	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
short	O
visit	O
from	O
the	O
charming	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
she	O
was	O
accompanied	O
by	O
her	O
Nephew	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
.	O
“	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
from	O
your	O
friend	O
my	O
dear	O
?	O
not	O
since	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
replied	O
--	O
“	O
what	O
only	O
twice	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
You	O
thats	O
a	O
little	O
hard	O
I	O
think	O
--	O
”	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
too	O
yet	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
for	O
You	O
;	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
also	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
too	O
grave	O
a	O
face	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
made	O
apologies	O
&	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Sisters	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
24	O
)	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
&	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
in	O
contriving	O
&	O
completing	O
a	O
Case	O
to	O
hold	O
all	O
my	O
Instruments	O
--	O
knives	O
--	O
sciſsars	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
We	O
begun	O
--	O
King	O
on	O
Ancient	O
Castles	O
,	O
a	O
book	O
Counteſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
lent	O
me	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
purchased	O
as	O
a	O
separate	O
work	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
fortune	O
&	O
only	O
printed	O
a	O
few	O
Copies	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
--	O
't	O
is	O
an	O
agreeable	O
work	O
to	O
lovers	O
of	O
Antiquity	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
we	O
proceed	O
.	O
After	O
Supper	O
I	O
got	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sister	O
to	O
play	O
some	O
leſsons	O
--	O
&	O
,	O
O	O
shame	O
to	O
our	O
promises	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
from	O
y	O
e	O
Dr	O
:	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
--	O
she	O
sent	O
us	O
some	O
Christmaſs	O
Fare	O
viz	O
a	O
Turkey	O
&	O
some	O
fine	O
Pork	O
.	O
her	O
Husband	O
has	O
again	O
got	O
ye	O
.	O
gout	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
Nor'ton	B-place
shire	I-place
.	O
Sunday	O
9	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
so	O
sudden	O
&	O
almost	O
total	O
darkneſs	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
a	O
Yellow	O
heavy	O
fog	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
like	O
an	O
eclipse	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
Candles	O
in	O
ye	O
Churches	O
.	O
Marall	B-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
friendly	O
visit	O
after	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
preſsing	O
meſsage	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
them	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
myself	O
to	O
others	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
mood	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
alone	O
all	O
day	O
if	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
trusted	O
by	O
myself	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
confeſs	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
of	O
late	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
spirits	O
in	O
any	O
degree	O
of	O
command	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
to	O
live	O
as	O
much	O
in	O
society	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
besides	O
too	O
as	O
my	O
society	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
select	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
first	O
Claſs	O
as	O
to	O
conversation	O
&	O
Characters	O
I	O
will	O
can	O
profit	O
more	O
by	O
living	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
than	O
occupying	O
myself	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
please	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
thinking	O
that	O
the	O
more	O
information	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
&	O
the	O
greater	O
scope	O
for	O
observation	O
for	O
observation	O
of	O
Characters	O
&	O
Minds	O
--	O
the	O
more	O
agreeable	O
will	O
my	O
conversation	O
be	O
render	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
hereafter	O
.	O
At	O
4	O
o'clock	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
herself	O
&	O
Daughter	O
--	O
the	O
Desert	O
was	O
just	O
putting	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
when	O
Her	O
son	O
came	O
flying	O
in	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Morning	O
Visit	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
chatting	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
us	O
Opera	O
news	O
&	O
bon-ton	O
intelligence	O
&	O
then	O
flew	O
away	O
again	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
a	O
6	O
or	O
rather	O
I	O
suppose	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
dinner	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Molesworth	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Books	O
&	O
characters	O
--	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
question	O
abt	O
.	O
You	O
--	O
then	O
25	O
some	O
agreeable	O
intimates	O
of	O
ours	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
viz	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
&	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Fairy	O
s	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
party	O
my	O
love	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
&	O
my	O
Dr	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Udney	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
--	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Conyngham	I-pers
--	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Cunynghame	I-pers
&	O
Mary	B-pers
Udney	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Eveg	O
pass	O
'd	O
away	O
very	O
agreeably	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
better	O
spirits	O
than	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
The	O
Fairy	O
wanted	O
to	O
detain	O
me	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
but	O
I	O
resisted	O
all	O
her	O
persuasions	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
her	O
threats	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
would	O
acquaint	O
You	O
how	O
shamefully	O
I	O
flirted	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Martha	B-pers
.	O
The	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
to	O
talk	O
over	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
heard	O
&	O
whom	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
&	O
parted	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Monday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1785	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
reading	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
this	O
morng	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
postpone	O
telling	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
for	O
a	O
loud	O
rap	O
&	O
is	O
Dr.	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
at	O
home	O
must	O
obliges	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
aside	O
my	O
pen	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
succeſsion	O
of	O
Visitors	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
dreſs	O
,	O
not	O
my	O
head	O
however	O
--	O
&	O
must	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
s	O
i	O
e	O
t	O
out	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
5	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
dine	O
to	O
meet	O
Belle	O
et	O
Beaux	O
Esprits	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
leisure	O
,	O
&	O
poor	O
Wharton	B-pers
must	O
be	O
paſs	O
'd	O
over	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
pity	O
for	O
't	O
is	O
likely	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
clever	O
observations	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
will	O
be	O
irrecoverably	O
lost	O
.	O
A	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
long	O
separate	O
visits	O
.	O
from	O
ye	O
:	O
Rev	O
d	O
.	O
Pope	B-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
very	O
kindly	O
after	O
you	O
--	O
he	O
shook	O
me	O
most	O
heartily	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
hand	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
to	O
ask	O
leave	O
permiſsion	O
of	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
accost	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
manner	O
he	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
Bulstrode	O
--	O
Thos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wharton	I-pers
a	O
worthy	O
&	O
very	O
sensible	O
friend	O
,	O
of	O
mine	O
succeded	O
Dr.	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
I	O
recd	O
.	O
sincere	O
pleasure	O
form	O
her	O
conversation	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
just	O
26	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Winter	O
--	O
She	O
encouraged	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
spirits	O
&	O
not	O
not	O
to	O
mind	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
foolish	O
things	O
people	O
said	O
&	O
to	O
pay	O
no	O
regard	O
to	O
impertinent	O
enquiries	O
--	O
The	O
Priest	O
also	O
&	O
his	O
Son	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Thos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warton	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
pleased	O
wth-	O
my	O
looks	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
a	O
meſsage	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
or	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
countenance	O
to	O
beg	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
gracious	O
&	O
appointed	O
Wednesday	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
stands	O
by	O
Tormenting	O
me	O
“	O
indeed	O
Ma'am	O
You	O
'll	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
--	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
“	O
dark	O
Your	O
things	O
will	O
be	O
pin	O
'd	O
awry	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
if	O
“	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lady	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
look	O
as	O
smart	O
as	O
other	O
“	O
people	O
&	O
you	O
never	O
do	O
one	O
any	O
credit	O
for	O
you	O
never	O
“	O
care	O
or	O
take	O
pains	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Your	O
hair	O
“	O
is	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
delightfully	O
”	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
must	O
“	O
bid	O
You	O
Adieu	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
Tuesday	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
hour	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
--	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
past	O
6	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
quitted	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
Room	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Guests	O
were	O
--	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
Bell	B-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
.	O
Mirander	B-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
Publish	O
Mr	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
life	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Daughter	O
--	O
(	O
my	O
sweet	O
little	O
friend	O
who	O
wrote	O
Cicilia	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
--	O
)	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
A.M	B-pers
(	O
AM	B-pers
s	O
son	O
)	O
The	O
Dinner	O
was	O
an	O
Elegant	O
one	O
&	O
ye-	O
--	O
wines	O
were	O
suitable	O
--	O
Burgundy	O
--	O
Claret	O
Tokay	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
dining	O
Room	O
lighted	O
wth	O
.	O
24	O
wax	O
lights	O
--	O
the	O
new	O
service	O
of	O
Plate	O
also	O
made	O
its	O
appearance	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
addition	O
of	O
Fk	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
the	O
day	O
paſs	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
taste	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Dr	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
B——	I-pers
's	O
conversation	O
--	O
they	O
all	O
rallied	O
me	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
not	O
to	O
offend	O
upon	O
my	O
being	O
avowedly	O
an	O
engaged	O
person	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
honor	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
Notice	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
somewhat	O
of	O
a	O
Coxcomb	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
detest	O
a	O
Coxcomb	O
--	O
Pieta	B-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
very	O
kindly	O
after	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
calls	O
You	O
her	O
dear	O
Blackamoor	O
--	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
again	O
soon	O
.	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Watts	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
precious	O
Miniature	O
Picture	O
of	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
was	O
painted	O
by	O
Master	B-pers
V.	I-pers
Dawson	I-pers
s	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
--	O
he	O
gave	O
100	O
L	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
undoubted	O
original	O
&	O
belonged	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
(	O
the	O
Daughter	O
who	O
served	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
as	O
an	O
Amanuensis	O
(	O
27	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
also	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
an	O
engraving	O
,	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
our	O
Sex	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
of	O
18	O
of	O
this	O
Picture	O
I	O
shall	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
inimitably	O
executed	O
.	O
M	O
r	O
The	B-pers
two	I-pers
Sisters	I-pers
treated	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
reading	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Manuscript	O
&	O
writings	O
--	O
both	O
in	O
Prose	O
&	O
Verse	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
remember	O
wht	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
now	O
to	O
mention	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
Nestor	B-pers
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
infinite	O
wit	O
--	O
though	O
of	O
infamous	O
Morals	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
something	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
that	O
Good	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
had	O
given	O
a	O
Portrait	O
of	O
himself	O
of	O
his	O
Painting	O
--	O
he	O
recollected	O
ye	O
.	O
Picture	O
&	O
very	O
genteely	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
would	O
renovate	O
it	O
with	O
lasting	O
Colors	O
--	O
he	O
also	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
Proof	O
Prints	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Charlotte	B-pers
from	O
his	O
painting	O
's	O
.	O
Though	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
supper	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
they	O
only	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
large	O
folio	O
wth	O
.	O
wht	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
today	O
yesterday	O
but	O
perhaps	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
pleased	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
for	O
so	O
much	O
scribbling	O
This	O
Morning	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Queen	O
Square	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
wth	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
9	O
Beautiful	O
Children	O
graced	O
the	O
Breakfast	O
table	O
--	O
ye	O
eldest	O
13	O
ye	O
youngest	O
1	O
year	O
old	O
--	O
the	O
father	O
&	O
Mother	O
so	O
amiable	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
in	O
such	O
perfect	O
order	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
sight	O
to	O
touch	O
a	O
sensible	O
heart	O
!	O
Their	O
income	O
is	O
a	O
slender	O
one	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
situation	O
in	O
life	O
&	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
family	O
but	O
they	O
happy	O
in	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
&	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
wth	O
:	O
talents	O
&	O
Virtue	O
--	O
educate	O
their	O
lovely	O
offspring	O
seem	O
raised	O
above	O
the	O
petty	O
distreſs	O
's	O
of	O
fortune	O
.	O
how	O
happy	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dear	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
--	O
his	O
Character	O
wd	O
.	O
lead	O
me	O
at	O
present	O
too	O
far	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
reserve	O
it	O
for	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
28	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
who	O
has	O
written	O
on	O
Music	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
write	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
life	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
&	O
to	O
save	O
two	O
Shillings	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Parks	O
home	O
--	O
full	O
2	O
Miles	O
I	O
believe	O
--	O
met	O
one	O
of	O
Baroneſs	B-pers
s	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
civil	O
speeches	O
paſs	O
'd	O
--	O
answering	O
Notes	O
&	O
some	O
confidential	O
converse	O
wth	O
..	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sister	O
--	O
&	O
working	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
Widow	O
Sister	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
private	O
converse	O
--	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
remain	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
The	O
Priest	O
s	O
daughter	O
also	O
came	O
to	O
dine	O
we	O
had	O
Music	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
came	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
&	O
I	O
exerted	O
myself	O
&	O
happily	O
succeeded	O
in	O
amusing	O
Pieta	B-pers
--	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
ye	O
.	O
Wife	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Good	I-pers
Dowgr-	I-pers
&	O
Duchess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
King	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
Snow	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
s	O
spirits	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Stranger	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
but	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
Our	O
Guests	O
staid	O
supper	O
&	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
kind	O
meſsages	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
s	O
friend	O
Wednesday	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
1785	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
stiff	O
&	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
limbs	O
from	O
my	O
long	O
walk	O
of	O
yesterday	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
move	O
a	O
joint	O
--	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
alone	O
--	O
&	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
not	O
ably	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Good	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Wife	O
&	O
Daughter	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
came	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
he	O
sat	O
on	O
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
then	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
promising	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
petitioning	O
for	O
these	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
whilst	O
ye	O
.	O
words	O
seemd	O
to	O
choak	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
really	O
had	O
now	O
brought	O
his	O
mind	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
happy	O
wth-	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
a	O
greater	O
original	O
exists	O
--	O
he	O
also	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
near	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
losing	O
his	O
senses	O
when	O
I	O
prohibited	O
his	O
visits	O
--	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
certainly	O
was	O
near	O
breaking	O
his	O
neck	O
for	O
he	O
fell	O
in	O
to	O
a	O
fit	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
top	O
of	O
my	O
Staircase	O
one	O
day	O
when	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
&	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
luckily	O
been	O
that	O
for	O
my	O
Maid	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
roll	O
'd	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sister	O
&	O
I	O
chatted	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
when	O
Ms	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
dined	O
early	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
yet	O
make	O
visits	O
not	O
being	O
recovered	O
from	O
her	O
Cold	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Woman	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
otherwise	O
than	O
by	O
going	O
before	O
Company	O
came	O
in	O
who	O
might	O
be	O
offended	O
at	O
her	O
not	O
paying	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
attention	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
came	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
were	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
party	O
--	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warton	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
Lord	B-pers
Hartcourt	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Carriage	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
carried	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
home	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Sisters	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
29	O
Thursday	O
13	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
1785	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
wretchedly	O
last	O
night	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
early	O
meſsages	O
of	O
enquiry	O
from	O
those	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
s	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
however	O
very	O
well	O
I	O
think	O
except	O
my	O
poor	O
bones	O
w	O
ch	O
ach	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
resolution	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
&	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
spirits	O
--	O
if	O
People	O
will	O
take	O
into	O
their	O
heads	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
well	O
or	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
Spirits	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
lose	O
all	O
patience	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Now	O
Sir	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
smart	O
breakfast	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
from	O
10	O
oClock	O
till	O
2	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
entertainingd	O
by	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
Edgcomb	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
the	O
two	O
Sister	O
s	O
--	O
Dr-	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
Whitehurst	B-pers
--	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
--	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Party	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
excuses	O
)	O
why	O
must	O
can	O
not	O
You	O
not	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
share	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
sensible	O
&	O
instructive	O
conversation	O
?	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
give	O
You	O
a	O
taste	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
Arts	O
&	O
literary	O
knowledge	O
--	O
what	O
infinite	O
future	O
resources	O
does	O
the	O
Mind	O
obtain	O
by	O
proper	O
early	O
acquisitions	O
.	O
pray	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
do	O
not	O
forget	O
that	O
You	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
Your	O
knowledge	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dead	O
languages	O
&	O
to	O
cultivate	O
Your	O
talents	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
in	O
this	O
request	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
selfish	O
--	O
nor	O
will	O
any	O
request	O
of	O
mine	O
ever	O
be	O
so	O
--	O
tis	O
Your	O
happineſs	O
Your	O
future	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
Yourself	O
that	O
leads	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
anxious	O
that	O
You	O
may	O
may	O
never	O
be	O
sensible	O
a	O
day	O
feel	O
that	O
an	O
hour	O
can	O
hang	O
heavy	O
on	O
Your	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
recommend	O
ed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
say	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
askd	O
a	O
better	O
judge	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
)	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
deserving	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Great	O
encomiums	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
--	O
&	O
also	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
very	O
late	O
publication	O
or	O
rather	O
translation	O
--	O
but	O
those	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
however	O
worth	O
reading	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L——	I-pers
was	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Rochester	O
&	O
You	O
may	O
see	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
writings	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Biographical	O
Dictionary	O
/	O
Octo	O
,	O
/	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
elegant	O
writer	O
--	O
perhaps	O
all	O
this	O
You	O
know	O
better	O
than	O
myself	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
these	O
letters	O
spoke	O
of	O
as	O
something	O
newly	O
