TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
your	O
Note	O
till	O
late	O
this	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
return	O
you	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
my	O
little	O
Creatures	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
their	B-pers
Rl	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hſs	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	I-pers
are	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
want	O
nothing	O
here	O
to	O
make	O
our	O
Séjour	O
delightful	O
,	O
but	O
better	O
Weatheer	O
;	O
the	O
Rain	O
has	O
been	O
almost	O
inceſsant	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
yet	O
has	O
prevented	O
our	O
going	O
once	O
upon	O
the	O
Terrace	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schwellenberg	I-pers
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
remain	O
Ever	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Most	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windſor	B-place
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1779	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
.	O
