TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
5	O
th	O
-	O
May	O
1779	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
honored	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
your	O
excuses	O
are	O
good	O
,	O
grant	O
you	O
a	O
free	O
pardon	O
for	O
your	O
late	O
supposed	O
offences	O
.	O
I	O
hardly	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
walk	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
or	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
having	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
Binning	B-pers
's	O
Marriage	O
,	O
where	O
every	O
thing	O
&	O
every	O
body	O
looked	O
&	O
spoke	O
the	O
happineſs	O
they	O
felt	O
.	O
Ly-	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
was	O
beautiful	O
,	O
affectionate	O
,	O
&	O
overcome	O
with	O
the	O
sincere	O
congratulations	O
she	O
received	O
and	O
this	O
day	O
paſsed	O
thro	O
'	O
Edinr-	B-place
in	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Tynninghome	B-place
Lord	B-pers
Hadinton	I-pers
's	O
Seat	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
follow	O
her	O
next	O
week	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
your	O
nervous	O
fevers	O
--	O
are	O
you	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
Melancholy	O
or	O
Maggoty	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
conversation	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
fail	O
of	O
making	O
you	O
laugh	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
The	O
Locket	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
accompany	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
containing	O
the	O
Quinteſsence	O
of	O
your	O
good	O
Wishes	O
--	O
My	O
Nonchalance	O
is	O
not	O
affected	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
other	O
crotchets	O
in	O
my	O
brain	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
A	O
sincere	O
attachment	O
,	O
even	O
unto	O
Marriage	O
occupies	O
my	O
thoughts	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
secret	O
unknown	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
your	O
Prudence	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
remain	O
so	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
'till	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
agreable	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
One	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
of	O
Noble	O
Alliance	O
,	O
handsome	O
fortune	O
,	O
Amiable	O
temper	O
,	O
&	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
as	O
my	O
friends	O
would	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
connected	O
with	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
plain	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
make	O
proposals	O
but	O
not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
yet	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
confeſs	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
's	O
Marriage	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
effect	O
in	O
hastening	O
Mine	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
Dr	B-pers
Hs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Child	O
should	O
ever	O
inherit	O
my	O
Titles	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
my	O
Sister	O
every	O
good	O
that	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
happen	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Your	O
Affair	O
I	O
delight	O
in	O
,	O
Was	O
Mr-	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
a	O
Widower	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
your	O
humble	O
Admirer	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
pride	O
will	O
be	O
lowered	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
married	O
in	O
America	B-place
to	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
aged	O
16	O
--	O
a	O
Girl	O
--	O
of	O
a	O
Scotch	O
family	O
--	O
Neice	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Sir	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
Elliot	I-pers
--	O
without	O
a	O
sixpence	O
&	O
her	O
father	O
has	O
Nine	O
Children	O
--	O
Ld-	B-pers
C——	I-pers
appears	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
crazy	O
.	O
In	O
himself	O
he	O
will	O
find	O
little	O
to	O
comfort	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
loaded	O
his	O
Estate	O
with	O
Debt	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
contracting	O
&	O
by	O
his	O
marriage	O
perhaps	O
entailed	O
beggary	O
upon	O
his	O
Posterity	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
disagreable	O
Idea	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
drop	O
it	O
--	O
May	O
heavenly	O
Angels	O
their	O
wide	O
wings	O
display	O
,	O
And	O
guard	O
thy	O
Steps	O
in	O
ev'ry	O
dangerous	O
Way	O
,	O
May	O
all	O
thy	O
future	O
days	O
be	O
blest	O
with	O
peace	O
And	O
every	O
hour	O
,	O
fresh	O
springs	O
of	O
Joy	O
increase	O
,	O
In	O
every	O
state	O
may	O
you	O
most	O
happy	O
be	O
,	O
And	O
when	O
far	O
distant	O
off	O
,	O
pray	O
think	O
of	O
me	O
Yours	O
sincerely	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
hint	O
about	O
the	O
frank	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
