TOKEN	NE
Copy	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
My	O
Dearest	O
Madam	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
a	O
Pavilion	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Nuns	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
which	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
brought	O
over	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
.	O
If	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
conveyed	O
to	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
&	O
placed	O
in	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
large	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
did	O
not	O
object	O
to	O
Her	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
receiving	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
present	O
from	O
Miſs	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Your	O
sincere	O
&	O
affte	O
Friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
March	O
1783	O
