TOKEN	NE
The	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Murrays	I-pers
think	O
themselves	O
very	O
unlucky	O
to	O
have	O
miſsed	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
t	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
Day	O
,	O
are	O
very	O
particularly	O
engaged	O
to	O
morrow	O
&	O
Friday	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
immediately	O
return	O
this	O
obliging	O
Visit	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
shew	O
their	O
pretty	O
Gallery	O
to	O
their	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
wait	O
upon	O
them	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
whichever	O
is	O
most	O
Agreeable	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
Evening	O
