TOKEN	NE
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
30	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
:	O
1787	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
Janry	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
We	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
happy	O
news	O
on	O
Saturday	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
being	O
safely	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
sincerely	O
congratulating	O
my	O
dear	O
brother	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lenton	I-pers
unites	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
will	O
answer	O
for	O
herself	O
as	O
she	O
intends	O
writing	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
;	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
so	O
anxious	O
,	O
so	O
busy	O
&	O
so	O
happy	O
;	O
walking	O
tip	O
toe	O
into	O
your	O
wive	O
s	O
Apartment	O
,	O
asking	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
tenderneſs	O
how	O
she	O
has	O
rested	O
,	O
peeping	O
at	O
the	O
little	O
brat	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
awake	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
your	O
arms	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
trying	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
it	O
is	O
like	O
&	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
hurting	O
it	O
return	O
it	O
with	O
such	O
care	O
into	O
the	O
nurses	O
arms	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
too	O
young	O
at	O
present	O
to	O
sing	O
“	O
lull	O
a	O
by	O
baby	O
”	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
amuse	O
myself	O
in	O
thinking	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
Alas	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
too	O
good	O
health	O
to	O
want	O
the	O
waters	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
too	O
very	O
dear	O
friends	O
&	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
though	O
a	O
stranger	O
I	O
will	O
love	O
for	O
there	O
sakes	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
conclude	O
my	O
letter	O
with	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
advice	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
Friends	O
of	O
all	O
lying	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
ten	O
days	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
quite	O
quiet	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
even	O
the	O
husband	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
with	O
her	O
without	O
he	O
can	O
hold	O
his	O
tongue	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
talking	O
that	O
fatigues	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
her	O
present	O
weak	O
condition	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
to	O
suffer	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
friends	O
to	O
soon	O
;	O
thus	O
much	O
for	O
my	O
dearest	O
father	O
s	O
advice	O
,	O
now	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
saucineſs	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
with	O
your	O
Mary	B-pers
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
can	O
neither	O
of	O
you	O
help	O
talking	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
together	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
spirits	O
being	O
remarkably	O
good	O
it	O
may	O
fatigue	O
her	O
more	O
that	O
she	O
or	O
you	O
think	O
s	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
My	O
love	O
to	O
your	O
excellent	O
wife	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
's	O
best	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
both	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
yr	O
.	O
Oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
&	O
Sister	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
am	O
prevented	O
from	O
going	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
hooping	O
cough	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
most	O
sincere	O
congratulations	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
happy	O
event	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
anxious	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
seven	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
our	O
young	O
friend	O
;	O
nothing	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
Equal	O
pleasure	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
your	O
Dear	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
with	O
her	O
sweet	O
Babe	O
upon	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
She	O
knows	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
both	O
;	O
&	O
may	O
every	O
bleſsing	O
attend	O
the	O
happy	O
pair	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
your	O
Days	O
.	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
NB	O
:	O
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
She	O
will	O
give	O
all	O
her	O
kind	O
attentions	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
three	O
notes	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
frank	O
from	O
Miss	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
and	O
hopes	O
that	O
her	O
cough	O
will	O
not	O
at	O
last	O
prove	O
the	O
hooping	O
Cough	O
.	O
The	O
Athenaid	O
is	O
begun	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
first	O
sheet	O
it	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
has	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
yr	O
.	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
again	O
join	O
in	O
congratulations	O
,	O
your	O
letter	O
is	O
written	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
feeling	O
&	O
warmth	O
of	O
affection	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
women	O
that	O
it	O
brought	O
tears	O
of	O
joy	O
into	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
&	O
so	O
is	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
good	O
Mother	O
that	O
our	O
amiable	O
Miranda	B-pers
is	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
may	O
the	O
lovely	O
innocent	O
add	O
every	O
day	O
more	O
happineſs	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
may	O
she	O
grow	O
up	O
&	O
be	O
a	O
bleſsing	O
to	O
her	O
excellent	O
Father	O
&	O
Mother	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
Man	O
you	O
deserve	O
the	O
wife	O
you	O
poſseſs	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
our	O
ardent	O
prayer	O
s	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
live	O
many	O
many	O
years	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
belov	O
'd	O
society	O
of	O
Each	O
other	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
so	O
many	O
blunders	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
this	O
sheet	O
.	O
