TOKEN	NE
July	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1782	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
Your	O
dear	O
letter	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
one	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
written	O
--	O
let	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
oblivion	O
be	O
paſs	O
'd	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
my	O
present	O
aſsurances	O
that	O
I	O
harbour	O
not	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
Your	O
affection	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
shock	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
every	O
proper	O
precaution	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
fresh	O
cold	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
riding	O
on	O
Horseback	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
You	O
,	O
gentle	O
exercise	O
without	O
fatigue	O
will	O
restore	O
your	O
strenght	O
better	O
than	O
medicines	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
melancholy	O
situation	O
indeed	O
!	O
surrounded	O
by	O
Invalids	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
hear	O
You	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
again	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
no	O
more	O
complaints	O
of	O
depreſsion	O
of	O
Spirits	O
.	O
--	O
Hero	B-pers
is	O
expected	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
whisper	O
'd	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Fairford	I-pers
means	O
to	O
propose	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
this	O
from	O
any	O
good	O
authority	O
.	O
Rhea	B-pers
's	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
never	O
look	O
'd	O
better	O
.	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
came	O
here	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Dinner	O
&	O
stays	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
no	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
do	O
I	O
enjoy	O
from	O
her	O
being	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
Roof	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
but	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
I	O
wish	O
a	O
certain	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
come	O
so	O
regularly	O
upon	O
the	O
T——	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
lose	O
their	O
own	O
consequence	O
in	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
on	O
Saty	O
.	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
You	O
were	O
so	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
inclose	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
Your	O
amusement	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
return	O
it	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
person	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Adieu	O
for	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
perceive	O
written	O
in	O
haste	O
Ever	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
Perfecta	B-pers
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Horton	B-place
Newport	B-place
Pagnel	I-place
Bucks	B-place
Free	O
Wake	O
