TOKEN	NE
A	O
good	O
part	O
typed	O
Taxal	B-place
Janry	O
:	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
1775	O
It	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
after	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
Silence	O
,	O
especiall	O
y	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Miscarriage	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
recd	O
.	O
&	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
your	O
having	O
forgot	O
me	O
.	O
had	O
this	O
been	O
the	O
case	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
in	O
reality	O
have	O
blamed	O
you	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
conscious	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
improper	O
Correspondent	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
Age	O
.	O
&	O
:	O
but	O
your	O
obliging	O
partiality	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
at	O
Northn	B-place
:	I-place
made	O
me	O
vain	O
enough	O
to	O
hope	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
totally	O
forget	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
mistaken	O
.	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Spring	O
&	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
uncomforable	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
.	O
&	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
little	O
hopes	O
of	O
surviving	O
it	O
.	O
&	O
poor	O
Sally	B-pers
was	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
dangerous	O
Situation	O
,	O
from	O
with	O
the	O
Measles	O
.	O
Thank	O
God	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
got	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
born	O
the	O
Winter	O
hitherto	O
.	O
beyond	O
my	O
Expectations	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Month	O
this	O
Summer	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
.	O
&	O
think	O
I	O
found	O
great	O
benefit	O
.	O
my	O
Chief	O
Complaint	O
was	O
Rhuematism	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
brought	O
me	O
so	O
very	O
weak	O
,	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
thin	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
coud	O
almost	O
ve	O
n	O
ture	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
without	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
you	O
.	O
Is	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
ever	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Rhuematism	O
?	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
Buxton	B-place
is	O
the	O
only	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
for	O
her	O
there	O
is	O
often	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
Company	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
good	O
you	O
may	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
there	O
,	O
very	O
agreeably	O
,	O
&	O
Matlock	B-place
(	O
which	O
most	O
People	O
go	O
to	O
after	O
bathing	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
)	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
pretty	O
romantic	O
Place	O
.	O
this	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
Wonders	O
of	O
the	O
Peak	O
)	O
wou	O
'd	O
entertain	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Summers	O
Excursion	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
then	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
without	O
the	O
Intention	O
at	O
least	O
of	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
visiting	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
I	O
think	O
be	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
Mr	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
to	O
return	O
my	O
Visit	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
angry	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
:	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
that	O
Gent	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
shoud	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
favour	O
if	O
you	O
woud	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
I	O
did	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
intend	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
soon	O
.	O
&	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
young	O
Friend	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
you	O
have	O
spent	O
your	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
?	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
coud	O
not	O
be	O
Idle	O
?	O
have	O
you	O
pursued	O
your	O
Latin	O
?	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
chief	O
Employment	O
?	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
learnt	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
performances	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
natural	O
Genious	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Sally	B-pers
begs	O
you	O
will	O
indulge	O
her	O
with	O
something	O
of	O
your	O
doing	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
be	O
but	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
most	O
affect	O
:	O
regards	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
she	O
still	O
remembers	O
with	O
gratitude	O
the	O
great	O
Civilities	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
your	O
old	O
Friend	O
Jack	B-pers
is	O
now	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
th	O
e	O
days	O
&	O
desires	O
his	O
Compts	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
happily	O
fix	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
worthy	O
Clergiman	O
near	O
Derby	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
great	O
Sen	O
s	O
e	O
&	O
Learning	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
takes	O
4	O
boarders	O
;	O
&	O
whose	O
behaviour	O
is	O
so	O
agreeable	O
to	O
Jack	B-pers
that	O
he	O
pursues	O
his	O
Studies	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
we	O
coud	O
wish	O
him	O
I	O
really	O
find	O
my	O
self	O
incapable	O
of	O
drawing	O
a	O
Character	O
which	O
woud	O
do	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
justice	O
to	O
the	O
Friend	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
deserving	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
towards	O
the	O
performance	O
of	O
my	O
promise	O
is	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
her	O
Letters	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
Idea	O
of	O
the	O
Beauties	O
of	O
her	O
Mind	O
her	O
Person	O
(	O
when	O
young	O
)	O
was	O
very	O
handsome	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
least	O
Perfection	O
.	O
my	O
Eyes	O
are	O
grown	O
extreamly	O
weak	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
letters	O
for	O
one	O
.	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
footing	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
dare	O
venture	O
to	O
correspond	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
favour	O
to	O
expect	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
in	O
return	O
but	O
the	O
sincere	O
regard	O
of	O
Your	O
Affect	O
&	O
obliged	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
joynes	O
with	O
us	O
all	O
in	O
wishing	O
you	O
the	O
Compts	O
:	O
of	O
the	O
Season	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
Calling	O
this	O
mo	O
at	O
Ab	O
&	O
understanding	O
your	O
