TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
a	O
Meſsenger	O
from	O
Bullstrode	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
also	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
interest	O
you	O
take	O
in	O
what	O
concerns	O
me	O
so	O
nearly	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
little	O
Grand	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
hope	O
she	O
may	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
troublesome	O
Complaints	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
herself	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
Comfort	O
about	O
it	O
by	O
instancing	O
an	O
almost	O
similar	O
Complaint	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
outgrown	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
is	O
not	O
here	O
but	O
Harriet	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
Compliments	O
to	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
Sunday	O
Morng	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
