TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
--	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Tuesday	O
near	O
three	O
March	O
28	O
th	O
1780	O
Many	O
thanks	O
my	O
Dearest	O
for	O
your	O
wellcome	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
my	O
Dear	O
little	O
Patient	O
has	O
given	O
you	O
such	O
an	O
Alarm	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
however	O
to	O
find	O
hear	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
sincerly	O
pray	O
H	B-pers
R	I-pers
H	I-pers
may	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
dr	O
aw	O
backs	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nobody	O
that	O
deserves	O
Health	O
more	O
thorough	O
,	O
for	O
nobody	O
is	O
more	O
patient	O
in	O
Sickneſs	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
affectionate	O
Duty	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
thoughts	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
very	O
much	O
the	O
leaving	O
her	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
want	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
felt	O
I	O
miſsed	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
still	O
do	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
Hunting	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Stag	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
two	O
hours	O
&	O
a	O
half	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
left	O
the	O
Hunters	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
's	O
,	O
returned	O
home	O
at	O
near	O
4	O
,	O
dined	O
at	O
6	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
upstairs	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Seven	O
with	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
at	O
8	O
&	O
then	O
spent	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Evg	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
agreable	O
manner	O
,	O
this	O
Morg	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
the	O
two	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
P	B-pers
William	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
escorted	O
by	O
King	B-pers
&	O
two	O
Princes	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Harleyford	B-place
,	O
they	O
bring	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
De	O
ar	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
,	O
&	O
comforted	O
myself	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Walk	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
Chevaliers	O
,	O
Genl	B-pers
Budé	I-pers
&	O
Col.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
,	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
red	O
yr	O
Letter	O
am	O
dreſsed	O
&	O
ready	O
to	O
walk	O
down	O
Stairs	O
&	O
begin	O
the	O
usual	O
busineſs	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
fai	O
thful	O
narrative	O
my	O
Dear	O
Child	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
must	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
to	O
your	O
penetration	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Love	O
to	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
&	O
Duty	O
to	O
the	O
Dear	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MC	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
both	O
Evgs	O
but	O
no	O
Cards	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
