TOKEN	NE
Loughboro	B-place
'	I-place
Sunday	O
Evg	O
19	O
--	O
March	O
1786	O
Now	O
my	O
dearest	O
Wife	O
I	O
begin	O
another	O
journal	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
dull	O
&	O
uninteresting	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
little	O
else	O
than	O
mere	O
Matter	O
of	O
fact	O
to	O
write	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
variation	O
of	O
that	O
--	O
You	O
my	O
Love	O
have	O
a	O
warm	O
interest	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
concerns	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
trifles	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
unacceptable	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Your	O
excellent	O
heart	O
will	O
inform	O
you	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
concern	O
I	O
feel	O
at	O
any	O
Separation	O
from	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
so	O
sincerely	O
love	O
&	O
esteem	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
D——	B-pers
will	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Racket	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Feveret	O
--	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
how	O
I	O
pity	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
sadly	O
tormented	O
by	O
that	O
Madcap	O
--	O
Dr-	B-pers
Heberden	I-pers
has	O
been	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Complaint	O
was	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Vagar	O
y	O
i	O
e	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
I	O
jogged	O
on	O
thro	O
dirty	O
roads	O
and	O
over	O
hard	O
pavements	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
forty	O
nine	O
Miles	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
Oh	O
how	O
I	O
miſs	O
your	O
charming	O
Saucineſses	O
--	O
dont	O
you	O
sometimes	O
wish	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
yr-	O
Elbow	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
tres	O
tres	O
chere	O
femme	O
Je	O
vous	O
aime	O
avec	O
tout	O
mon	O
cœur	O
--	O
bon	O
soir	O
mon	O
Amour	O
