TOKEN	NE
Burley	B-place
Decr	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1777	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Though	O
Ht	B-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
talked	O
of	O
writing	O
this	O
post	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
began	O
her	O
Letter	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
has	O
so	O
often	O
happened	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
fail	O
of	O
having	O
it	O
ready	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
telling	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Mother	O
arrived	O
well	O
&	O
happily	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
found	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
a	O
very	O
joyful	O
Houſe	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
commiſsioned	O
Ht	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
enclose	O
a	O
Little	O
Drawing	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
attempting	O
in	O
Water	O
Colours	O
&	O
Chalk	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Tapestry	O
here	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
really	O
not	O
worth	O
yr	O
.	O
acceptance	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
size	O
wd	O
.	O
suit	O
your	O
little	O
book	O
,	O
however	O
as	O
little	O
valuable	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
thinks	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
entirely	O
spoiled	O
in	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
hope	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
you	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
some	O
comfortable	O
meetings	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
charged	O
with	O
many	O
kind	O
Meſsages	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
promises	O
not	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
too	O
young	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
her	O
too	O
old	O
--	O
my	O
time	O
will	O
never	O
allow	O
of	O
making	O
you	O
proper	O
Compliments	O
of	O
Congratulation	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
Condolence	O
on	O
Publick	O
&	O
Private	O
Events	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
employ	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
in	O
begging	O
More	O
kindest	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
accept	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
all	O
at	O
Burley	O
&	O
particularly	O
of	O
from	O
yr	O
.	O
own	O
Child	O
who	O
has	O
now	O
learnt	O
to	O
say	O
Yes	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
loves	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
got	O
on	O
a	O
dangerous	O
subject	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
haste	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
really	O
quit	O
it	O
at	O
once	O
&	O
only	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
most	O
sincerely	O
&	O
faithfully	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Sophia	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
