TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
They	O
have	O
prevail	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
Party	O
to	O
Hammersmith	B-place
to	O
convey	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
there	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
Evening	O
is	O
so	O
fine	O
that	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
will	O
hardly	O
come	O
in	O
long	O
before	O
their	O
bed	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
excuse	O
me	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
back	O
before	O
their	B-pers
Majestys	I-pers
return	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
say	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
gone	O
.	O
Ever	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C.Finch	B-pers
7	O
o'Clock	O
Wednesday	O
Evening	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
