TOKEN	NE
Bourdeaux	B-place
Novr	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
To	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
only	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
kind	O
,	O
&	O
entertaining	O
a	O
Letter	O
as	O
that	O
I	O
recd	O
from	O
you	O
at	O
Madrid	B-place
,	O
I	O
'm	O
afraid	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
appear	O
but	O
unworthy	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
yet	O
the	O
hurry	O
I	O
write	O
in	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
but	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
would	O
excuse	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
few	O
words	O
therefore	O
be	O
aſsured	O
it	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
every	O
Sense	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
very	O
sincerely	O
all	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
friendship	O
,	O
&	O
value	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
deserves	O
.	O
Your	O
Envelope	O
contain	O
'd	O
an	O
Inestimable	O
Treasure	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dear	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
gracious	O
remembrance	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
handwriting	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
distance	O
between	O
the	O
Lines	O
allow	O
'd	O
of	O
dividing	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
Harriet	B-pers
&	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
variance	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
our	O
Lives	O
about	O
the	O
Poſseſsion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
pray	O
with	O
the	O
Grateful	O
Duties	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
tell	O
his	O
Royl	O
Highneſs	O
how	O
happy	O
he	O
made	O
us	O
;	O
Harriet	B-pers
is	O
to	O
Speak	O
for	O
herself	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
this	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
just	O
mention	O
without	O
entering	O
into	O
the	O
Detail	O
of	O
our	O
Journey	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
fortune	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
at	O
Madrid	B-place
,	O
&	O
to	O
continue	O
our	O
travels	O
together	O
all	O
thrō	O
Spain	B-place
to	O
Bayonne	B-place
where	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
they	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Toulouſe	B-place
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
where	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
will	O
join	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
leave	O
Bordeaux	B-place
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
bore	O
all	O
her	O
fatigues	O
vastly	O
well	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
thō	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
for	O
long	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
expect	O
to	O
ſee	O
me	O
ſoon	O
after	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
,	O
in	O
ye	O
mean	O
while	O
believe	O
me	O
Most	O
Affly	O
.	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Yours	O
C	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Bourdeaux	B-place
Novr	O
.	O
19	O
My	O
dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
It	O
seems	O
very	O
ungracious	O
,	O
to	O
begin	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
addreſs	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
without	O
seeing	O
,	O
or	O
Speaking	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Paper	O
--	O
&	O
yet	O
can	O
not	O
receive	O
such	O
a	O
Little	O
Note	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
on	O
my	O
Arrival	O
at	O
Madrid	B-place
;	O
&	O
not	O
intreat	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
from	O
me	O
--	O
How	O
much	O
I	O
th	O
ought	O
myself	O
honor	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Remembrance	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
enter	O
most	O
heartily	O
into	O
ye	O
Plan	O
of	O
Returning	O
to	O
dear	O
England	B-place
--	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
too	O
many	O
Friends	O
,	O
&	O
Amusements	O
,	O
&	O
intreating	O
Concerns	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
anxious	O
to	O
revisit	O
&	O
re	O
enter	O
into	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
however	O
sing	O
ye	O
Praises	O
of	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
Countries	O
I	O
have	O
Visited	O
(	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
own	O
)	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
One	O
,	O
of	O
Which	O
I	O
am	O
More	O
A	O
E	O
pris	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
ye	O
Charming	O
little	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Portugal	B-place
--	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
itself	O
Charming	O
But	O
its	O
Natives	O
are	O
ye	O
first	O
People	O
in	O
ye	O
World	O
--	O
&	O
talk	O
ye	O
most	O
delightful	O
Language	O
poſsible	O
--	O
They	O
are	O
likewise	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Hue	O
--	O
But	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
ye	O
Chev	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pinto	I-pers
--	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
England	B-place
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
quitted	O
that	O
little	O
Paradis	O
terrestre	O
--	O
Believe	O
me	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
could	O
say	O
a	O
great	O
Deal	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
but	O
have	O
really	O
not	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
&	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
may	O
sometimes	O
be	O
really	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
't	O
is	O
often	O
only	O
an	O
Excuse	O
But	O
in	O
time	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
part	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
Memoirs	O
when	O
i	O
ts	O
n	O
this	O
Part	O
of	O
ye	O
World	O
,	O
that	O
may	O
amuse	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
News	O
from	O
your	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
many	O
Marriages	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
left	O
to	O
amuse	O
me	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
Bp	I-pers
of	I-pers
Durham	I-pers
I	O
quite	O
Rejoice	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
will	O
no	O
longer	O
be	O
neceſsitated	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
ye	O
Crumbs	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
s	O
Table	O
--	O
But	O
still	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
being	O
amused	O
with	O
the	O
Idea	O
of	O
Made	B-pers
L'Ebegue	I-pers
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
envy	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thynne	I-pers
my	O
little	O
Ugly	O
Cousin	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
really	O
could	O
write	O
on	O
a	O
Great	O
deal	O
more	O
--	O
Altho	O
'	O
you	O
have	O
never	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
Single	O
Line	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
parted	O
:	O
but	O
once	O
more	O
adieu	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
obliged	O
&	O
muita	O
Sua	O
Amiga	O
Enriqueta	B-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
London	B-place
Angleterre	B-place
via	O
Ostende	B-place
