TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
decbr	O
.	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1800	O
Many	O
Thanks	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
yr	O
kind	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Note	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
pretty	O
little	O
bird	O
you	O
sent	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
this	O
morning	O
from	O
my	O
beloved	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
writes	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
a	O
Charming	O
Letter	O
from	O
her	O
now	O
dear	O
Dicky	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
fears	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
tempted	O
to	O
Answer	O
it	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
but	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
happen	O
in	O
this	O
Century	O
--	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
favor	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
my	O
Letters	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Str	O
Scratch	O
over	O
Wing	B-place
--	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
.	O
&	O
direct	O
them	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
John	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
's	O
Nevsells	O
Newsells	O
,	O
Royston	B-place
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
a	O
Member	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
.	O
for	O
indeed	O
the	O
more	O
we	O
know	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
we	O
(	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
write	O
)	O
delight	O
in	O
yr	O
friendship	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
have	O
his	O
Present	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Harriet	B-pers
can	O
procure	O
it	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
needed	O
not	O
to	O
to	O
put	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
mind	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
for	O
Lou	B-pers
who	O
I	O
trust	O
in	O
God	O
will	O
amply	O
recompense	O
the	O
virtuous	O
care	O
you	O
take	O
of	O
her	O
Education	O
,	O
her	O
Principles	O
she	O
inherits	O
--	O
or	O
she	O
wd	O
be	O
very	O
Unlucky	O
--	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
.	O
but	O
God	O
only	O
knows	O
what	O
how	O
the	O
change	O
from	O
Solitude	O
.	O
to	O
Society	O
,	O
may	O
affect	O
my	O
disorder	O
'd	O
Spirrits	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
support	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
any	O
new	O
trials	O
--	O
perhaps	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
fool	O
in	O
keeping	O
poor	O
Anne	B-pers
,	O
&	O
most	O
likely	O
every	O
body	O
thinks	O
so	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
such	O
apparent	O
Heartfelt	O
Greif	O
--	O
United	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
partiality	O
to	O
the	O
Object	O
--	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
also	O
to	O
suffer	O
my	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
yr	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
orders	O
with	O
Baily	B-pers
to	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
letters	O
.	O
kind	O
love	O
.	O
concludes	O
me	O
ever	O
&	O
Affcly	O
yrs	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
