TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
much	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
Clerk	O
has	O
neglected	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
your	O
annual	O
Remittance	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
before	O
he	O
sat	O
out	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
near	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
my	O
Rents	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
with	O
his	O
Account	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
your	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
are	O
expreſsly	O
charged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
immediately	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Balfour	I-pers
to	O
have	O
this	O
Error	O
rectified	O
;	O
if	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
nephew	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
his	O
Executor	O
,	O
is	O
returned	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
the	O
busineſs	O
will	O
be	O
soon	O
settled	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
will	O
desire	O
Mr.	B-pers
Balfour	I-pers
to	O
be	O
punctual	O
in	O
sending	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
great	O
goodneſ	O
in	O
mentioning	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Great	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
exposed	O
yourself	O
to	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
giving	O
offence	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
aſsured	O
you	O
I	O
meant	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
always	O
find	O
me	O
a	O
safe	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
never	O
expose	O
you	O
to	O
any	O
hazards	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
;	O
nothing	O
is	O
in	O
these	O
times	O
obtain	O
'd	O
but	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
barter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
certainly	O
well	O
founded	O
pretensions	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
urge	O
them	O
further	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
S_ts	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
contemptible	O
Persons	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
paſsing	O
my	O
window	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
he	O
landed	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
subject	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
he	O
retains	O
the	O
impreſsions	O
you	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
good	O
Terms	O
where	O
you	O
mention	O
you	O
was	O
certainly	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
critical	O
situation	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
Latour	O
is	O
now	O
extremely	O
beautiful	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
still	O
cold	O
&	O
unfavourable	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
Jane	B-pers
improves	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
really	O
great	O
abilities	O
&	O
sufficient	O
steadineſs	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
removed	O
my	O
Son	O
from	O
the	O
School	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
&	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
determined	O
where	O
to	O
place	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
handsome	O
Boy	O
with	O
very	O
good	O
dispositions	O
but	O
backward	O
for	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
perfectly	O
strong	O
&	O
healthy	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
with	O
proper	O
management	O
recover	O
his	O
lost	O
time	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Latour	O
,	O
near	O
Clontarf	B-place
--	O
Dublin	B-place
June	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
