TOKEN	NE
Wolverton	B-place
Decr	O
30	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
informing	O
you	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
safely	O
delivered	O
of	O
another	O
Daughter	O
both	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
obey	O
your	O
commands	O
by	O
meeting	O
you	O
at	O
Woburn	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
happy	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
Neice	O
Lady	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
much	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
s	O
satisfaction	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
kindly	O
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
tie	O
the	O
knot	O
I	O
readily	O
obey	O
the	O
summons	O
&	O
shall	O
soon	O
be	O
at	O
Dunkeld	B-place
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
only	O
add	O
kind	O
regards	O
to	O
yours	O
&	O
Ever	O
am	O
your	O
Affect	O
Cousin	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzard	I-place
