TOKEN	NE
50	O
Mortimer	O
Street	O
,	O
London	B-place
.	O
June	O
8	O
th	O
:	O
1809	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
apprehensive	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
long	O
silence	O
,	O
that	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
and	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
my	O
fears	O
were	O
just	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
lately	O
returned	O
from	O
making	O
a	O
visit	O
of	O
eight	O
weeks	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
time	O
was	O
approaching	O
when	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
saying	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
coming	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
season	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
recovered	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
the	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
long	O
visit	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Father	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
poor	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
that	O
it	O
so	O
happened	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Both	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
were	O
very	O
attentive	O
in	O
writing	O
him	O
preparatory	O
letters	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
illneſs	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
quit	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
:	O
a	O
removal	O
he	O
dreads	O
(	O
very	O
naturally	O
)	O
as	O
a	O
serious	O
operation	O
.	O
Were	O
it	O
not	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
spend	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
circumstance	O
at	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
much	O
rejoice	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Herefordshire	B-place
,	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
with	O
translating	O
into	O
English	O
Blank	O
Verse	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tragedies	O
of	O
Count	B-pers
Alfieri	I-pers
;	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
is	O
what	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
alludes	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
heard	O
me	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
manuscript	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
people	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
lent	O
it	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Peploe	I-pers
,	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
from	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
indebted	O
for	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
Alfieri	B-pers
's	O
Works	O
in	O
their	O
original	O
language	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
read	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
“	O
Cottagers	O
of	O
Glenburnie	O
”	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
on	O
your	O
recommendation	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
“	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
Modern	O
Philosophers	O
”	O
,	O
very	O
clever	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
no	O
relation	O
,	O
though	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
writing	O
is	O
become	O
troublesome	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
would	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
,	O
have	O
had	O
tidings	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
two	O
Concerts	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
a	O
private	O
one	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wroughton	I-pers
's	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Rauzzini	I-pers
's	O
Benefit	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Rooms	I-place
;	O
at	O
which	O
latter	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Braham	I-pers
and	O
Madame	B-pers
Catalani	I-pers
sung	O
:	O
I	O
need	O
add	O
no	O
praise	O
to	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
has	O
not	O
heard	O
Mad	B-pers
:	I-pers
Catalani	I-pers
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
crouds	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
play	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
once	O
since	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
's	O
farewell	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
36	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
profeſsion	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
leaving	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
by	O
many	O
degrees	O
,	O
his	O
equal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Stage	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
much	O
agitated	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
--	O
Covent-Garden	O
new	O
Theatre	O
,	O
will	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
,	O
positively	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
about	O
rebuilding	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
B——	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
Sad	O
work	O
indeed	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
justly	O
observe	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
paſsing	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
moral	O
and	O
political	O
world	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
of	O
to-day	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
states	O
,	O
that	O
Bonaparte	B-pers
has	O
experienced	O
a	O
defeat	O
on	O
the	O
Banks	O
of	O
the	O
Danube	B-place
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
How	O
come	O
the	O
De	O
Salis	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
Count	O
and	O
Counteſs	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
inheritance	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
soon	O
seeing	O
,	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
some	O
Irish	O
friends	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
They	O
went	O
thence	O
to	O
Cheltenham	B-place
;	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Daughters	O
is	O
married	O
,	O
en	O
paſsant	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
those	O
quick	O
elections	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
sincerely	O
interested	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
off	O
now	O
,	O
having	O
scrawled	O
over	O
all	O
my	O
paper	O
.	O
Very	O
truly	O
yours	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Single	O
