TOKEN	NE
Tuesday	O
morning	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1776	O
--	O
between	O
7	O
&	O
8	O
--	O
left	O
my	O
Drst-	O
mama	O
to	O
accompany	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
Spa	B-place
--	O
&	O
c	O
In	O
ye	O
coach	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
son	O
(	O
--	O
abt	O
17/	O
by	O
his	O
first	O
wife	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
--	O
Dined	O
at	O
Rochester	B-place
were	O
joind	O
by	O
Master	B-pers
Penns	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Tutor	O
--	O
oldest	O
age	O
16	O
youngest	O
14	O
.	O
--	O
Slept	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
Sunday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
--	O
Foster	B-pers
Dover	B-place
.	O
Thursday	O
night	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mr.	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
--	O
I	O
write	O
these	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
Dover	B-place
where	O
we	O
are	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
fair	O
wind	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mama	B-pers
from	O
Canterbury	B-place
where	O
we	O
got	O
safe	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
eveg	O
.	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
observation	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
in	O
its	O
Eclipse	O
its	O
appearance	O
I	O
thought	O
very	O
extroadinary	O
&	O
singular	O
;	O
not	O
remembering	O
ever	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
that	O
redneſs	O
or	O
blood	O
color	O
.	O
We	O
breakfasted	O
this	O
Morng	O
..	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
&	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
person	O
in	O
company	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
&	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
all	O
goodneſs	O
&	O
attention	O
,	O
wld-	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
Canterbury	B-place
without	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
this	O
Noble	O
structure	O
(	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
those	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
Salisbury	B-place
&	O
St.	B-place
Albans	I-place
--	O
plain	O
--	O
--	O
elegant	O
--	O
vast	O
in	O
size	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
for	O
particular	O
discreptions	O
--	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Dover	B-place
abt	O
.	O
1	O
o'clock	O
--	O
The	O
corn	O
fields	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
agreeable	O
objects	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
stalks	O
loaded	O
with	O
golden	O
grain	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
Harvest	O
--	O
the	O
fields	O
were	O
quite	O
luxuriant	O
--	O
the	O
Hops	O
also	O
in	O
their	O
most	O
beautiful	O
state	O
.	O
At	O
our	O
arrival	O
at	O
Dover	B-place
met	O
the	O
celebrated	O
&	O
amiable	O
Ldy	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
who	O
came	O
from	O
Deal	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
resides	O
in	O
Summer	O
,	O
(	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
miles	O
frm	O
.	O
hence	O
)	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
an	O
Irish	O
lady	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
me	O
mention	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
they	O
remained	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
carriages	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
Board	O
ye	O
Packet	O
but	O
the	O
Wind	O
&	O
Tide	O
were	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
steep	O
Hill	O
to	O
Dover	O
Castle	O
.	O
30	O
Acres	O
of	O
Land	O
are	O
inclosed	O
within	O
its	O
walls	O
;	O
The	O
walls	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
Tower	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
*	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
are	O
remaining	O
--	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
its	O
their	O
preservation	O
was	O
of	O
consequence	O
to	O
the	O
Curate	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
entitled	O
to	O
30	O
£	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
they	O
stand	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Round	O
Tower	O
close	O
to	O
these	O
walls	O
wch	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
times	O
of	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
had	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Bells	O
therefore	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
the	O
Belfrey	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
Julius	B-pers
Cæsar	I-pers
,	O
Julius	B-pers
Cæsar	I-pers
,	O
after	O
obtaining	O
a	O
victory	O
,	O
desired	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
Bells	O
to	O
Portsmouth	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
now	O
are	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
400	O
men	O
on	O
Garrison	O
at	O
Dover	O
--	O
Castle	O
--	O
the	O
Barracks	O
are	O
neat	O
and	O
comfortable	O
.	O
The	O
Well	O
which	O
was	O
sunk	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
is	O
360	O
feet	O
deep	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
enclosed	O
within	O
a	O
building	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
is	O
drawn	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
large	O
Wheel	O
turned	O
by	O
6	O
men	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
always	O
20	O
feet	O
water	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
echo	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
pin	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
distinctly	O
heard	O
,	O
--	O
a	O
stone	O
thrown	O
in	O
when	O
it	O
reaches	O
the	O
Water	O
sounds	O
like	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
--	O
the	O
noise	O
encreasing	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
thrown	O
down	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
bricked	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
feet	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Well	O
is	O
is	O
formed	O
by	O
a	O
fine	O
chalk	O
Cliff	O
:	O
They	O
also	O
shewed	O
us	O
an	O
immense	O
Cannon	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
call	O
Admiral	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
's	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
.	O
that	O
men	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
well	O
without	O
proving	O
any	O
inconvenience	O
from	O
damp	O
air	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Governors	O
apartments	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
&	O
spent	O
the	O
Eveg	O
most	O
sociably	O
and	O
cheerfully	O
--	O
the	O
youths	O
of	O
our	O
party	O
are	O
equally	O
agreeable	O
as	O
sensible	O
.	O
Thursday	O
Morg	O
.	O
Wind	O
still	O
contrary	O
--	O
the	O
Captain	O
says	O
that	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
but	O
Julius	B-pers
Cæsar	I-pers
's	O
apprehensions	O
and	O
dread	O
of	O
Sickneſs	O
,	O
from	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
suffers	O
so	O
severely	O
,	O
makes	O
us	O
young	O
folk	O
patient	O
notwithstanding	O
our	O
eagerneſs	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
acroſs	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
(	O
Queen	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
with	O
his	O
two	O
Sons	O
and	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tutor	O
are	O
here	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Calais	B-place
,	O
they	O
called	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
is	O
a	O
fine	O
handsome	O
looking	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
pleases	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
manners	O
.	O
We	O
walk	O
'd	O
before	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
Pier	O
head	O
,	O
saw	O
several	O
Ships	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Room	O
built	O
for	O
the	O
Pilots	O
from	O
whence	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
grand	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Tutor	O
walked	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
s	O
Cliff	O
we	O
ascended	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
&	O
spouted	O
that	O
immortal	O
s	O
bards	O
fine	O
description	O
in	O
King	O
Lear	O
:	O
--	O
the	O
prospect	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
from	O
hence	O
is	O
unbounded	O
--	O
to	O
look	O
down	O
is	O
tremendous	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
late	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
conclude	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
impatient	O
&	O
anxious	O
my	O
dear	O
Mama	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
I	O
embrace	O
you	O
tenderly	O
my	O
beloved	O
parent	O
--	O
your	O
dutiful	O
child	O
Mr.	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
“	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
that	O
your	O
amiable	O
Daughter	O
is	O
perfectly	O
well	O
and	O
in	O
charming	O
spirits	O
--	O
except	O
when	O
a	O
little	O
cloud	O
comes	O
over	O
them	O
at	O
being	O
absent	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
here	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
fair	O
wind	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
Sail	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
presents	O
his	O
Respects	O
&	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
repeating	O
our	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
entrusting	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
your	O
Treasure	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
great	O
est	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Madam	O
your	O
faithful	O
&	O
most	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
.	O
Servant	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
”	O
Dover	B-place
1	O
st	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
Sunday	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morng	O
.	O
left	O
Dover	B-place
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Packet	O
(	O
called	O
the	O
Mary	O
--	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
)	O
we	O
were	O
5	O
hours	O
getting	O
to	O
Calais	B-place
the	O
day	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
celebrated	O
Hotel	O
--	O
he	O
makes	O
111	O
beds	O
--	O
it	O
seemed	O
strange	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
5	O
hours	O
every	O
object	O
should	O
appear	O
so	O
different	O
--	O
the	O
Buildings	O
,	O
language	O
,	O
dreſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
before	O
Dinner	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Convent	O
of	O
English	O
nuns	O
--	O
P	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
an	O
English	O
lady	O
is	O
the	O
Abbeſs	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
stiled	O
Reverend	O
Mother	O
--	O
wch	O
it	O
seems	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
title	O
given	O
to	O
all	O
Abbeſs	O
's	O
of	O
Convents	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
only	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mama	O
--	O
Since	O
we	O
left	O
Calais	B-place
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
recd	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
little	O
Voyage	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
fears	O
but	O
was	O
sick	O
--	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mama	O
wth	O
--	O
truth	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
better	O
health	O
&	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
could	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
present	O
enjoments	O
would	O
be	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
with	O
good	O
accounts	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
Friday	O
at	O
Calais	B-place
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Convent	O
of	O
the	O
Dominicaines	O
--	O
an	O
English	O
Lady	O
is	O
the	O
Abbeſs	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Captn	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cosley	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
lively	O
and	O
polite	O
.	O
She	O
shewed	O
us	O
some	O
different	O
works	O
of	O
the	O
Nuns	O
--	O
Deſsien	B-pers
bought	O
a	O
purse	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Dominicaines	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chapel	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Capuchins	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
6	O
men	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
slept	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
--	O
L'Hotel	O
D'Angleterre	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
spacious	O
mansion	O
&	O
contains	O
111	O
beds	O
,	O
the	O
floors	O
are	O
are	O
dirty	O
but	O
the	O
linnen	O
is	O
white	O
&	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
waiters	O
are	O
clever	O
&	O
attentive	O
.	O
The	O
Town	O
is	O
not	O
remarkable	O
for	O
cleanlineſs	O
.	O
Saturday	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
Calais	B-place
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
Ardres	B-place
--	O
12	O
miles	O
--	O
(	O
6	O
miles	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
post	O
to	O
Recourse	B-place
1	O
post	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Omer	I-place
's	I-place
2	O
posts	O
)	O
dined	O
at	O
St.Omer	B-place
's	I-place
at	O
the	O
Hotel	O
de	O
Ville	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
we	O
dined	O
in	O
was	O
62	O
feet	O
long	O
&	O
had	O
13	O
windows	O
--	O
the	O
wainscote	O
painted	O
blue	O
,	O
ornamented	O
with	O
gilding	O
,	O
--	O
5	O
noble	O
cut	O
glaſs	O
Lustres	O
--	O
a	O
Portrait	O
of	O
Grey	B-pers
over	O
one	O
chimney	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
over	O
the	O
other	O
--	O
the	O
side	O
board	O
was	O
large	O
and	O
consisted	O
of	O
dirty	O
boards	O
laid	O
acroſs	O
a	O
frame	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
and	O
was	O
charmed	O
by	O
with	O
.	O
a	O
Picture	O
painted	O
by	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Defseins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
subject	O
was	O
the	O
descent	O
from	O
the	O
Croſs	O
;	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Tomb	O
in	O
this	O
Cathedral	O
ornamented	O
with	O
Filagree	O
work	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
contains	O
the	O
bones	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
the	I-pers
15th	I-pers
--	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
this	O
Tomb	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Coffin	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
deposited	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
an	O
Abbeſs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
another	O
Silver	O
Coffin	O
containing	O
those	O
of	O
a	O
Monk	O
.	O
The	O
City	B-place
of	I-place
St-	I-place
Omer	I-place
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
strongest	O
fortified	O
in	O
french	O
Flanders	B-place
--	O
the	O
fortifications	O
are	O
of	O
modern	O
structure	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
19	O
miles	O
from	O
Calais	B-place
,	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
trading	O
place	O
&	O
appears	O
very	O
populous	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
City	O
of	O
Artois	B-place
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
plain	O
building	O
wch	O
is	O
an	O
English	O
College	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
Sunday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
we	O
had	O
prayers	O
;	O
&	O
then	O
walked	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
3	O
shows	O
in	O
honor	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
place	O
near	O
wch	O
.	O
a	O
Woman	O
sang	O
Cantiques	O
for	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
surrounded	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
concourse	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
*	O
We	O
dined	O
early	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Aire	B-place
--	O
a	O
la	O
Poste	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
placed	O
is	O
two	O
posts	O
,	O
or	O
12	O
miles	O
,	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Omer	I-place
,	O
Aire	B-place
is	O
also	O
a	O
fortified	O
town	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Netherlands	B-place
,	O
the	O
Country	O
is	O
richly	O
cultivated	O
,	O
and	O
abundant	O
in	O
grain	O
of	O
all	O
kinds	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
in	O
one	O
Field	O
,	O
Wheat	O
,	O
Barley	O
,	O
Rye	O
,	O
Flax	O
,	O
French-wheat	O
,	O
Carrots	O
,	O
Beet-root	O
,	O
Rape	O
Seed	O
,	O
French-beans	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
--	O
the	O
people	O
are	O
uncommonly	O
neat	O
and	O
clean	O
&	O
appear	O
extremely	O
industrious	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
L'Eglise	O
de	O
St	O
Piere	O
&	O
heard	O
Maſs	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Convent	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Clara	O
--	O
the	O
Nuns	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
air	O
of	O
happineſs	O
as	O
the	O
Seours	O
Grises	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
25	O
English	O
Nuns	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
they	O
conversed	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
without	O
our	O
seeing	O
them	O
but	O
on	O
our	O
expreſsing	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
3	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
they	O
informed	O
us	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
privilege	O
of	O
appearing	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
never	O
allowed	O
to	O
eat	O
anything	O
but	O
Eggs	O
&	O
Milk	O
,	O
seldom	O
Cheese	O
,	O
nor	O
even	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Death	O
might	O
they	O
have	O
animal	O
food	O
,	O
they	O
exist	O
by	O
begging	O
alms	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Holy	O
Fathers	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
them	O
)	O
who	O
go	O
about	O
collecting	O
for	O
their	O
support	O
;	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Fathers	O
--	O
a	O
Monk	O
appeared	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
leave	O
he	O
reminded	O
us	O
of	O
ye	O
duty	O
of	O
his	O
office	O
--	O
viz	O
begging	O
for	O
their	O
support	O
.	O
from	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Clara	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Convent	O
of	O
the	O
Penitents	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
only	O
see	O
their	O
Chapel	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
who	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Chapel	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
sad	O
history	O
of	O
a	O
Young	O
Lady	O
who	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
this	O
Convent	O
of	O
Penitents	O
contrary	O
to	O
her	O
inclinations	O
by	O
her	O
Parents	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
an	O
attachment	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
her	O
inferior	O
/	O
in	O
fortune	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
confined	O
3	O
Months	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discovered	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
far	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Chapel	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Convent	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
a	O
part	O
priviledged	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
case	O
any	O
can	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
surrounds	O
ye	O
Altar	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
attempted	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
is	O
secure	O
,	O
&	O
can	O
never	O
again	O
be	O
placed	O
in	O
the	O
Convent	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
particularly	O
desires	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Young	O
Woman	O
--	O
(	O
who	O
our	O
guide	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
was	O
Jeune	O
et	O
belle	O
à	O
manger	O
)	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
ye	O
soldiers	O
when	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
--	O
who	O
are	O
always	O
there	O
on	O
guard	O
--	O
caught	O
her	O
&	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Abbeſs	O
--	O
who	O
ordered	O
her	O
immediately	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
between	O
4	O
brick	O
walls	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
allowed	O
a	O
small	O
portion	O
of	O
bread	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
water	O
daily	O
in	O
this	O
state	O
she	O
existed	O
8	O
Months	O
,	O
continually	O
praying	O
to	O
God	O
for	O
release	O
from	O
her	O
sufferings	O
:	O
When	O
her	O
lover	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
and	O
drowned	O
him	O
ſ	O
s	O
elf	O
--	O
this	O
happened	O
only	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
--	O
the	O
man	O
could	O
not	O
inform	O
us	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Ladys	O
Parents	O
.	O
We	O
sup't	O
and	O
slept	O
at	O
Aire	B-place
the	O
beds	O
good	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
very	O
clean	O
;	O
here	O
we	O
have	O
Hares	O
,	O
Partridges	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
game	O
as	O
plenty	O
as	O
Fowls	O
Rabbits	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
the	O
Poultry	O
is	O
also	O
good	O
,	O
plenty	O
,	O
and	O
cheap	O
:	O
Besides	O
two	O
courses	O
well	O
dreſsed	O
by	O
excellent	O
Cooks	O
there	O
is	O
always	O
7	O
or	O
ten	O
dishes	O
at	O
Desert	O
consisting	O
of	O
various	O
fruits	O
and	O
Cakes	O
--	O
the	O
wines	O
,	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
say	O
,	O
are	O
very	O
good	O
--	O
Claret	O
,	O
Burgundy	O
,	O
Vin	O
de	O
Greve	O
,	O
&	O
.	O
No	O
Port	O
wine	O
nor	O
Beer	O
.	O
The	O
magnificence	O
of	O
the	O
Churches	O
strike	O
me	O
extremely	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
reach	O
not	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
so	O
soon	O
as	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
intended	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Dauphin	I-pers
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
every	O
picture	O
worth	O
looking	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mama	O
write	O
more	O
particularly	O
&	O
accquaint	O
you	O
wth	O
.	O
every	O
occurence	O
,	O
but	O
Rubens	B-pers
has	O
made	O
some	O
gentle	O
remonstrances	O
against	O
St.	B-pers
Omer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
spending	O
too	O
much	O
time	O
in	O
scribbling	O
letters	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
settle	O
for	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
he	O
likes	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Domino	O
or	O
some	O
round	O
game	O
,	O
likewise	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
post	O
goes	O
out	O
at	O
uncertain	O
times	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
places	O
we	O
stop	O
at	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
letters	O
as	O
regularly	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mama	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mama	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
been	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
again	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
wondered	O
at	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
terribly	O
afflicted	O
on	O
losing	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
proved	O
herself	O
an	O
exemplary	O
wife	O
and	O
careful	O
Mother	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
arrived	O
at	O
an	O
age	O
when	O
the	O
paſsion	O
of	O
Love	O
one	O
should	O
imagine	O
could	O
not	O
master	O
the	O
sober	O
dictates	O
of	O
prudence	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
lately	O
met	O
my	O
Uncle	O
my	B-pers
Aunt	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
at	O
Geneva	B-place
&	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
on	O
the	O
very	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
--	O
it	O
seems	O
that	O
my	O
young	O
Cousin	O
is	O
rather	O
difficult	O
to	O
please	O
&	O
manage	O
,	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
conduct	O
herself	O
quite	O
so	O
amiably	O
as	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
wishes	O
;	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
pity	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
required	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Man	O
so	O
much	O
older	O
and	O
whom	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
in	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
say	O
she	O
evidently	O
dislikes	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
says	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
will	O
not	O
comply	O
properly	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Etiquettes	O
required	O
as	O
Lady	O
to	O
the	O
English	O
Ambaſsador	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
hoped	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
will	O
prevail	O
on	O
her	O
to	O
alter	O
her	O
conduct	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
also	O
says	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
intention	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
September	O
--	O
this	O
will	O
afford	O
you	O
great	O
pleasure	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
so	O
sincere	O
an	O
affection	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
Uncle	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
&	O
pray	O
aſsure	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
unalterable	O
affection	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
impatient	O
to	O
embrace	O
them	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
Dearest	O
Mama	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
extremely	O
happy	O
by	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
lose	O
time	O
I	O
will	O
continue	O
my	O
journal	O
Monday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
august	O
1776	O
Went	O
to	O
Lilliers	B-place
where	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
--	O
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
Bethune	B-place
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
said	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
was	O
very	O
imposing	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
very	O
dear	O
.	O
--	O
post	O
--	O
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
la	B-place
Waquet	I-place
a	O
single	O
house	O
The	O
people	O
were	O
particularly	O
civil	O
--	O
the	O
House	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
n	O
good	O
clean	O
English	O
Farm	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
farmers	O
fare	O
Bacon	O
&	O
Eggs	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
enjoyed	O
much	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
Merry	O
,	O
over	O
broiling	O
&	O
cooking	O
ourselves	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Domestics	O
were	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
plenty	O
of	O
good	O
Bacon	O
fresh	O
eggs	O
,	O
&	O
sweet	O
bread	O
,	O
to	O
eat	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
was	O
very	O
hot	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
for	O
William	B-pers
--	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
gasping	O
--	O
We	O
changed	O
Horses	O
again	O
at	O
Lisle	B-place
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
city	O
strongly	O
fortified	O
--	O
though	O
there	O
is	O
much	O
worth	O
seeing	O
our	O
curiosity	O
must	O
lie	O
dormant	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
are	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
intends	O
stopping	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
struck	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
windmills	O
near	O
Lisle	B-place
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
counted	O
200	O
at	O
least	O
--	O
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
Menin	B-place
--	O
post	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
here	O
obliged	O
for	O
every	O
set	O
of	O
4	O
horses	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
6	O
--	O
the	O
profit	O
they	O
say	O
goes	O
partly	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
--	O
one	O
Postilion	O
drives	O
4	O
horses	O
(	O
they	O
never	O
use	O
more	O
)	O
with	O
long	O
traces	O
,	O
faster	O
,	O
than	O
two	O
postilions	O
with	O
6	O
horses	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
.	O
In	O
paſsing	O
through	O
a	O
Village	O
we	O
saw	O
almost	O
at	O
--	O
every	O
door	O
women	O
spinning	O
Cotton	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
neatly	O
dreſsed	O
&	O
all	O
wore	O
wooden	O
shoes	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
to	O
to	O
Courtray	B-place
at	O
8	O
o'clock	O
--	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
gates	O
are	O
shut	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hotel	O
Damier	O
every	O
thing	O
perfectly	O
clean	O
,	O
the	O
Supper	O
was	O
served	O
on	O
Pewter	O
as	O
bright	O
as	O
silver	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
paid	O
only	O
5	O
escalins	O
(	O
2	O
s	O
:	O
11	O
d	O
English	O
)	O
per	O
head	O
)	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
fine	O
Fowls	O
,	O
a	O
larded	O
Hare	O
,	O
6	O
Quails	O
,	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
sweetbreads	O
--	O
Veal	O
à	O
la	O
Mode	O
,	O
hot	O
,	O
Stewed	O
Peas	O
--	O
French	O
beans	O
Do	O
.	O
and	O
7	O
dishes	O
at	O
desert	O
--	O
Tarts	O
--	O
and	O
7	O
dishes	O
of	O
fruit	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
desert	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Beds	O
were	O
excellent	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
extremely	O
civil	O
.	O
The	O
dreſs	O
continues	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
at	O
Calais	B-place
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
and	O
the	O
common	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
is	O
a	O
short	O
Casaquin	O
,	O
or	O
jacket	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
very	O
coarse	O
stuff	O
,	O
ye-	O
color	O
not	O
material	O
--	O
the	O
peticoats	O
remarkable	O
short	O
the	O
Stockings	O
white	O
&	O
clean	O
and	O
Slippers	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
only	O
cover	O
the	O
toes	O
,	O
without	O
hind	O
quarters	O
&	O
a	O
heel	O
rather	O
high	O
&	O
stout	O
.	O
The	O
caps	O
are	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
form	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
white	O
linnen	O
,	O
Cambric	O
,	O
Lawn	O
or	O
Muslin	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
border	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
plaited	O
uncommonly	O
small	O
&	O
neat	O
,	O
this	O
cap	O
is	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
hair	O
is	O
concealed	O
except	O
on	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
combed	O
flat	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
powdered	O
--	O
these	O
do	O
not	O
wear	O
any	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
but	O
white	O
bobbin	O
drawn	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
head	O
fastens	O
the	O
cap	O
,	O
no	O
woman	O
is	O
without	O
gold	O
earings	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
single	O
drops	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Croſs	O
of	O
gold	O
hangs	O
on	O
their	O
bosoms	O
,	O
these	O
that	O
can	O
afford	O
it	O
have	O
3	O
drops	O
to	O
their	O
earings	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
gold	O
Croſs	O
embelished	O
with	O
rose	O
diamonds	O
;	O
the	O
poorest	O
creature	O
who	O
has	O
scarcely	O
clothes	O
to	O
shelter	O
protect	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
gold	O
earings	O
and	O
a	O
Croſs	O
:	O
Stays	O
are	O
not	O
worn	O
--	O
the	O
jacket	O
is	O
made	O
high	O
&	O
conceals	O
the	O
bosom	O
&	O
neck	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
wear	O
a	O
small	O
white	O
Neck	O
-	O
kerchief	O
--	O
the	O
White	O
Caps	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
give	O
an	O
air	O
of	O
cleanliness	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
rank	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
England	B-place
have	O
not	O
,	O
--	O
Women	O
of	O
all	O
conditions	O
(	O
particularly	O
when	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
maſs	O
)	O
wear	O
long	O
Hoods	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
various	O
colours	O
--	O
chiefly	O
light	O
brown	O
,	O
the	O
Hood	O
shades	O
the	O
face	O
and	O
the	O
cloke	O
entirely	O
disguises	O
the	O
figure	O
--	O
the	O
poorest	O
rank	O
wear	O
a	O
long	O
square	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
stuff	O
;	O
silk	O
,	O
serge	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
which	O
they	O
throw	O
over	O
their	O
Heads	O
&	O
serves	O
to	O
cover	O
the	O
head	O
&	O
,	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
here	O
is	O
remarkably	O
white	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
stifly	O
starched	O
as	O
to	O
scratch	O
ones	O
legs	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
Courtray	B-place
We	O
saw	O
L'Eglise	O
Collegiate	O
,	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Great	O
Altar	O
is	O
a	O
capital	O
picture	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
declaration	O
of	O
the	O
Croſs	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
it	O
is	O
placed	O
between	O
the	O
Windows	O
therefore	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
light	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
another	O
picture	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
&	O
the	O
Trinity	O
:	O
from	O
L	O
Eglise	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chanoineſses	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
fine	O
picture	O
,	O
painted	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Nativity	O
,	O
the	O
Chan	O
n	O
oineſse	O
was	O
polite	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
private	O
Chapel	O
.	O
Vandyke	B-pers
could	O
not	O
procure	O
a	O
sufficient	O
number	O
of	O
Horses	O
so	O
early	O
as	O
he	O
wished	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
amusement	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
dine	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
D'Hote	O
at	O
our	O
Hotel	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
--	O
our	O
company	O
consisted	O
of	O
two	O
Priests	O
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
talked	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
eat	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
equally	O
impertinent	O
as	O
vulgar	O
,	O
a	O
well	O
bred	O
genteel	O
looking	O
Man	O
who	O
spoke	O
good	O
french	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
ill	O
dreſsed	O
strange	O
looking	O
people	O
--	O
for	O
2	O
Escalins	O
,	O
(	O
14	O
d	O
.	O
English	O
)	O
a	O
head	O
we	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
dinner	O
as	O
what	O
Crayer	B-pers
be	O
al	O
-	O
always	O
pays	O
5	O
Escalins	O
a	O
head	O
for	O
;	O
--	O
the	O
rooms	O
are	O
floored	O
with	O
Bricks	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
onto	O
Courtray	B-place
there	O
was	O
an	O
awful	O
storm	O
of	O
Thunder	O
,	O
lightning	O
&	O
torrents	O
of	O
rain	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
Courtray	B-place
soon	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
changed	O
horses	O
at	O
Vive	B-place
St	I-place
Cloy	I-place
,	O
also	O
at	O
Betghent	B-place
,	O
and	O
arrived	O
at	O
Gand	B-place
or	O
Ghent	B-place
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
L'Hotel	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Sebastian	O
on	O
the	O
Place	O
de	O
Parade	O
--	O
the	O
Landlords	O
name	O
Jourdain	B-pers
,	O
ye-	O
Hotel	O
is	O
very	O
large	O
--	O
excellent	O
beds	O
,	O
good	O
Waiters	O
,	O
and	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
himself	O
remarkably	O
attentive	O
--	O
Brick	O
floors	O
in	O
the	O
bed-rooms	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
covered	O
with	O
Old	O
fine	O
Tapestry	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
ragged	O
state	O
--	O
large	O
glaſs	O
Lustres	O
hanging	O
from	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
,	O
&	O
miserable	O
shabby	O
fire	O
places	O
--	O
like	O
those	O
in	O
a	O
poor	O
house	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
elegant	O
dinner	O
for	O
us	O
at	O
6	O
escalins	O
a	O
head	O
--	O
2	O
courses	O
,	O
--	O
the	O
Desert	O
very	O
handsome	O
with	O
Ices	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Supper	O
was	O
5	O
Escalins	O
a	O
head	O
--	O
fine	O
Wines	O
,	O
good	O
bread	O
,	O
--	O
only	O
,	O
the	O
Butter	O
indifferent	O
--	O
In	O
this	O
Country	O
you	O
have	O
always	O
Napkins	O
and	O
Silver	O
forks	O
&	O
spoons	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
dont	O
change	O
the	O
Knives	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
children	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
&	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
quit	O
his	O
room	O
--	O
Buſso	B-pers
took	O
Mr.	B-pers
Buſso	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Governeſs	O
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
)	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
abbey	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Piere	O
.	O
The	O
Salle	O
a	O
manger	O
is	O
a	O
magnificent	O
Room	O
--	O
300	O
feet	O
long	O
--	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
painted	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
(	O
on	O
linnen	O
)	O
who	O
is	O
living	O
at	O
Bruſsels	B-place
--	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
it	O
was	O
painted	O
in	O
47	O
days	O
--	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
are	O
covered	O
with	O
beautiful	O
Landscapes	O
--	O
painted	O
by	O
an	O
artist	O
named	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Fermor	I-pers
--	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
Abbe	O
's	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tables	O
were	O
ready	O
.	O
Over	O
the	O
doors	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
were	O
exquisite	O
paintings	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Southern	I-pers
in	O
Clair	O
Obscur	O
--	O
he	O
resides	O
at	O
Antwerp	B-place
--	O
this	O
room	O
is	O
97	O
feet	O
long	O
.	O
The	O
Abbe	O
de	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Piere	O
is	O
Comte	O
de	O
Flanders	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
32	O
Abbies	O
--	O
The	O
Chapel	O
or	O
Church	O
annexed	O
to	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
elegant	O
and	O
very	O
rich	O
--	O
and	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
nicest	O
order	O
--	O
the	O
Altar	O
is	O
solid	O
silver	O
as	O
are	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
above	O
6	O
feet	O
high	O
.	O
The	O
Stalls	O
for	O
the	O
Singers	O
are	O
of	O
Oak	O
carved	O
curiously	O
each	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
cost	O
1000	O
Florins	O
(	O
or	O
English	O
)	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
fine	O
Vestments	O
and	O
ornaments	O
worn	O
by	O
the	O
Priests	O
,	O
The	O
Point	O
and	O
Brussels	O
lace	O
was	O
most	O
superb	O
and	O
beautiful	O
--	O
The	O
whole	O
amazingly	O
rich	O
&	O
costly	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
very	O
fine	O
Tapestry	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
relicks	O
made	O
precious	O
by	O
ornaments	O
of	O
jewels	O
&	O
c	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
pictures	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
only	O
particularly	O
struck	O
by	O
2	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
Altar	O
--	O
Tobit	O
by	O
Simon	B-pers
,	O
and	O
our	O
Saviour	O
crucified	O
by	O
Artois	B-pers
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Bavon	O
where	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
picture	O
by	O
Girard	B-pers
the	O
subject	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
disputed	O
--	O
some	O
affirm	O
it	O
is	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Bavon	O
giving	O
up	O
his	O
treasures	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
--	O
others	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Emperor	O
G	B-pers
Crayer	I-pers
giving	O
up	O
the	O
Crown	O
to	O
his	O
Son	O
:	O
the	O
Altar	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
an	O
immense	O
size	O
,	O
of	O
Copper	O
richly	O
ornamented	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
from	O
York	B-place
,	O
the	O
arms	O
of	O
England	B-place
,	O
are	O
finely	O
engraved	O
on	O
them	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
purchased	O
by	O
a	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Ghent	B-place
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Monument	O
by	O
Janſsins	B-pers
.	O
From	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
the	O
Recollects	O
--	O
Three	O
fine	O
Pictures	O
by	O
Reubens	B-pers
--	O
Over	O
the	O
great	O
Altar	O
is	O
represented	O
Christ	O
going	O
to	O
punish	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
the	O
Virgin	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
as	O
interceding	O
--	O
and	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Francis	O
below	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
humble	O
affecting	O
attitude	O
of	O
supplication	O
.	O
Over	O
another	O
Altar	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Fra	O
n	O
cis	O
;	O
&	O
on	O
a	O
third	O
a	O
a	O
dying	O
Magdalen	O
August	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
1776	O
Ghent	B-place
Charles	B-pers
ye-	I-pers
5th	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
private	O
cabinet	O
of	O
pictures	O
belonging	O
to	O
an	O
Abbé	O
and	O
were	O
gratified	O
by	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
collection	O
of	O
flemish	O
pictures	O
highly	O
finished	O
--	O
two	O
Jerome	B-pers
du	I-pers
Qucesnoy	I-pers
admired	O
much	O
by	O
Reubens	B-pers
s	O
one	O
Bachus	O
and	O
Nymphs	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
From	O
the	O
Abbé	O
s	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Collection	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
--	O
many	O
fine	O
pictures	O
--	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Fermor	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
Meijer	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
After	O
Tea	O
a	O
Savoyard	O
played	O
/before	O
the	O
Windows/	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
Thursday	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
Left	O
Ghent	B-place
early	O
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
Quatrect	B-place
--	O
dined	O
at	O
Alost	O
at	O
Les	O
Trois	O
Rois	O
.	O
Saw	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Martin	O
saw	O
another	O
capital	O
picture	O
,	O
by	O
Reubens	B-pers
,	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Rock	O
interceading	O
during	O
a	O
Plague	O
.	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
the	O
Carmelites	O
a	O
picture	O
over	O
ye-	O
altar	O
by	O
Vandyck	B-pers
--	O
the	O
Virgin	O
with	O
the	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
altar	O
from	O
the	O
Pope	O
to	O
the	O
Monk	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
to	O
Bruſsels	B-place
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Rain	O
wch_	O
was	O
quite	O
refreshing	O
after	O
the	O
almost	O
intolerable	O
dust	O
and	O
heat	O
.	O
Lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Hotel	O
D'Angleterre	O
at	O
our	O
entrance	O
into	O
Bruſsels	B-place
the	O
Carriages	O
were	O
surrounded	O
by	O
men	O
called	O
Valet	O
de	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
Servants	O
during	O
a	O
strangers	O
residence	O
,	O
to	O
conduct	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Churches	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Carlo	B-pers
Maratti	I-pers
hired	O
one	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
Reubens	B-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
attentive	O
&	O
civil	O
--	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Wife	O
&	O
ten	O
Children	O
who	O
are	O
extremely	O
industrious	O
.	O
The	O
Room	O
we	O
sit	O
in	O
is	O
45	O
feet	O
long	O
.	O
--	O
Friday	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
Augst	O
.	O
Bruſsels	B-place
We	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
G.	B-pers
Crayer	I-pers
's	O
Cabinet	O
of	O
pictures	O
--	O
This	O
gentleman	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
25	O
years	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
in	O
sharing	O
his	O
pictures	O
,	O
particularly	O
to	O
strangers	O
,	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
us	O
in	O
his	O
study	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
bred	O
,	O
the	O
dreſs	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
(	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
always	O
wears	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
India	O
Chintz	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
,	O
--	O
a	O
Cambric	O
night	O
cap	O
bound	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
striped	O
border	O
of	O
chintz	O
--	O
Slippers	O
,	O
&	O
fine	O
Bruſsels	O
point	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
little	O
fingers	O
a	O
large	O
brilliant	O
Diamond	O
ring	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
fortune	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
man	O
Servants	O
in	O
superb	O
liveries	O
wch	O
.	O
denoted	O
it	O
--	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
appearance	O
goes	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
shewd	O
us	O
4	O
rooms	O
&	O
a	O
closét	O
cram̄ed	O
with	O
high	O
ly	O
finished	O
Flemish	O
&	O
Dutch	O
pictures	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
by	O
Sr.	B-pers
Philip	I-pers
which	O
Mr.	B-pers
Varrulst	I-pers
values	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
he	O
ever	O
painted	O
;	O
From	O
Mr.	B-pers
Varrulst	I-pers
's	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Rubens	B-pers
Prince	O
of	O
Lorraine	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
magnificient	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
taste	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
experience	O
to	O
judge	O
)	O
the	O
first	O
room	O
we	O
entered	O
was	O
hung	O
with	O
Tapestry	O
wrought	O
in	O
a	O
superiour	O
stile	O
from	O
designs	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
--	O
between	O
each	O
window	O
were	O
looking	O
Glaſses	O
from	O
ye	O
Ceiling	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
the	O
Cornice	O
&	O
Ceiling	O
beautiful	O
;	O
another	O
Room	O
was	O
wainscoated	O
with	O
the	O
wood	O
of	O
Nut-Tree	O
brought	O
from	O
Turkey	B-place
,	O
ornamented	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
yet	O
rich	O
manner	O
with	O
Copper	O
gilt	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
shewn	O
many	O
curious	O
pieces	O
of	O
mechanism	O
,	O
Clocks	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
narrow	O
Gallery	O
filled	O
with	O
very	O
mean	O
pictures	O
--	O
a	O
Salle	O
á	O
Manger	O
(	O
a	O
large	O
Room	O
)	O
also	O
full	O
of	O
pictures	O
,	O
some	O
good	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Varrulst	I-pers
has	O
two	O
Millions	O
of	O
Florins	O
per	O
annum	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
Noble	O
Summer	O
Palace	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
him	O
drive	O
past	O
us	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Carriage	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
,	O
bloated	O
,	O
plain	O
looking	O
Man	O
--	O
he	O
drinks	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
every	O
day	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
each	O
bottle	O
twice	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
English	O
quart	O
ones	O
.	O
--	O
besides	O
liquers	O
&	O
c.	O
From	O
the	O
Court	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Arsenaly	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
curious	O
Armour	O
amongst	O
that	O
of	O
others	O
we	O
particularly	O
noticed	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
and	O
Rubens	B-pers
's	O
--	O
the	O
workmanship	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
admirable	O
--	O
that	O
of	O
poor	O
Prince	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
's	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
Indian	O
Reeds	O
and	O
other	O
similar	O
materials	O
.	O
--	O
From	O
the	O
Arsenal	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Capuchins	O
--	O
over	O
the	O
great	O
Altar	O
a	O
Picture	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
the	I-pers
5th-	I-pers
'	O
,	O
of	O
Christ	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
the	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
a	O
very	O
affecting	O
and	O
beautiful	O
picture	O
,	O
the	O
Magdalaine	O
's	O
figure	O
and	O
countenance	O
is	O
very	O
lovely	O
.	O
Almost	O
(	O
The	O
works	O
of	O
Mountezuma	B-pers
,	O
Montezuma	B-pers
,	O
Rubens	B-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
are	O
chiefly	O
monopolized	O
by	O
the	O
Churches	O
in	O
Flanders	B-place
&	O
in	O
them	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
their	O
find	O
their	O
best	O
productions	O
)	O
The	O
Capuchin	O
who	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Church	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Sacristi	O
&	O
shewed	O
us	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
Christ	O
&	O
Mary	O
his	O
Mother	O
by	O
Rubens	B-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
fine	O
Ivory	O
Crucifix	O
by	O
Vandyck	B-pers
--	O
and	O
two	O
pictures	O
by	O
G.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Crayer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
one	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Anthony	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Francis	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mama	O
,	O
to	O
mention	O
all	O
the	O
pictures	O
,	O
Sculptures	O
,	O
Relicks	O
,	O
Architecture	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
worthy	O
notice	O
in	O
the	O
Churches	O
&	O
other	O
places	O
--	O
for	O
besides	O
my	O
want	O
of	O
judgment	O
,	O
we	O
see	O
things	O
too	O
rapidly	O
for	O
perfect	O
recollection	O
.	O
Atto	B-pers
Verrius	I-pers
&	O
suite	O
came	O
here	O
(	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
Antwerp	B-place
)	O
quite	O
recovered	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
is	O
fine	O
--	O
we	O
looked	O
at	O
Lace	O
and	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
dear	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
purchased	O
as	O
cheap	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
The	O
best	O
society	O
here	O
is	O
elegant	O
.	O
My	O
Hair	O
was	O
well	O
dreſsed	O
by	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
Hair	O
dreſser	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
extravagantly	O
large	O
as	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
the	O
fashion	O
s	O
very	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
have	O
their	O
heads	O
well	O
loaded	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
elegant	O
small	O
hats	O
composed	O
of	O
Blond	O
's	O
--	O
foils	O
flowers	O
&	O
c.	O
so	O
small	O
that	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
portion	O
of	O
hair	O
is	O
covered	O
--	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
wear	O
any	O
other	O
to	O
walk	O
abroad	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
they	O
leave	O
the	O
face	O
exposed	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
made	O
wth	O
.	O
open	O
wires	O
behind	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
down	O
to	O
appear	O
round	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
hats	O
have	O
extravagantly	O
high	O
feathers	O
waving	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
.	O
These	O
Hats	O
we	O
saw	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
milleners	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
Ladies	O
of	O
quality	O
.	O
Saturday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
Left	O
Bruſsels	B-place
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
,	O
dined	O
at	O
Maline	B-place
or	O
Mechlin	B-place
--	O
saw	O
some	O
Churches	O
--	O
arrived	O
in	O
Antwerp	B-place
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
L'Hotel	O
d'Angleterre	O
;	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
the	O
Recollects	O
--	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Augustines	O
--	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Notre	O
Dame	O
called	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
--	O
the	O
Tower	O
beautiful	O
Gothic	O
466	O
feet	O
high	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
Altar	O
entirely	O
of	O
Marble	O
very	O
superb	O
,	O
The	O
Statue	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Paul	O
finely	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
all	O
his	O
at	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
Quernoy	B-pers
--	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
pictures	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
memorandum	O
of	O
our	O
party	O
&	O
my	O
own	O
and	O
what	O
we	O
markd	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
--	O
Then	O
to	O
the	O
Dominicaines	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Sick	O
headach	O
wch-	O
kept	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
way	O
&	O
c	O
Sunday	O
11	O
th	O
August	O
Antwerp	B-place
Vandyck	B-pers
read	O
prayers	O
--	O
after	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
party	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
--	O
then	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
an	O
Historical	O
Painter	O
,	O
&	O
2	O
others	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
went	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Andre	O
--	O
opposite	O
to	O
ye	O
Chapel	O
of	O
the	O
Saint	O
Sacrament	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Epitaph	O
to	O
the	O
Memory	O
of	O
Capello	B-pers
ye	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Antwerp	I-pers
with	O
her	O
Portrait	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
is	O
beautiful	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
North	O
Side	O
a	O
picture	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
of	O
our	O
Saviour	O
&	O
the	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
--	O
The	O
Valet	O
de	O
Place	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lonty	I-pers
hired	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
intelligent	O
Man	O
&	O
could	O
give	O
an	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
every	O
Picture	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
a	O
clear	O
manner	O
--	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	I-pers
Scots	I-pers
.	O
The	O
City	B-place
of	I-place
Antwerp	I-place
is	O
the	O
Capital	O
of	O
the	O
Marquisate	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
in	O
the	B-place
Netherlands	I-place
,	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Citadel	O
reckon	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
strongest	O
in	O
the	O
Low	B-place
Countrys	I-place
--	O
the	O
City	O
is	O
built	O
in	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Crescent	O
on	O
the	O
River	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
esteemed	O
200	O
years	O
ago	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
Trading	O
port	O
in	O
Europe	B-place
--	O
but	O
the	O
traffic	O
is	O
removed	O
to	O
Amsterdam	B-place
&	O
other	O
Towns	O
in	O
Holland	B-place
--	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
private	O
collection	O
of	O
the	O
Chanoine	O
Vandyck	B-pers
,	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Abbé	O
de	O
Saint	O
Michel	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
some	O
capital	O
Pictures	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
de	B-pers
Bois	I-pers
,	O
&	O
other	O
eminent	O
painters	O
--	O
the	O
apartments	O
w	O
e	O
a	O
re	O
very	O
spacious	O
&	O
command	O
ed	O
an	O
extensive	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
--	O
Here	O
the	O
Royal	O
family	O
are	O
lodged	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
shewn	O
some	O
boards	O
burnt	O
,	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	B-place
&	O
Charles	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
England	B-place
burnt	O
some	O
papers	O
of	O
consequence	O
.	O
Antwerp	B-place
is	O
subject	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
Austria	B-place
Monday	O
12	O
th	O
August	O
1776	O
Left	O
Antwerp	B-place
at	O
11	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mecklin	B-place
--	O
(	O
or	O
Malines	B-place
)	O
at	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Inn	O
called	O
la	O
Grue	O
--	O
saw	O
ye-	O
Cathedral	O
saw	O
no	O
Pictures	O
to	O
rival	O
those	O
at	O
Antwerp	B-place
--	O
went	O
to	O
L'Eglise	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Jean	O
where	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Picture	O
of	O
the	O
Adoration	O
of	O
the	O
Maji	O
by	O
Chanoine	B-pers
Knyffe	I-pers
--	O
We	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
slept	O
at	O
Bruſsels	B-place
to	O
wch	O
place	O
we	O
returned	O
from	O
Antwerp	B-place
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
Tuesday	O
13	O
th	O
August	O
Saw	O
the	O
Jesuists	O
Church	O
,	O
College	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
was	O
melancholy	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
place	O
so	O
deserted	O
--	O
all	O
the	O
Vestments	O
of	O
the	O
Priests	O
&	O
abt	O
.	O
2000	O
pictures	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
--	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
pictures	O
were	O
chiefly	O
copies	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
good	O
originals	O
--	O
many	O
were	O
sad	O
daubs	O
--	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Abbé	O
de	O
Colbert	O
--	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Jacques	O
de	O
Coudenberg	O
--	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
politeneſs	O
,	O
shewed	O
us	O
his	O
private	O
apartments	O
&	O
his	O
Chapel	O
--	O
saw	O
two	O
beautiful	O
sketches	O
by	O
Rubens	B-pers
,	O
--	O
he	O
also	O
shewed	O
us	O
a	O
drawing	O
of	O
the	O
Abbey	O
&	O
Church	O
&	O
apartments	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
built	O
upon	O
a	O
noble	O
&	O
extensive	O
scale	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
enabled	O
to	O
complete	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
intend	O
selling	O
some	O
valuable	O
Pictures	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Madona	O
&	O
Child	O
by	O
Vandycke	B-pers
--	O
and	O
3	O
Pictures	O
by	O
Rubens	B-pers
for	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
said	O
3	O
Pictures	O
they	O
ask	O
four	O
thousand	O
Guineas	O
--	O
The	O
Abbé	O
de	O
Coudenberg	O
is	O
a	O
jolly	O
well	O
looking	O
Man	O
,	O
appears	O
abt	O
.	O
60	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Abbé	O
with	O
him	O
who	O
very	O
politely	O
invited	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
from	O
Spa	B-place
to	O
see	O
some	O
curious	O
paintings	O
--	O
flowers	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Bruſsels	B-place
is	O
Capital	O
of	O
Brabant	B-place
&	O
all	O
the	O
Austrian	O
--	O
Netherlands	O
on	O
the	O
Senne	O
--	O
&	O
Residence	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Vice	O
Roy	O
.	O
Vandycke	B-pers
,	O
&	O
subject	O
to	O
Austria	B-place
--	O
The	O
The	O
Road	O
for	O
some	O
Miles	O
from	O
Antwerp	B-place
near	O
Bruſsels	B-place
is	O
charming	O
--	O
one	O
side	O
thickly	O
planted	O
wth	O
.	O
Trees	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
fine	O
clear	O
River	O
&	O
a	O
broad	O
good	O
road	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
Pavé	O
Tuesday	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
Left	O
Bruſsels	B-place
at	O
12	O
,	O
the	O
road	O
beautiful	O
between	O
B	B-place
:	I-place
&	O
Louvain	B-place
,	O
3	O
&	O
sometimes	O
4	O
rows	O
of	O
Trees	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
--	O
no	O
hedge	O
rows	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
3	O
wheels	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
some	O
malefactors	O
had	O
been	O
executed	O
these	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
public	O
road	O
--	O
the	O
land	O
is	O
cultivated	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
trees	O
planted	O
on	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Road	O
--	O
The	O
Harvest	O
is	O
begun	O
,	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
corn	O
wth	O
a	O
short	O
Scythe	O
&	O
hold	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
women	O
labour	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Men	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
them	O
reap	O
Poppies	O
in	O
ye-	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
the	O
Corn	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
long	O
narrow	O
--	O
Carriages	O
drawn	O
sometimes	O
by	O
4	O
sometimes	O
5	O
horses	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
abreast	O
--	O
on	O
there	O
Vehicles	O
they	O
load	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
.	O
Women	O
&	O
children	O
wear	O
wooden	O
Shoes	O
,	O
few	O
have	O
stockings	O
--	O
Beggars	O
are	O
numerous	O
on	O
The	O
Road	O
&	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
Inns	O
--	O
we	O
dined	O
at	O
Louvaine	B-place
(	O
at	O
the	O
Ville	O
de	O
Cologne	O
)	O
--	O
every	O
thing	O
good	O
&	O
well	O
dreſsed	O
--	O
excellent	O
Beds	O
,	O
very	O
clean	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
people	O
very	O
attentive	O
.	O
The	O
State	O
House	O
at	O
Louvaine	B-place
is	O
esteemed	O
a	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Gothic	O
Building	O
--	O
tis	O
in	O
good	O
preservation	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
admired	O
it	O
much	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Chapel	O
of	O
the	O
Convent	O
of	O
Les	O
Dames	O
Blanches	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
fine	O
Picture	O
by	O
Vandyck	B-pers
--	O
the	O
adoration	O
of	O
the	O
Maji	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
large	O
Church	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Piere	O
we	O
saw	O
some	O
exquisite	O
carving	O
in	O
Oak	O
,	O
--	O
walked	O
to	O
the	O
Eglise	O
Dominicaines	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Women	O
&	O
Convent	O
,	O
heard	O
Vespers	O
--	O
was	O
not	O
charmed	O
either	O
by	O
the	O
voices	O
of	O
playing	O
of	O
the	O
Nuns	O
&	O
their	O
Organ	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
.	O
Saw	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Augustins	O
Church	O
--	O
a	O
fine	O
picture	O
by	O
Rubens	B-pers
--	O
a	O
Monk	O
gave	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
Miracles	O
--	O
Louvaine	B-place
is	O
not	O
a	O
clean	O
nor	O
agreeable	O
Town	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
At	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
left	O
Louvaine	B-place
,	O
changed	O
Horses	O
at	O
Tirlemont	B-place
--	O
a	O
large	O
Town	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
old	O
Churches	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
of	I-pers
Lorraine	I-pers
did	O
not	O
think	O
,	O
worth	O
--	O
while	O
stopping	O
to	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
changed	O
Horses	O
again	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Trond	I-place
,	O
and	O
of	O
Tongres	B-place
where	O
we	O
dined	O
at	O
La	O
Poste	O
--	O
they	O
made	O
Rubens	B-pers
pay	O
extravagantly	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
dinner	O
--	O
The	O
weather	O
was	O
exceſsively	O
hot	O
wch	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
wth-	O
dear	O
Crayer	B-pers
&	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Maistretch	B-place
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Inn	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
clean	O
,	O
good	O
Beds	O
,	O
well	O
attended	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
remarkably	O
civil	O
,	O
The	O
Inn	O
called	O
the	O
Moulinn	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
found	O
the	O
charge	O
reasonable	O
for	O
an	O
elegant	O
Supper	O
&	O
Desert	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
entrance	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
strict	O
search	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Burreau	O
(	O
or	O
Customhouse	O
officer	O
)	O
&	O
asked	O
more	O
questions	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
every	O
great	O
Town	O
travellers	O
are	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Gates	O
,	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
&	O
whether	O
they	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
sujet	O
au	O
droit	O
de	O
sa	O
Majesté	O
,	O
&	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chappelle	I-place
as	O
travellers	O
&	O
not	O
Merchants	O
were	O
permitted	O
to	O
paſs	O
without	O
the	O
Trunks	O
being	O
opened	O
--	O
The	O
officer	O
who	O
examined	O
us	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Ensign	O
about	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
&	O
short	O
of	O
that	O
age	O
,	O
the	O
Burreaus	O
at	O
some	O
other	O
Towns	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
of	O
equal	O
Dignity	O
as	O
they	O
always	O
asked	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
some	O
--	O
money	O
for	O
Drink	O
.	O
Maestritch	B-place
is	O
a	O
well	O
built	O
Town	O
,	O
large	O
&	O
clean	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
situated	O
on	O
the	O
River	O
Maes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
garrison	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Dutch	O
who	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
civil	O
government	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
called	O
the	O
Town	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
4	O
miles	O
in	O
circuit	O
,	O
&	O
strongly	O
&	O
curiously	O
fortified	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
3	O
Dutch	O
Churches	O
--	O
none	O
for	O
Roman	O
Catholics	O
,	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
here	O
.	O
This	O
City	O
(	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
acct	O
..	O
published	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Dutch	O
from	O
ye-	O
Spania	O
d	O
r	O
ds	O
in	O
1632	O
,	O
&	O
retaken	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
1673	O
,	O
who	O
restored	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Dutch	O
by	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
Nemigen	B-place
in	O
1679	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
since	O
continued	O
in	O
their	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
Thursday	O
15	O
August	O
1776	O
Left	O
Maestritch	B-place
after	O
breakfast	O
,	O
a	O
tolerable	O
road	O
but	O
no	O
Pavé	O
or	O
rows	O
of	O
Trees	O
--	O
N.B	O
.	O
the	O
Road	O
from	O
Calais	B-place
to	O
near	O
M	B-place
:	I-place
is	O
paved	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Streets	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
pavement	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
broad	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Road	O
equal	O
to	O
our	O
best	O
turnpike	O
roads	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
(	O
In	O
Winter	O
or	O
rainy	O
Weather	O
they	O
drive	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
.	O
The	O
Postilions	O
wear	O
enormous	O
boots	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
are	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
covered	O
with	O
leather	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
these	O
Boots	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
Inn-yard	O
at	O
Calais	B-place
&	O
the	O
Postilions	O
just	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
mount	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
thrusting	O
their	O
legs	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
shoes	O
on	O
their	O
feet	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
refrain	O
laughing	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
amused	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Novel	O
sight	O
of	O
Postilions	O
with	O
long	O
grises	O
dangling	O
down	O
their	O
backs	O
&	O
Cocked	O
3	O
Cornered	O
Hats	O
--	O
they	O
use	O
short	O
ha	O
d	O
n	O
dle	O
whips	O
with	O
long	O
lashes	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
thick	O
near	O
the	O
handle	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
dexterously	O
crack	O
several	O
times	O
wth	O
.	O
considerable	O
noise	O
when	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
or	O
arrive	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Boots	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
more	O
useful	O
than	O
laughable	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
calculated	O
to	O
save	O
a	O
limb	O
from	O
being	O
fractured	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
paved	O
road	O
.	O
)	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
Village	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
usual	O
humanity	O
,	O
to	O
rest	O
the	O
horses	O
--	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Village	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
Cold	O
meat	O
&	O
good	O
Boullie	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
made	O
an	O
excellent	O
meal	O
--	O
The	O
Road	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
is	O
hilly	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
country	O
on	O
are	O
wooded	O
--	O
(	O
The	O
roads	O
in	O
Flanders	B-place
being	O
flat	O
it	O
appeared	O
ridicoulous	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
slow	O
snail-like	O
pace	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Postilions	O
if	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
least	O
,	O
almost	O
imperceptible	O
,	O
rise	O
of	O
ground	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
road	O
near	O
Aix	B-place
is	O
bad	O
--	O
the	O
surrounding	O
country	O
beautiful	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
Great	O
Hotel	O
kept	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
where	O
Louis	B-pers
the	I-pers
14th	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
found	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
suit	O
of	O
apartments	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
&	O
their	O
party	O
,	O
viz	O
:	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
dining	O
Room	O
wth	O
.	O
painted	O
hangings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
stop	O
to	O
describe	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
I	O
feel	O
ashamed	O
to	O
occupy	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
&	O
largest	O
,	O
but	O
Dr	O
.	O
De	B-pers
Bigh	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
would	O
have	O
it	O
so	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
next	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
very	O
large	O
&	O
hung	O
wth	O
.	O
painted	O
hangings	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Daughters	O
were	O
lo	O
d	O
ged	O
in	O
this	O
Hotel	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
days	O
at	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
--	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth-	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
felt	O
herself	O
stout	O
enough	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
all	O
our	O
party	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
XBoughton	I-pers
to	O
see	O
the	O
Baths	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
oposite	O
to	O
this	O
Hotel	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
Emperor	O
's	O
Baths	O
Baths	O
which	O
are	O
at	O
a	O
greater	O
distance	O
--	O
we	O
lodge	O
near	O
the	O
Pump	O
,	O
Ball	O
room	O
,	O
&	O
walks	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mama	O
to	O
continue	O
my	O
journal	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
The	O
weather	O
very	O
Sultry	O
.	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
is	O
sovere	O
g	O
i	O
gn	O
State	O
of	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
&	O
an	O
Imperial	O
City	O
--	O
large	O
not	O
handsome	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
the	O
discoverer	O
of	O
the	O
hot	O
spring	O
--	O
The	O
Baths	O
are	O
large	O
,	O
handsome	O
&	O
convenient	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
particularly	O
beneficial	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
afflicted	O
by	O
Palsey	O
or	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
the	O
water	O
is	O
so	O
strongly	O
impregnated	O
with	O
Sulphur	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
smell	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
open	O
my	O
bed-Room	O
Windows	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Baths	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
Court	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
or	O
street	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
water	O
at	O
the	O
Emperors	O
Baths	O
are	O
so	O
hot	O
as	O
require	O
sipping	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
drunk	O
as	O
the	O
water	O
from	O
the	O
Pump	O
near	O
ye	O
Hotel	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
cooler	O
.	O
Friday	O
16	O
th	O
August	O
1776	O
Germany	B-place
During	O
some	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
awful	O
Storm	O
of	O
Thunder	O
,	O
Rain	O
Lightning	O
&	O
Hail	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
particularly	O
affected	O
by	O
Thunder	O
but	O
the	O
lightning	O
flash	O
'd	O
so	O
terribly	O
on	O
me	O
in	O
Bed	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
thought	O
over	O
those	O
lines	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
in	O
her	O
little	O
Book	O
of	O
poems	O
,	O
she	O
wrote	O
them	O
during	O
a	O
storm	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
--	O
they	O
begin	O
,	O
“	O
Let	O
coward	O
guilt	O
wth	O
pallid	O
fear	O
”	O
Hymn	O
,	O
found	O
for	O
example	O
in	O
Lindley	O
Murray	O
(	O
ed	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
1802	O
)	O
The	O
English	O
reader	O
,	O
part	O
II	O
p.266	O
.	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
:	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Pump	O
,	O
this	O
Morng	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
glaſses	O
of	O
water	O
--	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
chiefly	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lyttleton	I-pers
&	O
The	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
Charlemagne	I-pers
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
the	O
friend	O
(	O
&	O
formerly	O
Secretary	O
)	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	O
paid	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
a	O
visit	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
w	O
a	O
i	O
s	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
superior	O
political	O
abilities	O
--	O
but	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
voice	O
and	O
countenance	O
are	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
prepossing	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
tall	O
,	O
thin	O
,	O
&	O
most	O
ungainly	O
&	O
aw	O
kward	O
.	O
there	O
is	O
however	O
great	O
shrewdneſs	O
in	O
his	O
eyes	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
squeezed	O
up	O
by	O
laughing	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
does	O
often	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
no	O
very	O
harmonious	O
tones	O
.	O
Saturday	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
1776	O
We	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Pump	O
--	O
people	O
take	O
Magnesia	O
&	O
Sulphur	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
they	O
intend	O
drinking	O
the	O
water	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
Walked	O
on	O
the	O
Parade	O
made	O
acquaintance	O
wth-	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
(	O
she	O
has	O
an	O
elegant	O
figure	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
handsome	O
--	O
Fine	O
dark	O
brown	O
hair	O
wch	O
.	O
grows	O
well	O
on	O
her	O
forehead	O
--	O
face	O
oval	O
--	O
Nose	O
rather	O
Acquiline	O
,	O
eyes	O
well	O
cut	O
,	O
dark	O
haz	O
el	O
le	O
--	O
fine	O
eye-brows	O
--	O
good	O
teeth	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
--	O
also	O
with	O
a	O
polite	O
old	O
French	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
we	O
hear	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
consequence	O
&	O
very	O
rich	O
--	O
his	O
Daughter	O
just	O
gone	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
--	O
After	O
Dinner	O
we	O
walked	O
to	O
a	O
Convent	O
in	O
a	O
Village	O
or	O
little	O
Town	O
called	O
Spa	B-place
--	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Bourchet	B-place
it	O
is	O
calld	O
an	O
Abbaye	O
founded	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Ladies	O
are	O
Noble	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
who	O
,	O
obligingly	O
,	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
has	O
the	O
air	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
high	O
fashion	O
and	O
appears	O
amiable	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Abbeſs	O
and	O
,	O
only	O
,	O
ten	O
Ladies	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
leave	O
of	O
absence	O
once	O
a	O
year	O
to	O
visit	O
their	O
distant	O
Relations	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
have	O
liberty	O
to	O
pay	O
visits	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
&	O
receive	O
company	O
:	O
each	O
have	O
4	O
Rooms	O
.	O
wch	O
appeared	O
but	O
shabbily	O
furnished	O
,	O
&	O
each	O
a	O
Garden	O
with	O
paltry	O
pictures	O
&	O
Prints	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
walls	O
white	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
on	O
their	O
own	O
fortunes	O
,	O
each	O
have	O
a	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
--	O
or	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
stile	O
,	O
a	O
Ladys	O
Maid	O
--	O
A	O
Table	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
requisite	O
for	O
their	O
Board	O
is	O
provided	O
for	O
them	O
free	O
cost	O
--	O
They	O
have	O
lately	O
built	O
a	O
large	O
handsome	O
Chapel	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
just	O
completed	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
hot	O
spring	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
wch	O
.	O
boils	O
an	O
Egg	O
in	O
3	O
Minutes	O
--	O
it	O
smells	O
strong	O
of	O
Sulphur	O
.	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
C——	I-place
Aug	O
15	O
th	O
to	O
29	O
th	O
p.20-41	O
Aix	B-place
Aug	O
29	O
th	O
Oct	O
11	O
th	O
42-62	O
Spa	B-place
Oct	O
11	O
th	O
13	O
th	O
65	O
Liege	B-place
15	O
Louvain	B-place
16	O
17	O
70	O
Brussels	B-place
Ghent	B-place
Lille	B-place
25	O
S	B-place
Omers	I-place
I	O
left	O
off	O
my	O
journal	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
--	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
-	O
walked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
on	O
the	O
Esplanade	O
met	O
Emperor	B-pers
's	I-pers
Otho	I-pers
2d	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
3d	B-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
English	O
and	O
Roman	O
Catholics	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
likes	O
a	O
little	O
french	O
Hair	O
Dreſser	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
tell	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
every	O
one	O
here	O
if	O
you	O
chose	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Estate	O
in	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
and	O
is	O
shabby	O
&	O
pernicious	O
,	O
chiefly	O
residing	O
on	O
the	O
Continent	O
--	O
Henrys	B-pers
2	I-pers
is	O
his	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
married	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
13	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
3d	B-pers
of	O
England	B-place
--	O
she	O
is	O
handsome	O
,	O
has	O
delicate	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
looks	O
very	O
unhappy	O
.	O
Met	O
also	O
Madame	B-pers
Platenburgh	I-pers
a	O
pleasant	O
old	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
rich	O
--	O
Finnancier	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
Uncle	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
visit	O
York	B-place
next	O
year	O
Winter	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
--	O
(	O
a	O
Bed	O
chamber	O
woman	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
)	O
and	O
her	O
Eldest	O
,	O
and	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Salvin	I-pers
)	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
after	O
dinner	O
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
a	O
Village	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Bourchet	B-place
to	O
see	O
an	O
Abbaye	O
founded	O
by	O
the	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bartin	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
there	O
are	O
only	O
ten	O
Ladies	O
including	O
the	O
Abbeſs	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
Noble	O
;	O
Madame	B-pers
Monboisier	I-pers
who	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Chapel	O
&	O
c.	O
is	O
remarkably	O
well	O
bred	O
&	O
polite	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
have	O
4	O
Rooms	O
a	O
Garden	O
&	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
allowed	O
to	O
visit	O
their	O
Relations	O
&	O
friends	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
also	O
a	O
very	O
ample	O
table	O
kept	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
enquired	O
much	O
after	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
:	O
She	O
made	O
us	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
another	O
visit	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
She	O
she	O
shewed	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
drinking	O
tea	O
,	O
they	O
joined	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
attended	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
boiling	O
Well	O
--	O
The	O
water	O
is	O
of	O
that	O
degree	O
of	O
heat	O
as	O
to	O
boil	O
an	O
Egg	O
in	O
3	O
minutes	O
;	O
We	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
to	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Aſsembly	O
,	O
wch	O
,	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
this	O
Hotel	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
few	O
people	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
Jane	B-pers
and	O
myself	O
were	O
to	O
Bathe	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
so	O
early	O
that	O
Cards	O
were	O
not	O
begun	O
--	O
We	O
made	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
a	O
Emperors	B-pers
Otto	I-pers
a	O
handsome	O
interesting	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Madame	B-pers
Platenburg	I-pers
,	O
&	O
another	O
Lady	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
civil	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Bathing	O
very	O
agreeablye	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
attendants	O
and	O
accomodations	O
excellent	O
.	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
drank	O
the	O
proper	O
quantity	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
3	O
glaſses	O
,	O
before	O
breakfast	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
breakfast	O
till	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Glaſs	O
,	O
Madame	B-pers
Platenburgh	I-pers
calls	O
me	O
up	O
every	O
Morning	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
walked	O
to	O
the	O
Emperor	O
's	O
Bath	O
es	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Effingham	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
honors	O
me	O
by	O
much	O
notice	O
)	O
he	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
very	O
clever	O
man	O
but	O
not	O
an	O
agreeable	O
one	O
to	O
suit	O
my	O
taste	O
)	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
Marquise	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Bedoyere	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
After	O
breakfast	O
Mrs	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
(	O
the	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Tutor	O
)	O
read	O
prayers	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
Sermon	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
drank	O
tea	O
wth-	O
us	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
left	O
us	O
early	O
&	O
was	O
so	O
gracious	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
Daughters	O
remain	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
spent	O
the	O
Eveg	O
very	O
cheerfully	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
:	O
Monday	O
Spent	O
the	O
Morng	O
most	O
comfortably	O
with	O
Dr	O
.	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Butin	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Young	O
men	O
&	O
their	O
Tutor	O
otherwise	O
engaged	O
--	O
I	O
bathed	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
afterwards	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſsed	O
by	O
a	O
celebrated	O
performer	O
on	O
heads	O
of	O
this	O
Town	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
some	O
good	O
humoured	O
acquaintance	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
laugh	O
&	O
Goſsip	O
till	O
7	O
when	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ball	O
,	O
I	O
danced	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
a	O
French	O
Count	O
&	O
two	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
dance	O
wth	O
:	O
them	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
my	O
partner	O
--	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
was	O
a	O
queer	O
looking	O
mortal	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
--	O
we	O
danced	O
English	O
Country	O
Dances	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
8	O
couple	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
gave	O
tea	O
to	O
all	O
our	O
party	O
,	O
he	O
lamented	O
that	O
his	O
lameneſs	O
prevented	O
his	O
opening	O
the	O
Ball	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
These	O
little	O
parties	O
are	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
a	O
thousand	O
time	O
more	O
cheerful	O
than	O
a	O
fine	O
Ball	O
or	O
great	O
aſsembly	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
danced	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Monr	B-pers
Butin	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
genteel	O
handsome	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Small	O
Blond	O
Hats	O
,	O
&	O
quantities	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
worn	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
is	O
the	O
general	O
fashion	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
both	O
smart	O
&	O
elegant	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
too	O
bad	O
to	O
walk	O
much	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
amused	O
us	O
by	O
teaching	O
us	O
Taro	O
--	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
w	O
as	O
er	O
e	O
as	O
interested	O
about	O
our	O
fou	O
r	O
th	O
part	O
of	O
farthings	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
21	O
walk	O
'd	O
wth-	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Butin	I-pers
&	O
The	B-pers
Marquise	I-pers
De	I-pers
La	I-pers
Bedoyer	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
visits	O
,	O
see	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Needle	O
Manufacturing	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
curious	O
--	O
we	O
dined	O
early	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Le	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Summit	O
of	O
a	O
Mountain	O
it	O
was	O
difficult	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
climb	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
rewarded	O
for	O
my	O
labour	O
by	O
seeing	O
a	O
beautiful	O
&	O
extensive	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Mountain	O
saw	O
many	O
foſsil	O
shells	O
--	O
and	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
aromatic	O
herbs	O
which	O
perfumed	O
the	O
air	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eveg	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
tot	O
he	O
aſsembly	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Thursday	O
22	O
Went	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
the	O
amiable	O
Mr	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
--	O
hired	O
some	O
French	O
Books	O
at	O
the	O
Book	O
Sellers	O
.	O
--	O
saw	O
the	O
Market	O
place	O
and	O
la	O
Grand	O
Place	O
where	O
their	O
is	O
a	O
Noble	O
State	O
House	O
or	O
Maison	O
de	O
Ville	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
la	O
Grand	O
place	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
beautiful	O
fountain	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
seen	O
in	O
every	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
Town	O
we	O
have	O
gone	O
through	O
remarkable	O
Pumps	O
and	O
Fountains	O
.	O
We	O
dined	O
early	O
&	O
went	O
afterwards	O
with	O
the	B-pers
2	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Foster	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
ancient	O
building	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
we	O
have	O
yet	O
seen	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
any	O
paintings	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
great	O
store	O
of	O
Relics	O
,	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
showed	O
us	O
every	O
thing	O
worthy	O
observation	O
--	O
b	O
q	O
uantities	O
of	O
celebrated	O
Relics	O
,	O
Bones	O
of	O
Charlema	O
n	O
gne	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
inclosed	O
in	O
gold	O
cases	O
&	O
studdied	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
pearls	O
,	O
onyx	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Onyx	O
of	O
an	O
uncommon	O
size	O
,	O
a	O
Cameo	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
his	O
wives	O
heads	O
;	O
Marquise	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Bedoyere	I-pers
is	O
buried	O
in	O
this	O
Cathedral	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Monument	O
--	O
a	O
large	O
square	O
pavement	O
marks	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
:	O
In	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
Chapels	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Pulpit	O
of	O
Maſsy	O
gold	O
enriched	O
with	O
precious	O
stones	O
&	O
gems	O
--	O
one	O
Onyx	O
measures	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
foot	O
:	O
L'Archi	O
Pretre	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Crowns	O
that	O
the	O
Infanta	O
Isabella	O
presented	O
to	O
ye-	O
Virgin	O
Mary	O
&	O
the	O
young	O
Saviour	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
wear	O
on	O
high	O
days	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
ornamented	O
with	O
fine	O
diamond	O
&	O
pearls	O
&	O
their	O
form	O
is	O
beautiful	O
,	O
she	O
she	O
likewise	O
presented	O
the	O
Vestments	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
Sattin	O
finely	O
embroidered	O
with	O
color	O
'd	O
flowers	O
,	O
and	O
quantities	O
of	O
White	O
Lillies	O
in	O
small	O
pearls	O
--	O
the	O
border	O
is	O
almost	O
grounded	O
with	O
small	O
pearls	O
,	O
diamonds	O
and	O
large	O
pearls	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
hangings	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Chair	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
the	O
gift	O
of	O
some	O
Bishop	O
(	O
I	O
'dont	O
just	O
now	O
recollect	O
his	O
name	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Velvet	O
embroidered	O
with	O
pearls	O
&	O
gold	O
.	O
We	O
noticed	O
the	O
Stone	O
Chair	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
on	O
wch	O
.	O
all	O
the	O
Emperors	O
are	O
seated	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
crowned	O
,	O
near	O
it	O
are	O
two	O
fine	O
Verd	O
antique	O
pillars	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
beautiful	O
Granite	O
.	O
Over	O
the	O
great	O
Altar	O
is	O
the	O
Escutcheon	O
of	O
La	B-pers
Marquise	I-pers
&	O
L'Archi	B-pers
Pretre	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
Otho	I-pers
was	O
burried	O
they	O
sent	O
his	O
to	O
be	O
placed	O
under	O
The	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
Charlemagne	I-pers
--	O
In	O
this	O
Choir	O
is	O
the	O
Tomb	O
of	O
Charlemagne	B-pers
.	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
a	O
small	O
Organ	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
the	I-pers
13	I-pers
returned	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
tea	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Agreeably	O
Rooms	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
Music	O
,	O
14th-	B-pers
very	O
good	O
naturedly	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Violin	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
dance	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
aſsured	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Procés	O
commenced	O
against	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
infringing	O
the	O
rights	O
of	O
the	O
Band	O
of	O
Musicians	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
paid	O
by	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
made	O
this	O
appear	O
ridiculous	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Musicians	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Aſsembly	O
rooms	O
was	O
because	O
they	O
thought	O
there	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
Gentlemen	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
dancing	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Card	O
Rooms	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
no	O
party	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
our	O
own	O
&	O
were	O
amused	O
by	O
the	O
agreeable	O
Marquise	O
teaching	O
us	O
some	O
french	O
recreations	O
--	O
similar	O
to	O
Blind	O
Man	O
's	O
Buff	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
have	O
beg	O
'd	O
Lewis	B-pers
the	I-pers
15th	I-pers
to	O
a	O
me	O
to	O
add	O
a	O
Postcript	O
to	O
her	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
almost	O
scruple	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Permiſsion	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
takes	O
up	O
ye	O
:	O
Paper	O
She	O
would	O
otherwise	O
fill	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
Letters	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
in	O
as	O
few	O
words	O
as	O
poſsible	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
aſsured	O
how	O
sensibly	O
I	O
feel	O
my	O
obligations	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
ye	O
:	O
Treasure	O
you	O
intrust	O
me	O
with	O
=	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
delightful	O
Companion	O
I	O
ever	O
travelled	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
hope	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
not	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
this	O
little	O
Excursion	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Waters	O
&	O
Bathing	O
seem	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
the	I-pers
14th	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
charmed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
admired	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
careful	O
Chaperone	O
.	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
trés	O
chere	O
Madme	O
:	O
nous	O
parlons	O
Francais	O
du	O
matin	O
jusqua	O
'	O
u	O
Soir	O
,	O
mi	O
Lord	O
vous	O
presente	O
ses	O
baisemains	O
--	O
&	O
permettez	O
que	O
Je	O
vous	O
offre	O
mes	O
d	O
R	O
espects	O
&	O
toute	O
la	O
reconnaisance	O
,	O
qui	O
vous	O
est	O
dit	O
,	O
de	O
la	O
part	O
de	O
votre	O
Servante	O
Obbeeist	O
&	O
tres	O
humble	O
the	B-pers
German	I-pers
Emperor	I-pers
Otho	I-pers
a	O
thousand	O
Thanks	O
for	O
ye	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
my	O
Child	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Taro	O
-table	O
in	O
the	O
rooms	O
and	O
3	O
desperate	O
Gamesters	O
hold	O
the	O
Bank	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
painful	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
agitation	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
play	O
,	O
both	O
men	O
&	O
women	O
.	O
France	B-place
Friday	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
walkd	O
with	O
The	B-pers
Marquise	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Bedoyere	I-pers
to	O
a	O
Church	O
upon	O
a	O
Hill	O
near	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
charming	O
prospect	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
who	O
resides	O
in	O
a	O
Cottage	O
near	O
the	O
Church	O
brought	O
us	O
chairs	O
and	O
without	O
our	O
asking	O
her	O
went	O
&	O
milked	O
her	O
Cow	O
,	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
&	O
waiting	O
for	O
the	O
milk	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
poor	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
sick	O
infant	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
two	O
children	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
a	O
Rosary	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
holy	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Candles	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cottage	O
&	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Candles	O
lighted	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
wth-	O
an	O
expreſsive	O
countenance	O
of	O
deep	O
affliction	O
mad	O
a	O
sign	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
and	O
to	O
our	O
great	O
surprise	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
filled	O
with	O
Straw	O
&	O
Wheat	O
like	O
a	O
granary	O
Barn	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
got	O
through	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Barn	O
without	O
any	O
partition	O
was	O
a	O
Chapel	O
filled	O
with	O
Crucifixes	O
and	O
wretched	O
daubs	O
of	O
pictures	O
--	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
lay	O
an	O
image	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
as	O
dead	O
--	O
dreſsed	O
in	O
mourning	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Virgin	O
&	O
Two	O
Saints	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
also	O
in	O
Mourning	O
,	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Altar	O
,	O
a	O
Pulpit	O
,	O
Confeſsional	O
chair	O
&	O
c.	O
decorated	O
in	O
as	O
miserable	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
the	O
Images	O
;	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
was	O
a	O
Hay	O
loft	O
,	O
filled	O
.	O
The	O
poor	O
young	O
Woman	O
placed	O
her	O
Candles	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
figure	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
knelt	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Sick	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
--	O
her	O
two	O
other	O
children	O
knelt	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
silent	O
but	O
appeared	O
to	O
offer	O
up	O
prayers	O
with	O
a	O
devotion	O
that	O
was	O
truly	O
affecting	O
,	O
Such	O
a	O
scene	O
is	O
not	O
easily	O
described	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
easily	O
,	O
be	O
effaced	O
from	O
my	O
memory	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Chapel	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
Some	O
Gothic	O
architecture	O
--	O
&	O
an	O
open	O
arched	O
Vault	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Stone	O
Tomb	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
something	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
very	O
fervant	O
wishes	O
that	O
her	O
prayers	O
might	O
be	O
granted	O
.	O
I	O
bathed	O
at	O
one	O
,	O
.	O
We	O
dined	O
early	O
and	O
walked	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
where	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
House	O
called	O
L'Ceriviſse	O
here	O
there	O
are	O
Baths	O
&	O
Vapeur	O
Baths	O
hotter	O
than	O
those	O
at	O
Bourchet	B-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Garden	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Needle	O
Merchant	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
Garden	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
figures	O
some	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
as	O
life	O
,	O
of	O
Men	O
&	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
composed	O
of	O
Shell	O
work	O
,	O
finished	O
in	O
a	O
stile	O
you	O
could	O
hardly	O
imagine	O
--	O
notwithstanding	O
Dear	O
Mama	O
your	O
own	O
skill	O
and	O
taste	O
in	O
Shell	O
work	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
large	O
Grotto	O
where	O
some	O
Officers	O
were	O
regaling	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
the	O
inside	O
was	O
entirely	O
covered	O
with	O
beautiful	O
Shell-work	O
of	O
fruits	O
,	O
flowers	O
and	O
other	O
ornaments	O
,	O
in	O
shells	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
figures	O
likewise	O
,	O
the	O
drapery	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
so	O
well	O
executed	O
as	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
a	O
short	O
distance	O
like	O
painting	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
£	O
30,00	O
has	O
been	O
expended	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
P	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
must	O
be	O
a	O
rich	O
Man	O
for	O
Aix	B-place
.	O
NB	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
admire	O
the	O
needle	O
--	O
Merchants	O
taste	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Man	O
.	O
--	O
Saturday	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
tete	O
à	O
tète	O
all	O
Morng	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
tea	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
great	O
form	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
wch	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
fidgets	O
most	O
terribly	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Kounan	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
they	O
all	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
Commerce	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
scribble	O
till	O
supper	O
time	O
Sunday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
prayers	O
early	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kounan	I-pers
read	O
an	O
excellent	O
Sermon	O
:	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
through	O
the	O
principla	O
streets	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
preparations	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
making	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
Spectacle	O
,	O
viz	O
:	O
the	O
Reception	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Students	O
of	O
a	O
College	O
of	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
chosen	O
every	O
year	O
out	O
of	O
of	O
4	O
Colledges	O
and	O
6000	O
Students	O
who	O
has	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
Merit	O
--	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
receive	O
these	O
marks	O
of	O
honor	O
is	O
18	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
distinguished	O
himself	O
worthy	O
of	O
the	O
prize	O
in	O
several	O
branches	O
of	O
learning	O
particularly	O
philosophy	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
enter	O
Louvain	B-place
this	O
day	O
in	O
triumph	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
received	O
wth-	O
every	O
demonstration	O
of	O
joy	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
native	O
place	O
--	O
there	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
one	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
worthy	O
of	O
this	O
prize	O
honor	O
140	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
adjudged	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
The	O
Streets	O
through	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
paſs	O
are	O
decorated	O
with	O
young	O
trees	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
4	O
feet	O
aſsunder	O
,	O
--	O
fine	O
Shrubs	O
are	O
put	O
out	O
at	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
Doors	O
,	O
in	O
pots	O
,	O
tubs	O
&	O
c	O
We	O
drove	O
through	O
26	O
triumphal	O
Arches	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
different	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
coloured	O
&	O
white	O
Egg-shells	O
beautifully	O
&	O
simply	O
entermixt	O
wth-	O
Ever-greens	O
--	O
others	O
equally	O
pretty	O
with	O
flowers	O
,	O
paintings	O
--	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
&	O
Feathers	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
,	O
is	O
embroidered	O
upon	O
Coloured	O
flags	O
with	O
inscriptions	O
of	O
his	O
abilities	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
others	O
with	O
tin	O
Silvered	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
hundreds	O
of	O
colored	O
lamps	O
prepared	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
every	O
thing	O
yt	O
.	O
can	O
look	O
most	O
gay	O
--	O
As	O
we	O
re	O
w	O
ere	O
paſsing	O
his	O
Father	O
s	O
House	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
's	I-pers
ordered	O
the	O
carriage	O
to	O
stop	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
look	O
at	O
its	O
decorations	O
,	O
&	O
seeing	O
some	O
Servants	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
handsome	O
meſsage	O
(	O
in	O
all	O
our	O
names	O
)	O
of	O
congratulations	O
on	O
an	O
event	O
wch	O
.	O
must	O
be	O
sensibly	O
felt	O
by	O
Parents	O
--	O
(	O
was	O
not	O
this	O
amiable	O
in	O
Mr-	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
?	O
but	O
a	O
heart	O
benevolent	O
and	O
overflowing	O
with	O
the	O
milk	O
of	O
human	O
kindneſs	O
like	O
his	O
is	O
always	O
on	O
the	O
alert	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
family	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
but	O
the	O
Mother	O
&	O
Sister	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
us	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
able	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
proceſsion	O
,	O
afterwards	O
join	O
in	O
the	O
cavalcade	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
2	O
thus	O
1	O
able	O
3	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
where	O
Te	O
Deum	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
finely	O
performed	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
ride	O
through	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Streets	O
&	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Hotel	O
de	O
Ville	O
,	O
where	O
ye-	O
Burge	O
Maester	O
,	O
&	O
Towns	O
People	O
are	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
speech	O
in	O
Latin	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
magnificent	O
Supper	O
:	O
every	O
Town	O
he	O
paſses	O
through	O
from	O
Aix	B-place
make	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
a	O
considerable	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
heard	O
£	O
2,000	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
place	O
of	O
any	O
Prince	O
,	O
Duke	O
&	O
c.	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
gives	O
him	O
the	O
upper	O
hand	O
.	O
A	O
Silver	O
Basin	O
&	O
Ewer	O
are	O
likewise	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Town	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
of	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
is	O
a	O
Merchant	O
worth	O
£	O
6,000	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
esteemed	O
a	O
worthy	O
respectable	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
Bells	O
ringing	O
and	O
guns	O
firing	O
in	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
dreſsed	O
myself	O
as	O
gay	O
&	O
fine	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
Josephus	B-pers
Widlt	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
(	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
had	O
a	O
cold	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
venture	O
out	O
)	O
again	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
&	O
Prince	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
of	I-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
in	O
another	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Father	O
s	O
House	O
through	O
an	O
innumerable	O
crowd	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
aſsembled	O
,	O
Uncles	O
,	O
Cousins	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
The	O
Mother	O
appears	O
a	O
plain	O
sensible	O
Woman	O
&	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
happineſs	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
--	O
greatest	O
propriety	O
--	O
the	O
Proceſsion	O
arrived	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
one	O
--	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
is	O
handsome	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
charming	O
countenance	O
full	O
of	O
sense	O
and	O
sweetneſs	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
a	O
White	O
Horse	O
--	O
had	O
an	O
air	O
of	O
Modesty	O
,	O
bowed	O
and	O
smiled	O
gracefully	O
and	O
waved	O
a	O
Branch	O
of	O
Laurel	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
hand	O
--	O
we	O
followed	O
the	O
proceſsion	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
and	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
kiſsing	O
our	O
hands	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
paſsed	O
our	O
windows	O
in	O
Calvalade	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
Town	O
is	O
illuminated	O
;	O
Balls	O
&	O
feasting	O
will	O
continue	O
some	O
days	O
;	O
Prince	B-pers
Chs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
supped	O
wth-	O
us	O
.	O
Monday	O
26	O
August	O
Walking	O
Bathing	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
dined	O
early	O
--	O
All	O
our	O
party	O
went	O
to	O
tea	O
at	O
our	B-pers
favourite	I-pers
Marquise	I-pers
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Concert	O
,	O
he	O
played	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
--	O
and	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
treated	O
us	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
sweet	O
songs	O
;	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
supper	O
We	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
polite	O
meſsage	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Marquise	I-pers
(	O
the	O
young	O
Student	O
is	O
so	O
stiled	O
)	O
to	O
envite	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ball	O
at	O
the	O
Jesuists	O
'	O
College	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
after	O
making	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
our	O
dreſs	O
--	O
we	O
drove	O
through	O
a	O
great	O
concourse	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
every	O
Tree	O
had	O
a	O
Lamp	O
stuck	O
in	O
it	O
wch	O
.	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
decorations	O
had	O
a	O
beautiful	O
effect	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Ball	O
,	O
I	O
danced	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
de	I-pers
La	I-pers
Bedoyere	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
dancer	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
felt	O
more	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
declined	O
other	O
partners	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
dancing	O
a	O
Cottilion	O
with	O
the	O
Primus	O
who	O
preſsed	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
the	O
entertainment	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
Ball	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
offered	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
chaperon	O
if	O
if	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
I	O
prefer̄	O
'd	O
returning	O
home	O
wth-	O
the	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
;	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Ball	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
a	O
late	O
hour	O
at	O
Louvain	B-place
.	O
Marquise	B-pers
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
supped	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
very	O
merry	O
we	O
all	O
were	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1776	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
In	O
reply	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Primus	I-pers
's	O
question	O
pray	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Flemish	O
Farmers	O
never	O
let	O
their	O
Lands	O
lie	O
fallow	O
but	O
sew	O
them	O
succeſsively	O
wth	O
.	O
different	O
kinds	O
of	O
Grain	O
,	O
&	O
pulse	O
,	O
as	O
best	O
suits	O
the	O
Ground	O
which	O
they	O
occasionally	O
aſsist	O
by	O
manure	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
sparing	O
.	O
To	O
continue	O
my	O
journal	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
all	O
Morning	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Marquise	I-pers
being	O
a	O
little	O
indisposed	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Jesuits	O
College	O
where	O
the	O
Ball	O
was	O
yesterday	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
pictures	O
--	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
indifferent	O
Copies	O
--	O
from	O
good	O
&	O
bad	O
originals	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hotel	O
de	O
Ville	O
or	O
State	O
House	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
building	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
large	O
Showy	O
Rooms	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
Pictures	O
not	O
worth	O
looking	O
at	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
however	O
a	O
large	O
Picture	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
subject	O
--	O
The	O
last	O
judg-ment	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
wretched	O
condition	O
--	O
Another	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
The	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
--	O
Representing	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
giving	O
the	O
Charter	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Magistrates	O
of	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
--	O
In	O
the	O
great	O
Room	O
is	O
an	O
interesting	O
Picture	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
well	O
painted	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
persons	O
aſsembled	O
at	O
the	O
Congreſs	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
Peace	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1748	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
the	O
English	O
Minister	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
likewise	O
single	O
Portraits	O
of	O
each	O
Ambaſsador	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
different	O
Nations	O
employ	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
badly	O
painted	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Hotel	O
found	O
a	O
polite	O
sensible	O
,	O
agreeable	O
Man	O
in	O
conversation	O
wth	O
Ly.-	B-pers
D——	I-pers
he	O
is	O
the	O
Polish	O
Ambaſsador	O
at	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
--	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
visit	O
as	O
having	O
lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Hotel	O
--	O
--	O
now	O
in	O
Rome	B-place
or	O
London	B-place
this	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
leſs	O
than	O
impertinent	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
ye	O
saying	O
is	O
,	O
different	O
Countries	O
different	O
Customs	O
.	O
27	O
August	O
1776	O
Rubens	B-pers
,	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
frm	O
.	O
England	B-place
to	O
Spa	B-place
,	O
Vandyck	B-pers
invited	O
him	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
his	O
conversation	O
was	O
entertaining	O
&	O
interesting	O
--	O
he	O
related	O
many	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
the	O
celebrated	O
the	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
Charlemagne	I-pers
--	O
This	O
singular	O
eccentric	O
characte	O
d	O
r	O
was	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Congreſs	O
:	O
--	O
The	O
Germans	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
time	O
for	O
relaxation	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
great	O
surprise	O
that	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
always	O
got	O
their	O
busineſs	O
forward	O
yet	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
pay	O
proper	O
attention	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
spent	O
his	O
Mornings	O
at	O
Cricket	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Wortley	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
held	O
a	O
Farro	O
Bank	O
--	O
however	O
Lord	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
neglect	O
their	O
duty	O
,	O
&	O
aſsured	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
3	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
written	O
fair	O
by	O
Ld-	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
task	O
wch	O
.	O
would	O
have	O
every	O
Moment	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
s	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
accomplished	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
told	O
us	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
for	O
fact	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
had	O
recd-	O
information	O
of	O
his	O
Legal	O
Wife	O
's	O
death	O
--	O
he	O
sent	O
Advertisements	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
Newspapers	O
--	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
would	O
marry	O
--	O
he	O
wanting	O
to	O
disappoint	O
the	O
next	O
heirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
immediately	O
proposed	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	B-place
wch-	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
wife	O
(	O
for	O
as	O
a	O
Mahometan	O
i	O
n	O
had	O
several	O
wives	O
)	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
Poison	O
wch-	O
caused	O
his	O
death	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
truth	O
in	O
other	O
reports	O
circulated	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
choked	O
by	O
a	O
Bone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
's	O
spirit	O
dared	O
not	O
attempt	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
genius	O
to	O
accomplish	O
every	O
thing	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
related	O
the	O
following	O
anecdote	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Merchant	O
resident	O
at	O
England	B-place
who	O
had	O
a	O
beautiful	O
&	O
amiable	O
Wife	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
admired	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lady	O
and	O
got	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
Husband	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
particularly	O
agreeable	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
intimacy	O
soon	O
took	O
place	O
--	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
every	O
opportunity	O
to	O
make	O
love	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
truly	O
attached	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
who	O
in	O
return	O
loved	O
her	O
wth	O
ye	O
.	O
truest	O
affection	O
,	O
she	O
she	O
therefore	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
most	O
fatal	O
consequence	O
wd-	O
insue	O
should	O
the	O
infamous	O
treachery	O
of	O
this	O
insidious	O
friend	O
be	O
discovered	O
,	O
&	O
suffered	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
cruel	O
Martrydom	O
--	O
this	O
continued	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
finding	O
her	O
proof	O
against	O
all	O
his	O
wiles	O
changed	O
his	O
plan	O
&	O
became	O
respectful	O
,	O
distant	O
,	O
&	O
reserved	O
--	O
the	O
Lady	O
flattered	O
herself	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
grown	O
weary	O
of	O
persecuting	O
her	O
&	O
ashamed	O
of	O
the	O
part	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acting	O
--	O
&	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
prudence	O
to	O
conceal	O
his	O
Conduct	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
whose	O
partiallity	O
,	O
and	O
unbounded	O
confidence	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Montague	I-pers
was	O
without	O
bounds	O
.	O
Some	O
affairs	O
required	O
the	O
Merchant	O
s	O
personal	O
attendance	O
in	O
Venice	B-place
&	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
convenient	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
he	O
earnestly	O
entreated	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
to	O
be	O
her	O
proctetor	O
during	O
his	O
absence	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
he	O
thought	O
worthy	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
trust	O
.	O
&	O
departed	O
from	O
Holland	B-place
wth	O
.	O
a	O
lighter	O
heart	O
than	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
poſseſsed	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
imagined	O
)	O
so	O
true	O
a	O
frd-	O
The	O
Merchant	O
s	O
Wife	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
happy	O
at	O
this	O
arrangement	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
herself	O
to	O
awaken	O
suspicion	O
&	O
distrust	O
in	O
a	O
breast	O
whos	O
only	O
aim	O
was	O
to	O
promote	O
her	O
happineſs	O
--	O
he	O
not	O
only	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
highest	O
opinion	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
s	O
integrity	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
find	O
the	O
separation	O
leſs	O
tedious	O
by	O
having	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
so	O
calculated	O
to	O
amuse	O
by	O
the	O
brilliancy	O
of	O
his	O
wit	O
imagination	O
&	O
inexhaustible	O
fund	O
of	O
entertainment	O
by	O
he	O
poſseſsed	O
by	O
remembering	O
every	O
occurrence	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
extroadinary	O
life	O
,	O
--	O
(	O
The	O
vicious	O
part	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
however	O
always	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Guard	O
to	O
conceal	O
)	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Montague	I-pers
behaviour	O
,	O
toward	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
was	O
such	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
s	O
departure	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
&	O
had	O
almost	O
lost	O
recollection	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
base	O
--	O
conduct	O
--	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
state	O
when	O
she	O
recd-	O
a	O
letter	O
with	O
the	O
heart	O
breaking	O
intelligence	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
suddenly	O
ill	O
&	O
was	O
dead	O
Montague	B-pers
did	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
aſsuage	O
her	O
Grief	O
He	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
credit	O
the	O
report	O
but	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Venice	B-place
for	O
certificates	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
the	O
certainty	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
fact	O
could	O
be	O
known	O
--	O
Montagu	B-pers
wrote	O
--	O
the	O
fatal	O
certificate	O
arrived	O
--	O
Montagu	B-pers
s	O
whole	O
study	O
was	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
console	O
ye	O
.	O
wretched	O
Widow	O
--	O
after	O
a	O
decent	O
time	O
he	O
proposed	O
himself	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
his	O
unwearied	O
attention	O
deserved	O
some	O
recompence	O
&	O
who	O
could	O
she	O
so	O
properly	O
accept	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
loved	O
&	O
esteem	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
late	O
worthy	O
Husband	O
--	O
the	O
Widow	O
hesitated	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
she	O
lay	O
under	O
particular	O
obligations	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
rendered	O
himself	O
servicable	O
to	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
respect	O
to	O
her	O
affairs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
likewise	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
truly	O
lov	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
man	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
very	O
aſsidious	O
,	O
so	O
long	O
constant	O
--	O
she	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
criminality	O
of	O
his	O
first	O
offers	O
--	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
marry	O
him	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
expiration	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
&	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
approved	O
of	O
her	O
Residing	O
in	O
a	O
Convent	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
married	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Merchant	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
?	O
&	O
That	O
Montague	B-pers
had	O
practised	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
deceit	O
on	O
him	O
by	O
sendg	O
.	O
him	O
forged	O
certificates	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
s	O
death	O
--	O
whose	O
disposition	O
he	O
knew	O
wld	O
.	O
prevent	O
him	O
from	O
returning	O
to	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
died	O
--	O
This	O
adventure	O
was	O
near	O
5	O
Years	O
in	O
acting	O
--	O
some	O
preſsing	O
affairs	O
obliged	O
the	O
Merchant	O
to	O
revisit	O
Holland	B-place
,	O
judge	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
felt	O
on	O
finding	O
his	O
Wife	O
alive	O
&	O
Married	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
M——	I-pers
--	O
the	O
injured	O
pair	O
sought	O
for	O
redreſs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
escaped	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
Ambaſsador	O
screened	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
punishment	O
due	O
to	O
his	O
crimes	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
artful	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
that	O
could	O
happen	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
August	O
.	O
27	O
continued	O
After	O
dinner	O
all	O
our	O
party	O
wth	O
.	O
Montagu	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Montagu	B-pers
&	O
Montagu	B-pers
went	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
Comedy	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
Mile	O
&	O
½	O
from	O
Venice	B-place
--	O
the	O
Road	O
bad	O
--	O
the	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
.	O
--	O
one	O
large	O
house	O
like	O
an	O
Hotel	O
,	O
--	O
the	O
Country	O
romantic	O
--	O
The	O
Theatre	O
is	O
small	O
but	O
conveniently	O
contrived	O
--	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
every	O
act	O
the	O
company	O
go	O
go	O
into	O
Rooms	O
from	O
their	O
Boxes	O
--	O
where	O
is	O
Lemonade	O
and	O
various	O
kinds	O
of	O
refreshments	O
--	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Billiard	O
Table	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
another	O
a	O
Far̄o	O
bank	O
is	O
held	O
.	O
The	O
Petite	O
Piece	O
was	O
the	O
Pupile	O
of	O
Montagu	B-pers
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
indifferently	O
acted	O
--	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
Opera	O
s	O
of	O
ye	O
De	O
ſs	O
The	O
Man	O
who	O
performed	O
ye	O
.	O
Deserteur	O
had	O
good	O
action	O
&	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
judge	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
voice	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
actors	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
recommend	O
them	O
to	O
admiration	O
yet	O
they	O
recd	O
.	O
applause	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Rooms	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
dancing	O
as	O
the	O
Primus	O
had	O
engaged	O
the	O
musicians	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
jesuits	O
College	O
--	O
Montagu	B-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
--	I-pers
Standhope	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
28	O
August	O
I	O
again	O
accompanied	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
to	O
the	O
jesuits	O
Colledge	O
to	O
hunt	O
after	O
pictures	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
purchase	O
some	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
Paintings	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
moveables	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
--	O
the	O
jesuits	O
being	O
extirpated	O
--	O
we	O
roamed	O
about	O
the	O
immense	O
building	O
went	O
into	O
numberleſs	O
Rooms	O
,	O
all	O
looked	O
deserted	O
&	O
made	O
one	O
feel	O
quite	O
melancholy	O
--	O
Marquise	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Bedoyere	I-pers
could	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
Picture	O
worth	O
buying	O
--	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
the	O
jesuits	O
had	O
valuable	O
pictures	O
but	O
had	O
prudently	O
conveyed	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
secret	O
;	O
in	O
this	O
Diderot	B-pers
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hotel	O
de	O
Ville	O
or	O
Town	O
Hall	O
to	O
meet	O
The	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
Marquise	B-pers
de	I-pers
