TOKEN	NE
Boston	B-place
Aprill	O
12	O
th	O
1769	O
D	O
ear	O
Madam	O
If	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
has	O
reacht	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
'll	O
see	O
what	O
has	O
so	O
long	O
prevented	O
my	O
Answering	O
yr	O
last	O
Obligeing	O
Letter	O
I	O
hope	O
none	O
of	O
you	O
imputed	O
my	O
Sillence	O
to	O
any	O
want	O
of	O
Anxiety	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Welfare	O
of	O
friends	O
to	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
obliged	O
&	O
whom	O
we	O
regreate	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
likely	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
Seeing	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
find	O
you	O
all	O
Well	O
I	O
congratulate	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
Victory	O
you	O
have	O
obteined	O
in	O
Election	O
matters	O
:	O
I	O
gueſs	O
some	O
people	O
will	O
look	O
rather	O
Small	O
upon	O
the	O
Occaſsion	O
but	O
hope	O
Good	O
Neighbourhood	O
will	O
now	O
take	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Party	O
rage	O
in	O
yr	O
good	O
Town	O
&	O
its	O
Environs	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
rellieve	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
from	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
the	O
Pappers	O
in	O
ye	O
Douglaſs	B-pers
&	O
Hamilton	B-pers
cause	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
than	O
by	O
beging	O
he	O
'll	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
Use	O
he	O
pleases	O
:	O
the	O
Sentence	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peers	O
haveing	O
put	O
an	O
End	O
to	O
that	O
affair	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
does	O
not	O
Love	O
writeing	O
Letters	O
but	O
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Notiffie	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
his	O
fourth	O
Daughter	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
hapned	O
(	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
of	O
Last	O
Month	O
)	O
I	O
'm	O
now	O
got	O
down	O
Stairs	O
again	O
after	O
being	O
Ill	O
&	O
confined	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
yr	O
new	O
Cousin	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Jolly	O
Girl	O
she	O
is	O
Cristened	O
Jane	O
Wilhelmina	O
for	O
her	B-pers
Aunt	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Pappa	O
.	O
the	O
others	O
are	O
much	O
Yours	O
&	O
often	O
talk	O
of	O
You	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Letters	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
later	O
than	O
those	O
you	O
mention	O
but	O
hear	O
from	O
other	O
people	O
they	O
are	O
Well	O
&	O
Happy	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
is	O
marcht	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
but	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
here	O
remain	O
till	O
Relieved	O
from	O
some	O
other	O
Regt	O
:	O
as	O
our	O
Few	O
Men	O
are	O
as	O
mischiviously	O
enclined	O
as	O
ever	O
we	O
expect	O
to	O
Sett	O
out	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
some	O
time	O
this	O
Month	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
continue	O
to	O
enclose	O
my	O
Letters	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
who	O
will	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
forward	O
them	O
saffe	O
--	O
my	O
next	O
to	O
you	O
will	O
proveably	O
be	O
from	O
Edbr	B-place
:	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Children	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
offers	O
of	O
best	O
compts	O
to	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
accept	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
ever	O
Affect	O
:	O
Cousin	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
April	O
13	O
th	O
Col	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
begs	O
his	O
Compts	O
may	O
be	O
acceptable	O
has	O
this	O
instant	O
been	O
favored	O
wt	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
obliging	O
letter	O
&	O
is	O
extremely	O
Sorry	O
to	O
find	O
ye	O
Gout	O
still	O
continues	O
to	O
plague	O
him	O
,	O
croſser	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
ye	O
rancour	O
of	O
ye	O
Babylonians	O
at	O
pres	O
e	O
nt	O
tho	O
he	O
sincerely	O
wishes	O
it	O
may	O
soon	O
blow	O
over	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Hamilton	O
Family	O
will	O
have	O
ye	O
greatest	O
Loſs	O
--	O
