TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
enclose	O
two	O
Letters	O
&	O
add	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
from	O
myself	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
yours	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
already	O
told	O
Brawn	B-pers
what	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
said	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
home	O
but	O
his	O
poor	O
Child	O
is	O
dead	O
Compton	B-pers
aſsists	O
Powel	B-pers
till	O
he	O
returns	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
dear	O
Children	O
here	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
just	O
now	O
preparing	O
for	O
a	O
Commerce	O
Party	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
3	O
Princes	O
are	O
invited	O
&	O
little	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
teach	O
Me	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
Youngest	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
her	O
Roy	O
Hſs	O
Pſs	B-pers
Sophie	I-pers
breakfasted	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
were	O
in	O
charming	O
Spirits	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
News	O
you	O
can	O
expect	O
from	O
Me	O
.	O
who	O
am	O
Ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
Octr	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
--	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
