TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
is	O
now	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
desired	O
my	O
opinion	O
upon	O
a	O
step	O
that	O
you	O
think	O
advisable	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
drawing	O
Two	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
from	O
the	O
3	O
pr.Ct	O
.	O
stock	O
for	O
the	O
uses	O
you	O
mention	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
perfectly	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
propriety	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
moreover	O
think	O
that	O
this	O
diminution	O
of	O
your	O
little	O
capital	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
requires	O
no	O
further	O
proofs	O
of	O
your	O
tenderdeſs	O
&	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
yet	O
you	O
will	O
undoubtedly	O
feel	O
a	O
secret	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
reflection	O
of	O
having	O
doubled	O
your	O
attentions	O
at	O
this	O
critical	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
opinion	O
of	O
German	O
Doctors	O
,	O
their	O
prescriptions	O
are	O
commonly	O
too	O
rough	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
and	O
think	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
consult	O
a	O
better	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fetherston	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
here	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
&	O
seem	O
'd	O
much	O
pleased	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
remit	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
half	O
years	O
Rent	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
before	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
distreſses	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
are	O
so	O
uncommonly	O
great	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
really	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
expect	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
that	O
Rents	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
paid	O
as	O
formerly	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
little	O
money	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
&	O
no	O
trade	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
his	B-pers
M——y	I-pers
's	I-pers
recollection	O
of	O
me	O
attended	O
with	O
trivial	O
enquiries	O
,	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
repeated	O
promises	O
of	O
a	O
more	O
substantial	O
remembrance	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
deferr	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
that	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
foll	O
e	O
y	O
to	O
ground	O
any	O
hopes	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
arrived	O
to	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
fifty	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
discouraged	O
from	O
the	O
pursuit	O
of	O
favors	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
good	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
for	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
matter	O
of	O
real	O
consolation	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
aſsert	O
with	O
confidence	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
fail	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
expectations	O
of	O
royal	O
favor	O
so	O
often	O
promised	O
,	O
my	O
conduct	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
such	O
as	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
discredit	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
honor	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
low	O
&	O
mean	O
Persons	O
in	O
general	O
that	O
fill	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Bishops	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
seem	O
that	O
our	O
Governors	O
thought	O
the	O
interests	O
of	O
Religion	O
safer	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Schoolmasters	O
and	O
Tutors	O
than	O
in	O
those	O
men	O
of	O
birth	O
&	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
digreſsion	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
avoided	O
,	O
however	O
it	O
shall	O
introduce	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
advice	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
remain	O
with	O
a	O
firm	O
&	O
constant	O
persuasion	O
that	O
r——l	O
favor	O
is	O
hardly	O
earned	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
frequently	O
blown	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
slightest	O
blast	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
accept	O
of	O
our	O
best	O
wishes	O
&	O
remember	O
us	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
whom	O
we	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
receive	O
better	O
accounts	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
December	O
1	O
st	O
1778	O
Latour	O
,	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
