TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
friend	O
How	O
kind	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
your	O
old	O
woman	O
and	O
true	O
friend	O
in	O
sending	O
such	O
a	O
rarity	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
birds	O
who	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
enemies	O
must	O
be	O
scarce	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
therefore	O
for	O
your	O
love	O
which	O
I	O
return	O
from	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
this	O
six	O
week	O
a	O
sick	O
animal	O
and	O
kept	O
my	O
room	O
:	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
is	O
no	O
great	O
hardship	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
in	O
great	O
pain	O
and	O
can	O
amuse	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
and	O
lazy	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
your	O
true	O
and	O
faithful	O
E	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Hampton	B-place
Saturday	O
Octr	O
:	O
the	O
15	O
:	O
To	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
love	O
the	B-pers
Dickensons	I-pers
'	I-pers
.	O
at	O
the	O
si	O
ng	O
gn	O
of	O
comfort	O
