TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
Decr	O
:	O
2	O
8	O
9	O
th	O
:	O
1780	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Why	O
were	O
you	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
one	O
moment	O
in	O
Stanhope	B-place
St	I-place
:	I-place
I	O
answer	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
continue	O
to	O
come	O
--	O
be	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
this	O
Line	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
whether	O
Miſs	B-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
,	O
may	O
come	O
to	O
yr	O
:	O
Room	O
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
Princesses	O
--	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
gratification	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
are	O
always	O
happy	O
in	O
giving	O
pleasure	O
,	O
whenever	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
shall	O
only	O
have	O
a	O
glimpse	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
I	O
am	O
quite	O
happy	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
so	O
soon	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
pretty	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
has	O
not	O
quite	O
forgot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
sorry	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Riddles	O
Jeux	O
d'Esprits	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
now	O
but	O
nursing	O
my	O
Julia	B-pers
--	O
who	O
bears	O
parting	O
with	O
her	O
Nurse	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
wd	O
:	O
touch	O
your	O
heart	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
begs	O
her	O
kindest	O
Comps	O
:	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
is	O
still	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
&	O
is	O
better	O
for	O
the	O
Waters	O
Yrs	O
:	O
very	O
sincerely	O
PDartrey	B-pers
I	O
must	O
send	O
you	O
some	O
pretty	O
Lines	O
the	B-pers
Dss	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
repeated	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Palmerston	I-pers
's	O
upon	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
Yours	O
,	O
this	O
Triffle	O
to	O
improve	O
,	O
Its	O
worth	O
depends	O
on	O
You	O
;	O
a	O
Trifle	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
love	O
,	O
A	O
Treasure	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
--	O
[	O
Specific	O
source	O
not	O
yet	O
identified	O
]	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
London	B-place
Haller	B-pers
's	O
Letters	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
