TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
doe	O
my	O
self	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
this	O
evening	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
past	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
feverish	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
Doctor	B-pers
Fordice	I-pers
threatens	O
me	O
this	O
morning	O
with	O
a	O
second	O
bleeding	O
,	O
which	O
obliges	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
at	O
home	O
very	O
quiet	O
,	O
I	O
regret	O
extremly	O
the	O
being	O
prevented	O
from	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
waiting	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
allways	O
happy	O
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
who	O
I	O
highly	O
respect	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
likewise	O
be	O
disapointed	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cherteris	I-pers
as	O
her	O
poor	O
little	O
Child	O
Hamilton	B-pers
dyed	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
for	O
granted	O
you	O
goe	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
for	O
the	O
holly	O
days	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
dell	O
of	O
health	O
and	O
pleasure	O
and	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
beleive	O
me	O
very	O
Sincerly	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
your	O
affectionat	O
and	O
much	O
obliged	O
Cath	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Maddox	O
Street	O
Thursday	O
1	O
2	O
th	O
April	O
1781	O
