TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
July	O
8	O
th	O
1769	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
fear	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
be	O
tempted	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
entirely	O
off	O
the	O
Civill	O
list	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
her	O
Debt	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
obligeing	O
Letter	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
too	O
Well	O
to	O
doubt	O
of	O
my	O
friendship	O
or	O
desire	O
to	O
hear	O
good	O
Acts	O
:	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
go	O
on	O
--	O
but	O
realy	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
attempt	O
towards	O
it	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
yours	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
down	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
Contracted	O
so	O
violent	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
inflamation	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
that	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
half	O
blind	O
ever	O
since	O
&	O
still	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
tryeing	O
to	O
get	O
Well	O
if	O
poſsible	O
--	O
:	O
besides	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
wore	O
out	O
&	O
miserable	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
&	O
Harriot	B-pers
s	O
accounts	O
who	O
both	O
were	O
extreamly	O
Ill	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
feavers	O
&	O
Agues	O
the	O
bad	O
effects	O
of	O
which	O
still	O
sticks	O
by	O
them	O
especialy	O
Mary	B-pers
for	O
whom	O
our	O
Anxiety	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
--	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
ret	O
ir	O
e	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
at	O
first	O
comeing	O
down	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
encounter	O
the	O
Hurry	O
&	O
bustle	O
of	O
Setling	O
ourselves	O
here	O
--	O
:	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
we	O
have	O
yet	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
accomplish	O
--	O
haveing	O
a	O
whole	O
House	O
to	O
furnish	O
which	O
in	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
is	O
no	O
easy	O
matter	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
ones	O
mind	O
--	O
besides	O
that	O
Receiveing	O
&	O
returning	O
Visitts	O
&	O
civilitys	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
work	O
that	O
leaves	O
one	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hope	O
it	O
would	O
soon	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
conclusion	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
quite	O
tired	O
--	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
much	O
obliged	O
by	O
yr	O
kind	O
Anxiety	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
litle	O
Jane	B-pers
held	O
out	O
amazeingly	O
&	O
continues	O
to	O
thrive	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
shew	O
yr	O
Skill	O
in	O
the	O
Nurseing	O
way	O
wt	O
her	O
.	O
since	O
yr	O
Babylonians	O
are	O
demolisht	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
better	O
Sett	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
Ld	B-pers
North.ptn	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
the	O
true	O
Anti	O
qu	O
e	O
taste	O
--	O
:	O
two	O
old	O
Wives	O
would	O
be	O
rather	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
one	O
man	O
if	O
his	O
Loſs	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
dash	O
of	O
Modern	O
gout	O
--	O
.	O
has	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
heard	O
lately	O
from	O
Edinburgh	B-place
?	O
I	O
have	O
twice	O
since	O
being	O
here	O
they	O
all	O
continue	O
in	O
high	O
Health	O
&	O
Spiritts	O
are	O
much	O
careſsed	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
pleas	O
'd	O
wt	O
their	O
Situation	O
--	O
my	O
Br	O
I	O
find	O
has	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
nobody	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
&	O
Cousins	O
does	O
.	O
Poor	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
'm	O
very	O
Sorry	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Aimiable	O
Youth	O
&	O
would	O
proveably	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
fine	O
figure	O
in	O
Liffe	O
his	O
Death	O
was	O
foreseen	O
by	O
most	O
people	O
except	O
his	O
own	O
familly	O
the	B-pers
present	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Lively	O
Healthy	O
Boy	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
Mr	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
gained	O
his	O
Law	O
suit	O
against	O
Ld	B-pers
Selkirk	I-pers
Unanimously	O
my	O
Ld	B-pers
attempted	O
to	O
dispoſseſs	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Estate	O
--	O
.	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
Bustle	O
wt	O
our	O
Races	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
collected	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
Company	O
together	O
--	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
would	O
think	O
of	O
comeing	O
amongst	O
Us	O
we	O
shall	O
ever	O
rejoice	O
to	O
See	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
&	O
in	O
all	O
places	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
wish	O
this	O
may	O
reach	O
you	O
Soon	O
--	O
I	O
've	O
given	O
a	O
Member	O
some	O
Covers	O
to	O
frank	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
worth	O
yr	O
while	O
to	O
pay	O
postage	O
for	O
my	O
Letters	O
.	O
such	O
is	O
the	O
hurry	O
I	O
at	O
present	O
live	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
though	O
this	O
was	O
begun	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
't	O
is	O
now	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
I	O
shall	O
conclude	O
it	O
however	O
by	O
beging	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
all	O
our	O
most	O
affectionate	O
good	O
Wishes	O
;	O
we	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
Your	O
Cousins	O
are	O
very	O
Buſsie	O
in	O
different	O
ways	O
but	O
all	O
as	O
much	O
Yours	O
as	O
ever	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
bellieve	O
me	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
July	O
25	O
th	O
My	O
Covers	O
are	O
but	O
this	O
moment	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
;	O
do	O
write	O
me	O
a	O
full	O
Act	O
:	O
of	O
Yourselves	O
soon	O
in	O
tocken	O
you	O
admitt	O
my	O
Excuse	O
for	O
Sillence	O
--	O
once	O
more	O
A	O
dieu	O
--	O
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Abbey	O
--	O
Ruſsia	B-place
