TOKEN	NE
Balgowan	B-place
2	O
nd	O
-	O
Febry-	O
1779	O
.	O
Since	O
you	O
are	O
saucy	O
and	O
wo	O
n't	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
revenged	O
by	O
writing	O
often	O
&	O
making	O
you	O
pay	O
the	O
Postage	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
whom	O
has	O
very	O
frequently	O
&	O
very	O
affectionately	O
enquired	O
after	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
prodigious	O
favourite	O
of	O
mine	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
alter	O
my	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
we	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
Body	O
to	O
Dunkeld	B-place
,	O
how	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
will	O
receive	O
us	O
I	O
'm	O
quite	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
gueſs	O
.	O
Her	O
Noble	O
Hub	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
ashamed	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
twice	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
promise	O
to	O
myself	O
&	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
--	O
Now	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
leisure	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
short	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
Sisters	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
Situation	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
begin	O
regularly	O
&	O
methodically	O
I	O
shall	O
first	O
touch	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
Her	O
person	O
is	O
not	O
tall	O
,	O
thin	O
&	O
not	O
ungraceful	O
.	O
Her	O
countenance	O
good	O
were	O
she	O
a	O
little	O
fatter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
poor	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
made	O
a	O
visible	O
alteration	O
in	O
her	O
looks	O
.	O
This	O
joined	O
to	O
a	O
natural	O
lowneſs	O
of	O
Spirits	O
has	O
made	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
turn	O
which	O
I	O
ever	O
dreaded	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
she	O
lives	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
a	O
recluse	O
;	O
aſsociates	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
disposition	O
&	O
gives	O
herself	O
up	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
her	O
religious	O
duties	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
measure	O
neglect	O
her	O
social	O
ones	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
with	O
Concern	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
Life	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
into	O
,	O
but	O
find	O
matters	O
become	O
too	O
serious	O
to	O
afford	O
even	O
a	O
hope	O
of	O
her	O
relaxing	O
in	O
her	O
strictneſs	O
--	O
But	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
entre	O
nous	O
&	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
--	O
Harriot	B-pers
is	O
short	O
,	O
rather	O
inclined	O
to	O
be	O
fat	O
,	O
chearful	O
,	O
lively	O
,	O
affectionate	O
&	O
is	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
as	O
fine	O
a	O
countenance	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
improvement	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
hurt	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
serious	O
turn	O
of	O
her	O
elder	O
Sister	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
is	O
a	O
most	O
delightful	O
child	O
,	O
promises	O
to	O
be	O
tall	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
remarkable	O
degree	O
of	O
gentility	O
in	O
her	O
figure	O
&	O
is	O
reckoned	O
in	O
Temper	O
&	O
countenance	O
not	O
unlike	O
her	O
Brother	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
full	O
as	O
lightheaded	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
a	O
boarding	O
School	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
pardon	O
for	O
not	O
sending	O
you	O
the	O
Hair	O
I	O
promised	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
next	O
week	O
and	O
to	O
atone	O
for	O
my	O
neglect	O
by	O
accompanying	O
the	O
Hair	O
with	O
a	O
Miniature	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
which	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
will	O
be	O
equally	O
acceptable	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
copyed	O
from	O
a	O
half	O
length	O
of	O
him	O
done	O
by	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
Chalmers	I-pers
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
likest	O
picture	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
Were	O
I	O
richer	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
you	O
must	O
e'en	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
Case	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
make	O
out	O
my	O
Match	O
with	O
the	O
Fair	O
Miſstreſs	O
of	O
the	O
Cannons	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
treat	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
forget	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
send	O
the	O
purse	O
you	O
was	O
working	O
for	O
you	O
me	O
.	O
Present	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
K.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
