TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
escaped	O
inundation	O
during	O
the	O
uncommon	O
weather	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
suspended	O
my	O
journey	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
for	O
the	O
accounts	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
roads	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
are	O
tremendous	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
experienced	O
no	O
illneſs	O
nor	O
inconvenience	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
in	O
deep	O
concern	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
General	B-pers
Anstruther	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
married	O
a	O
friend	O
and	O
near	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
left	O
with	O
five	O
little	O
ones	O
,	O
to	O
deplore	O
this	O
dreadful	O
misfortune	O
.	O
The	O
recent	O
events	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
calamitous	O
.	O
Every	O
one	O
must	O
poignantly	O
lament	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Moore	I-pers
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
(	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
)	O
overwhelmed	O
with	O
grief	O
--	O
his	O
poor	O
Mother	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
lately	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
tolerably	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
purpose	O
visiting	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
weather	O
will	O
permit	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
comfortable	O
in	O
my	O
little	O
Apartments	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
had	O
a	O
trial	O
of	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
heat	O
and	O
cold	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
remember	O
,	O
was	O
intense	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Piano-Forte	O
;	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
made	O
any	O
great	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
yet	O
,	O
as	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
stirring	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Àpropos	O
to	O
fire	O
--	O
what	O
terrible	O
conflagrations	O
have	O
occurred	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
remember	O
so	O
many	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
--	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Theatre	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
:	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
,	O
an	O
Hotel	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
houses	O
in	O
Conduit	O
Street	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
The	O
Theatre	O
is	O
rebuilding	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
open	O
in	O
September	O
next	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
doubts	O
;	O
but	O
suppose	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
make	O
the	O
assertion	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
than	O
I	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
papers	O
(	O
and	O
so	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
doubt	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
E.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
H——y	I-pers
is	O
over	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Damages	O
were	O
shamefully	O
light	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Merrion	O
Square	O
,	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
conclude	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
this	O
season	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
it	O
better	O
avoided	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
period	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
receive	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
idea	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
for	O
this	O
Spring	O
?	O
I	O
flattered	O
myself	O
the	O
Leſsons	O
in	O
music	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
inducement	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
however	O
the	O
re	O
are	O
such	O
various	O
attractions	O
beside	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
still	O
,	O
rather	O
believe	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
your	O
opinion	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
;	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
kindest	O
regards	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
your	O
sincerely	O
obliged	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
50	O
Mortimer	O
Street	O
London	B-place
Feb	O
:	O
4	O
th	O
:	O
1809	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
the	O
changes	O
of	O
weather	O
have	O
been	O
trying	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
sprained	O
arm	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Single	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
1809	O
