TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
reply	O
to	O
your	O
Letter	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
is	O
better	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
continuing	O
to	O
amend	O
these	O
two	O
last	O
days	O
:	O
the	O
Physicians	O
pronounce	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
information	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Princeſses	O
:	O
as	O
the	O
Queens	O
Palace	O
is	O
barred	O
against	O
all	O
visitors	O
of	O
every	O
description	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
delay	O
another	O
moment	O
I	O
lose	O
the	O
Post	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Madm	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
J.	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
Fludyer	O
St	O
Feb	O
:	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1804	O
London	B-place
February	O
eighteenth	O
1804	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Bedfordshire	B-place
free	O
J.	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
