TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
October	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
am	O
infinitely	O
Oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
admire	O
your	O
prudence	O
in	O
not	O
complying	O
with	O
my	O
request	O
;	O
in	O
your	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
perfectly	O
right	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
ſure	O
,	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
propersition	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
great	O
benevolence	O
of	O
heart	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
You	O
have	O
Objects	O
sufficient	O
of	O
Your	O
own	O
to	O
give	O
too	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
do	O
insiſt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
my	O
distreſsd	O
family	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
lest	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
sufficiently	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
perpose	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
it	O
out	O
my	O
Self	O
,	O
&	O
send	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
Children	O
Cloath	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
put	O
to	O
School	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
subscription	O
with	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
give	O
more	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
might	O
prevent	O
People	O
giveing	O
their	O
crowns	O
&	O
half	O
Crowns	O
:	O
Amongst	O
my	O
requaintance	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
shall	O
make	O
my	O
application	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
sake	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
distreſs	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
purſe	O
was	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
greatneſs	O
of	O
your	O
soul	O
.	O
--	O
But	O
my	O
Dear	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
comfort	O
your	O
Self	O
,	O
with	O
thinking	O
of	O
the	O
Widows	O
mite	O
.	O
--	O
Your	O
good	O
Father	O
desires	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
his	O
greatful	O
returns	O
of	O
thanks	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
attention	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
his	O
now	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
Planting	O
:	O
Miranda	B-pers
is	O
reading	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
that	O
great	O
Poem	O
in	O
manuscript	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
pleasure	O
I	O
can	O
inform	O
you	O
She	O
reads	O
exseeding	O
well	O
;	O
&	O
he	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
dare	O
not	O
,	O
indulge	O
the	O
thought	O
:	O
I	O
hear	O
'd	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
;	O
The	O
Clarkes	O
are	O
coming	O
to	O
us	O
soon	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
without	O
dumb	O
Nanny	B-pers
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
accomplish	O
that	O
point	O
.	O
--	O
accept	O
of	O
our	O
warmest	O
love	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
Dear	O
Bell	B-pers
Miranda	B-pers
Sister	O
&	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
desire	O
their	O
best	O
compts	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
