TOKEN	NE
Chelsea	B-place
Octr	O
:	O
2	O
3	O
d	O
:	O
1780	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
We	O
arrived	O
safely	O
here	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
&	O
found	O
our	O
D	O
:	O
Julia	B-pers
thank	O
God	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
laugh	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
infinite	O
distreſs	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
a	O
Common	O
,	O
seven	O
miles	O
from	O
Uckfield	B-place
,	O
or	O
from	O
any	O
Place	O
where	O
we	O
cd	O
:	O
get	O
a	O
Postilion	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
poor	O
miserable	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
the	O
1	O
st	O
:	O
Postilion	O
very	O
nearly	O
falling	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
&	O
being	O
conducted	O
in	O
this	O
a	O
state	O
,	O
on	O
of	O
intoxication	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Cottage	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Monet	B-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Postilion	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
guard	O
us	O
--	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
Monet	B-pers
,	O
with	O
his	O
usual	O
accomodating	O
Spirit	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
n'ayez	O
pas	O
peur	O
Mi	O
Ladi	O
,	O
N'ayez	O
pas	O
peur	O
,	O
&	O
offered	O
to	O
conduct	O
us	O
safely	O
&	O
as	O
fist	O
Postilion	O
,	O
&	O
lead	O
the	O
Saddle	O
Horse	O
into	O
the	O
bargain	O
--	O
this	O
he	O
not	O
only	O
offered	O
,	O
but	O
executed	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
amazement	O
,	O
&	O
fright	O
,	O
&	O
amidst	O
the	O
laughs	O
of	O
the	O
Town	B-place
of	I-place
Uckfield	I-place
,	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
with	O
Monet	B-pers
1	O
st	O
:	O
Postilion	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
his	O
hair	O
in	O
a	O
Queu	O
&	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
a	O
most	O
laughable	O
figure	O
.	O
--	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
laugh	O
'd	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
cry	O
almost	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
--	O
that	O
poor	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
must	O
at	O
last	O
be	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
this	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
read	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
,	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Secret	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
is	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
conveniently	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Heatherly	I-pers
&	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
Poor	O
Woman	O
whose	O
Daughter	O
is	O
near	O
lying	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
either	O
send	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
bye	O
a	O
pr	O
:	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
them	O
baught	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
repay	O
you	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
.	O
Adieu	O
in	O
haſte	O
yrs	O
:	O
PD	B-pers
pray	O
tell	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
with	O
my	O
duty	O
how	O
often	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
pretty	O
little	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Sophia	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
her	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
's	O
House	O
By	O
Lewis	B-place
Bag	I-place
--	O
Eastbourne	B-place
Suſsex	B-place
Oct	O
br	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1780	O
Lady	B-pers
D——	I-pers
