TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
Evening	O
3	O
d	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1784	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
inflammation	O
in	O
your	O
Eyes	O
;	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
disappointed	O
in	O
not	O
seeing	O
you	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
suited	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
House	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
carriage	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
If	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
mistake	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Bed	O
at	O
your	O
service	O
,	O
&	O
no	O
one	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
wellcome	O
then	O
your	O
Self	O
to	O
have	O
occupied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
from	O
Bullstrode	B-place
,	O
if	O
the	O
good	O
Dutcheſs	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
over	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
love	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
kind	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
continue	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
our	O
friend	O
Ann	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
will	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
us	O
these	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
confind	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
;	O
he	O
admires	O
this	O
place	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
observe	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
constant	O
attendat	O
upon	O
poor	O
Penny	B-pers
;	O
I	O
now	O
fear	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
chance	O
for	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
She	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
releas	O
'd	O
from	O
all	O
her	O
troubles	O
.	O
--	O
Mary	B-pers
will	O
take	O
the	O
pen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
you	O
are	O
oft	O
in	O
my	O
thoughts	O
.	O
upon	O
one	O
subject	O
,	O
succeſs	O
attend	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
love	O
--	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
I	O
must	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
for	O
your	O
indisposition	O
.	O
Last	O
week	O
my	O
father	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lenton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Weybridge	B-place
,	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Tamest	O
Squirrel	O
they	O
ever	O
saw	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holland	I-pers
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
therefore	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
my	O
father	O
went	O
yesterday	O
&	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
&	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
pretty	O
,	O
very	O
tame	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
am	O
already	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
my	O
mother	O
my	O
father	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Squirrels	O
nose	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
great	O
hopes	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Dr	O
..	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
,	O
ere	O
long	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
Holiford	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
&	O
stays	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
has	O
been	O
often	O
here	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
always	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
Suppose	O
)	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
would	O
think	O
that	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
often	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
with	O
tears	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
..	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
whom	O
ere	O
long	O
we	O
shall	O
lose	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
D-	I-pers
is	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
last	O
night	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
next	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
here	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
R.	I-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
leaves	O
us	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
three	O
weeks	O
here	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
leave	O
this	O
place	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
A	O
Colonel	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
has	O
bought	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
s	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
neighbour	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
our	O
Compts	O
..	O
to	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
disappointed	O
as	O
none	O
of	O
Family	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
terrace	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Company	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
..	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
&	O
now	O
I	O
must	O
conclude	O
myself	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
yrs	O
.	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
M.	B-pers
G——	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
beg	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
contrive	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
over	O
here	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
us	O
so	O
very	O
happy	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
