TOKEN	NE
Yours	O
of	O
Friday	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
reached	O
me	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
kind	O
warmth	O
of	O
the	O
invitation	O
contained	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
too	O
gratifying	O
to	O
be	O
resisted	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
busineſs	O
that	O
will	O
prevent	O
my	O
leaving	O
town	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
fortnight	O
:	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
suit	O
myself	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
in	O
Herefordshire	B-place
;	O
but	O
,	O
during	O
my	O
visit	O
here	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
distreſs	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
want	O
any	O
comfort	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
been	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
of	O
late	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
without	O
succeſs	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
yet	O
still	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
B	B-place
.	I-place
;	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
apprehend	O
it	O
will	O
contain	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
affairs	O
.	O
--	O
Should	O
nothing	O
very	O
unforeseen	O
,	O
occur	O
,	O
I	O
propose	O
availing	O
myself	O
of	O
your	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
pointing	O
out	O
the	O
mode	O
of	O
conveyance	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
adopt	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
would	O
have	O
much	O
pleasure	O
in	O
accompanying	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paying	O
her	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
domestic	O
busineſs	O
will	O
not	O
permit	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
satisfied	O
at	O
having	O
your	O
joint	O
approbation	O
of	O
my	O
conduct	O
in	O
not	O
insisting	O
upon	O
visiting	O
at	O
B	B-place
.	I-place
--	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
when	O
made	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
difficulty	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
one	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
fellow-feeling	O
.	O
With	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
I	O
remain	O
most	O
truly	O
your	O
obliged	O
and	O
affectionate	O
.	O
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
Jan	O
:	O
31	O
st	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
specify	O
the	O
precise	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
having	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
waiting	O
on	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
