TOKEN	NE
H	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
If	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
punctual	O
and	O
regular	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
depart	O
I	O
suppose	O
from	O
that	O
family	O
likeneſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
flatterd	O
in	O
thinking	O
subsists	O
between	O
the	O
lady	O
and	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
however	O
aſſure	O
ye	O
most	O
faithfully	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
value	O
myself	O
on	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
likeneſs	O
(	O
if	O
such	O
there	O
be	O
)	O
for	O
I	O
honor	O
regularity	O
œconomy	O
sobriety	O
and	O
chastity	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
poſseſs	O
such	O
virtues	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
dont	O
make	O
an	O
outcry	O
about	O
such	O
matters	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
perhaps	O
were	O
born	O
with	O
them	O
which	O
alltogether	O
makes	O
the	O
longest	O
sentence	O
about	O
chastity	O
that	O
perhaps	O
ever	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
As	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
is	O
clear	O
another	O
affair	O
--	O
how	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
pearls	O
and	O
other	O
valuables	O
are	O
disposed	O
of	O
--	O
Well	O
often	O
have	O
I	O
puzzled	O
my	O
brain	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
poſſibl	O
y	O
e	O
to	O
see	O
others	O
mens	O
property	O
without	O
invading	O
it	O
leſs	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
or	O
as	O
Bayes	O
expreſses	O
“	O
graſping	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
eye	O
”	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
that	O
confeſſion	O
tho	O
not	O
a	O
rite	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Church	O
has	O
its	O
inconveniencies	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
little	O
dependance	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
on	O
human	O
resolutions	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
none	O
but	O
rash	O
resolutions	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
leſs	O
gravity	O
in	O
forgetting	O
them	O
--	O
the	O
mention	O
of	O
that	O
rare	O
bird	O
may	O
convince	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
been	O
reading	O
your	O
letter	O
my	O
kind	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
de	I-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
if	O
I	O
never	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
by	O
these	O
presents	O
thank	O
you	O
by	O
wishing	O
I	O
could	O
accept	O
your	O
invitation	O
to	O
Derbyshire	B-place
,	O
a	O
Shire	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
attachment	O
to	O
--	O
Pray	O
is	O
little	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
solitary	O
or	O
does	O
she	O
begin	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
a	O
brother	O
or	O
a	O
Sister	O
?	O
this	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
Wo	O
Mankind	O
is	O
so	O
unreasonable	O
as	O
to	O
wish	O
for	O
additions	O
to	O
their	O
happyneſs	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
more	O
to	O
regret	O
--	O
But	O
I	O
,	O
having	O
such	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
mentioning	O
should	O
lament	O
first	O
growing	O
old	O
,	O
then	O
going	O
into	O
some	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
eat	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
pleased	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
starving	O
life	O
have	O
I	O
led	O
--	O
Here	O
was	O
lately	O
a	O
West	O
Indian	O
who	O
seldom	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
elegant	O
pair	O
of	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
turn	O
of	O
cheek	O
,	O
chin	O
and	O
throat	O
that	O
was	O
eternally	O
saying	O
come	O
eat	O
me	O
--	O
yet	O
that	O
miserable	O
wretch	O
never	O
sprung	O
from	O
his	O
chair	O
in	O
a	O
transport	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
dear	O
Villain	O
by	O
the	O
throat	O
and	O
act	O
the	O
loving	O
cannibal	O
.	O
I	O
heartily	O
wished	O
him	O
dead	O
and	O
sent	O
into	O
everlasting	O
redemption	O
--	O
After	O
all	O
,	O
such	O
is	O
the	O
incertainty	O
of	O
that	O
capricious	O
animal	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
cant	O
promise	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
marryed	O
to	O
just	O
such	O
another	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
call	O
her	O
Madam	O
--	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
conjugal	O
death	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
Marlows	O
Angler	O
,	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
fancy	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
give	O
better	O
Derbyshire	B-place
Views	O
that	O
the	O
editor	O
has	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
or	O
I	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
brain	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
pencilling	O
small	O
views	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
replace	O
those	O
you	O
should	O
cut	O
out	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
delicate	O
,	O
pretty	O
Girl	O
(	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
)	O
at	O
Matlock	B-place
when	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
a	O
fancy	O
to	O
a	O
scratch	O
of	O
mine	O
of	O
Middleton	B-place
Dale	I-place
,	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
sweet	O
scenery	O
about	O
the	O
wells	O
,	O
the	O
clear	O
gravelly	O
road	O
,	O
the	O
living	O
water	O
of	O
the	O
pebbly	O
river	O
,	O
the	O
hanging	O
clifs	O
adornd	O
with	O
varied	O
Shrubs	O
,	O
miſs	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
s	O
eyes	O
smiling	O
so	O
well	O
a	O
pleasing	O
countenance	O
to	O
which	O
luxuriant	O
brown	O
hair	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
back	O
ground	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
forget	O
pleasing	O
prospects	O
--	O
and	O
now	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
hair	O
is	O
far	O
more	O
gray	O
than	O
bay	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
I	O
follow	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
the	O
Psalmist	O
,	O
if	O
wrinkles	O
encrease	O
set	O
not	O
your	O
heart	O
upon	O
them	O
Psalm	O
62:10	O
:	O
“	O
if	O
riches	O
increase	O
,	O
set	O
not	O
your	O
heart	O
upon	O
them	O
”	O
.	O
--	O
such	O
symptoms	O
of	O
departure	O
do	O
not	O
entirely	O
quash	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
and	O
truly	O
my	O
reflexions	O
are	O
seldom	O
of	O
the	O
gloomy	O
cast	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
allow	O
a	O
little	O
tinge	O
of	O
melancholy	O
to	O
steal	O
upon	O
my	O
leisure	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
upon	O
certain	O
pleasant	O
people	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
very	O
likely	O
to	O
see	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
doomsday	O
--	O
It	O
would	O
require	O
a	O
considerable	O
consumption	O
of	O
Sea	O
coal	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
fireside	O
conversations	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
store	O
should	O
we	O
three	O
meet	O
again	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Macbeth	O
1.1	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
question	O
with	O
me	O
which	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
silent	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
conveniant	O
treaty	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
being	O
umpire	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
divert	O
myself	O
with	O
drawing	O
up	O
Articles	O
but	O
that	O
our	O
conversation	O
may	O
be	O
differr	O
'd	O
without	O
great	O
detriment	O
to	O
the	O
parties	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
there	O
appeard	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Soul	O
in	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
of	O
life	O
in	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shrewd	O
intelligence	O
which	O
well	O
directed	O
(	O
not	O
controuled	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
would	O
bid	O
fair	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
clever	O
fellow	O
a	O
happy	O
man	O
,	O
what	O
say	O
you	O
.	O
Page	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
holiday	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
letters	O
of	O
letters	O
of	O
busyneſs	O
and	O
fly	O
to	O
my	O
quarto	O
paper	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
(	O
in	O
my	O
58	O
th	O
Year	O
,	O
whisper	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Waddington	I-pers
)	O
not	O
half	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
sort	O
,	O
another	O
myself	O
,	O
yet	O
much	O
happyer	O
as	O
Banquo	O
's	O
Witches	O
expreſs	O
themselves	O
,	O
for	O
because	O
I	O
care	O
little	O
about	O
conveniencies	O
,	O
and	O
delicacies	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
people	O
say	O
or	O
think	O
--	O
by	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
Mob	O
of	O
any	O
rank	O
in	O
life	O
--	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Devil	O
ails	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
talks	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
own	O
mind	O
--	O
stay	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
great	O
admirer	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
admirable	O
--	O
the	O
sweetneſs	O
of	O
flowers	O
makes	O
me	O
religious	O
,	O
the	O
harmonies	O
of	O
Nature	O
in	O
general	O
delight	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
Woman	O
makes	O
me	O
devout	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
--	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
--	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
sympathizer	O
,	O
and	O
men	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
,	O
besides	O
indeed	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
made	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
rough	O
faces	O
&	O
rough	O
manners	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
millions	O
of	O
times	O
more	O
selfish	O
--	O
thus	O
I	O
am	O
myself	O
for	O
example	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
vis	O
à	O
vis	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
cast	O
of	O
Character	O
smooth	O
&	O
soft	O
that	O
would	O
temper	O
the	O
quirkishneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
teach	O
him	O
how	O
moderation	O
&	O
considerateneſs	O
are	O
better	O
&	O
more	O
estimable	O
than	O
hate	O
&	O
willfulneſs	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
own	O
will	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
most	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
from	O
being	O
only	O
old	O
&	O
unmarried	O
,	O
degenerate	O
into	O
a	O
downright	O
old	O
Batchelor	O
,	O
precise	O
,	O
positive	O
,	O
impatient	O
of	O
advice	O
&	O
controle	O
--	O
The	O
foresight	O
of	O
this	O
probability	O
is	O
not	O
flattering	O
--	O
one	O
comfort	O
I	O
have	O
among	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
turned	O
a	O
hoarder	O
--	O
Wine	O
does	O
not	O
grow	O
old	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
a	O
hidden	O
groat	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
--	O
my	O
servants	O
tho	O
have	O
been	O
14	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
six	O
years	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
are	O
not	O
tired	O
.	O
I	O
farm	O
,	O
garden	O
,	O
read	O
,	O
have	O
some	O
pleasant	O
society	O
,	O
that	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
in	O
times	O
past	O
--	O
very	O
faintly	O
--	O
the	O
beautiful	O
&	O
singular	O
prospects	O
these	O
Islands	O
afford	O
,	O
would	O
well	O
fill	O
a	O
large	O
pamphlet	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
find	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
sauntering	O
stile	O
of	O
drawing	O
I	O
used	O
when	O
in	O
Dovedale	B-place
,	O
Castleton	B-place
dale	I-place
,	O
Matlock	B-place
&	O
c	O
or	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
capital	O
amusements	O
your	O
situation	O
at	O
present	O
affords	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
travelling	O
about	O
which	O
implies	O
,	O
search	O
after	O
reasonable	O
pastime	O
,	O
and	O
useful	O
variety	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
recommend	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
a	O
tour	O
(	O
for	O
your	O
knowlege	O
must	O
better	O
direct	O
you	O
than	O
mine	O
)	O
but	O
objects	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
from	O
,	O
Ilam	B-place
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Staffordsh	B-place
--	O
Wetton	B-place
Mill	I-place
and	O
the	O
fairyes	O
cave	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
--	O
Bolton	B-place
Abbey	I-place
Castle	I-place
in	O
Craven	B-place
--	O
Hardwick	B-place
a	O
seat	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Port	I-pers
--	O
Keddleston	B-place
--	O
tho	O
Chatsworths	O
a	O
tiresome	O
piece	O
of	O
old	O
dignity	O
&	O
bad	O
taste	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
entreat	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
complete	O
British	O
Angler	O
with	O
plates	O
by	O
Wale	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
simplicity	O
and	O
natural	O
Stile	O
which	O
is	O
perfectly	O
in	O
tune	O
with	O
my	O
youthful	O
taste	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
order	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonsh	I-pers
Lime	O
Street	O
London	B-place
to	O
whom	O
addreſs	O
any	O
letter	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
greet	O
me	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
view	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
twofold	O
light	O
,	O
provided	O
it	O
should	O
suit	O
your	O
fancy	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
Vandal	O
am	O
I	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
little	O
cherry	O
cheekd	O
girl	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
heart	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
its	O
strongest	O
tyes	O
?	O
You	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
think	O
her	O
cherrubic	O
,	O
or	O
Cherryrubic	O
--	O
perhaps	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
are	O
contemplating	O
with	O
divided	O
affection	O
her	O
little	O
brother	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
occasion	O
to	O
compliment	O
and	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
you	O
please	O
John	B-pers
Brickwood	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mercht	I-pers
as	O
wife	O
&	O
Mother	O
if	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
--	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
under	O
so	O
watchful	O
&	O
vigilant	O
a	O
hen	O
as	O
used	O
to	O
hatch	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
figure	O
to	O
great	O
advantage	O
--	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
uncommon	O
face	O
characteristic	O
&	O
nearly	O
handsome	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
pleasing	O
form	O
,	O
then	O
pretty	O
well	O
formed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
cunning	O
&	O
intelligent	O
cast	O
of	O
countenance	O
,	O
announcing	O
,	O
what	O
?	O
do	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
shant	O
paſs	O
for	O
censorious	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
are	O
agreed	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
preparing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Spaniards	O
--	O
I	O
wont	O
lead	O
you	O
about	O
our	O
rocks	O
or	O
our	O
fortifications	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
I	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
so	O
trite	O
among	O
my	O
correspondents	O
)	O
regale	O
you	O
with	O
Oranges	O
,	O
lemons	O
Citrons	O
limes	O
Shadocks	O
,	O
grapes	O
,	O
pomegranates	O
dates	O
,	O
olives	O
,	O
mulberries	O
all	O
in	O
disorder	O
and	O
so	O
most	O
beautifully	O
diversifyd	O
by	O
the	O
negligent	O
skill	O
of	O
Dame	O
Vertue	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
&	O
whales	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
more	O
knowingly	O
than	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Waddington	I-pers
who	O
never	O
was	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
help	O
to	O
marry	O
young	O
Waller	B-pers
to	O
a	O
man	O
you	O
approve	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
my	O
eye	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
understanding	O
a	O
valuable	O
piece	O
of	O
Household	O
furniture	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
die	O
if	O
she	O
hangs	O
too	O
long	O
on	O
the	O
bough	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
marry	O
her	O
to	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Prince	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
--	O
now	O
if	O
you	O
dont	O
think	O
this	O
too	O
long	O
a	O
talk	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
Authority	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
tired	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
reason	O
in	O
many	O
things	O
--	O
my	O
letters	O
remind	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
grains	O
of	O
wheat	O
&	O
c	O
no	O
matter	O
if	O
my	O
friends	O
provoke	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
them	O
that	O
were	O
I	O
as	O
tedious	O
as	O
a	O
Prince	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
heart	O
to	O
bestow	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
them	O
&	O
continue	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
favor	O
.	O
Adieu	O
M	B-pers
.	I-pers
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
when	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
red	O
your	O
letter	O
more	O
than	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
chance	O
of	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
answer	O
it	O
--	O
It	O
contains	O
qu	O
.	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
ans	O
.	O
happy	O
years	O
and	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
gr	O
.	O
gr	O
.	O
gr	O
grand	O
Children	O
--	O
England	B-place
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
--	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
