TOKEN	NE
Wimbledon	B-place
29	O
th	O
June	O
1790	O
.	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
embrace	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
Letter	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
broken	O
heart	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
since	O
something	O
better	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
a	O
contested	O
Election	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
imment	O
imminent	O
danger	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
from	O
the	O
Riot	O
;	O
however	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
escaped	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
two	O
Members	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
notwithstandg	O
every	O
species	O
of	O
bribery	O
practised	O
by	O
our	O
Opponents	O
with	O
very	O
high	O
numbers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
most	O
ably	O
aſsisted	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Garrow	I-pers
as	O
Counsel	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
four	O
.	O
The	O
loſs	O
of	O
my	O
lovely	O
Boy	O
is	O
a	O
stroke	O
&	O
a	O
shock	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
long	O
feel	O
--	O
Fanny	B-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
danger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
intended	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
Kath	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
but	O
previous	O
to	O
my	O
leaving	O
London	B-place
I	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Eton	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
are	O
w	O
i	O
e	O
ll	O
&	O
will	O
remain	O
the	O
Holidays	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
is	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
un	O
likely	O
to	O
paſs	O
much	O
time	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
let	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
to	O
Moreau	B-pers
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
with	O
my	O
Children	O
--	O
I	O
intend	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
near	O
Town	B-place
'till	O
she	O
is	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
give	O
you	O
great	O
pleasure	O
that	O
Services	O
rendered	O
Fanny	B-pers
has	O
induced	O
him	O
to	O
signify	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
handsomely	O
provided	O
for	O
--	O
His	O
Grace	O
joins	O
most	O
heartily	O
in	O
my	O
succeſs	O
;	O
--	O
But	O
with	O
all	O
these	O
prospects	O
a	O
gloom	O
at	O
times	O
siezes	O
my	O
mind	O
still	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
afflicted	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Dear	O
boy	O
..	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
P——	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
are	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
obed	O
ſert	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackſon	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Cheshire	B-place
21	O
2-2	O
23	O
2	O
10-6	O
23	O
12-6	O
