TOKEN	NE
A	O
letter	O
was	O
this	O
morning	O
given	O
me	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
immediately	O
perceived	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
F	I-pers
's	O
absence	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
informing	O
her	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
shall	O
think	O
myself	O
in	O
executing	O
any	O
Commands	O
she	O
may	O
perhaps	O
have	O
intended	O
for	O
another	O
:	O
His	O
return	O
is	O
fixed	O
for	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
no	O
orders	O
for	O
Letters	O
to	O
be	O
forwarded	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
indeed	O
do	O
I	O
exactly	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
--	O
I	O
returnd	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
from	O
Suſsex	B-place
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
last	O
Fortnigt	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
scarcely	O
had	O
one	O
bad	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
lucky	O
enough	O
therefore	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
my	O
Relations	O
&	O
old	O
Friends	O
:	O
The	O
Benefit	O
I	O
have	O
receivd	O
from	O
this	O
Little	O
Excursion	O
is	O
really	O
wonderful	O
;	O
my	O
native	O
Air	O
has	O
had	O
great	O
Effect	O
on	O
my	O
Health	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
Break	O
in	O
the	O
Chain	O
of	O
diurnal	O
duty	O
has	O
had	O
an	O
equal	O
effect	O
on	O
my	O
Spirits	O
,	O
which	O
either	O
from	O
real	O
or	O
imaginary	O
ills	O
were	O
before	O
somewhat	O
too	O
low	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
most	O
sincerely	O
you	O
coud	O
change	O
the	O
Scene	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
your	O
Health	O
surely	O
must	O
require	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
Request	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
is	O
in	O
itself	O
so	O
reasonable	O
that	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
delicacy	O
on	O
that	O
Head	O
.	O
Bruyeres	B-pers
seems	O
totally	O
unhing	O
'd	O
&	O
drooping	O
:	O
how	O
then	O
must	O
it	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
whose	O
Attendance	O
is	O
constant	O
and	O
care	O
double	O
!	O
The	O
Time	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
among	O
your	O
Friends	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
number	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
you	O
still	O
continue	O
to	O
enroll	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Yrss	O
most	O
sincerely	O
John	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Wednesday	O
Eve	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
