TOKEN	NE
in	O
book	O
not	O
typed	O
Friday	O
Morng	O
.	O
20	O
Augt	O
It	O
is	O
poſsible	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
will	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
Tomorrow	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
Port	O
Place	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
I	O
sett	O
off	O
for	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
yours	O
most	O
afftly	O
WH	B-pers
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
August	O
-84	O
