TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
110	O
--	O
29	O
May	O
1787	O
my	O
Dear	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
answer	O
'd	O
Your	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
much	O
concern	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
melancholy	O
Scene	O
,	O
You	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
--	O
hope	O
,	O
the	O
Effects	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
proved	O
bad	O
,	O
for	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
;	O
who	O
just	O
recovering	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
was	O
ill	O
prepared	O
,	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
shock	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
if	O
His	O
Father	O
recovers	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
intellects	O
are	O
restored	O
,	O
for	O
such	O
dreadfull	O
falls	O
,	O
often	O
occasion	O
complaints	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Brain	O
;	O
that	O
deprive	O
themselves	O
,	O
&	O
friends	O
of	O
comfort	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
You	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
smiling	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
;	O
who	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
has	O
no	O
cause	O
to	O
frown	O
by	O
this	O
,	O
You	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
supose	O
her	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
as	O
pain	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
as	O
yet	O
alter	O
her	O
good	O
humor	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
now	O
packed	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
Stanley	B-place
,	O
for	O
which	O
place	O
we	O
shall	O
sett	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
--	O
so	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
,	O
to	O
direct	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
will	O
know	O
,	O
where	O
to	O
forward	O
them	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
is	O
of	O
our	O
party	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
surprise	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
acquantance	O
:	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
but	O
barren	O
ground	O
,	O
frost	O
,	O
and	O
snow	O
;	O
--	O
but	O
,	O
the	O
amendment	O
they	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
;	O
prevent	O
the	O
outcry	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
otherwise	O
make	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
only	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Rehearsal	O
(	O
Westminster	B-place
Abbey	I-place
)	O
on	O
friday	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
there	O
again	O
to	O
day	O
:	O
and	O
dines	O
out	O
,	O
after	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
is	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
some	O
good	O
wind	O
,	O
would	O
blow	O
You	O
north	O
,	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
You	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
inhabitants	O
:	O
and	O
find	O
,	O
a	O
hearty	O
,	O
&	O
friendly	O
welcome	O
,	O
at	O
Stanley	B-place
;	O
a	O
comfortable	O
Snug	O
peninsula	O
that	O
only	O
boasts	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
real	O
pleasures	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
without	O
its	O
shew	O
,	O
or	O
Extravagance	O
--	O
After	O
much	O
Joy	O
,	O
often	O
comes	O
sorrow	O
:	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
crouding	O
to	O
court	O
,	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
the	O
reconciliation	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
sooner	O
over	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Prince	O
taken	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
:	O
made	O
a	O
general	O
mourning	O
,	O
aprehended	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
siezed	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
oclock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
Ball	O
;	O
and	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
:	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Duchess	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
s.	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
think	O
it	O
late	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
fashon	O
is	O
for	O
those	O
parties	O
to	O
end	O
with	O
a	O
Breakfast	O
;	O
as	O
five	O
,	O
seven	O
,	O
or	O
even	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
of	O
course	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
is	O
quite	O
in	O
time	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
,	O
is	O
again	O
disapointed	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Bride	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
inconsolable	O
She	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
holidays	O
,	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
who	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
by	O
fame	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
surprise	O
of	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Macnamarra	I-pers
:	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
conquest	O
;	O
all	O
her	O
friends	O
thought	O
a	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
accepted	O
his	O
proposal	O
,	O
&	O
told	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
certainty	O
;	O
they	O
,	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
can	O
only	O
settle	O
70	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
1000	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
fortune	O
:	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
enough	O
to	O
live	O
on	O
--	O
so	O
now	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
,	O
&	O
notifye	O
in	O
form	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
match	O
is	O
quite	O
off	O
--	O
a	O
foolish	O
buſsineſs	O
!	O
--	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
Young	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
,	O
if	O
inclination	O
was	O
equal	O
;	O
on	O
ten	O
thousand	O
a	O
Year	O
they	O
might	O
very	O
well	O
save	O
for	O
joynture	O
,	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
need	O
not	O
live	O
like	O
a	O
Duke	O
--	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
Wild	O
&	O
Drunken	O
;	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
better	O
off	O
without	O
him	O
--	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
is	O
come	O
out	O
this	O
winter	O
,	O
ready	O
for	O
a	O
Bride	O
:	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
yet	O
presented	O
.	O
--	O
Susan	B-pers
,	O
has	O
married	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
richest	O
fortunes	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
;	O
a	O
neice	O
of	O
the	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aldbourough	I-pers
--	O
Dowr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dutchſs	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Chandois	I-pers
,	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
Lord	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
her	O
father	O
gives	O
25	O
thousd	O
:	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Familly	O
is	O
so	O
rich	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
now	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
,	O
has	O
made	O
an	O
awkward	O
sort	O
of	O
Bustle	O
;	O
about	O
his	O
seat	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
himself	O
too	O
soon	O
a	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
all	O
acts	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
some	O
say	O
,	O
his	O
title	O
will	O
be	O
disputed	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
his	O
Estate	O
which	O
is	O
worse	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
joyns	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Elco	I-pers
and	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Dear	O
Capt	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
pray	O
present	O
all	O
our	O
compts	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
believe	O
me	O
Yours	O
Sincerely	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
