TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
1789	O
--	O
31	O
July	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
,	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
most	O
of	O
her	O
children	O
about	O
her	O
&	O
an	O
upper	O
Maid	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
reading	O
to	O
them	O
a	O
religious	O
story	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
concluſion	O
she	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
prayers	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
“	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
man	O
who	O
would	O
join	O
with	O
them	O
”	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
uncommonly	O
wet	O
day	O
--	O
the	O
rain	O
began	O
soon	O
after	O
8	O
and	O
continued	O
without	O
intermiſsion	O
till	O
past	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
succeeded	O
by	O
a	O
prodigious	O
high	O
wind	O
--	O
1	O
August	O
/	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
irresolute	O
this	O
morning	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
determine	O
whether	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
pickwick	O
or	O
Corsham	B-place
as	O
the	O
Clouds	O
were	O
lowering	O
&	O
threatened	O
us	O
with	O
another	O
deluge	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
decided	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
improbable	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Isted	I-pers
who	O
was	O
riding	O
out	O
upon	O
busineſs	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
village	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
&	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
return	O
soon	O
&	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Methuen	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
Catering	O
--	O
&	O
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
my	O
coming	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
fully	O
expected	O
me	O
&	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
suitable	O
calculation	O
in	O
the	O
provision	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
lucky	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
spent	O
this	O
day	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
but	O
for	O
an	O
ill	O
natured	O
Headache	O
,	O
which	O
almost	O
prevented	O
my	O
looking	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Pictures	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
on	O
before	O
12	O
&	O
continued	O
till	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
recollect	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
before	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
charming	O
pictures	O
indeed	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
enjoy	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
distracted	O
with	O
pain	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
&	O
returned	O
to	O
pickwick	O
--	O
one	O
portrait	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
mention	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Methuen	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
by	O
Gainsborough	B-pers
--	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
picture	O
&	O
the	O
strongeſt	O
likeneſs	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
taken	O
of	O
your	O
Husband	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
pointed	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
ridiculously	O
like	O
--	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
little	O
larger	O
scale	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
unpleasant	O
bluntneſs	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
yt	O
she	O
thought	O
my	O
visit	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
pictures	O
&	O
yt	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
ye	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
aſsured	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
ye	O
case	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
convince	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
return	O
to	O
them	O
the	O
first	O
opporty-	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
Letters	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	B-place
to	O
inform	O
them	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jekyl	I-pers
,	O
tired	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
objections	O
&	O
Tardineſs	O
had	O
plunged	O
,	O
like	O
us	O
,	O
into	O
matrimony	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
thrown	O
themselves	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
a	O
parent	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
has	O
very	O
little	O
feeling	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
deprive	O
his	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
estate	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
may	O
keep	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
scanty	O
allowance	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
outlive	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
merit	O
in	O
these	O
young	O
people	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
much	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
was	O
married	O
last	O
week	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
the	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
&	O
rode	O
very	O
hard	O
home	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
the	O
exercise	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
effect	O
which	O
it	O
produced	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
free	O
from	O
pain	O
before	O
I	O
reached	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
rode	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Mare	O
,	O
a	O
Hack	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
playful	O
tricks	O
of	O
Madcap	O
2	O
/	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
last	O
night	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Letter	O
&	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
contained	O
one	O
too	O
you	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beavoir	I-pers
,	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
forward	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
Church	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Sermon	O
delivered	O
in	O
so	O
fine	O
a	O
manner	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
tone	O
of	O
voice	O
so	O
particularly	O
affecting	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
person	O
was	O
charmed	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
equally	O
edified	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
except	O
my	O
righthand	O
Neighbor	O
who	O
seemed	O
comfortably	O
asleep	O
)	O
--	O
the	O
subject	O
was	O
the	O
vanity	O
of	O
human	O
Wishes	O
--	O
after	O
the	O
Close	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
fine	O
&	O
solemn	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
Turned	O
round	O
to	O
expreſs	O
the	O
raptures	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
half	O
in	O
tears	O
--	O
We	O
both	O
agreed	O
that	O
we	O
never	O
heard	O
such	O
a	O
sermon	O
&	O
delivered	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
deepest	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
our	O
minds	O
before	O
--	O
or	O
as	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Oratory	O
,	O
nothing	O
equal	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
so	O
affected	O
&	O
entertained	O
,	O
&	O
could	O
have	O
sat	O
with	O
delight	O
for	O
hours	O
--	O
from	O
the	O
honesty	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
he	O
said	O
“	O
I	O
wish	O
the	B-pers
Marquiſ	I-pers
of	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
heard	O
him	O
--	O
surely	O
his	O
heart	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
affected	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
made	O
this	B-pers
worthy	I-pers
curate	I-pers
happy	O
by	O
bestowing	O
a	O
living	O
upon	O
so	O
deserving	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
”	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
not	O
only	O
unexceptionable	O
but	O
truly	O
estimable	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
the	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
--	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
Major	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Huntindon	I-pers
's	O
Chapel	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
the	O
first	O
Volume	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
s	O
tour	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
astonished	O
at	O
the	O
Vulgarity	O
of	O
the	O
Language	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
extract	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
ode	O
to	O
Society	O
in	O
which	O
She	O
notices	O
ye	O
manners	O
of	O
different	O
Countries	O
--	O
&	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
--	O
Or	O
if	O
to	O
wiser	O
Britain	O
led	O
,	O
Your	O
vagrant	O
Feet	O
desire	O
to	O
tread	O
with	O
measured	O
step	O
and	O
anxious	O
care	O
The	O
precincts	O
pure	O
of	O
Portman	O
square	O
While	O
wit	O
with	O
elegance	O
combined	O
,	O
And	O
polished	O
manners	O
there	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
The	O
taste	O
correct	O
--	O
and	O
fertile	O
mind	O
Remember	O
vigilance	O
lurks	O
near	O
And	O
silence	O
with	O
unnotic	O
'd	O
sneer	O
Who	O
watches	O
but	O
to	O
tell	O
again	O
Your	O
foibles	O
with	O
tomorrow	O
's	O
pen	O
Till	O
titt'ring	O
malice	O
smiles	O
to	O
see	O
Your	O
wonder	O
--	O
grave	O
Society	O
--	O
Hester	O
Lynch	O
Piozzi	O
,	O
Observations	O
and	O
Reflections	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
Journey	O
through	O
France	O
,	O
Italy	O
,	O
and	O
Germany	O
Vol	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Ode	O
to	O
Society	O
III	O
.	O
Speaking	O
of	O
the	O
friendlineſs	O
of	O
Lizards	O
to	O
the	O
human	O
race	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
“	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
many	O
vipers	O
and	O
so	O
few	O
Lizards	O
it	O
is	O
surprising	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
London	O
--	O
Hester	O
Lynch	O
Piozzi	O
,	O
Observations	O
and	O
Reflections	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
Journey	O
through	O
France	O
,	O
Italy	O
,	O
and	O
Germany	O
Vol	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
20	O
October	O
1786	O
.	O
She	O
gives	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
travels	O
&	O
seems	O
inchanted	O
with	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
she	O
frightens	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
Account	O
of	O
ye	O
Muskitoes	O
&	O
Buggs	O
--	O
they	O
would	O
devour	O
me	O
well	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
risk	O
my	O
body	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
certainty	O
of	O
being	O
Tormented	O
--	O
3	O
/	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
perverse	O
Creature	O
--	O
after	O
writing	O
me	O
a	O
scrap	O
of	O
figitts	O
about	O
me	O
--	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
consolation	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Venice	B-place
this	O
morning	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
have	O
put	O
off	O
my	O
little	O
Tour	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
spending	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
She	O
wrote	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Trinet	I-pers
,	O
mentioned	O
my	O
being	O
here	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
--	O
excentrick	O
young	O
man	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
seemed	O
to	O
love	O
my	O
Wife	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
&	O
never	O
appeared	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
's	O
exceſsive	O
Vanity	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
She	O
you	O
She	O
had	O
any	O
said	O
was	O
We	O
have	O
lovely	O
fine	O
weather	O
these	O
three	O
last	O
days	O
--	O
And	O
I	O
aſsure	O
my	O
health	O
is	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
your	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
wish	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
unlikely	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
stay	O
a	O
week	O
extraordinary	O
for	O
I	O
hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
&	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
is	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
not	O
unlikely	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
introduced	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilberforce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
conjecture	O
,	O
I	O
expreſsed	O
a	O
wish	O
,	O
this	O
morning	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
.	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
favorite	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
--	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
shall	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
and	O
go	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
look	O
so	O
clear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
small	O
pritensions	O
to	O
a	O
Colour	O
&	O
am	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
spirits	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
our	O
separation	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
that	O
an	O
hours	O
recollection	O
&	O
thought	O
of	O
things	O
past	O
&	O
paſsing	O
has	O
destroyed	O
the	O
good	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
waters	O
for	O
the	O
preceding	O
week	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
said	O
“	O
a	O
bilious	O
Man	O
like	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
never	O
be	O
separated	O
from	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
is	O
so	O
dear	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
the	O
Waters	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
infinitely	O
more	O
more	O
service	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
”	O
This	O
is	O
certainly	O
very	O
true	O
&	O
hard	O
is	O
our	O
Fate	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
enjoy	O
ourselves	O
as	O
we	O
might	O
do	O
--	O
my	O
agreeable	O
Major	B-pers
is	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
a	O
similar	O
situation	O
--	O
What	O
horrid	O
Accounts	O
from	O
Bristol	B-place
--	O
and	O
too	O
many	O
perfectly	O
true	O
--	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
does	O
not	O
give	O
information	O
of	O
such	O
savage	O
barbarities	O
being	O
ever	O
committed	O
by	O
a	O
Nation	O
even	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
the	O
most	O
rude	O
&	O
uncivilized	O
--	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
people	O
so	O
enlightenined	O
as	O
the	O
French	O
&	O
who	O
have	O
boasted	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
their	O
liberality	O
of	O
Sentiment	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
premeditated	O
cruelties	O
is	O
amazing	O
--	O
one	O
would	O
suppose	O
that	O
hell	O
was	O
let	O
loose	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
country	O
teemed	O
with	O
Infernal	O
Spirits	O
--	O
These	O
commotions	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
settled	O
so	O
easily	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
as	O
the	O
Patriots	O
expect	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
has	O
just	O
sent	O
me	O
an	O
invitation	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
longs	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
You	O
--	O
Tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
that	O
I	O
shall	O
ruin	O
him	O
--	O
Adieu	O
My	O
ever	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Affy	O
&	O
ardently	O
Your	O
own	O
J.D——	B-pers
Louisa	B-pers
must	O
have	O
Kiſses	O
in	O
abundance	O
--	O
papa	B-pers
loves	O
her	O
dearly	O
.	O
