TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
this	O
Morning	O
a	O
sweet	O
girl	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
my	O
Nephew	O
in	O
a	O
Putred	O
fever	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
with	O
the	O
Poor	O
Parents	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
gueſs	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
mood	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
written	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Ailesbury	I-pers
to	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Ticket	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
succeed	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
the	O
Ticket	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
.	O
believe	O
me	O
always	O
to	O
remain	O
both	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
Maria	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Friday	O
June	O
the	O
13	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
June	O
13	O
th	O
1788	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
