TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
--	O
Saffron	B-place
Walden	I-place
Janry	O
9	O
th	O
1801	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
So	O
far	O
are	O
you	O
from	O
being	O
to	O
Blame	O
in	O
giving	O
me	O
your	O
advice	O
concerning	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Tring	B-place
--	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
my	O
self	O
More	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
Expreſs	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
adopt	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
determination	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
Secret	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
also	O
been	O
of	O
further	O
Service	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
convince	O
my	O
dear	O
Infatuated	O
Sister	O
--	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
means	O
than	O
by	O
sending	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
so	O
kindly	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
apprise	O
you	O
of	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
will	O
(	O
however	O
neceſsary	O
)	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
without	O
informing	O
the	O
writer	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
paragraph	O
which	O
reflected	O
in	O
the	O
smallest	O
degree	O
upon	O
my	O
Sister	O
s	O
Conduct	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
therefore	O
safe	O
&	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
yr	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
private	O
intimation	O
of	O
the	O
Wickedneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
whom	O
she	O
has	O
plac	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Confidence	O
has	O
at	O
length	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
eyes	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
be	O
productive	O
of	O
great	O
Advantage	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
trouble	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Harry	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Enclos	O
'd	O
Note	O
--	O
my	O
first	O
order	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Turkey	O
's	O
&	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
No	O
8	O
Berkely	O
Square	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
allow	O
Baily	B-pers
to	O
read	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
&	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
as	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
are	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
entrusted	O
that	O
Secret	O
Excuse	O
my	O
giving	O
you	O
this	O
trouble	O
--	O
believe	O
me	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
much	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
do	O
desire	O
Hūtley	B-pers
,	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
people	O
who	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
--	O
or	O
some	O
little	O
Cabin	O
or	O
other	O
where	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
til	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
Major	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
&	O
beg	O
&	O
implore	O
him	O
to	O
Expedite	O
matters	O
with	O
all	O
poſsible	O
dispatch	O
--	O
I	O
sd	O
think	O
Either	O
Woburn	B-place
or	O
Ampthill	B-place
--	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
parts	O
such	O
as	O
convenient	O
temporary	O
Habitation	O
may	O
be	O
found	O
after	O
imploring	O
yr	O
forgiveneſs	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
to	O
attempt	O
amusing	O
you	O
.	O
but	O
first	O
I	O
must	O
aſsure	O
you	O
how	O
truly	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
indispos	O
'd	O
,	O
into	O
his	O
troublesome	O
complaint	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
recipe	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Dr	B-pers
Freind	I-pers
which	O
has	O
done	O
great	O
Service	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
to	O
some	O
constitutions	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
too	O
heating	O
.	O
but	O
Sir	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Milman	I-pers
s	O
remedy	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
most	O
certain	O
Cold	O
Water	O
any	O
Morning	O
at	O
first	O
rising	O
--	O
this	O
Place	O
is	O
as	O
all	O
the	O
world	O
knows	O
very	O
Magnificent	O
,	O
tho	O
Still	O
the	O
Salon	O
,	O
the	O
Source	O
that	O
Slots	O
out	O
what	O
was	O
formerly	O
the	O
Buttery	O
Hall	O
&	O
the	O
Chaple	O
--	O
are	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
finer	O
than	O
is	O
to	O
see	O
--	O
was	O
at	O
Warwick	O
Castle	O
--	O
than	O
here	O
are	O
magnificent	O
buildings	O
&	O
a	O
Column	O
in	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
Ground	O
which	O
are	O
extensive	O
--	O
a	O
fine	O
river	O
the	O
Cam	O
Meanders	O
thr	O
'	O
o	O
the	O
Park	O
--	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Menagerie	O
&	O
pretty	O
flower	O
garden	O
are	O
new	O
tho	O
Have	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
--	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
&	O
round	O
the	O
Garden	O
&	O
home	O
again	O
--	O
at	O
my	O
first	O
arrival	O
I	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Crutchly	I-pers
great	O
friends	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
s	O
both	O
Members	O
of	O
Parlmt	O
&	O
both	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Trade	O
--	O
Metcalf	B-pers
is	O
a	O
great	O
distiller	O
&	O
pays	O
£60	O
000	O
pr	O
annum	O
duty	O
--	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
Judge	O
of	O
his	O
Wealth	O
--	O
Crutchly	B-pers
more	O
properly	O
descends	O
from	O
Trade	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
Brewer	O
his	O
Uncle	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
dyer	O
.	O
Who	O
left	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
£100	O
000	O
.	O
These	O
Men	O
are	O
full	O
Sensible	O
--	O
&	O
full	O
Vote	O
the	O
right	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
for	O
Pitt	B-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Grenvilles	I-pers
--	O
my	O
good	O
Host	O
is	O
more	O
Aimiable	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
my	O
Heart	O
better	O
than	O
any	O
body	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
but	O
one	O
thing	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
be	O
perfect	O
!	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
up	O
to	O
Pity	O
!	O
what	O
was	O
mean	O
'd	O
for	O
Mankind	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
intolerant	O
in	O
his	O
Political	O
Principles	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
He	O
lets	O
bad	O
News	O
made	O
him	O
ill	O
--	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
much	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
but	O
Thank	O
god	O
without	O
a	O
Cause	O
.	O
Of	O
Course	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
you	O
no	O
information	O
respecting	O
Politicks	O
the	O
Papers	O
will	O
record	O
all	O
we	O
hear	O
upon	O
that	O
Subject	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
Six	O
Children	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
Eldest	O
daughter	O
the	O
most	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
Young	O
Woman	O
I	O
ever	O
yet	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
Pretty	O
in	O
her	O
person	O
lively	O
,	O
Gay	O
&	O
Youthfull	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
has	O
the	O
most	O
serious	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
religious	O
,	O
her	O
mornings	O
are	O
occupied	O
in	O
visiting	O
the	O
Sick	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
needy	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
this	O
large	O
Establishment	O
she	O
is	O
peculiarly	O
clever	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
gone	O
to	O
pray	O
by	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
41	O
years	O
in	O
this	O
Garden	O
.	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
dying	O
--	O
the	O
Chaplain	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
she	O
lost	O
no	O
Time	O
in	O
giving	O
her	O
aſsistance	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
Tell	O
you	O
a	O
pretty	O
Episode	O
--	O
about	O
Ten	O
days	O
or	O
more	O
since	O
--	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
Young	O
Girl	O
in	O
rags	O
begging	O
--	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
many	O
questions	O
which	O
she	O
Answer	O
'd	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
Orphan	O
Girl	O
without	O
Father	O
or	O
Mother	O
.	O
she	O
also	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
resided	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
impartial	O
account	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
spoke	O
the	O
truth	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
destitute	O
Situation	O
--	O
adding	O
that	O
it	O
wd	O
be	O
a	O
mercy	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
saved	O
from	O
Prostitution	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
cloath	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
maintains	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
already	O
taught	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
her	O
Prayers	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
not	O
teaching	O
her	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
as	O
yet	O
the	O
Girl	O
goes	O
on	O
vastly	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
will	O
be	O
recorded	O
by	O
saving	O
a	O
Soul	O
from	O
death	O
.	O
she	O
sends	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
Lecture	O
her	O
.	O
the	O
Girl	O
already	O
knows	O
her	O
Letters	O
.	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
Aimiable	O
to	O
see	O
with	O
what	O
patience	O
&	O
perseverance	O
she	O
gives	O
her	O
leſsons	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Crutchly	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
have	O
all	O
left	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
since	O
their	O
departure	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
Mr	B-pers
Tho	I-pers
's	I-pers
Milles	I-pers
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
Exeter	O
s	O
Son	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
also	O
departed	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
only	O
inmate	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
charges	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
&	O
has	O
occasion	O
'd	O
me	O
much	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
we	O
Yesterday	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
advice	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
but	O
complains	O
of	O
being	O
Weak	O
&	O
low	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
&	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sad	O
News	O
,	O
we	O
read	O
that	O
Col.	B-pers
Byng	I-pers
was	O
killed	O
he	O
is	O
Nephew	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
&	O
no	O
letter	O
having	O
been	O
received	O
from	O
her	O
since	O
her	O
departure	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
his	O
Employment	O
abroad	O
did	O
not	O
require	O
him	O
to	O
hazard	O
his	O
Life	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Scandalous	O
jots	O
of	O
this	O
Ministry	O
.	O
Wyndham	B-pers
having	O
married	O
his	O
Aunt	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
Whilst	O
we	O
are	O
starving	O
the	O
Publick	O
Money	O
is	O
wasted	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
that	O
little	O
Margaret	B-pers
will	O
as	O
fully	O
compensate	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
may	O
that	O
this	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Margaret	B-pers
is	O
very	O
grateful	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
favor	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
Sign	O
--	O
tell	O
yr	O
dear	O
daughter	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
be	O
aſsured	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
all	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
many	O
happy	O
years	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
or	O
read	O
the	O
Modern	O
Philosophers	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
read	O
this	O
Novel	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
entirely	O
sicken	O
'd	O
into	O
French	O
principles	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Author	O
has	O
entered	O
by	O
ridicule	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
effectual	O
Service	O
tho	O
the	O
most	O
serious	O
divines	O
has	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
Confeſs	O
--	O
pray	O
read	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
infinite	O
humour	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
moral	O
is	O
fine	O
for	O
it	O
proves	O
that	O
however	O
good	O
the	O
disposition	O
--	O
without	O
the	O
foundation	O
in	O
religion	O
it	O
must	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
Lady	B-pers
H——n	I-pers
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
at	O
Court	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
positively	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
excited	O
some	O
uneasineſs	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Story	O
goes	O
that	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
s	O
she	O
bawl	O
'd	O
out	O
is	O
that	O
old	O
Woman	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
.	O
she	O
calls	O
her	O
self	O
32	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
:	O
the	O
P	O
:	O
forc	O
'd	O
Sir	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
H——n	I-pers
to	O
stay	O
thro	O
supper	O
but	O
whether	O
Fitz	B-pers
terrified	O
him	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Caprice	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
did	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
--	O
She	O
was	O
Mistreſs	O
to	O
C	B-pers
:	I-pers
——	I-pers
G——lle	I-pers
--	O
I	O
for	O
one	O
think	O
this	O
last	O
News	O
is	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
News	O
can	O
be	O
,	O
when	O
so	O
many	O
human	O
creatures	O
see	O
Sacrific	O
'd	O
to	O
Ambition	O
,	O
it	O
certainly	O
will	O
oblige	O
the	O
Emperor	O
to	O
make	O
Peace	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
we	O
shall	O
also	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
follow	O
his	O
example	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
&	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
return	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
enable	O
us	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Advantageous	O
Peace	O
--	O
how	O
good	O
you	O
are	O
about	O
my	O
letters	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
much	O
the	O
one	O
from	O
my	B-pers
Aunt	I-pers
St	I-pers
Leger	I-pers
.	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
one	O
from	O
her	O
direction	O
here	O
poor	O
Mama	O
she	O
is	O
almost	O
blind	O
.	O
who	O
wd	O
wish	O
for	O
old	O
Eyes	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bring	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
wish	O
that	O
hers	O
may	O
see	O
another	O
Century	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
Prayers	O
in	O
this	O
Chaple	O
every	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
trait	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
dying	O
--	O
&	O
read	O
him	O
a	O
Chapter	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Testament	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
these	O
Children	O
are	O
brought	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
tired	O
yr	O
Eyes	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
tried	O
yr	O
Patience	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
bid	O
you	O
Adieu	O
with	O
my	O
kind	O
wish	O
to	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
the	O
dear	O
Lsa	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
most	O
truly	O
&	O
Affecly	O
yrs	O
,	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
Pray	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
goes	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
or	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
so	O
do	O
not	O
inclose	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mind	O
Postage	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
--	O
pray	O
write	O
after	O
seeing	O
Harry	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
Walden	B-place
Janry	O
nine	O
.	O
1801	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Griffin	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
