TOKEN	NE
Mary	B-pers
on	O
tour	O
in	O
1776	O
My	O
dearest	O
Clara	B-pers
I	O
am	O
quite	O
penetrated	O
with	O
sorrow	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
extremely	O
Ill	O
--	O
&	O
quite	O
hate	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
her	O
want	O
of	O
feeling	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
aſsured	O
me	O
She	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
look	O
better	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
perfectly	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
occasion	O
'd	O
that	O
agitation	O
of	O
Spirits	O
You	O
hint	O
at	O
--	O
for	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
be	O
indifferent	O
when	O
your	O
happineſs	O
is	O
concern	O
'd	O
--	O
--	O
Surely	O
,	O
Surely	O
my	O
Clara	B-pers
you	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
earnest	O
when	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
imagind	O
my	O
Sentiments	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
you	O
wld	O
.	O
vary	O
with	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
allow	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
“	O
my	O
“	O
superiours	O
in	O
every	O
“	O
Respect	O
”	O
--	O
was	O
they	O
equal	O
to	O
you	O
Clara	B-pers
in	O
Sentiment	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
many	O
Shining	O
Characters	O
in	O
high	O
Life	O
--	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Dearth	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
astonish	O
'd	O
&	O
vextd	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
recd	O
.	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
Letters	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
--	O
that	O
(	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
Manner	O
--	O
for	O
many	O
letters	O
she	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
she	O
finds	O
have	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
)	O
than	O
attributing	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
a	O
Valet	O
de	O
Place	O
--	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
an	O
Unfair	O
action	O
)	O
--	O
&	O
who	O
was	O
charged	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
Letters	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
office	O
--	O
we	O
imagine	O
he	O
put	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
given	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Letters	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
&	O
then	O
destroy	O
'd	O
them	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
directed	O
to	O
Dover	B-place
as	O
I	O
desired	O
--	O
ye	O
Letters	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
safely	O
forwarded	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
People	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Inn	O
to	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
for	O
Your	O
amusement	O
transcribe	O
ye	O
:	O
chief	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
no	O
critisism	O
or	O
remarks	O
&	O
pray	O
burn	O
it	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
You	O
read	O
it	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
bear	O
a	O
re-perusal	O
Tuesday	O
30	O
Left	O
London	B-place
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Rochester	B-place
where	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
P——	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
F——	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
our	O
party	O
--	O
slept	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
we	O
did	O
not	O
omit	O
taking	O
an	O
observation	O
of	O
that	O
vast	O
body	O
wch	O
.	O
almost	O
obscur	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
singular	O
&	O
extroadinary	O
appearance	O
--	O
I	O
leave	O
ye	O
.	O
discription	O
to	O
astronomers	O
&	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
presumption	O
in	O
me	O
Clara	B-pers
to	O
tell	O
You	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Thursday	O
Wed	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
person	O
in	O
Company	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
ye	O
.	O
Cathedral	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
were	O
all	O
goodneſs	O
&	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
Canterbury	B-place
without	O
Seeing	O
it	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
breakfast	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
Noble	O
&	O
venerable	O
Structure	O
--	O
Vast	O
in	O
Size	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Architecture	O
P	O
plain	O
&	O
Elegant	O
--	O
no	O
Pictures	O
or	O
remains	O
of	O
Romish	O
Ornaments	O
or	O
decorations	O
--	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
C	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
french	O
Church	O
.	O
--	O
About	O
one	O
oClock	O
got	O
to	O
Dover	B-place
--	O
the	O
Corn	O
fields	O
was	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
least	O
agreeable	O
Objects	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Stalks	O
loaded	O
with	O
grain	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
beautiful	O
richest	O
tints	O
of	O
Gold	O
--	O
but	O
yet	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
Harvest	O
--	O
the	O
Fields	O
were	O
quite	O
luxuriant	O
--	O
the	O
Hops	O
too	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
beautifull	O
state	O
--	O
at	O
our	O
arrival	O
at	O
Dover	B-place
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
--	O
they	O
remaind	O
at	O
our	O
Inn	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
--	O
the	O
Carriages	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
ye	O
.	O
Ship	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Wind	O
&	O
tide	O
against	O
us	O
for	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
Steep	O
Hill	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
--	O
a	O
sight	O
worthy	O
ye	O
.	O
observation	O
--	O
30	O
Acres	O
of	O
Land	O
are	O
inclosed	O
within	O
its	O
walls	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
now	O
of	O
no	O
great	O
use	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
walls	O
of	O
ye	O
Square	O
Tower	O
of	O
Julius	B-pers
Caesar	I-pers
are	O
still	O
rem	O
remaining	O
--	O
its	O
preservation	O
is	O
of	O
consequence	O
to	O
ye	O
Curate	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
here	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
£	O
30	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
whilst	O
it	O
remains	O
standing	O
--	O
a	O
Round	O
Tower	O
is	O
Close	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Above	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Belfry	O
--	O
Admiral	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Reign	O
of	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
After	O
obtaining	O
a	O
Victory	O
;	O
--	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
home	O
to	O
England	B-place
--	O
desired	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
remove	O
those	O
the	O
Bells	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
of	O
J.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
)	O
to	O
Portsmouth	B-place
--	O
were	O
they	O
now	O
are	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
400	O
Men	O
now	O
in	O
Garrison	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Castle	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
comfortable	O
&	O
neat	O
barracks	O
--	O
a	O
Most	O
remarkable	O
Well	O
360	O
feet	O
deep	O
is	O
enclosed	O
within	O
a	O
Building	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
sunk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
of	O
J.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
a	O
large	O
Wheel	O
turn	O
'd	O
by	O
6	O
men	O
draws	O
ye	O
.	O
water	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
top	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
always	O
20	O
feet	O
water	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
renders	O
it	O
still	O
more	O
remarkable	O
is	O
ye	O
echo	O
--	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pin	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
in	O
beat	O
against	O
ye	O
.	O
Sides	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
heard	O
it	O
distinctly	O
fall	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
water	O
--	O
a	O
small	O
pebble	O
Stone	O
thrown	O
in	O
--	O
when	O
it	O
reaches	O
ye	O
.	O
Water	O
sounds	O
like	O
ye	O
.	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
noise	O
encreasing	O
according	O
to	O
ye	O
size	O
of	O
whatever	O
is	O
cast	O
in	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
brick	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
feet	O
--	O
a	O
fine	O
Chalk	O
Cliff	O
forms	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
this	O
well	O
--	O
a	O
Man	O
has	O
ventur	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Bottom	O
without	O
being	O
annoy	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
damp	O
.	O
--	O
Queen	B-pers
Elizth-	I-pers
Pocket	O
Pistol	O
is	O
another	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Curiosities	O
they	O
show	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
an	O
Immense	O
Cannon	O
and	O
formidable	O
looking	O
Cannon	O
--	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
shew	O
'd	O
shown	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
Govenor	O
s	O
appartments	O
;	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
too	O
late	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fatigued	O
wth	O
.	O
walking	O
down	O
this	O
Steep	O
Hill	O
--	O
spent	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
Evening	O
in	O
a	O
Sociable	O
manner	O
at	O
our	O
Inn	O
--	O
Thursday	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
Wind	O
still	O
Contrary	O
--	O
the	O
Sailors	O
&	O
Capt	O
.	O
tell	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
paſsage	O
is	O
safe	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Wind	O
make	O
little	O
difference	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
apprenhensions	O
alone	O
keeps	O
us	O
here	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
always	O
suffers	O
so	O
much	O
from	O
Sickneſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
ye	O
younger	O
part	O
of	O
us	O
--	O
are	O
as	O
patient	O
as	O
Young	O
people	O
can	O
be	O
--	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
fears	O
--	O
&	O
are	O
eager	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
Idea	O
's	O
realiz	O
'd	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
before	O
dinner	O
upon	O
ye	O
other	O
head	O
--	O
saw	O
several	O
Ships	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
come	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Harbour	O
--	O
The	O
Sailors	O
told	O
