TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
Janry	O
26	O
th	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
Lord	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
again	O
to	O
attend	O
Parliamt	O
without	O
getting	O
a	O
direction	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
impatient	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
over	O
&	O
over	O
again	O
for	O
yr	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
aware	O
of	O
the	O
magnitude	O
of	O
the	O
favor	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
well	O
knowing	O
how	O
unpleasant	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
a	O
Vulgar	O
mind	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
implicated	O
in	O
other	O
peoples	O
Affairs	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
more	O
so	O
to	O
a	O
mind	O
like	O
yours	O
,	O
not	O
my	O
only	O
with	O
high	O
Principles	O
of	O
Honour	O
--	O
but	O
with	O
Polish	O
'd	O
manners	O
.	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
add	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
trust	O
me	O
safely	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
committed	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
smallest	O
degree	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
exactly	O
the	O
Censure	O
that	O
Baily	B-pers
sent	O
me	O
,	O
first	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
wrote	O
him	O
respecting	O
my	O
Letter	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
acquainting	O
her	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
busineſs	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
thi	O
nk	O
was	O
Sufficient	O
to	O
Alarm	O
any	O
one	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
shut	O
her	O
Eyes	O
&	O
Ears	O
to	O
Conviction	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
it	O
has	O
done	O
so	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
wrote	O
a	O
tolerably	O
Spirited	O
Letter	O
to	O
Stevens	B-pers
--	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
an	O
Answer	O
last	O
Friday	O
--	O
perhaps	O
she	O
may	O
not	O
answer	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
but	O
upon	O
that	O
Answer	O
depends	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Wing	B-place
--	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
think	O
my	O
self	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
if	O
you	O
wd	O
Enquire	O
--	O
if	O
a	O
Lodging	O
could	O
be	O
procur	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighborhood	O
of	O
the	O
Lodge	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
Answer	O
from	O
Major	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
--	O
who	O
promises	O
to	O
put	O
order	O
the	O
Painting	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
longest	O
traces	O
&	O
the	O
most	O
dangerous	O
behind	O
them	O
)	O
immediately	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
my	O
Sister	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
however	O
my	O
Conduct	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
thought	O
strict	O
respecting	O
the	O
keeping	O
or	O
discharging	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
suffer	O
such	O
Vermin	O
as	O
Virgin	B-pers
&	O
his	O
daughter	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
fool	O
--	O
or	O
to	O
sneer	O
at	O
me	O
--	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
was	O
now	O
under	O
my	O
Protection	O
,	O
&	O
til	O
I	O
could	O
ensure	O
Peace	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
&	O
my	O
Servants	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
if	O
by	O
Chance	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
or	O
you	O
sd	O
see	O
Baily	B-pers
ask	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
disposing	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
.	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
Sister	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
from	O
Steven	O
's	O
--	O
she	O
however	O
wrote	O
Anne	B-pers
a	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
almost	O
mocking	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
folly	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
happy	O
if	O
my	O
Turkey	O
was	O
Either	O
pleasure	O
or	O
Service	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fisherson	I-pers
was	O
long	O
prepar	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
marries	O
with	O
the	O
Approbation	O
of	O
her	O
Mistreſs	O
--	O
&	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
--	O
What	O
Times	O
these	O
are	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
does	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
--	O
&	O
hear	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Gangche	O
Gauche	O
that	O
people	O
in	O
London	B-place
are	O
rather	O
disatisfied	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
t	O
are	O
not	O
very	O
happy	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
goes	O
this	O
year	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
Parliamentary	O
Season	O
in	O
PallMall	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Steady	O
watch	O
I	O
conclude	O
.	O
They	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
Supplementary	O
Militia	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
reduc	O
'd	O
the	O
regular	O
Milit	O
i	O
a	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
the	O
Opposition	O
are	O
making	O
a	O
Stir	O
--	O
for	O
Grey	B-pers
also	O
is	O
the	O
declar	O
'd	O
Head	O
of	O
that	O
Party	O
--	O
as	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Shop	O
(	O
my	O
frd	O
stil	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Thatch	O
'd	O
House	O
.	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Cockpit	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Grey	B-pers
made	O
the	O
Amendment	O
--	O
God	O
send	O
all	O
honest	O
Men	O
to	O
succeed	O
in	O
getting	O
us	O
Peace	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
most	O
lively	O
pleasant	O
Letter	O
from	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
that	O
can	O
be	O
conceived	O
--	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Deal	B-place
by	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Mail	O
Coach	O
.	O
her	O
friends	O
all	O
remonstrated	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
hoped	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
repeat	O
this	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
but	O
Ly	B-pers
Nelthorpe	I-pers
writes	O
word	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
at	O
Chaple	O
--	O
&	O
thought	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
sadly	O
--	O
she	O
&	O
I	O
are	O
Engaged	O
in	O
a	O
warm	O
dispute	O
,	O
(	O
an	O
Amiable	O
one	O
)	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
Buonaparte	B-pers
will	O
restore	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
France	I-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
sincerely	O
believe	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
the	O
dear	O
Emigrant	O
Count	B-pers
Sulé	I-pers
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
Spirits	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
the	O
K	O
of	O
France	O
will	O
be	O
upon	O
the	O
Throne	O
in	O
leſs	O
than	O
Six	O
Months	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
thinks	O
that	O
Buonaparte	B-pers
will	O
be	O
King	O
of	O
Lombardy	B-place
,	O
take	O
Mantua	B-place
,	O
Peschiare	B-place
,	O
the	O
Piedmontese	B-place
all	O
to	O
Tuscany	B-place
&	O
that	O
side	O
the	O
Alps	O
--	O
I	O
say	O
--	O
No	O
--	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
real	O
Great	O
Ambition	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
restore	O
the	O
Monarchy	O
--	O
make	O
them	O
a	O
rational	O
free	O
Government	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
already	O
aggrandis	O
'd	O
France	B-place
.	O
&	O
then	O
retire	O
into	O
private	O
Life	O
--	O
with	O
a	O
name	O
far	O
Super	O
ior	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
made	O
the	O
World	O
turn	O
pale	O
.	O
to	O
point	O
a	O
Moral	O
,	O
or	O
adorn	O
a	O
tale	O
--	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
only	O
have	O
saved	O
France	B-place
,	O
but	O
Europe	B-place
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
his	O
Consulate	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
change	O
in	O
one	O
year	O
--	O
what	O
Nation	O
wd	O
Suffer	O
a	O
generation	O
of	O
Monarchs	O
--	O
Count	B-pers
Sulé	I-pers
writes	O
,	O
that	O
Buonaparte	B-pers
had	O
sent	O
an	O
Ambaſsador	O
to	O
Petersburgh	B-place
&	O
that	O
Paul	B-pers
sent	O
one	O
from	O
himself	O
to	O
Britain	B-place
to	O
Louis	B-pers
18	I-pers
,	O
&	O
has	O
received	O
one	O
from	O
Louis	B-pers
ye	I-pers
18	I-pers
--	O
he	O
adds	O
that	O
25	O
French	O
Emigrants	O
are	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Calais	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
sent	O
that	O
letter	O
.	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
til	O
the	B-pers
king	I-pers
is	O
upon	O
the	O
Throne	O
--	O
the	O
Chatter	O
is	O
that	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
facilitated	O
the	O
match	O
between	O
Col	B-pers
Erskine	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Paget	I-pers
by	O
making	O
the	O
Col	O
:	O
an	O
Aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
.	O
&	O
his	O
quickneſs	O
in	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
H——n	I-pers
.	I-pers
by	O
getting	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
letter	O
for	O
yr	O
Uncle	O
is	O
much	O
applauded	O
.	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
one	O
Queen	O
to	O
another	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Trifled	O
with	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
ye	O
Interview	O
which	O
is	O
Customary	O
upon	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
a	O
foreign	O
Minister	O
he	O
saw	O
yr	O
Uncle	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
Enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
.	O
&	O
then	O
Sir	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
told	O
his	O
Majesty	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
commiſsion	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
her	O
Majesty	O
The	B-pers
K	I-pers
instantly	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
your	O
Uncle	O
gave	O
the	O
Letter	O
--	O
et	O
en	O
resta	O
la	O
--	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
is	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
.	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
Uneasy	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
very	O
much	O
so	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
dare	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
sends	O
her	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
s	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
goes	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
alarm	O
'd	O
.	O
for	O
16	O
is	O
rather	O
a	O
dangerous	O
age	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
now	O
great	O
hopes	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
Establish	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
principles	O
Sufficiently	O
to	O
enable	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
farmers	O
Servant	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
given	O
proofs	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
divine	O
Truths	O
have	O
made	O
some	O
impreſsions	O
on	O
her	O
mind	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
give	O
my	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
the	O
dear	O
Lsa	B-pers
--	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
a	O
more	O
upright	O
,	O
Steady-Spirited	O
Man	O
does	O
not	O
exist	O
than	O
Baily	B-pers
--	O
I	O
trust	O
in	O
God	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
truly	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
Merits	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
really	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Women	O
.	O
her	O
merit	O
is	O
indeed	O
exalted	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
proud	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
so	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
dupe	O
of	O
Wicked	O
people	O
.	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
too	O
tenacious	O
a	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Abilities	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
once	O
convinc	O
'd	O
no	O
one	O
more	O
ready	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
an	O
Error	O
--	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
God	O
only	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
costs	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
mortification	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
Groſsly	O
abus	O
'd	O
--	O
direct	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
&	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
two	O
letters	O
which	O
I	O
duly	O
received	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
sad	O
cold	O
morning	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
L	I-pers
s	O
breakfast	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Whisky	O
this	O
morng	O
it	O
was	O
dreadfully	O
cold	O
--	O
once	O
more	O
Adieu	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
truly	O
&	O
Affcly	O
yrs	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
Walden	B-place
Janry	O
twentysix	O
1801	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Griffin	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
