TOKEN	NE
--	O
we	O
go	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Family	O
here	O
ex	O
p	O
c	O
ept	O
Osyris	B-pers
&	O
Rhea	B-pers
(	O
who	O
w	O
h	O
e	O
nt	O
to	O
Babel	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
return	O
Monday	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Pray	O
send	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Colley	I-pers
a	O
great	O
Aunt	O
of	O
mine	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Circus	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Brother	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
Health	O
--	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
something	O
about	O
ym	O
if	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
or	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
ym-	O
My	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
love	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
--	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
writing	O
on	O
Monday	O
