TOKEN	NE
Hambledon	B-place
Janry	O
:	O
15	O
th	O
:	O
1815	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
You	O
will	O
ere	O
this	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
melancholy	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
expected	O
event	O
which	O
has	O
taken	O
place	O
in	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Plowden	B-pers
's	O
family	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
very	O
poor	O
Cousin	O
Loui	B-pers
,	O
whose	O
long	O
sufferings	O
were	O
terminated	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
last	O
;	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
regret	O
in	O
common	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
family	O
,	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
Being	O
,	O
we	O
yet	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
be	O
thankful	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
pleased	O
the	O
Almighty	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
consider	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
no	O
human	O
skill	O
could	O
avert	O
the	O
fatal	O
disorder	O
,	O
her	O
death	O
has	O
relieved	O
her	O
family	O
from	O
a	O
sad	O
,	O
&	O
hopeleſs	O
state	O
of	O
anxiety	O
&	O
suspense	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
regret	O
that	O
anything	O
should	O
have	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
having	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
attending	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
:	O
ins	O
t	O
:	O
but	O
,	O
putting	O
my	O
own	O
feelings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
my	O
aſsisting	O
on	O
any	O
joyful	O
occasion	O
,	O
so	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
sad	O
scene	O
will	O
have	O
taken	O
place	O
in	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
aſsure	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
of	O
every	O
kindest	O
interest	O
in	O
her	O
happineſs	O
,	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
offer	O
her	O
in	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
mean	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
love	O
&	O
regards	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
the	O
affectt	O
.	O
remembrance	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Family	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Yrs	O
:	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
Most	O
sincerely	O
,	O
Yr	O
:	O
obliged	O
&	O
affect	O
:	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
HORNDEAN	B-place
(	O
32	O
)	O
