TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
Octobr	O
:	O
6	O
th	O
1787	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
leading	O
for	O
this	O
Month	O
past	O
an	O
unsettled	O
rambling	O
kind	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
prevented	O
me	O
doing	O
anything	O
I	O
ought	O
,	O
or	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
--	O
particularly	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
allowed	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
for	O
chès	O
nous	O
nobody	O
does	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
abused	O
whenever	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
pen	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
lately	O
the	O
House	O
has	O
been	O
full	O
of	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
totally	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
settle	O
comfortably	O
to	O
anything	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
visiti	O
n	O
g	O
too	O
--	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Races	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Inshort	O
my	O
dear	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
constantly	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
heart	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
have	O
much	O
to	O
reproach	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
score	O
of	O
writing	O
--	O
I	O
used	O
you	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
excellent	O
correspondant	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
intercour	O
se	O
was	O
kept	O
up	O
briskly	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
you	O
liked	O
writi	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
had	O
good	O
Eyes	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
now	O
you	O
are	O
married	O
have	O
other	O
occupations	O
,	O
other	O
pursuits	O
,	O
of	O
much	O
greater	O
consequence	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
frequently	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
love	O
&	O
are	O
interested	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
cela	O
est	O
naturel	O
et	O
de	O
raison	O
,	O
auſsi	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
think	O
you	O
very	O
good	O
indeed	O
if	O
you	O
kn	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
of	O
your	O
letters	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
allow	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
two	O
in	O
your	O
debt	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
this	O
year	O
no	O
nor	O
any	O
year	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
decided	O
&	O
I	O
give	O
the	O
thing	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
,	O
again	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
expecti	O
n	O
g	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
being	O
vexed	O
&	O
almost	O
angry	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
inclined	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
very	O
ridiculous	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
more	O
probability	O
of	O
our	O
meeting	O
in	O
London	B-place
to	O
that	O
idea	O
I	O
will	O
attach	O
myself	O
--	O
&	O
will	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
that	O
of	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Honble-	B-pers
Mſ	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
enjoyi	O
n	O
g	O
somethi	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
your	O
society	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
unreas	O
onable	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
monopolize	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
daresay	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
devourd	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
expect	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
submit	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bit	O
myself	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
in	O
a	O
scrambli	O
n	O
g	O
way	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
your	O
naughty	O
Eyes	O
woul	O
d	O
get	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
their	O
continuing	O
weak	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
--	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
them	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
not	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
you	O
hav	O
e	O
so	O
perfect	O
a	O
Secretary	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
be	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
when	O
with	O
his	O
imitation	O
both	O
of	O
your	O
hand	O
&	O
style	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
discovered	O
the	O
differ	O
ence	O
pray	O
thank	O
him	O
sincerely	O
&	O
return	O
ing	O
the	O
very	O
affece	O
regards	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
.	O
Since	O
your	O
first	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
,	O
slept	O
there	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
at	O
Northamton	B-place
with	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
Louisa	B-pers
vastly	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
pleasing	O
,	O
gentle	O
&	O
unaffected	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
exclude	O
Ly	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
by	O
only	O
mentioni	O
n	O
g	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
improves	O
much	O
upon	O
further	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
best	O
bred	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
age	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
in	O
love	O
to	O
with	O
the	O
dear	O
Boys	O
,	O
particularly	O
not	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
great	O
Ld	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
is	O
the	O
tallest	O
Boy	O
of	O
3	O
&	O
½	O
years	O
old	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
seen	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Breeches	O
at	O
13	O
Months	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
prodigy	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
je	O
n'en	O
reviens	O
pas	O
!	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Dorsetshire	B-place
at	O
at	O
Wm	B-pers
's	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
fancy	O
they	O
intend	O
returning	O
soon	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
now	O
gone	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
that	O
name	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
poor	O
Admira	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
--	O
is	O
it	O
poſsible	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
still	O
ignora	O
nt	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
which	O
happened	O
near	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
--	O
she	O
suffered	O
cruelly	O
for	O
many	O
hours	O
previous	O
to	O
that	O
event	O
,	O
particularly	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
suffered	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
Months	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
happy	O
release	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
hopes	O
from	O
the	O
beginni	O
n	O
g	O
almost	O
of	O
her	O
disorder	O
,	O
&	O
nobody	O
certainly	O
could	O
be	O
better	O
prepared	O
for	O
another	O
world	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
properly	O
detached	O
from	O
this	O
,	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
since	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
's	O
Death	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
with	O
his	O
relations	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
leave	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
November	O
when	O
he	O
will	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
Drawingroom	O
--	O
he	O
h	O
as	O
suffered	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
Health	O
&	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
min	O
d	O
from	O
anxiety	O
&	O
attendance	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
will	O
never	O
recover	O
a	O
loſs	O
,	O
that	O
so	O
entirely	O
changes	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
&	O
all	O
his	O
plans	O
&	O
prospects	O
of	O
Comfort	O
&	O
happineſs	O
--	O
his	O
little	O
Girl	O
stayed	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
School	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
again	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
little	O
excursion	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
's	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
the	O
latter	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
musical	O
party	O
at	O
Kelmarsh	B-place
on	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
&	O
other	O
Singers	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
that	O
vastly	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
leſs	O
fond	O
of	O
musick	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
after	O
the	O
Acceſsion	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Mara	B-pers
s	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
where	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
since	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
of	O
June	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
excepted	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
come	O
up	O
for	O
Drawingrooms	O
--	O
in	O
Nov	O
:	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
H	B-place
.	I-place
for	O
another	O
fortnight	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
before	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Yorkshire	B-place
--	O
she	O
looked	O
very	O
ill	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
is	O
recovered	O
&	O
will	O
enjoy	O
herself	O
at	O
her	O
Father	O
s	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
returns	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
her	O
then	O
certain	O
ly	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
you	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
pleasant	O
of	O
your	O
Friend	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
or	O
believe	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
eſsentially	O
blam	O
able	O
in	O
her	O
Conduct	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Girl	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
style	O
&	O
way	O
&	O
will	O
certainly	O
get	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
--	O
i.	O
e	O
.	O
make	O
a	O
very	O
foolish	O
&	O
bad	O
match	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Armitage	I-pers
Brother	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
vulgar	O
affected	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
style	O
&	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
who	O
admires	O
her	O
,	O
rides	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
(	O
that	O
indeed	O
she	O
does	O
with	O
every	O
Man	O
at	O
North	B-place
:	I-place
!	O
)	O
&	O
they	O
say	O
will	O
marry	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
she	O
(	O
what	O
the	O
world	O
calls	O
)	O
encourag	O
es	O
other	O
Men	O
--	O
she	O
only	O
means	O
to	O
talk	O
&	O
laugh	O
to	O
amuse	O
hers	O
elf	O
but	O
it	O
hurts	O
her	O
tho	O
it	O
is	O
perfectly	O
innocent	O
of	O
any	O
bad	O
intentions	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
advice	O
--	O
her	O
Friend	O
Sir	B-pers
Ges	I-pers
scampers	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
violent	O
way	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
perfectly	O
so	O
--	O
my	O
rooms	O
here	O
have	O
been	O
new	O
papered	O
painted	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
Books	O
,	O
more	O
Bookcases	O
,	O
tables	O
&	O
c	O
inshort	O
am	O
perfectly	O
comfortable	O
&	O
shall	O
delight	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
enjoy	O
&	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
comfort	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
adieu	O
--	O
Oh	O
!	O
My	O
dear	O
what	O
would	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
Calwick	B-place
--	O
what	O
a	O
delight	O
!	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
kiſsed	O
every	O
step	O
I	O
trod	O
--	O
how	O
happy	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
!	O
but	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
ever	O
feel	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
don	O
e	O
poor	O
,	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
!	O
To	O
Rouſseau	B-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
