TOKEN	NE
4	O
Febry	O
.	O
1786	O
Saturday	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
is	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
birthday	O
,	O
may	O
you	O
live	O
to	O
enjoy	O
many	O
many	O
returns	O
of	O
that	O
happy	O
day	O
is	O
the	O
ardent	O
&	O
sincere	O
wish	O
es	O
of	O
your	O
mMary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
My	O
dear	O
Mother	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
likewise	O
join	O
in	O
their	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
very	O
long	O
continuance	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
good	O
health	O
&	O
many	O
years	O
of	O
uninterrupted	O
happineſs	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
Dickenson	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
hurried	O
&	O
hurt	O
about	O
bu	O
ſ	O
s	O
ineſs	O
of	O
various	O
kinds	O
,	O
the	O
chief	O
is	O
respecting	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
My	O
dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
during	O
our	O
conversation	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
surprized	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Palmerston	I-pers
should	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
consulted	O
about	O
the	O
publishing	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
manuscripts	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
hurt	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
anecdotes	O
about	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
applied	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
as	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
Forty	O
years	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
Dr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
paper	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
very	O
angrily	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
english	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
Dr.	B-pers
B——	I-pers
might	O
not	O
be	O
consulted	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
difference	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
&	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
wish	O
to	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cadell	I-pers
the	O
bookseller	O
&	O
talk	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
works	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
think	O
my	O
Affairs	O
were	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
train	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
that	O
Dr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
displeased	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
as	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
poet	O
Laureat	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
sons	O
in	O
the	O
church	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
disadvantage	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
as	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
must	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
paragraph	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
wch	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
put	O
into	O
the	O
papers	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
s	O
death	O
.	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
concluded	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
generous	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
release	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
promise	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
I	O
breakfasted	O
wth	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
&	O
we	O
between	O
us	O
we	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
released	O
him	O
entirely	O
from	O
his	O
promise	O
of	O
writing	O
the	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
S	O
:	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
from	O
him	O
all	O
Tuesday	O
&	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
compleatly	O
miserable	O
between	O
hope	O
&	O
fear	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
him	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
&	O
in	O
it	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
unhappy	O
least	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
mistaken	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
for	O
answer	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
&	O
Friday	O
came	O
&	O
no	O
Dr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
nor	O
a	O
single	O
line	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
ill	O
with	O
anxiety	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
left	O
Town	B-place
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
without	O
sending	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Winchester	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
uneasy	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
consulted	O
with	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
this	O
scrape	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
talks	O
of	O
writing	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
week	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
explain	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
being	O
wrote	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
happier	O
when	O
she	O
has	O
wrote	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
ill	O
upon	O
it	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
vex	O
'd	O
me	O
is	O
about	O
Richd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
My	O
dr	O
Father	O
who	O
had	O
an	O
estate	O
in	O
hand	O
of	O
about	O
600	O
a	O
year	O
&	O
which	O
after	O
his	O
death	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
&	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Rich	B-pers
'd	I-pers
&	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
dies	O
without	O
Iſsue	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
heirs	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
Richd	B-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
asking	O
counsels	O
oppinion	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
codicil	O
aside	O
in	O
short	O
to	O
deprive	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
entail	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
feel	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
It	O
has	O
hurt	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
calls	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
he	O
is	O
ashamed	O
to	O
show	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
for	O
life	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
poſseſsion	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blacke	I-pers
our	O
attorney	O
,	O
(	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
trustee	O
)	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
inventory	O
but	O
that	O
their	O
were	O
large	O
&	O
small	O
waiters	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
sizes	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
