TOKEN	NE
27	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
detained	O
here	O
a	O
Week	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
told	O
Lord	B-pers
Liverpool	I-pers
yesterday	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
depart	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Parents	O
of	O
my	O
Servant	O
live	O
within	O
three	O
miles	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Albans	I-place
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
fulfilling	O
his	O
Filial	O
Duties	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
with	O
You	O
about	O
two	O
O'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
remain	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
purpose	O
to	O
proceed	O
to	O
Archy	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
's	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
&	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
Napier	B-pers
Best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
My	O
black	O
Seal	O
,	O
is	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
died	O
lately	O
.	O
