TOKEN	NE
N	O
o	O
.	O
61	O
Prince	O
's	O
Street	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
5	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1787	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
old	O
Ld	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	O
yet	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
for	O
the	O
accident	O
he	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
gueſs	O
the	O
distreſs	O
&	O
anxiety	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
occasioned	O
you	O
to	O
experience	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
the	O
fall	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
seemed	O
at	O
first	O
to	O
fear	O
.	O
The	O
date	O
of	O
my	O
Letter	O
may	O
surprise	O
You	O
;	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Edinburgh	B-place
has	O
been	O
our	O
place	O
of	O
residence	O
since	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
Your	O
letter	O
from	O
Buxton	B-place
of	O
course	O
went	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
Me	O
out	O
'till	O
very	O
lately	O
.	O
My	O
only	O
motive	O
for	O
leaving	O
Ireland	B-place
in	O
March	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
effectual	O
Use	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Peers	O
Election	O
.	O
From	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Correspondents	O
amongst	O
the	O
Peers	O
,	O
I	O
very	O
plainly	O
saw	O
,	O
the	O
Contest	O
would	O
run	O
hard	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
had	O
hopes	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
succeſsfull	O
.	O
The	O
event	O
disappointed	O
Me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
mortification	O
of	O
seeing	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
disliked	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Peerage	O
sent	O
to	O
Parliament	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
of	O
some	O
use	O
to	O
Cathcart	B-pers
,	O
as	O
a	O
Check	O
to	O
that	O
absurd	O
Manner	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
within	O
these	O
few	O
Years	O
thought	O
becoming	O
.	O
The	O
consequential	O
indifference	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
treated	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Brethren	O
,	O
lost	O
him	O
Votes	O
.	O
Two	O
particular	O
friends	O
of	O
mine	O
aſsured	O
Me	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
Cathcart	B-pers
behaved	O
in	O
general	O
to	O
them	O
with	O
decency	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
preferred	O
him	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Candidates	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
his	O
Attention	O
&	O
Civility	O
was	O
only	O
visible	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
canvaſsing	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
would	O
support	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
your	O
little	O
Cathcart	B-pers
agrees	O
with	O
Spoon	O
meat	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
allmost	O
inclined	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
same	O
plan	O
,	O
should	O
Providence	O
please	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
.	O
My	O
poor	O
Louisa	B-pers
suffered	O
violently	O
from	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
Itch	O
which	O
her	O
Nurse	O
gave	O
her	O
&	O
which	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
suspected	O
.	O
The	O
Nurse	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
carefully	O
concealed	O
,	O
'till	O
her	O
increase	O
of	O
size	O
caught	O
my	O
attention	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
Mary	B-pers
naturally	O
poſseſsed	O
a	O
good	O
constitution	O
,	O
the	O
bad	O
Milk	O
joined	O
to	O
the	O
Itch	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
sufficient	O
to	O
have	O
destroyed	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
likewise	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
wean	O
my	O
Boy	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
Seven	O
Months	O
old	O
.	O
People	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
Children	O
are	O
constantly	O
wishing	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
bleſsed	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
things	O
,	O
are	O
kept	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
in	O
a	O
continued	O
state	O
of	O
anxiety	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
House	O
here	O
&	O
consequently	O
propose	O
making	O
this	O
our	O
Head	O
Quarters	O
in	O
future	O
.	O
My	O
Regt-	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Halifax	B-place
&	O
Newfoundland	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
visit	O
them	O
for	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
expreſs	O
desire	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
;	O
You	O
may	O
beleive	O
her	O
wish	O
was	O
not	O
disagreable	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
T	O
he	O
House	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
o	O
ne	O
with	O
C	O
oac	O
h	O
House	O
,	O
Stables	O
for	O
four	O
Hor	O
ses	O
,	O
Laundry	O
&	O
Wash	O
House	O
,	O
c	O
osts	O
Us	O
£1100	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
busy	O
furnishing	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
which	O
being	O
now	O
accomplished	O
,	O
on	O
friday	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
where	O
we	O
mean	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
Visitation	O
style	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
wish	O
it	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
Country	O
Air	O
will	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
e'en	O
make	O
a	O
convenience	O
of	O
his	O
invitation	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
Sir	B-pers
T.	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
now	O
forms	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Establishment	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
accompany	O
Us	O
to	O
Axwell	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Addition	O
to	O
out	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
her	O
situation	O
in	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
full	O
as	O
agreable	O
as	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
arrival	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
your	O
Cousin	O
Harriet	B-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
Town	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
we	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
illneſs	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
returned	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
begs	O
her	O
wishes	O
for	O
the	O
health	O
&	O
happyneſs	O
of	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
may	O
be	O
added	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
's	O
Affect	O
.	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Maria	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Napier	B-pers
is	O
convinced	O
of	O
his	O
Jerryism	O
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Axwell	O
Park	O
,	O
Gateshead	B-place
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxall	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
