TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
So	O
you	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
it	O
without	O
seeing	O
you	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Binning	I-pers
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
could	O
not	O
receive	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
there	O
miſsed	O
the	O
opportunity	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
of	O
paying	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
I	O
liked	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
diſsappointed	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
little	O
plans	O
or	O
hopes	O
of	O
enjoymen	O
t	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
whom	O
after	O
above	O
two	O
months	O
absence	O
&	O
bad	O
Health	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
extremely	O
desirous	O
of	O
seeing	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
Saturday	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
go	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
here	O
till	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
stupid	O
&	O
enervated	O
&	O
have	O
hardly	O
strength	O
&	O
spirits	O
left	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
survived	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
&	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
tired	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
pale	O
faces	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
remain	O
--	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
myself	O
airs	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
pale	O
as	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
with	O
raking	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
12	O
for	O
these	O
three	O
weeks	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
literally	O
with	O
ennui	O
&	O
disgust	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
the	O
sincerest	O
pleasure	O
&	O
with	O
more	O
alacrity	O
than	O
I	O
though	O
t	O
myself	O
capable	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
arranged	O
&	O
packed	O
up	O
my	O
books	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
for	O
Horton	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
for	O
5	O
Weeks	O
exclusive	O
of	O
my	O
leave	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
equally	O
have	O
in	O
November	O
&	O
December	O
--	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
journey	O
has	O
been	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
of	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
sets	O
me	O
at	O
liberty	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Drawingroom	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
of	O
August	O
--	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
beneficial	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
agreea	O
ble	O
as	O
an	O
excursion	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
and	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
whom	O
I	O
hope	O
Richmond	B-place
air	O
agrees	O
perfectly	O
with	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
your	O
plans	O
,	O
&	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
chance	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
into	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
before	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
any	O
certainty	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
stay	O
longer	O
with	O
us	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
November	O
--	O
Co	O
me	O
you	O
must	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
upon	O
it	O
&	O
you	O
shall	O
no	O
longer	O
be	O
let	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
settled	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
happy	O
&	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
better	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
for	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
to	O
make	O
us	O
so	O
--	O
adieu	O
,	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
may	O
you	O
always	O
be	O
as	O
happy	O
&	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
adieu	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
July	O
9	O
th	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
July	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1788	O
