TOKEN	NE
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bullstrode	B-place
I	O
return	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
yr-	O
kind	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
continue	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Ladies	O
return	O
their	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
Lower	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Saturdy	O
