TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
August	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
delightful	O
long	O
Letter	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
this	O
short	O
one	O
is	O
making	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
return	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
excuse	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
hurry	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
,	O
being	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
Square	I-place
this	O
Day	O
.	O
Papa	O
explained	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
reason	O
that	O
prevented	O
your	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
the	O
life	O
you	O
lead	O
is	O
so	O
suited	O
to	O
your	O
taste	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
expreſs	O
much	O
joy	O
at	O
your	O
resolution	O
of	O
not	O
returning	O
'till	O
the	O
Winter	O
Season	O
;	O
however	O
you	O
will	O
spend	O
your	O
time	O
very	O
agreeably	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
amends	O
for	O
your	O
long	O
absence	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
your	O
's	O
sincerely	O
Jane	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
