TOKEN	NE
11	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1801	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
Inst-	O
having	O
reached	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
after	O
my	O
departure	O
,	O
only	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
poſsibly	O
have	O
been	O
induced	O
to	O
have	O
favoured	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
reply	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
extended	O
Scale	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
convenient	O
for	O
You	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
very	O
moment	O
You	O
was	O
certain	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
equally	O
inconvenient	O
for	O
Me	O
to	O
waste	O
my	O
precious	O
time	O
in	O
scribbling	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
State	O
requires	O
my	O
most	O
profound	O
meditations	O
.	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
my	O
Rib	O
and	O
Chatterers	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
alter	O
my	O
plan	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
improbable	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
Easter	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
may	O
take	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
enquiring	O
about	O
You	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
North	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
fixed	O
.	O
But	O
my	O
Love	O
,	O
towards	O
your	O
Husband	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
strong	O
inducement	O
to	O
draw	O
me	O
to	O
Leighton	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
scolding	O
and	O
tormenting	O
You	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
do	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
little	O
chance	O
of	O
his	O
thinking	O
it	O
worth	O
his	O
while	O
to	O
honour	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Visit	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
old	O
fashioned	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
easily	O
reconcile	O
my	O
ideas	O
to	O
the	O
propriety	O
of	O
approving	O
and	O
countenancing	O
the	O
fair	O
Emma	B-pers
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
Sixteen	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
step	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
pardonable	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
really	O
at	O
his	O
time	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
espouse	O
the	O
Mistreſs	O
of	O
his	O
Nephew	O
,	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
seems	O
such	O
an	O
intolerable	O
peice	O
of	O
folly	O
,	O
and	O
meaneſs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
quite	O
despise	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
Uncle	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
plead	O
privilege	O
,	O
and	O
avoid	O
darkening	O
his	O
Doors	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
expectation	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
possibility	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
the	O
fair	O
Emma	B-pers
there	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
curiosity	O
to	O
behold	O
this	O
prodigy	O
remains	O
ungratified	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
our	O
Gracious	O
Queen	B-pers
can	O
not	O
be	O
prevailed	O
on	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
applaud	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Our	O
great	O
Cousins	O
are	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Invite	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
and	O
pretend	O
that	O
they	O
regard	O
me	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
should	O
be	O
more	O
of	O
late	O
Years	O
,	O
than	O
formerly	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
receive	O
all	O
their	O
attentions	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
felt	O
they	O
were	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
may	O
convince	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
attentive	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
The	O
plague	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Carriage	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
Magnificence	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
ruling	O
paſsion	O
amongst	O
our	O
Relatives	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
certainly	O
hold	O
me	O
cheap	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
,	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
,	O
contrive	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
at	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
keeping	O
up	O
my	O
Dignity	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
tells	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
So	O
Adieu	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
abhorrence	O
to	O
You	O
;	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
and	O
Daughter	O
;	O
and	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
growing	O
blind	O
,	O
though	O
too	O
vain	O
to	O
wear	O
Spectacles	O
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Eighth	O
Janry	O
.	O
1801	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
