TOKEN	NE
Stanley	O
House	O
1	O
of	O
August	O
1788	O
my	O
Dear	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
am	O
too	O
vain	O
perhaps	O
,	O
but	O
judging	O
of	O
a	O
Friends	O
heart	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
am	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
imagine	O
because	O
they	O
are	O
silent	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
adage	O
is	O
verified	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
mind	O
:	O
but	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
supose	O
they	O
are	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
something	O
more	O
material	O
than	O
writing	O
:	O
but	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
yours	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
fair	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
pains	O
:	O
believe	O
me	O
I	O
thought	O
your	O
silence	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
amends	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
soon	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
in	O
future	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
Correspondent	O
:	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
your	O
young	O
charge	O
will	O
every	O
day	O
have	O
a	O
longer	O
claim	O
upon	O
your	O
time	O
yet	O
remember	O
I	O
was	O
honor	O
'd	O
with	O
your	O
Friendship	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
you	O
make	O
after	O
my	O
health	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
very	O
good	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
when	O
last	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
and	O
never	O
having	O
known	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
health	O
made	O
my	O
friends	O
think	O
the	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
myself	O
too	O
I	O
believe	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
did	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
bid	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
following	O
good	O
advice	O
from	O
Louisa	B-pers
and	O
coming	O
into	O
this	O
good	O
air	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
has	O
taught	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
as	O
we	O
grow	O
old	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
expect	O
sometimes	O
to	O
be	O
sick	O
--	O
Your	O
picture	O
of	O
the	O
Bon	O
Ton	O
is	O
well	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
very	O
like	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
opinion	O
the	O
World	O
is	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
proportion	O
of	O
Virtue	O
&	O
Vice	O
always	O
have	O
prevail	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
fashon	O
makes	O
some	O
ages	O
more	O
flagrant	O
than	O
others	O
because	O
they	O
are	O
more	O
sincere	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
shrewdly	O
suspect	O
our	O
Great	O
Grandmothers	O
days	O
were	O
not	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
ours	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
difference	O
from	O
a	O
reserve	O
of	O
Manner	O
,	O
a	O
stiffneſs	O
of	O
the	O
times	O
characters	O
were	O
carefully	O
hid	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
there	O
were	O
greater	O
cheats	O
at	O
present	O
nobody	O
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
complain	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
quite	O
their	O
own	O
faults	O
if	O
deceived	O
by	O
apearances	O
--	O
all	O
our	O
Friends	O
are	O
returned	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
our	O
young	O
ones	O
much	O
improved	O
by	O
their	O
journey	O
to	O
London	B-place
we	O
spent	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
Dunkeld	B-place
and	O
celebrated	O
Doctor	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
s	O
birthday	O
's	O
with	O
fireworks	O
and	O
good	O
chear	O
--	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
returned	O
home	O
and	O
the	O
Duke	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Man	I-place
with	O
his	O
two	O
Uncles	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
and	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Tullibardine	I-pers
and	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
all	O
returned	O
last	O
Monday	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
rain	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
here	O
:	O
Mr.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
's	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
were	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Dunkeld	B-place
she	O
is	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
s	O
--	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
as	O
do	O
Mr.	B-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
continue	O
to	O
Excersise	O
your	O
pencil	O
,	O
we	O
find	O
great	O
amusement	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
taken	O
some	O
preaty	O
views	O
in	O
the	O
great	O
stile	O
while	O
my	O
humbler	O
pencil	O
,	O
makes	O
a	O
card	O
or	O
draws	O
a	O
flower	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Botanic	O
Garden	O
at	O
Perth	B-place
;	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
flowers	O
sent	O
me	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
draw	O
--	O
how	O
amused	O
the	O
R	O
.	O
F	O
.	O
must	O
be	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
the	O
scene	O
and	O
country	O
so	O
new	O
,	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
Amelia	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
but	O
dont	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
punishment	O
,	O
for	O
His	O
laughing	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
water	O
drinking	O
places	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
forced	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
go	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
experience	O
their	O
virtue	O
?	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
from	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Spring	O
;	O
find	O
very	O
great	O
benefit	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
--	O
supose	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
his	O
scheme	O
for	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Estate	O
in	O
Yorkshire	B-place
&	O
purchase	O
Oatlands	B-place
--	O
the	O
one	O
was	O
too	O
far	O
North	O
to	O
be	O
agreable	O
I	O
imagine	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
just	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
Prince	O
to	O
amuse	O
himself	O
with	O
,	O
without	O
gaining	O
command	O
or	O
interest	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
beautifull	O
spot	O
within	O
reach	O
of	O
court	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
supose	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
I	O
may	O
give	O
you	O
joy	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
cousin	O
as	O
her	O
Graces	O
apearance	O
would	O
make	O
one	O
supose	O
its	O
arrival	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
settled	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
son	O
there	O
is	O
daughters	O
plenty	O
and	O
Dukes	O
should	O
have	O
but	O
few	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
hard	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
&	O
good	O
husband	O
joyn	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
yourself	O
beging	O
best	O
compts	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
sincere	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
least	O
12	O
Kiſses	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
No	O
.	O
27-	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
