TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
!	O
Many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
melancholy	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
indeed	O
distressed	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
more	O
aware	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Aunt	O
's	O
dreadful	O
state	O
than	O
you	O
were	O
(	O
not	O
having	O
seen	O
her	O
so	O
lately	O
as	O
myself	O
)	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
idea	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
as	O
you	O
represent	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
her	O
since	O
she	O
left	O
Ramsgate	B-place
&	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
letters	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
I	O
begged	O
her	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Bromley	B-place
to	O
write	O
for	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
her	O
better	O
.	O
knowing	O
the	O
misery	O
this	O
receiving	O
&	O
answering	O
letters	O
causes	O
her	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
write	O
as	O
frequently	O
as	O
I	O
otherwise	O
shou	O
'd	O
which	O
I	O
find	O
she	O
sometimes	O
thinks	O
unkind	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
God	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
cou	O
'd	O
soothe	O
&	O
relieve	O
her	O
miserable	O
situation	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
to	O
our	O
being	O
often	O
must	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
plainly	O
see	O
all	O
the	O
objections	O
you	O
doe	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
what	O
she	O
most	O
wishes	O
&	O
what	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
her	O
cou	O
'd	O
we	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
bear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
aſsure	O
if	O
I	O
only	O
stay	O
with	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
&	O
tho	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
in	O
general	O
good	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
wretched	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
Fanny	B-pers
said	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
pay	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
but	O
My	O
Aunt	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
fearful	O
she	O
might	O
think	O
her	O
unkind	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
to	O
refuse	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
present	O
circumstances	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
her	O
doing	O
it	O
she	O
must	O
therefore	O
decline	O
going	O
in	O
as	O
delicate	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
she	O
can	O
,	O
Fanny	B-pers
's	O
visit	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
having	O
been	O
longer	O
deferred	O
than	O
she	O
expected	O
(	O
owing	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
FFern	I-pers
's	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
will	O
of	O
course	O
detain	O
her	O
longer	O
in	O
Town	O
than	O
she	O
expected	O
&	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
FFern	I-pers
is	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
she	O
may	O
perhaps	O
go	O
to	O
Cheltenham	B-place
in	O
the	O
spring	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
Fanny	B-pers
will	O
probably	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
hope	O
something	O
will	O
be	O
settled	O
relative	O
to	O
our	O
Estate	O
which	O
will	O
enable	O
her	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
settling	O
herself	O
in	O
Northampton	B-place
for	O
as	O
that	O
seems	O
the	O
plan	O
she	O
prefers	O
&	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
promise	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
towards	O
introducing	O
her	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
Friends	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
imensly	O
sorry	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
shou	O
'd	O
occur	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
going	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
yourself	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
upon	O
a	O
subject	O
which	O
has	O
long	O
dwelt	O
much	O
upon	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
know	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
have	O
ever	O
shown	O
me	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
truth	O
say	O
encreases	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
distreſs	O
them	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
ought	O
or	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
when	O
Fanny	B-pers
settles	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
esteem	O
my	O
kind	O
Friends	O
you	O
will	O
readily	O
believe	O
that	O
my	O
own	O
inclinations	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
but	O
believe	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
up	O
every	O
idea	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
think	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
acting	O
unkindly	O
towards	O
the	B-pers
Bp	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	O
It	O
may	O
perhaps	O
be	O
said	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
that	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
my	O
Sister	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
'	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
think	O
me	O
ungrateful	O
in	O
leaving	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
alarmingly	O
these	O
six	O
weeks	O
past	O
&	O
she	O
still	O
continues	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
precarious	O
state	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
she	O
never	O
can	O
recover	O
this	O
attack	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
for	O
I	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
as	O
ill	O
before	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
fear	O
have	O
some	O
difficulty	O
in	O
decyphering	O
this	O
scrawl	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
night	O
that	O
the	O
nurse	O
may	O
get	O
a	O
good	O
nights	O
rest	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
past	O
3	O
o'clock	O
the	O
rush	O
light	O
burning	O
very	O
dim	O
&	O
the	O
mice	O
running	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
like	O
a	O
Fool	O
am	O
frightened	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Rats	O
that	O
ran	O
acroſs	O
ye	O
dining	O
Parlor	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
the	O
first	O
year	O
I	O
spent	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
absurd	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
cured	O
of	O
my	O
absurdity	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
more	O
by	O
getting	O
accustomed	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
I	O
feel	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
crawling	O
over	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
enclosed	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
my	O
Aunt	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
having	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
kind	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
wishing	O
her	O
to	O
lengthen	O
her	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
nerves	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
to	O
bear	O
with	O
her	O
unfortunate	O
uncertainties	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
comfort	O
wou	O
'd	O
it	O
have	O
be	O
en	O
to	O
us	O
had	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
only	O
near	O
relations	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
society	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
thas	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
may	O
never	O
dare	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
,	O
God	O
grant	O
my	O
poor	O
Aunt	B-pers
Anna	I-pers
may	O
not	O
still	O
be	O
worse	O
than	O
she	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
we	O
must	O
be	O
prepared	O
for	O
an	O
event	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
far	O
more	O
dreadful	O
than	O
a	O
final	O
release	O
from	O
her	O
sufferings	O
.	O
by	O
I	O
dr	O
ead	O
seeing	O
her	O
yet	O
want	O
it	O
for	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
sincere	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
am	O
fully	O
sensible	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
&	O
the	O
great	O
regard	O
she	O
has	O
for	O
us	O
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
most	O
afftly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
ever	O
grateful	O
&	O
affte	O
Goddaughter	O
Mary	B-pers
J	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Brighton	B-place
February	O
Fourteenth	O
1805	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
St.	B-pers
Asaph	I-pers
Bedfordshire	B-place
