TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
The	O
hurry	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
in	O
moving	O
my	O
Family	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
has	O
prevented	O
my	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
much	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
by	O
good	O
fortune	O
got	O
a	O
most	O
elegant	O
and	O
complete	O
house	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
street	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
and	O
quite	O
convenient	O
to	O
the	O
outlet	O
leading	O
to	O
my	O
Villa	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
am	O
every	O
morning	O
supplied	O
with	O
the	O
produce	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
Farm	O
&	O
Garden	O
in	O
much	O
greater	O
perfection	O
than	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
get	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sincerely	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
account	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
of	O
your	O
encreasing	O
good	O
fortune	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
persuaded	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
prudence	O
that	O
guided	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
former	O
situation	O
,	O
will	O
point	O
out	O
the	O
proper	O
line	O
line	O
of	O
conduct	O
in	O
your	O
present	O
more	O
arduous	O
one	O
.	O
Your	O
understanding	O
with	O
the	O
experience	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
is	O
perfectly	O
sufficient	O
to	O
direct	O
you	O
in	O
almost	O
any	O
case	O
that	O
can	O
offer	O
;	O
nothing	O
can	O
hurt	O
you	O
but	O
flattery	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
always	O
held	O
in	O
abhorrence	O
;	O
its	O
object	O
is	O
fatally	O
bent	O
to	O
undermine	O
the	O
judgement	O
by	O
instilling	O
into	O
the	O
unguarded	O
mind	O
an	O
arrogant	O
self-approbation	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
noble	O
simplicity	O
of	O
conduct	O
which	O
will	O
guide	O
you	O
safely	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
qualification	O
of	O
all	O
others	O
the	O
most	O
proper	O
for	O
your	O
situation	O
.	O
Make	O
no	O
apologies	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
answering	O
my	O
letters	O
with	O
precise	O
punctuality	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
time	O
is	O
engaged	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
very	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
thinking	O
yourself	O
in	O
default	O
might	O
prevent	O
that	O
frankneſs	O
which	O
renders	O
your	O
correspondence	O
so	O
interesting	O
and	O
agreeable	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
acquainting	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
application	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
feeble	O
effort	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
merited	O
no	O
other	O
answer	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
than	O
what	O
it	O
produced	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
from	O
the	B-pers
K——g	I-pers
alone	O
that	O
I	O
entertain	O
'd	O
any	O
hopes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
has	O
changed	O
his	O
sentiments	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
my	O
Memorial	O
and	O
the	O
probability	O
of	O
its	O
having	O
effect	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
and	O
even	O
proposed	O
an	O
amendment	O
to	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
&	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
perhaps	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
can	O
put	O
you	O
into	O
a	O
method	O
of	O
getting	O
it	O
presented	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
recollect	O
my	O
sentiments	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
your	O
interference	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
still	O
invariably	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
considerd	O
by	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
safe	O
and	O
disinterested	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
idea	O
must	O
for	O
ever	O
have	O
been	O
loſs	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
wanting	O
to	O
put	O
you	O
into	O
an	O
improper	O
and	O
dangerous	O
situation	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
is	O
quite	O
different	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
who	O
at	O
present	O
is	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Preferments	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
department	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
will	O
serve	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
any	O
civil	O
employment	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
suppose	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
disappointed	O
or	O
made	O
unhappy	O
by	O
these	O
answers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
experiment	O
of	O
the	O
estimation	O
I	O
stand	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
with	O
reluctance	O
&	O
totally	O
against	O
my	O
own	O
judgement	O
,	O
however	O
by	O
having	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
acquitted	O
myself	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
hereafter	O
be	O
reproach	O
'd	O
with	O
having	O
fail	O
'd	O
through	O
my	O
own	O
indolence	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
born	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
prosperity	O
with	O
an	O
equal	O
mind	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
suffer	O
'd	O
anxious	O
expectations	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
unmindful	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
bleſsings	O
I	O
am	O
daily	O
enjoying	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
very	O
nearly	O
attained	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
52	O
;	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
rather	O
too	O
late	O
a	O
period	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
creating	O
a	O
new	O
interest	O
?	O
With	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
present	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
will	O
readily	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
little	O
can	O
be	O
expected	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
obtain	O
anything	O
upon	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
woud	O
be	O
doating	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
for	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
longer	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
the	O
turmoils	O
between	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
untoward	O
Husband	O
give	O
us	O
much	O
uneasineſs	O
God	O
knows	O
what	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
them	O
!	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
with	O
the	O
sincerest	O
Affection	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Uncle	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sackville	O
Street	O
,	O
Dublin	B-place
November	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
