TOKEN	NE
March	O
29	O
th	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
Hail	O
yr	O
arrival	O
in	O
Town	B-place
th	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
Cause	O
which	O
brings	O
you	O
amongst	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
perpetually	O
Engag	O
'd	O
every	O
Evening	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
Morning	O
.	O
not	O
having	O
Strength	O
of	O
Constitution	O
Sufficient	O
to	O
Encounter	O
such	O
fatigue	O
or	O
I	O
wd	O
have	O
made	O
this	O
Enquiry	O
in	O
person	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
Unite	O
in	O
best	O
Compliments	O
&	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
Speedy	O
recovery	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
brought	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
yr	O
sweet	O
Girl	O
in	O
perffect	O
Health	O
--	O
yrs	O
most	O
truly	O
DBlosset	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
No	O
21	O
South	O
Audly	O
Street	O
