TOKEN	NE
¾	O
pt	O
8	O
Good	O
Friday	O
--	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
April	O
1779	O
You	O
are	O
now	O
my	O
Dearest	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Marble	O
Table	O
,	O
admiring	O
the	O
Beauties	O
of	O
Andromeda	B-pers
(	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
whose	O
Person	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
heart	O
)	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
not	O
unlikely	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
thinking	O
of	O
your	O
Nursing	O
Friend	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
,	O
you	O
know	O
we	O
often	O
sympathise	O
therefore	O
I	O
may	O
perhaps	O
not	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
General	O
to	O
comunicate	O
my	O
though	O
ts	O
to	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
talking	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
perfectly	O
easy	O
for	O
my	O
Vanity	O
prompts	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
y	O
e	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
would	O
have	O
rather	O
increased	O
it	O
then	O
diminished	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
Saucy	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
Spirits	O
if	O
poſsible	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
they	O
are	O
better	O
then	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
if	O
God	O
grants	O
me	O
Succeſs	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
amply	O
rewarded	O
,	O
Heaven	O
avert	O
so	O
dreadful	O
a	O
blow	O
as	O
the	O
reverse	O
to	O
your	O
Friend	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
consequence	O
,	O
it	O
appea	O
rs	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
present	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
support	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
Dear	O
little	O
Angels	O
are	O
in	O
vast	O
Spirits	O
&	O
vastly	O
good	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
fancy	O
Prſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
changed	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
indeed	O
her	O
present	O
Character	O
is	O
uncommonly	O
lovely	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
poſsible	O
I	O
doat	O
upon	O
her	O
more	O
then	O
Ever	O
,	O
Dear	O
little	O
P	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
is	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
ten	O
times	O
more	O
amiable	O
then	O
before	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
well	O
entertained	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
I	O
rejoice	O
4	O
fievres	O
has	O
not	O
killed	O
you	O
--	O
write	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
Affly	O
Your	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
House	O
