TOKEN	NE
Wolverton	B-place
September	O
5	O
th	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
concerned	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
tomorrow	O
but	O
the	O
accounts	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
in	O
law	O
Mrs	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
widow	O
of	O
Coln	B-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Fremantle	I-pers
)	O
leaving	O
some	O
very	O
unprotected	O
girls	O
together	O
with	O
an	O
alarming	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
a	O
Nephew	O
of	O
hers	O
is	O
returned	O
in	O
Portugal	B-place
renders	O
her	O
so	O
unwell	O
&	O
uncomfortable	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
just	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
shortly	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
remembering	O
us	O
mos	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Beleive	O
me	O
most	O
Faithfully	O
Yrs	O
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
