TOKEN	NE
Sunninghill	B-place
11	O
th	O
.	O
Augt	O
.	O
1800	O
Ansed	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
It	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
Your	O
good	O
Man	O
,	O
did	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
You	O
,	O
&	O
Your	O
Dear	O
Daughter	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
regard	O
for	O
&	O
c-	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
busineſs	O
upon	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
importance	O
,	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
till	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
July	O
--	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
dust	O
,	O
&	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Camps	O
,	O
horse	O
&	O
foot	O
,	O
being	O
stationd	O
very	O
near	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
times	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
very	O
Croſs	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
here	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
am	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
good	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
Croſs	O
,	O
this	O
hot	O
Weather	O
,	O
my	O
good	O
friend	O
(	O
we	O
very	O
seldom	O
stir	O
out	O
to	O
Walk	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
d	O
o	O
id	O
,	O
almost	O
ancle	O
in	O
dust	O
)	O
the	O
dear	O
King	B-pers
has	O
brought	O
this	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
amusement	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
he	O
his	O
gone	O
to	O
Weymouth	B-place
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
soon	O
the	O
Camp	O
will	O
be	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
a	O
Red	O
Coat	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
whent	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
feild	O
Days	O
,	O
what	O
with	O
smoke	O
,	O
&	O
dust	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
whent	O
with	O
a	O
Party	O
,	O
&	O
paid	O
very	O
dear	O
for	O
her	O
amusement	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
cold	O
,	O
swell	O
'd	O
face	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
laid	O
up	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
whent	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saltwell	I-pers
,	O
I	O
like	O
the	O
foot	O
Camp	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
one	O
Evening	O
a	O
large	O
party	O
of	O
us	O
drank	O
Tea	O
in	O
Coln	B-pers
.	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Markee	O
,	O
in	O
number	O
15	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Harewood	I-pers
the	B-pers
Tibbalds	I-pers
party	O
,	O
&	O
ours	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Band	O
of	O
Music	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
very	O
agreeable	O
indeed	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Harewood	I-pers
goes	O
constantly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
every	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
always	O
meets	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
ones	O
acqaintance	O
,	O
pleasant	O
enough	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
reinstated	O
to	O
our	O
rural	O
felicity	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
can	O
repair	O
the	O
Garth	O
being	O
tore	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
good	O
showers	O
of	O
Rain	O
--	O
Our	O
friends	O
at	O
Broomley	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
She	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
taking	O
her	O
Sister	O
Bell	B-pers
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
side	O
,	O
She	O
thought	O
her	O
o	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
th	O
ink	O
it	O
a	O
prudent	O
scheme	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
,	O
done	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
hot	O
&	O
dry	O
Summer	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
harvest	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
truſt	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
set	O
all	O
right	O
again	O
,	O
no	O
meat	O
under	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
pence	O
per	O
pound	O
,	O
Bread	O
18	O
pence	O
the	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
,	O
the	O
poor	O
must	O
have	O
sufferd	O
greatly	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
the	O
Bread	O
is	O
falling	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
ont	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
has	O
been	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
at	O
a	O
friend	O
s	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
stiff	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
trouble	O
her	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
askd	O
the	O
two	O
ladies	O
to	O
my	O
Aſsembly	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
engag	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
understand	O
they	O
were	O
full	O
of	O
engagements	O
.	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
favorit	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Openion	O
there	O
is	O
few	O
like	O
her	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
good	O
father	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
,	O
he	O
his	O
,	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
best	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
We	O
all	O
unite	O
in	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
Yours	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
best	O
Com	O
pliment	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Leighton	O
house	O
Staines	B-place
