TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
I	O
yesterday	O
kiſsed	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
hand	O
&	O
am	O
now	O
vulgarly	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Excellency	O
but	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
part	O
is	O
the	O
payt	O
beginning	O
.	O
My	O
Br	O
.	O
Fred	B-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
given	O
me	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
china	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
thinking	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
save	O
my	O
buying	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
for	O
I	O
might	O
then	O
do	O
with	O
only	O
a	O
first	O
Course	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
if	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
what	O
remains	O
of	O
yours	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
you	O
some	O
good	O
China	O
in	O
return	O
&	O
when	O
my	O
Envoyship	O
is	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
what	O
remains	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
least	O
objection	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
realy	O
I	O
beleive	O
it	O
will	O
save	O
me	O
at	O
least	O
500£	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
conveniently	O
to	O
yourself	O
do	O
it	O
the	O
sooner	O
you	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
better	O
as	O
a	O
ship	O
is	O
soon	O
going	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
next	O
week	O
for	O
Colby	B-place
but	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
again	O
about	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
of	O
August	O
when	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
joins	O
in	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Br	O
.	O
most	O
affectionately	O
Yrs	O
W	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mews	B-place
July	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1764	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
July	O
1764	O
