TOKEN	NE
Sunning	O
Hill	O
Novr	O
:	O
28	O
th	O
:	O
1786	O
What	O
my	O
dear	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
my	O
dear	O
Brother	O
of	O
your	O
very	O
long	O
silence	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
interested	O
in	O
the	O
Welfare	O
of	O
yr	O
better	O
half	O
,	O
more	O
particularly	O
in	O
her	O
present	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
mother	O
&	O
myself	O
accuse	O
you	O
of	O
neglect	O
,	O
not	O
yr	O
wife	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
engaged	O
,	O
write	O
soon	O
&	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
does	O
,	O
you	O
forget	O
the	O
distance	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
&	O
the	O
love	O
we	O
bear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
question	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
from	O
our	O
Dear	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
much	O
engaged	O
in	O
settling	O
her	O
accounts	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
before	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
they	O
will	O
be	O
finally	O
adjusted	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
heavy	O
load	O
taken	O
f	O
r	O
om	O
her	O
,	O
The	O
little	O
Henry	B-pers
(	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
youngest	O
child	O
)	O
is	O
just	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
.	O
Our	O
neighborhood	O
is	O
rather	O
dull	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Lodger	O
's	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
most	O
agreeable	O
people	O
we	O
miſs	O
them	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
the	O
Cole	O
's	O
particularly	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Coln	O
.	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
house	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
fine	O
a	O
Lady	O
&	O
we	O
visit	O
at	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
distance	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
prevail	O
on	O
myself	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
one	O
family	O
who	O
are	O
most	O
ami	O
a	O
ble	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
quite	O
an	O
affection	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
see	O
each	O
other	O
continually	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
the	O
country	O
pleasant	O
this	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
Athenaid	O
an	O
Epic	O
Poem	O
left	O
in	O
Man	O
.	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
have	O
not	O
begun	O
publishing	O
yet	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
friends	O
are	O
rather	O
dilatary	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
unpleasant	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
must	O
submit	O
where	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
one	O
's	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
set	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
its	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
next	O
Febry-	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
great	O
luck	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
set	O
about	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
myself	O
promise	O
a	O
thing	O
without	O
performing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
fashion	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
times	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
's	O
fault	O
is	O
unsteadineſs	O
,	O
an	O
unpleasant	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
,	O
t	O
T	O
he	O
expence	O
of	O
publishing	O
is	O
enormous	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
succeſs	O
,	O
I	O
print	O
a	O
thousand	O
Copies	O
,	O
the	O
expence	O
is	O
£250	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
sold	O
I	O
gain	O
£250	O
&	O
so	O
on	O
in	O
proportion	O
,	O
the	O
size	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
Leonidas	O
as	O
Mr-	B-pers
Cadell	I-pers
thought	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
more	O
Saleable	O
,	O
4	O
volumes	O
at	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
--	O
Tell	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
I	O
have	O
sent	O
this	O
account	O
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
gives	O
her	O
pleasure	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
.	O
Excuse	O
this	O
sad	O
scrawl	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
sent	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
in	O
Spirits	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
it	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
days	O
post	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
most	O
melancholy	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
a	O
school	O
Fellow	O
&	O
an	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
having	O
been	O
thwarted	O
in	O
a	O
love	O
affair	O
,	O
having	O
thrown	O
herself	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
pr	O
.	O
of	O
Stairs	O
window	O
.	O
her	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
merchant	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
form	O
'd	O
a	O
connexion	O
with	O
a	O
merchants	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
her	O
father	O
expostulated	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
impropriety	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
connexion	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
but	O
would	O
eat	O
nothing	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
dinner	O
her	O
Father	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
ail	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
answer	O
was	O
“	O
she	O
would	O
rather	O
die	O
”	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
usual	O
being	O
post	O
night	O
to	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
&	O
found	O
his	O
only	O
daughter	O
senseleſs	O
&	O
motionleſs	O
,	O
her	O
arm	O
much	O
shatter	O
'd	O
&	O
otherwise	O
greatly	O
bruised	O
,	O
having	O
as	O
before	O
related	O
throw	O
n	O
herself	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
pr	O
.	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
,	O
his	O
agonies	O
at	O
the	O
dreadful	O
spectacle	O
is	O
a	O
re	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
described	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
thought	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
hapleſs	O
miserable	O
girl	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
rein	O
in	O
her	O
paſsions	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
has	O
finally	O
adjusted	O
his	O
Family	O
affairs	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
Nancy	B-pers
is	O
still	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
we	O
go	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
our	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
mine	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
pray	O
present	O
our	O
united	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
Father	O
&	O
sisters	O
whom	O
we	O
hope	O
continue	O
well	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
.	O
Sincere	O
friend	O
&	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
PS	O
whenever	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr-	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
near	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
single	O
Sheet	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Novm	O
.	O
1786	O
