TOKEN	NE
Eastbourne	B-place
Monday	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1780	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
&	O
happy	O
--	O
pleased	O
--	O
infinitely	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
present	O
situation	O
--	O
delighted	O
with	O
our	O
society	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
consists	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
--	O
whom	O
(	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
love	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
tenderneſs	O
as	O
o	O
i	O
f	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Mother	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
--	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
are	O
but	O
the	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
appear	O
in	O
an	O
advantageous	O
light	O
from	O
their	O
conversation	O
&	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
from	O
the	O
countenance	O
of	O
each	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
good	O
minds	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
if	O
poſsible	O
improves	O
upon	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
our	O
society	O
I	O
must	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
Journey	O
was	O
extremely	O
pleasant	O
--	O
the	O
roads	O
the	O
whole	O
way	O
perfectly	O
good	O
--	O
the	O
views	O
charming	O
,	O
particularly	O
after	O
we	O
quitted	O
East	B-place
Grinstead	I-place
to	O
Ucfield	B-place
--	O
from	O
thence	O
till	O
within	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
miles	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
the	O
prospect	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
extensive	O
--	O
the	O
scene	O
became	O
more	O
domestic	O
--	O
fields	O
of	O
beautiful	O
verdure	O
enclosed	O
by	O
wth	O
fine	O
Hedge	O
rows	O
.	O
as	O
we	O
approach	O
'd	O
nearer	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
the	O
Country	O
was	O
open	O
but	O
flat	O
uncultivated	O
&	O
barren	O
.	O
Nothing	O
cld	O
.	O
equal	O
the	O
testimonies	O
of	O
loyalty	O
&	O
affection	O
wch	O
.	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
every	O
Town	O
,	O
Village	O
,	O
&	O
Hamlet	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
shew	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
Children	O
--	O
Bells	O
ringing	O
--	O
firing	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
poor	O
Women	O
&	O
children	O
running	O
out	O
to	O
strew	O
flowers	O
&	O
rushes	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
we	O
were	O
cover	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
flowers	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
honest	O
f	O
ol	O
ks	O
shook	O
over	O
us	O
as	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
respect	O
--	O
large	O
nosegays	O
were	O
thrown	O
continually	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
carriages	O
&	O
often	O
saluted	O
us	O
wth-	O
a	O
pretty	O
smart	O
blow	O
up	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
cheek	O
.	O
P.	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Govenor	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
reward	O
their	O
loyalty	O
by	O
throwing	O
silver	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
among	O
ym	O
.	O
&	O
giving	O
money	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell-ringers	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
8	O
miles	O
from	O
East-	B-place
Bourne	I-place
we	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
some	O
wth-	O
their	O
Wives	O
&	O
Children	O
daughters	O
behind	O
ym	O
.	O
,	O
after	O
giving	O
us	O
three	O
Cheers	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
their	O
Horses	O
&	O
escorted	O
us	O
to	O
our	O
habitation	O
--	O
Small	O
Cannon	O
were	O
planted	O
by	O
the	O
Sailors	O
&	O
fishermen	O
before	O
our	O
Windows	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
fired	O
off	O
at	O
intervals	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
Hoisted	O
all	O
their	O
flags	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Beach	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Cask	O
of	O
Beer	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
soon	O
emptied	O
in	O
healths	O
to	O
