TOKEN	NE
P.	B-place
Grove	I-place
Sepr	O
:	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
begged	O
to	O
begin	O
this	O
Sheet	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
to	O
lament	O
over	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
your	O
most	O
kind	O
Letter	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
have	O
suffered	O
by	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
Storm	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
have	O
hurried	O
you	O
most	O
sadly	O
besides	O
the	O
serious	O
mischief	O
that	O
such	O
an	O
Inundation	O
must	O
have	O
occasion	O
'd	O
to	O
your	O
Dwelling	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
,	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
very	O
happy	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
making	O
you	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
afforded	O
me	O
a	O
particular	O
pleasure	O
&	O
gratification	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
so	O
happy	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Home	O
,	O
with	O
so	O
amiable	O
and	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
sweet	O
&	O
promising	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
very	O
much	O
have	O
liked	O
to	O
see	O
Grandpapa	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
telling	O
you	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
now	O
I	O
once	O
again	O
begin	O
writing	O
;	O
(	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
such	O
a	O
sad	O
poor	O
Creature	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
Letter	O
writing	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
those	O
whom	O
I	O
love	O
best	O
.	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
confine	O
myself	O
therefore	O
to	O
this	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
however	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
&	O
comfortable	O
than	O
she	O
seems	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
She	O
walks	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
suffer	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
of	O
late	O
;	O
indeed	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
better	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
Summer	O
than	O
she	O
has	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
that	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
eſsentially	O
relieved	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
discipline	O
she	O
underwent	O
after	O
her	O
accident	O
;	O
She	O
certainly	O
looks	O
infinitely	O
better	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
accounts	O
from	O
my	O
dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Ducie	I-pers
s	O
;	O
He	O
returns	O
sooner	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
leave	O
my	B-pers
Dr	I-pers
:	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
:	O
how	O
happy	O
should	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
met	O
me	O
here	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
every	O
good	O
wish	O
to	O
Yourself	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Your	O
's	O
very	O
Affly	O
PC	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Comps	O
:	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
When	O
I	O
read	O
of	O
the	O
tremendous	O
Storm	O
of	O
Hail	O
Thunder	O
&	O
Rain	O
wch	O
.	O
fell	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	B-place
I	O
little	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
extended	O
its	O
alarming	O
influence	O
to	O
your	O
Habitation	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
(	O
as	O
is	O
your	O
usual	O
custom	O
)	O
you	O
ma	O
y	O
k	O
e	O
the	O
Evil	O
as	O
slight	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
sadly	O
hurried	O
your	O
poor	O
nerves	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
have	O
occasioned	O
you	O
innumerable	O
inconveniences	O
--	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
repairing	O
the	O
Pipes	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
but	O
be	O
defrayed	O
by	O
your	O
rich	O
Land-Lady	O
.	O
The	O
disappointment	O
of	O
not	O
visiting	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
once	O
hoped	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Month	O
is	O
no	O
trifling	O
one	O
I	O
can	O
truly	O
say	O
;	O
not	O
that	O
entre	O
nous	O
I	O
ever	O
entertained	O
much	O
dependance	O
upon	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
from	O
one	O
cause	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
,	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
would	O
rejoice	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
we	O
could	O
have	O
managed	O
it	O
this	O
Week	O
&	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
impoſsible	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
House	O
quite	O
full	O
of	O
Company	O
.	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
delight	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
well	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
nerves	O
--	O
indeed	O
both	O
your	O
old	O
friends	O
have	O
great	O
cause	O
of	O
thankfulneſs	O
for	O
the	O
comfortable	O
State	O
of	O
health	O
we	O
now	O
enjoy	O
.	O
My	O
only	O
material	O
infirmity	O
is	O
increased	O
deafneſs	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
seldom	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Person	O
sitting	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
of	O
course	O
makes	O
me	O
appear	O
very	O
stupid	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
fact	O
deprives	O
me	O
of	O
much	O
pleasure	O
in	O
society	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
your	O
good	O
Father	O
in	O
Law	O
has	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
his	O
spasmodic	O
complaints	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
will	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickn	I-pers
will	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
spend	O
their	O
Winter	O
in	O
your	O
cheerful	O
Dom	O
e	O
stic	O
Circle	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
hope	O
He	O
will	O
enable	O
you	O
to	O
visit	O
London	B-place
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
convenience	O
.	O
&	O
comfort	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
lately	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
&	O
like	O
them	O
much	O
--	O
they	O
all	O
dined	O
here	O
on	O
Thursday	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Weddell	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
with	O
dr	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
&	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Nagell	I-pers
(	O
who	O
wth	O
her	O
Sons	O
have	O
spent	O
a	O
Week	O
here	O
)	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
made	O
a	O
d	O
e	O
lightful	O
Party	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
is	O
seldom	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
heartily	O
wishing	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
&	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Nagell	I-pers
,	O
both	O
made	O
Enquiries	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
remembered	O
when	O
I	O
next	O
wrote	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Chief	I-pers
Baron	I-pers
has	O
sold	O
his	O
Place	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
--	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
anxious	O
to	O
procure	O
another	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
the	B-pers
Ladies	I-pers
Montgomerys	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
are	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
our	O
Paper	O
of	O
yesterday	O
mentions	O
an	O
alarming	O
Riot	O
at	O
Nottingham	B-place
on	O
acct	O
of	O
the	O
rise	O
of	O
Bread	O
;	O
nor	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
wonder	O
at	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
abundant	O
Harvest	O
,	O
must	O
have	O
raise	O
d	O
their	O
reasonable	O
&	O
sanguine	O
expectations	O
of	O
returning	O
plenty	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
this	O
Example	O
may	O
not	O
spread	O
;	O
it	O
certainly	O
will	O
,	O
unleſs	O
vigorous	O
measures	O
are	O
taken	O
that	O
Corn	O
should	O
be	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
proper	O
price	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
the	O
finest	O
Verdure	O
imaginable	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
wd-	O
think	O
this	O
place	O
much	O
improved	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
here	O
(	O
Alas	O
!	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
that	O
is	O
!	O
)	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
wd	O
give	O
me	O
credit	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
is	O
g	O
one	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burgoyne	I-pers
,	O
&	O
afterwards	O
dear	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
Jane	B-pers
.	O
She	O
left	O
us	O
yesterday	O
&	O
it	O
never	O
ceased	O
raining	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
our	O
Glaſs	O
is	O
very	O
low	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
is	O
still	O
confined	O
,	O
but	O
hopes	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
liberty	O
soon	O
--	O
indeed	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
do	O
duty	O
in	O
his	O
Church	O
;	O
&	O
is	O
shortly	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
side	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
charges	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
his	O
kindest	O
compts	O
to	O
yourself	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
his	O
recreation	O
this	O
Vacation	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
study	O
of	O
Italian	O
,	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
makes	O
a	O
very	O
rapid	O
Progreſs	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
read	O
a	O
new	O
Book	O
Modern	O
Philosophy	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Madme	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
has	O
just	O
published	O
another	O
Work	O
,	O
wch	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
has	O
merit	O
.	O
the	O
Title	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
Ly	B-pers
Lilford	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
Eldest	O
Daughter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stopford	I-pers
a	O
clergyman	O
Lord	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
s	O
Son	O
--	O
he	O
bear	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
amiable	O
Character	O
--	O
but	O
their	O
Income	O
will	O
be	O
narrow	O
.	O
Marianne	B-pers
has	O
heard	O
from	O
dear	O
Nanny	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
abode	O
at	O
Ramsgate	B-place
&	O
finds	O
living	O
there	O
much	O
cheaper	O
than	O
at	O
Bromley	B-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
neices	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
.	O
MA	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
D	O
ear	O
Miſs	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
on	O
“	O
the	O
Rose	O
”	O
,	O
by	O
Cooper	B-pers
being	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Ly	B-pers
Hesketh	I-pers
,	O
wth	O
a	O
prohibition	O
not	O
to	O
Copy	O
the	O
Lines	O
.	O
W	O
hat	O
wonder	O
if	O
my	O
wandering	O
hand	O
Had	O
dared	O
to	O
disobey	O
,	O
when	O
Hesketh	B-pers
gave	O
a	O
harsh	O
command	O
and	O
Cooper	B-pers
led	O
astray	O
?	O
Then	O
broke	O
this	O
tempting	O
Gift	O
of	O
thine	O
,	O
By	O
Pen	O
uncopied	O
yet	O
;	O
But	O
can'st	O
thou	O
Memory	O
confine	O
or	O
Teach	O
me	O
to	O
forget	O
?	O
More	O
lasting	O
than	O
the	O
touch	O
of	O
art	O
,	O
Her	O
character	O
's	O
remain	O
,	O
When	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
feeling	O
Heart	O
on	O
Tablets	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
upon	O
learning	O
his	O
Verses	O
by	O
heart	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
Letter	O
--	O
provided	O
you	O
ansr	O
this	O
soon	O
.	O
remember	O
to	O
give	O
My	O
k	O
i	O
nd	O
Compts	O
&	O
M	B-pers
s	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Daughter	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
Lines	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
written	O
by	O
a	O
mad	O
Woman	O
?	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
