TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Answer	O
--	O
Windsor	B-place
Novbr	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
1786	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Her	O
acknowledgments	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
acceptable	O
present	O
He	O
has	O
made	O
her	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
last	O
night	O
)	O
of	O
his	O
new	O
Edition	O
of	O
His	O
anecdotes	O
on	O
Painting	O
--	O
nor	O
is	O
she	O
insensible	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Honor	O
done	O
her	O
in	O
mentioning	O
her	O
name	O
in	O
so	O
ingenious	O
&	O
valuable	O
a	O
work	O
wth	O
.	O
so	O
much	O
delicacy	O
as	O
to	O
reconcile	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Publication	O
that	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
rather	O
Painful	O
from	O
any	O
other	O
hand	O
.	O
