TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
presents	O
his	O
Comp	O
:	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
begs	O
she	O
will	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
his	O
books	O
of	O
Drawings	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wishes	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
early	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
before	O
he	O
leaves	O
London	B-place
.	O
The	O
Drawings	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
service	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
sorry	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
waiting	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
tomorrow	O
--	O
Thursd	O
:	O
3	O
oCl	O
