TOKEN	NE
Caldes	B-place
.	O
Aug	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
every	O
post	O
day	O
prevented	O
from	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
of	O
May	O
2	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
since	O
my	O
return	O
hither	O
July	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
receiving	O
it	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
such	O
an	O
old	O
Story	O
that	O
I	O
daresay	O
you	O
have	O
almost	O
forgot	O
you	O
wrote	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
feel	O
myself	O
very	O
ungrateful	O
not	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
determined	O
though	O
much	O
hurried	O
that	O
this	O
pen	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
acknowledgements	O
.	O
as	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
short	O
I	O
am	O
desirous	O
resolved	O
to	O
begin	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
which	O
I	O
most	O
long	O
just	O
now	O
to	O
mention	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
charming	O
amiable	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
G	I-pers
's	O
friendly	O
attentions	O
&	O
the	O
infinite	O
comfort	O
we	O
received	O
from	O
them	O
in	O
our	O
fine	O
distreſses	O
here	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
two	O
Months	O
without	O
interruption	O
with	O
her	O
also	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
fortunate	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
in	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
&	O
friendship	O
for	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
I	O
may	O
claim	O
both	O
&	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
really	O
a	O
more	O
thorough	O
intimacy	O
than	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
have	O
boasted	O
of	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
years	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
in	O
all	O
our	O
mutual	O
distreſses	O
I	O
suppose	O
we	O
were	O
never	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
others	O
sight	O
--	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
think	O
more	O
highly	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
wch	O
.	O
makes	O
me	O
leſs	O
copious	O
just	O
now	O
on	O
his	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
comfortable	O
&	O
happy	O
&	O
indeed	O
merry	O
when	O
we	O
all	O
were	O
together	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
Agromonte	B-place
near	O
Oporto	B-place
the	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
their	O
proceedings	O
were	O
quite	O
unsettled	O
--	O
she	O
now	O
writes	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
(	O
very	O
judiciously	O
I	O
think	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
advise	O
it	O
)	O
determined	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
all	O
hopes	O
thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
England	B-place
,	O
&	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
next	O
Winter	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
or	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
of	O
France	B-place
but	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
former	O
as	O
it	O
agreed	O
so	O
well	O
with	O
her	O
last	O
year	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
this	O
determination	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
disappointment	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
a	O
mortification	O
it	O
certainly	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
sending	O
her	O
word	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
had	O
expreſsed	O
an	O
idea	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
returned	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
ensuing	O
spring	O
,	O
so	O
this	O
will	O
prove	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
friends	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
surprised	O
at	O
her	O
now	O
remaining	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
approve	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
not	O
setting	O
out	O
for	O
England	B-place
in	O
Augst	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
also	O
mentioned	O
Ly	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
being	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
comfort	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
since	O
May	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
a	O
charming	O
little	O
Girl	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
send	O
this	O
Letter	O
off	O
directly	O
--	O
we	O
never	O
recd	O
that	O
first	O
Letter	O
of	O
M	O
wch	O
.	O
you	O
mention	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
we	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
loſs	O
for	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
it	O
wd	O
have	O
been	O
charming	O
--	O
Yrs	O
.	O
sincerely	O
S.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
are	O
all	O
going	O
on	O
well	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
London	B-place
pr	O
via	O
Ostend	B-place
