TOKEN	NE
Leuctra	B-place
Satry	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1779	O
I	O
am	O
grieved	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
“	O
Soul	O
my	O
Beloved	O
”	O
Friend	O
to	O
think	O
yt	O
.	O
so	O
many	O
days	O
have	O
paſs	O
'd	O
away	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
last	O
date	O
being	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
--	O
my	O
time	O
has	O
been	O
indispensably	O
occupied	O
--	O
Perfecta	B-pers
is	O
absent	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
have	O
been	O
Ill	O
--	O
last	O
Thursday	O
I	O
spent	O
in	O
nursing	O
Agnés	B-pers
;	O
--	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
yt	O
.	O
if	O
common	O
humanity	O
could	O
make	O
me	O
so	O
attentive	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
feel	O
&	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
act	O
was	O
I	O
with	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
tenderly	O
attach	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
yourself	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
--	O
Ill	O
yourself	O
and	O
requiring	O
every	O
tender	O
attention	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
separated	O
--	O
&	O
by	O
Illneſs	O
too	O
from	O
I——	B-pers
&	O
yor	O
.	O
F——	B-pers
--	O
poor	O
man	O
how	O
I	O
pity	O
him	O
!	O
Saty	O
.	O
Eve.g	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
wrote	O
thus	O
far	O
very	O
early	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
went	O
Elise	B-pers
was	O
indisposed	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
.	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Post	O
brought	O
me	O
your	O
dear	O
letter	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
through	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
just	O
comforted	O
myself	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Health	O
&	O
Is——	B-pers
thank	O
God	O
You	O
are	O
both	O
better	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
as	O
usu	O
a	O
l	O
to	O
Babel	B-place
--	O
Elise	B-pers
,	O
Agnés	B-pers
&	O
the	O
3	O
--	O
&	O
on	O
M	O
onday	O
,	O
P.W	B-pers
&	O
F	B-pers
k——g	I-pers
for	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
this	O
Year	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
what	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
night	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
lose	O
another	O
post	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
continue	O
to'morrow	O
&	O
send	O
by	O
Mondays	O
post	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
your	O
letters	O
my	O
love	O
as	O
likewise	O
ye	O
.	O
packets	O
safe	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
procure	O
franks	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
will	O
venture	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	O
for	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
send	O
send	O
as	O
I	O
promised	O
by	O
Monday	O
nights	O
Post	O
.	O
--	O
Melsom	O
Street	O
!	O
perhaps	O
you	O
are	O
lodged	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
very	O
House	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
was	O
was	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
--	O
I	O
forget	O
ye	O
.	O
name	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Landlord	O
--	O
How	O
such	O
little	O
circumstances	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
touch	O
sensibly	O
upon	O
the	O
secret	O
impulses	O
of	O
the	O
mind	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
may	O
style	O
them	O
friendly	O
fallacies	O
.	O
Indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
blushed	O
as	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
praises	O
you	O
so	O
liberally	O
bestow	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
knowing	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
wld	O
.	O
write	O
to	O
Miranda	B-pers
me	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
,	O
&	O
feeling	O
so	O
conscious	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
merit	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
character	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
however	O
make	O
me	O
ambitious	O
of	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
deserve	O
it	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
to	O
retract	O
your	O
opinion	O
--	O
Let	O
no	O
presentiments	O
disturb	O
ye	O
.	O
veracity	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
wrong	O
very	O
wrong	O
to	O
indulge	O
such	O
a	O
disposition	O
--	O
the	O
past	O
&	O
present	O
are	O
but	O
too	O
ampl	O
y	O
e	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
circumstances	O
to	O
exercise	O
&	O
keep	O
alive	O
our	O
sensibility	O
without	O
ye	O
.	O
addition	O
of	O
presentiment	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
O	O
do	O
no	O
t	O
suffer	O
yourself	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
away	O
by	O
it	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
for	O
to	O
night	O
.	O
May	O
the	O
Almighty	O
preserve	O
You	O
&	O
take	O
you	O
under	O
his	O
protection	O
and	O
Oh	O
may	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
deserve	O
the	O
felicity	O
promised	O
in	O
another	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
procured	O
by	O
the	O
ever	O
bleſsed	O
&	O
adored	O
redeemer	O
of	O
Mankind	O
“	O
To	O
Him	O
,	O
to	O
Him	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
given	O
,	O
“	O
Paſsion	O
&	O
care	O
&	O
Anguish	O
to	O
destroy	O
,	O
“	O
Thro	O
'	O
Him	O
soft	O
Peace	O
&	O
Plentitude	O
of	O
Joy	O
“	O
Perpetual	O
o'er	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
redeem	O
'd	O
shall	O
flow	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Prior	O
,	O
Solomon	O
on	O
the	O
Vanity	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
book	O
III	O
.	O
Prior	O
's	O
Solomon	O
let	O
us	O
with	O
all	O
our	O
best	O
endeavours	O
cultivate	O
ye	O
.	O
love	O
of	O
God	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
by	O
yt	O
.	O
means	O
our	O
path	O
of	O
duty	O
can	O
be	O
made	O
straight	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
13	O
th	O
November	O
1779	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Melsom	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
