TOKEN	NE
Babel	B-place
--	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1781	O
How	O
grieved	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
beloved	O
friend	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
alarmed	O
on	O
my	O
Account	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
unavoidable	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
another	O
than	O
to	O
suffer	O
the	O
torment	O
of	O
suspense	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
recovering	O
very	O
fast	O
--	O
every	O
tender	O
attention	O
has	O
been	O
paid	O
to	O
Your	O
friend	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Jebb	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
attended	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
Illneſs	O
was	O
a	O
Nervous	O
&	O
Bilious	O
Fever	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
reduced	O
in	O
strength	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
appearance	O
.	O
Ah	O
how	O
ardently	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
were	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
H.Horton	B-place
,	O
&	O
how	O
delighted	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
every	O
post	O
if	O
but	O
two	O
lines	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
what	O
a	O
comfort	O
it	O
is	O
t	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
You	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
must	O
give	O
you	O
franks	O
for	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
H	B-place
.	I-place
Their	O
M——	O
went	O
to	O
Leuctra	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
AttoſsaPrinceſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
on	O
my	O
Acct	O
.	O
is	O
left	O
behind	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
till	O
Friday	O
spend	O
her	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
more	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Dearest	O
Astrea	B-pers
Friend	O
M	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
just	O
sent	O
me	O
Yor	O
.	O
Letter	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
How	O
sensibly	O
my	O
love	O
do	O
I	O
feel	O
every	O
mark	O
of	O
your	O
tender	O
affection	O
4	O
th	O
July	O
1781	O
