TOKEN	NE
Billingbear	O
Ocbr	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
1792	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
Mortified	O
my	O
dear	O
Sir	O
&	O
Madam	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
long	O
Silence	O
&	O
apparent	O
Coldneſs	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
but	O
was	O
Still	O
more	O
Concern	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
rect	O
of	O
Blosset	B-pers
s	O
kind	O
letter	O
that	O
the	O
silence	O
was	O
so	O
Accounted	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
indeed	O
truly	O
Griev	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
Unlucky	O
as	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
little	O
Brother	O
or	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
most	O
truly	O
hope	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
great	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
in	O
case	O
she	O
sd	O
be	O
bleeding	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
told	O
)	O
that	O
these	O
Accidents	O
are	O
very	O
hurtful	O
to	O
the	O
general	O
Constitution	O
--	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
future	O
Chasms	O
in	O
our	O
Correspondence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
believe	O
how	O
many	O
little	O
immemorable	O
Events	O
take	O
place	O
which	O
prevent	O
one	O
from	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
&	O
are	O
too	O
insignificant	O
to	O
be	O
Inescere	O
imprimis	O
as	O
to	O
yr	O
Enquiry	O
respecting	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
honours	O
you	O
were	O
perfectly	O
right	O
in	O
your	O
Conjectures	O
.	O
Mon	O
sr	O
.	O
le	O
Medicin	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
abroad	O
.	O
except	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
where	O
perhaps	O
that	O
Title	O
wd	O
be	O
now	O
too	O
aſsuming	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
Party	O
paſs	O
'd	O
thr	O
'	O
o	O
France	B-place
without	O
interruption	O
their	O
original	O
design	O
was	O
to	O
remain	O
at	O
Geneva	B-place
till	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
if	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
Croſs	O
'd	O
the	O
Alps	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
their	O
Chance	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
--	O
take	O
the	O
Season	O
--	O
the	O
Uncommon	O
Events	O
which	O
have	O
occur	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
as	O
few	O
Months	O
the	O
appearance	O
is	O
awful	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
&	O
more	O
Serious	O
part	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
are	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
all	O
these	O
are	O
preludes	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Event	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
taught	O
to	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
this	O
is	O
much	O
beyond	O
the	O
boundaries	O
of	O
my	O
reason	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
ventur	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
on	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lonely	O
hour	O
--	O
most	O
horrible	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Effects	O
of	O
this	O
Wonderful	O
revolution	O
in	O
France	B-place
--	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
surpris	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
general	O
is	O
certainly	O
more	O
Civilis	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
People	O
sd	O
be	O
so	O
Ferocious	O
now	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
280	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
reading	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
reformation	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
reform	O
'd	O
Churches	O
in	O
France	B-place
--	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
frequently	O
surpris	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
same	O
accounts	O
in	O
the	O
Stir	O
of	O
last	O
Week	O
that	O
I	O
read	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
in	O
that	O
book	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Book	O
wrote	O
with	O
Vivacity	O
&	O
impartiality	O
--	O
by	O
Dr	B-pers
Blagden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
paſs	O
'd	O
Nine	O
Weeks	O
at	O
Trunkwell	O
with	O
my	O
the	B-pers
Revd	I-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Laval	I-pers
it	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
place	O
&	O
I	O
sd	O
rather	O
imagine	O
not	O
Unlike	O
Taxall	B-place
.	O
It	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
alter	O
'd	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
fashion	O
of	O
the	O
times	O
.	O
there	O
I	O
live	O
very	O
much	O
Secluded	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
has	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Estate	O
in	O
her	O
hands	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
Events	O
of	O
the	O
Farm	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
can	O
have	O
in	O
Affairs	O
of	O
State	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
lucky	O
in	O
our	O
Harvest	O
.	O
&	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
meadow	O
Hay	O
has	O
been	O
Succeſsful	O
.	O
we	O
arriv	O
'd	O
here	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Yesterday	O
&	O
find	O
Aunt	B-pers
St	I-pers
Leger	I-pers
much	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
last	O
year	O
--	O
he	O
says	O
leſs	O
for	O
he	O
certainly	O
grows	O
Weaker	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
a	O
report	O
prevail	O
'd	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
,	O
but	O
Yesterday	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
account	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
sure	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
Announc	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
her	O
Mother	O
the	B-pers
Eldest	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Thrale	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
learn	O
how	O
to	O
regulate	O
a	O
State	O
--	O
so	O
perhaps	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
the	O
Ci	O
devant	O
R	O
de	O
F	O
:	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
expect	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
Extremity	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
they	O
will	O
keep	O
them	O
prisoners	O
for	O
Life	O
--	O
the	O
Gracious	O
R	O
:	O
has	O
committed	O
an	O
indescretion	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
for	O
Several	O
hours	O
he	O
Eat	O
Apple	O
Pye	O
&	O
Tea	O
--	O
his	O
R——l	O
Consort	O
has	O
something	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
her	O
R——l	O
foot	O
.	O
now	O
reste	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Court	O
is	O
now	O
Much	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
s	O
Time	O
--	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
any	O
return	O
of	O
her	O
Stomach	O
Complaint	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
little	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
attends	O
Louisa	B-pers
upon	O
Myra	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
she	O
will	O
send	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Turkeys	O
--	O
poor	O
Grandpapa	B-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
Complaint	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
much	O
better	O
for	O
the	O
Angostura	O
Bark	O
--	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
goes	O
abroad	O
.	O
I	O
sd	O
hardly	O
think	O
she	O
wd	O
venture	O
.	O
&	O
yet	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
inclination	O
that	O
perhaps	O
she	O
may	O
go	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
by	O
Sea	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
are	O
going	O
inmediately	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Camelford	I-pers
was	O
to	O
meet	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
:	O
but	O
I	O
sd	O
suppose	O
it	O
wd	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
easy	O
matter	O
to	O
appoint	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
to	O
meet	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
my	O
Mother	O
is	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
joi	O
Un	O
ites	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
in	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
&	O
wishes	O
--	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
very	O
faithful	O
&	O
oblig	O
'd	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
NB	O
:	O
direct	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
DBloſset	B-pers
Billingbear	O
Maidenhead	B-place
I	O
shall	O
now	O
see	O
by	O
the	O
Time	O
you	O
take	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
--	O
