TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
omit	O
taking	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
telling	O
you	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
condole	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
melancholy	O
news	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
last	O
Post	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
I	O
regret	O
being	O
at	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
distance	O
to	O
prove	O
more	O
eſsentially	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
very	O
sincere	O
&	O
tender	O
affection	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
regret	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
real	O
esteem	O
&	O
regard	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
had	O
every	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
good	O
qualities	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
account	O
she	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
that	O
her	O
departure	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
real	O
release	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
&	O
thank	O
God	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
so	O
happy	O
a	O
situation	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
considerable	O
weight	O
off	O
her	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
pleasing	O
reflection	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
balm	O
to	O
your	O
tender	O
Affectionate	O
Heart	O
,	O
mine	O
overflows	O
with	O
with	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
embrace	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
cordial	O
Affection	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
thank	O
'd	O
your	O
amicable	O
,	O
respectable	O
friend	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
her	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
half	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
her	O
friendship	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
eſsential	O
Bleſsings	O
you	O
poſseſs	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
fear	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
many	O
hearts	O
like	O
hers	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
lately	O
been	O
witneſses	O
to	O
a	O
sad	O
scene	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
were	O
among	O
the	O
small	O
number	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Hereditary	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
Death	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
melancholy	O
proofs	O
that	O
the	O
Diadem	O
can	O
not	O
shield	O
from	O
Shokes	O
like	O
these	O
,	O
nor	O
from	O
the	O
Grief	O
wch	O
.	O
must	O
ensue	O
the	O
poor	O
Queen	B-pers
just	O
ready	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
has	O
severely	O
felt	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
favourite	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
write	O
several	O
disagreeable	O
letters	O
of	O
bus'neſs	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
which	O
has	O
quite	O
worn	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
therefore	O
will	O
not	O
add	O
more	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
than	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
longer	O
letter	O
in	O
a	O
Post	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
out	O
shooting	O
with	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
his	O
sincere	O
regard	O
&	O
Affection	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
join	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
condoling	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
your	O
loſs	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
neither	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
or	O
place	O
can	O
ever	O
alter	O
the	O
true	O
regard	O
with	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Yr	O
Most	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
&	O
faithfull	O
friend	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Naples	B-place
Janry	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
1779	O
Sotch	O
Shotch	O
Scotland	B-place
Scotch	O
Scotch	O
Sotch	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
