TOKEN	NE
The	O
mornful	O
and	O
melancholy	O
Ditty	O
of	O
the	O
Dear	O
Blackamoor	O
's	O
metamorphosed	O
wife	O
Gave	O
me	O
infinite	O
pleasure	O
and	O
delight	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
cause	O
of	O
complaints	O
against	O
You	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Amen	O
!	O
You	O
want	O
now	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
Your	O
charming	O
letter	O
sooner	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
it	O
till	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
Camden	O
place	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
was	O
expected	O
at	O
home	O
every	O
moment	O
,	O
so	O
no	O
letter	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
:	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
our	O
exp	O
e	O
dition	O
:	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
inlisted	O
himself	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
Tyrconnel	I-pers
s	O
Service	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
so	O
hard	O
Duty	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
fever	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Blood	O
veſsel	O
and	O
all	O
appearance	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
consumption	O
.	O
When	O
his	O
mother	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
that	O
abominable	O
house	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
immediately	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
;	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
that	O
wretched	O
woman	O
Lady	B-pers
Tyrconnel	I-pers
came	O
every	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
next	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
Garden	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
for	O
many	O
sons	O
except	O
You	O
could	O
be	O
sure	O
they	O
that	O
in	O
time	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
bad	O
quality	O
your	O
Blackamoor	O
now	O
poſseſses	O
.	O
Has	O
More	B-pers
written	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
told	O
You	O
all	O
how	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Yearsley	I-pers
treated	O
her	O
and	O
still	O
does	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
unheard	O
of	O
ingratitude	O
;	O
because	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
Secured	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
prevent	O
that	O
wretch	O
of	O
squandering	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
will	O
shut	O
up	O
her	O
feelings	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
writings	O
of	O
Trust	O
at	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
You	O
invite	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
sweet	O
&	O
happy	O
Habitation	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
you	O
by	O
Storm	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
My	O
Power	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
more	O
pleased	O
to	O
see	O
again	O
then	O
--	O
gueſs	O
whom	O
--	O
But	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
converted	O
into	O
a	O
Blackamoor	O
likewise	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
flirting	O
on	O
horseback	O
in	O
all	O
weather	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
does	O
me	O
the	O
Honour	O
of	O
giving	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
Toast	O
.	O
Pray	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Respects	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
long	O
as	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
does	O
me	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
inclined	O
I	O
think	O
pretty	O
much	O
to	O
love	O
you	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
alway	O
find	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
Your	O
faithful	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Hampton	B-place
Septr	O
.	O
the	O
30	O
:	O
1785	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
by	O
Derby	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
1785	O
Sepbr-	O
