TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
return	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
your	O
obliging	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
by	O
last	O
post	O
,	O
your	O
agreeable	O
account	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
young	O
Royall	O
family	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
most	O
infinet	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
any	O
body	O
can	O
have	O
all	O
their	O
happineſs	O
more	O
at	O
heart	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Charmin	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
is	O
it	O
posible	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
love	O
respect	O
and	O
esteem	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
perhaps	O
be	O
takeing	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
liberty	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
self	O
so	O
freely	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
warmth	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
for	O
her	O
makes	O
me	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
rejoice	O
at	O
the	O
discription	O
of	O
the	O
Beautyfull	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
his	O
haveing	O
that	O
good	O
old	O
English	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
all	O
those	O
attentions	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
bestows	O
upon	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
distinguishing	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
his	O
Royall	O
Children	O
,	O
ought	O
to	O
please	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
does	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
seeing	O
Prince	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
my	O
unfortunate	O
bad	O
health	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
has	O
prevented	O
by	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
times	O
thy	O
wear	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
allways	O
heard	O
with	O
pleasure	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
charmin	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
hope	O
some	O
time	O
this	O
winter	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Duty	O
as	O
I	O
bliſs	O
god	O
my	O
health	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
a	O
great	O
dell	O
then	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
your	O
friends	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
like	O
your	O
discription	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
much	O
preferable	O
to	O
being	O
a	O
beauty	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
likes	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
behaves	O
well	O
that	O
is	O
sufficient	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
feel	O
so	O
interested	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
family	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
be	O
indifferent	O
about	O
any	O
thing	O
Concerns	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
long	O
uninterupted	O
friendship	O
my	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
honourd	O
me	O
wi	O
th	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
love	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
belongd	O
to	O
either	O
my	O
Lord	O
or	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
is	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
think	O
she	O
did	O
right	O
to	O
prefer	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
more	O
people	O
recover	O
Consumptive	O
illneſs	O
's	O
that	O
have	O
gone	O
there	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
south	O
of	O
France	B-place
,	O
poor	O
Dutches	B-pers
of	I-pers
Athol	I-pers
writ	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
melancholy	O
letter	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
apprehending	O
her	O
worse	O
then	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
affraid	O
the	O
nursing	O
would	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
this	O
winter	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
dont	O
mention	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
two	O
sons	O
I	O
hope	O
thy	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
Dutches	B-pers
Athol	I-pers
wrot	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
to	O
goe	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
I	O
must	O
now	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
trouble	O
again	O
about	O
this	O
same	O
knotting	O
Silk	O
,	O
Cadman	B-pers
must	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
a	O
fine	O
blundering	O
meſsange	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
wee	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
befor	O
new	O
years	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
therefor	O
should	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Cadman	I-pers
he	O
knows	O
how	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
safe	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
fine	O
,	O
Idle	O
work	O
at	O
candle	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dar	O
not	O
streſs	O
my	O
eyes	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
better	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
all	O
finished	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
wants	O
it	O
befor	O
I	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
it	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
so	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
the	O
other	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
perfect	O
health	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Sea	O
Air	O
is	O
charmin	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
did	O
me	O
much	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
goeing	O
Constantly	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
is	O
very	O
fine	O
for	O
weak	O
nerves	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
intirly	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlote	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
was	O
so	O
perfectly	O
recovered	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
realy	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
respect	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlote	I-pers
and	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
ever	O
Sincerly	O
your	O
affectionat	O
and	O
much	O
obliged	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Hale	B-place
by	O
Downton	B-place
Wilts	B-place
Novr	O
29	O
1780	O
