TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
before	O
me	O
your	O
very	O
interesting	O
&	O
affectionate	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
last	O
unanswerd	O
!	O
A	O
shameful	O
return	O
for	O
your	O
unwearied	O
&	O
effectual	O
services	O
at	O
the	O
period	O
of	O
my	O
unspeakable	O
distreſs	O
;	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
lost	O
to	O
all	O
manly	O
energies	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
deed	O
too	O
evident	O
that	O
the	O
imbecillity	O
of	O
old	O
age	O
has	O
the	O
almost	O
absolute	O
dominion	O
over	O
me	O
&	O
writing	O
is	O
now	O
become	O
a	O
very	O
painful	O
employment	O
;	O
be	O
aſsured	O
therefore	O
my	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
without	O
repetitions	O
that	O
the	O
services	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
indebted	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
were	O
most	O
judicious	O
&	O
consolatory	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
degree	O
.	O
The	O
event	O
of	O
your	O
late	O
loſs	O
is	O
somewhat	O
different	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
worthy	O
Parent	O
must	O
always	O
be	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
very	O
sincere	O
regret	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Aldborough	I-pers
my	O
only	O
remaining	O
Child	O
&	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
solicitous	O
concern	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
for	O
near	O
this	O
month	O
past	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
constant	O
resort	O
to	O
medical	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
her	O
constitution	O
being	O
much	O
impaired	O
&	O
subject	O
to	O
most	O
alarming	O
attacks	O
;	O
her	O
complaint	O
has	O
been	O
thought	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
eminent	O
of	O
the	O
faculty	O
in	O
London	B-place
to	O
be	O
seated	O
in	O
the	O
liver	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
apprehension	O
has	O
of	O
late	O
much	O
subsided	O
,	O
still	O
it	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
wished	O
that	O
her	O
disorder	O
which	O
gives	O
gives	O
her	O
great	O
uneasineſs	O
were	O
more	O
clearly	O
ascertain	O
'd	O
;	O
being	O
arrived	O
at	O
a	O
crititical	O
period	O
in	O
life	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
happen	O
that	O
a	O
sudden	O
fortunate	O
change	O
may	O
take	O
place	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
her	O
friends	O
by	O
whom	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
beloved	O
;	O
live	O
in	O
constant	O
anxiety	O
on	O
her	O
anxiety	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
esteem	O
it	O
a	O
want	O
of	O
due	O
confidence	O
not	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
relation	O
the	B-pers
late	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensberry	I-pers
,	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
legacy	O
of	O
£10,000	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
altogether	O
a	O
surprize	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
once	O
aſsured	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
remember	O
me	O
;	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
regard	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
dear	O
Daugher	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
your	O
faithful	O
&	O
affectionate	O
humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
Bath	B-place
January	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1811	O
.	O
15	O
Jany	O
1811	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Telling	O
of	O
his	O
Legacy	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queensberry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
49	O
.	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
