TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
was	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
yesterday	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
that	O
you	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
indisposed	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
relapsed	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
nearly	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
former	O
illneſs	O
;	O
I	O
shoud	O
suffer	O
the	O
greatest	O
anxiety	O
if	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
had	O
not	O
aſsured	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
recovering	O
fast	O
and	O
regaining	O
your	O
appetite	O
by	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
air	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
again	O
by	O
an	O
impatience	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
your	O
attendance	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
find	O
yourself	O
perfectly	O
restored	O
,	O
nor	O
suffer	O
yourself	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
anxious	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
a	O
very	O
hasty	O
return	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
expected	O
as	O
it	O
must	O
take	O
a	O
certain	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
strength	O
&	O
spirits	O
can	O
be	O
recover	O
'd	O
after	O
such	O
an	O
illneſs	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
time	O
comes	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
favor	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
engaged	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
in	O
making	O
preparations	O
for	O
my	O
residence	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
about	O
three	O
miles	O
from	O
Dublin	B-place
which	O
turns	O
out	O
far	O
beyond	O
my	O
expectations	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
indeed	O
uncommonly	O
beautiful	O
&	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
answerable	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
propose	O
to	O
remove	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
dupe	O
to	O
expectations	O
of	O
further	O
Preferment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
certainly	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
in	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
founded	O
upon	O
repeated	O
promises	O
of	O
Persons	O
who	O
might	O
have	O
served	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
now	O
entertain	O
but	O
small	O
hopes	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
.	O
My	O
residence	O
upon	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
farthest	O
northern	O
part	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
is	O
expected	O
&	O
may	O
probably	O
be	O
insisted	O
upon	O
,	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
the	O
finishing	O
stroke	O
of	O
my	O
perverse	O
fortune	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
situated	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
disagreeable	O
climate	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
rigid	O
Presbeterian	O
Independants	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
whom	O
wou	O
'd	O
emigrate	O
to	O
their	O
Friends	O
in	O
America	B-place
cou	O
'd	O
they	O
be	O
permitted	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
sooner	O
determine	O
to	O
resign	O
my	O
Living	O
than	O
attend	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
duty	O
among	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
People	O
that	O
have	O
an	O
unconquerable	O
aversion	O
to	O
the	O
established	O
Church	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
being	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
Friends	O
to	O
our	O
Constitution	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
labouring	O
if	O
possible	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
small	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
near	O
Dublin	B-place
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
option	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
residence	O
&	O
with	O
propriety	O
dispense	O
with	O
my	O
removal	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
abhor	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Ld	O
Lieutenant	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
but	O
as	O
my	O
request	O
has	O
no	O
other	O
advocate	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
but	O
myself	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
propable	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
meet	O
with	O
succeſs	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
expensive	O
&	O
extravagant	O
times	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
fixed	O
myself	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
for	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
a	O
gratuitous	O
surrender	O
of	O
my	O
Living	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
measure	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
approbation	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
my	O
circumstances	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
to	O
justify	O
my	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
very	O
greedy	O
or	O
ambitious	O
when	O
my	O
only	O
wish	O
is	O
to	O
realize	O
m	O
y	O
present	O
Income	O
with	O
propriety	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
by	O
having	O
the	O
a	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Living	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
procure	O
the	O
one	O
in	O
th	O
e	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
reside	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
lately	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chas	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
London	B-place
attending	O
an	O
Appeal	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
make	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
's	I-pers
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
is	O
extremely	O
well	O
very	O
handsome	O
,	O
agreeable	O
&	O
remarkably	O
clever	O
but	O
most	O
unfortunately	O
match	O
'd	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Gloucester	O
Street	O
Dublin	B-place
April	O
15	O
th	O
1778	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
James	O
Street	O
near	O
Buckingham	O
Gate	O
London	B-place
