TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
thank	O
'd	O
you	O
for	O
immediately	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
expected	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
Account	O
;	O
that	O
letter	O
is	O
now	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
no	O
objections	O
to	O
make	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
inform	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
receive	O
your	O
instructions	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
proper	O
you	O
may	O
draw	O
upon	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
amount	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Bill	O
payable	O
at	O
sight	O
.	O
Two	O
Dogs	O
arrived	O
here	O
from	O
Taxal	B-place
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
use	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
well	O
understand	O
,	O
&	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
succeſs	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
kind	O
information	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
the	O
Servant	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
imprudently	O
engaged	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
letter	O
has	O
been	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
great	O
lamentations	O
for	O
his	O
disappointment	O
.	O
A	O
letter	O
was	O
also	O
wrote	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
maker	O
at	O
Manchester	B-place
,	O
informing	O
him	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Clock	O
was	O
not	O
finish	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
promised	O
,	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
received	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
persuaded	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
true	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
debts	O
,	O
which	O
do	O
not	O
exceed	O
one	O
hundred	O
&	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
;	O
upwards	O
of	O
sixty	O
of	O
which	O
are	O
for	O
Telescopes	O
&	O
Air	O
Pumps	O
bought	O
at	O
different	O
shops	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
trifling	O
Bills	O
&	O
money	O
borrow	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
upon	O
myself	O
the	O
payment	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
final	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
;	O
for	O
what	O
debts	O
he	O
may	O
contract	O
hereafter	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
himself	O
responsible	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
consequences	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
allowance	O
of	O
£300	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
Annum	O
which	O
is	O
fully	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
expect	O
from	O
my	O
Income	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
had	O
nearly	O
twice	O
as	O
much	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
allow	O
'd	O
my	O
Brother	O
only	O
£200	O
.	O
Robert	O
has	O
aſsured	O
me	O
most	O
solemnly	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
break	O
off	O
his	O
connexion	O
with	O
Risman	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
however	O
endeavor	O
to	O
strengthen	O
this	O
promise	O
by	O
a	O
penal	O
obligation	O
.	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
after	O
his	O
arrival	O
was	O
silent	O
to	O
a	O
surprising	O
degree	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
of	O
late	O
become	O
much	O
more	O
cheerful	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
acknowledge	O
behaves	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
dupe	O
me	O
any	O
further	O
&	O
I	O
keep	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
allowance	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
do	O
till	O
our	O
agreement	O
is	O
completed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
may	O
dispose	O
of	O
himself	O
&	O
his	O
money	O
as	O
he	O
may	O
think	O
proper	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
determined	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Kiel	B-place
for	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
improving	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
chuses	O
in	O
preference	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
English	O
there	O
&	O
as	O
his	O
money	O
will	O
go	O
there	O
much	O
further	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
repeat	O
my	O
sincere	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
the	O
kind	O
interest	O
you	O
have	O
always	O
you	O
have	O
always	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
&	O
hope	O
the	O
time	O
may	O
come	O
when	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
throughly	O
conscious	O
of	O
his	O
obli	O
gations	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
altogether	O
despair	O
of	O
his	O
amen	O
dment	O
,	O
he	O
now	O
perceives	O
that	O
a	O
perseverance	O
in	O
his	O
errors	O
must	O
be	O
fatal	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
reflection	O
may	O
probably	O
make	O
him	O
more	O
cautious	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
your	O
obliging	O
invitation	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
having	O
much	O
busineſs	O
to	O
detain	O
me	O
here	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
unite	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
'	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
Obliged	O
&	O
Affect	O
.	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
Portman	O
Square	O
September	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1792	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
in	I-place
Frith	I-place
DerbyShire	B-place
