TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
--	O
By	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
rect	O
of	O
your	O
Ladyship	O
s	O
letter	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
inclosed	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
dare	O
flatter	O
myself	O
will	O
prove	O
satisfactory	O
respecting	O
yr-	O
request	O
you	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
solicit	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
with	O
Concern	O
of	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
&	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
sensible	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
knowg	O
from	O
such	O
undoubted	O
authority	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
recovering	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
from	O
the	O
dictates	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
common	O
place	O
civility	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
are	O
taught	O
to	O
hold	O
commerce	O
wth-	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
a	O
sincere	O
heartfelt	O
regard	O
&	O
esteem	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
yr-	O
Ladyship	O
wh	O
.	O
makes	O
me	O
feel	O
interested	O
in	O
whatever	O
nearly	O
concerns	O
your	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
pleasure	O
answer	O
yr-	O
obliging	O
enquiries	O
after	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
our	O
little	O
Darling	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
health	O
&	O
the	O
latter	O
growing	O
daily	O
more	O
engaging	O
and	O
endearing	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
her	O
understanding	O
&	O
the	O
fair	O
promise	O
of	O
an	O
amiable	O
disposition	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
presents	O
his	O
respects	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
be	O
remain	O
Yr	O
.	O
Ladyship	O
s	O
Affe	O
friend	O
&	O
Servt	O
.	O
MDickenson	B-pers
We	O
propose	O
spending	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
London	B-place
next	O
spring	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
--	O
In	O
case	O
your	O
Lad	O
y	O
ship	O
should	O
again	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
Liberty	O
of	O
sendg	O
you	O
my	O
addreſs	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
