TOKEN	NE
30	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1791	O
London	B-place
Tuesday	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
J	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
&	O
saw	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Portraits	O
of	O
Romney	B-pers
,	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
satisfied	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
the	O
Emma	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
matters	O
adjusted	O
respecting	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
went	O
home	O
when	O
we	O
separated	O
from	O
AMaria	B-pers
--	O
Emma	B-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sr	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
who	O
had	O
altered	O
her	O
plans	O
&	O
meant	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
when	O
She	O
quitted	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
now	O
when	O
She	O
is	O
there	O
--	O
Wedn	O
:	O
At	O
9	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lincolns	B-place
Inn	I-place
fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Acct	O
.	O
--	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Cr-	B-pers
s	O
for	O
Some	O
Cash	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
to	O
other	O
places	O
--	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Sir	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
who	O
seems	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
two	O
Girls	O
--	O
both	O
She	O
&	O
her	O
Husband	O
look	O
old	O
--	O
last	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
Oppy	O
of	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
Line	O
of	O
Conduct	O
that	O
I	O
wished	O
her	O
to	O
persue	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
Eliza	B-pers
's	O
Mother	O
came	O
here	O
&	O
repeating	O
her	O
profeſsions	O
of	O
kind	O
Offices	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
will	O
be	O
realized	O
if	O
neceſsary	O
)	O
took	O
a	O
very	O
friendly	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
Emma	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Court	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Malmsbury	I-pers
,	O
She	O
came	O
thrō	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
rain	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
Emma	B-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
after	O
our	O
conversation	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
answers	O
of	O
Monosyllables	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
parting	O
with	O
a	O
Sister	O
,	O
probably	O
for	O
ever	O
--	O
Eliza	B-pers
drank	O
a	O
Glaſs	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Wine	O
&	O
without	O
saying	O
one	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Word	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
without	O
mentioning	O
Father	O
Sister	O
or	O
Niece	O
or	O
friend	O
She	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Carriage	O
&	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Sang	O
froid	O
adjusted	O
the	O
Blinds	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
This	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Eliza	B-pers
came	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
exclaimed	O
--	O
“	O
My	O
God	O
!	O
Emma	B-pers
--	O
is	O
this	O
poſsible	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
with	O
what	O
Philosophy	O
She	O
bears	O
this	O
Separation	O
--	O
how	O
She	O
must	O
love	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
leave	O
all	O
her	O
dearest	O
Relations	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
composure	O
”	O
--	O
She	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
Dab	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
you	O
sealed	O
--	O
Yours	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
of	O
the	O
27	O
th	O
arrived	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
what	O
related	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
&	O
Sister	O
--	O
She	O
talked	O
cheerfully	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
no	O
endearing	O
meſsage	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
Can	O
this	O
Creature	O
have	O
feelings	O
or	O
of	O
what	O
Nature	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
She	O
never	O
mentioned	O
E	B-pers
.	I-pers
since	O
we	O
left	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
The	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
sent	O
you	O
many	O
Compts-	O
he	O
seemed	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
&	O
poor	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
have	O
a	O
bad	O
beginning	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
ceased	O
raining	O
since	O
morng	O
--	O
Samuel	B-pers
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
She	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Tonbridge	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
recollected	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
day	O
to	O
meet	O
Devaynes	B-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
forgetting	O
it	O
as	O
my	O
head	O
is	O
so	O
confused	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
aversion	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
is	O
too	O
well	O
founded	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
he	O
poſseſses	O
great	O
duplicity	O
&	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
honor	O
&	O
common	O
honesty	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
proposal	O
made	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
form	O
respecting	O
him	O
,	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
yr-	O
Sentiments	O
dont	O
mention	O
Names	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
probably	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
letter	O
--	O
Robert	B-pers
told	O
me	O
yt	O
the	O
marriage	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
therefore	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
leave	O
town	O
till	O
this	O
day	O
Sent	O
--	O
A	O
Demur	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Emma	B-pers
about	O
a	O
special	O
licence	O
owg	O
to	O
an	O
expreſsion	O
in	O
AB——p	B-pers
of	I-pers
Canty	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
application	O
therefore	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
solemnized	O
in	O
a	O
Church	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
is	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
is	O
dying	O
--	O
therefore	O
they	O
are	O
afraid	O
lest	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
prevented	O
from	O
attending	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
luck	O
in	O
not	O
meetg	O
this	O
person	O
--	O
but	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
introduction	O
poſsible	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abern	I-pers
..	I-pers
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
&	O
he	O
seemed	O
pleased	O
I	O
am	O
prevented	O
from	O
adding	O
another	O
Line	O
,	O
except	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
these	O
Lodggs	O
on	O
till	O
next	O
Wedy	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
best	O
of	O
Women	O
Adieu	O
--	O
Cs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
Single	O
sheet	O
To	O
J	B-pers
D	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
