TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
25	O
th	O
-	O
May	O
1801	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
most	O
obedient	O
Brother	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
although	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
here	O
above	O
Eight	O
&	O
Forty	O
Hours	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
fulfil	O
your	O
commands	O
by	O
announcing	O
my	O
own	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Eight	O
Children	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
jolly	O
Company	O
we	O
Ten	O
make	O
around	O
the	O
Dining	O
Table	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
the	O
sounds	O
somewhat	O
remind	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Story	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
fashioned	O
,	O
antiquated	O
Book	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
Babel	O
.	O
Such	O
Society	O
would	O
not	O
suit	O
the	O
delicate	O
Nerves	O
of	O
fine	O
folks	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
We	O
do	O
not	O
aspire	O
to	O
any	O
dignity	O
above	O
that	O
of	O
Rustick	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
bear	O
it	O
tolerably	O
well	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
very	O
instant	O
my	O
hopeful	O
Heir	O
Apparent	O
is	O
spitting	O
in	O
the	O
Flute	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
produce	O
the	O
Dusty	O
Miller	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
Paſsenger	O
in	O
this	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
consigned	O
to	O
his	O
Studies	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
near	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
making	O
him	O
comprehend	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
labouring	O
and	O
idling	O
over	O
at	O
Houghton	B-place
.	O
He	O
is	O
grown	O
a	O
fine	O
stout	O
,	O
decent	O
looking	O
Lad	O
;	O
poſseſses	O
a	O
tolerable	O
share	O
of	O
capability	O
;	O
without	O
much	O
desire	O
of	O
exerting	O
it	O
,	O
well	O
tempered	O
,	O
and	O
free	O
from	O
any	O
Vice	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
discover	O
.	O
One	O
thing	O
was	O
certainly	O
to	O
his	O
Credit	O
.	O
On	O
leaving	O
Houghton	O
School	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
debt	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
of	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
contracted	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
I	O
beleive	O
,	O
is	O
seldom	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
at	O
public	O
Schools	O
.	O
The	O
sight	O
of	O
Green	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Music	O
of	O
the	O
Birds	O
,	O
make	O
me	O
ample	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
Employment	O
in	O
attending	O
on	O
the	O
affairs	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Not	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
idle	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
busily	O
,	O
and	O
perplexedly	O
employed	O
,	O
in	O
finding	O
Places	O
for	O
a	O
Cargo	O
of	O
large	O
Books	O
,	O
just	O
arrived	O
from	O
London	B-place
,	O
in	O
my	O
Library	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
consumed	O
the	O
whole	O
morning	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
accommodate	O
Twenty	O
Folio	O
Volumes	O
(	O
Rymer	B-pers
's	O
Fœdera	O
)	O
,	O
my	O
next	O
operation	O
was	O
to	O
inspect	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
fault	O
(	O
for	O
without	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Authority	O
would	O
be	O
lost	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
my	O
farm	O
,	O
during	O
my	O
absence	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
in	O
conscience	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
abuse	O
my	O
Overseer	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
tolerably	O
good	O
order	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
.	O
Her	O
arrival	O
at	O
home	O
brought	O
many	O
painful	O
recollections	O
to	O
her	O
Mind	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
evidently	O
better	O
for	O
removing	O
from	O
Town	B-place
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
a	O
particular	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
will	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
and	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Sixth	O
May	O
1801	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
120	O
6	O
30	O
6	O
180	O
52	O
360	O
900	O
9360	O
