TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
,	O
From	O
July	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
to	O
Septr	O
.	O
10	O
th	O
,	O
no	O
Packet	O
arrived	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
is	O
come	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
made	O
us	O
amends	O
for	O
our	O
long	O
Expectations	O
by	O
the	O
many	O
kind	O
Letters	O
it	O
has	O
brought	O
&	O
good	O
Accounts	O
of	O
our	O
friends	O
,	O
except	O
of	O
yourself	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
whose	O
Letter	O
dated	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
your	O
health	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
confined	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
&	O
your	O
Complaint	O
continued	O
obstinate	O
after	O
two	O
bleedings	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
wrote	O
soon	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
quite	O
unhappy	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
feel	O
for	O
the	O
sad	O
Disappointment	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
the	O
Festivities	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
birth-day	O
,	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
goodneſs	O
shews	O
itself	O
upon	O
every	O
occasion	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
their	O
bringing	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Princes	O
(	O
from	O
Kew	B-place
)	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
a	O
Cordial	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
enclose	O
in	O
this	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
my	O
dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
whose	O
kind	O
Attentions	O
in	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
the	O
prettiest	O
most	O
entertaining	O
Letter	O
imaginable	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
.	O
pray	O
present	O
the	O
enclosed	O
with	O
my	O
Grateful	O
Duty	O
to	O
H	B-pers
R	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
I	O
did	O
myself	O
the	O
honr	O
.	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
the	O
m	O
3	O
Princeſses	O
have	O
long	O
before	O
this	O
been	O
received	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
busiest	O
of	O
my	O
Preparations	O
for	O
leaving	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
,	O
think	O
what	O
an	O
Undertaking	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
upon	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
make	O
the	O
Journey	O
by	O
Land	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
we	O
must	O
,	O
as	O
no	O
Neutral	O
Veſsels	O
but	O
Portuguese	O
offer	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
to	O
carry	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
later	O
in	O
ye	O
Year	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
venture	O
a	O
Sea	O
Voyage	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
by	O
no	O
means	O
approves	O
of	O
a	O
Portuguese	O
Veſsel	O
so	O
that	O
nothing	O
remains	O
but	O
a	O
good	O
Resolution	O
,	O
to	O
encounter	O
the	O
difficulties	O
&	O
tediousneſs	O
we	O
must	O
expect	O
in	O
a	O
Land	O
Journey	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
thank	O
God	O
continues	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
so	O
anxious	O
to	O
ſee	O
us	O
safe	O
in	O
our	O
Journey	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
France	B-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
means	O
to	O
accompany	O
us	O
to	O
Bordeaux	B-place
at	O
least	O
,	O
as	O
probably	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
our	O
Route	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
agree	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
then	O
as	O
to	O
Climate	O
I	O
shall	O
think	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
of	O
France	B-place
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
staid	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
by	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
s	O
gracious	O
Meſsage	O
about	O
my	O
Absence	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mind	O
once	O
satisfied	O
about	O
Ld	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
's	O
Safety	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
wish	O
so	O
strong	O
as	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
my	O
Duty	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
equally	O
anxious	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
,	O
being	O
gratefully	O
Sensible	O
to	O
both	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
for	O
their	O
kind	O
Indulgence	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
his	O
Account	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
without	O
putting	O
a	O
great	O
restraint	O
upon	O
himself	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
personally	O
to	O
expreſs	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Injunctions	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
Physical	O
People	O
are	O
so	O
strong	O
for	O
his	O
not	O
attempting	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
England	B-place
till	O
the	O
Winter	O
is	O
over	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
yeilded	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
promises	O
only	O
to	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
sees	O
us	O
in	O
some	O
safe	O
&	O
comfortable	O
Train	O
of	O
proceeding	O
in	O
our	O
Journey	O
.	O
Poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
's	O
Accident	O
,	O
will	O
neceſsarily	O
occasion	O
her	O
a	O
longer	O
Absence	O
from	O
her	O
Duty	O
about	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
(	O
which	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
perform	O
)	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
longer	O
Anxiety	O
about	O
her	O
little	O
family	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
encreas	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
last	O
packet	O
bringing	O
her	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Severe	O
Illneſs	O
poor	O
little	O
Matilda	B-pers
has	O
gone	O
thrō	O
,	O
which	O
thō	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
she	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
yet	O
it	O
has	O
awaked	O
in	O
her	O
Mind	O
a	O
thouſd	O
.	O
Apprehensions	O
of	O
what	O
may	O
happen	O
in	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
Absence	O
.	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
have	O
consider	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
wishing	O
Mrs	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
have	O
remain	O
'd	O
on	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Case	O
stood	O
when	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
let	O
her	O
miſs	O
such	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
returning	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
joining	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
I	O
own	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
Ld	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
compleatly	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
thrō	O
her	O
petition	O
'd	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
for	O
a	O
longer	O
Stay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Case	O
Mrs	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
might	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
too	O
long	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
s	O
coming	O
.	O
She	O
&	O
Harriet	B-pers
both	O
send	O
their	O
Love	O
&	O
wishes	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
recovery	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
add	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
remain	O
ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
most	O
affecte	O
.	O
&	O
Faithful	O
CFinch	B-pers
Remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
