TOKEN	NE
Copy	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
March	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
1789	O
sent	O
9	O
th	O
--	O
Though	O
it	O
is	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
or	O
written	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
&	O
respected	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
equally	O
persuaded	O
of	O
the	O
constancy	O
of	O
their	O
regard	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
towards	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
the	O
constancy	O
of	O
my	O
attachment	O
towards	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
animated	O
to	O
break	O
through	O
the	O
silence	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
prevailed	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
communicating	O
to	O
them	O
how	O
my	O
heart	O
glows	O
with	O
Rapture	O
at	O
the	O
happy	O
thrice	O
happy	O
restoration	O
of	O
our	O
beloved	O
and	O
good	O
King	B-pers
s	O
health	O
--	O
God	O
has	O
been	O
exceedingly	O
gracious	O
towards	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
relieved	O
us	O
from	O
our	O
Sorrow	O
--	O
may	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
just	O
sense	O
of	O
the	O
bleſsing	O
he	O
has	O
vouchsafed	O
to	O
restore	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
merit	O
that	O
our	O
amiable	O
sovereign	O
may	O
very	O
long	O
continue	O
to	O
reign	O
over	O
these	O
kingdoms	O
--	O
few	O
,	O
very	O
few	O
of	O
his	O
Subjects	O
(	O
comparatively	O
speaking	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
so	O
senseleſs	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
feel	O
&	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
in	O
the	O
Recovery	O
of	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
strongly	O
felt	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
must	O
suffer	O
,	O
&	O
prayed	O
fervently	O
for	O
a	O
mitigation	O
of	O
her	O
troubles	O
--	O
bleſsed	O
be	O
God	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
only	O
now	O
mitigated	O
but	O
ended	O
;	O
deeply	O
has	O
she	O
drank	O
of	O
the	O
bitter	O
cup	O
of	O
Affliction	O
--	O
may	O
She	O
never	O
again	O
taste	O
it	O
.	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
has	O
ever	O
set	O
a	O
bright	O
example	O
to	O
the	O
female	O
Sex	O
of	O
every	O
moral	O
virtue	O
by	O
acting	O
with	O
undeviat	O
ing	O
propriety	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
now	O
shewn	O
them	O
what	O
advantages	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
reaped	O
from	O
christian	O
piety	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
so	O
enabled	O
her	O
to	O
bear	O
up	O
under	O
the	O
preſsure	O
of	O
a	O
grievous	O
trial	O
&	O
affliction	O
with	O
proper	O
resignation	O
to	O
the	O
divine	O
will	O
,	O
&	O
supported	O
her	O
to	O
fulfill	O
her	O
duties	O
in	O
an	O
exemplary	O
manner	O
when	O
her	O
heart	O
was	O
pierced	O
by	O
the	O
most	O
poignant	O
Anguish	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
lately	O
who	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
honor	O
&	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
her	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
looked	O
like	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
much	O
trouble	O
and	O
was	O
thinner	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
very	O
happy	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
not	O
materially	O
injured	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
recovered	O
her	O
looks	O
with	O
her	O
happineſs	O
--	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
have	O
not	O
suffered	O
in	O
their	O
's	O
from	O
their	O
late	O
affliction	O
--	O
This	O
question	O
I	O
likewise	O
ask	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
friends	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
how	O
deeply	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
affected	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cholmondley	I-pers
of	O
whom	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
good	O
Accounts	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
desires	O
you	O
will	O
accept	O
his	O
affe	O
.	O
Respects	O
.	O
our	O
little	O
Girl	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
delights	O
our	O
hearts	O
,	O
by	O
seeming	O
to	O
have	O
(	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
one	O
can	O
judge	O
at	O
her	O
tender	O
age	O
)	O
an	O
amiable	O
affecte	O
.	O
disposition	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
health	O
from	O
herself	O
--	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
glad	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
is	O
married	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
heard	O
any	O
particular	O
relative	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Warrddington	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
made	O
a	O
prudent	O
choice	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
esteem	O
it	O
a	O
favor	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Comps	O
.	O
to	O
ye-	O
Ladies	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
at	O
the	O
Palace	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
Opporty	O
;	O
and	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
us	O
very	O
affy	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
's	O
Sincere	O
&	O
Affe	O
.	O
friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
7	O
March	O
1789	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Montagu	O
's	O
are	O
well	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
day	O
at	O
Sandleford	B-place
in	O
the	O
autumn	O
pray	O
present	O
our	O
kind	O
Compliments	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
