TOKEN	NE
pt	O
10	O
Monday	O
Night	O
My	O
Dst	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
kind	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
stout	O
to	O
morrow	O
but	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
illneſs	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
again	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
as	O
your	O
Mama	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
,	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
my	O
Brother	O
has	O
constantly	O
enquired	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
interested	O
himself	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
so	O
indeed	O
does	O
every	O
body	O
here	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
vastly	O
Stout	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
quite	O
fat	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
oportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
what	O
you	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
to	O
day	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
the	O
better	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
him	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
yo	O
u	O
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
