TOKEN	NE
Somerset	O
Street	O
July	O
7	O
th	O
You	O
have	O
hit	O
upon	O
it	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
when	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
Numerous	O
diſsipations	O
(	O
for	O
they	O
scarcely	O
deserve	O
a	O
better	O
Name	O
)	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
answering	O
your	O
kind	O
Letter	O
sooner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
exactly	O
when	O
some	O
little	O
busineſs	O
still	O
remaining	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
will	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
London	B-place
but	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
imagine	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
my	O
self	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
paſs	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
many	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
other	O
visits	O
to	O
make	O
&	O
we	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
certainly	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
perfectly	O
right	O
in	O
the	B-pers
Cavr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Palombo	I-pers
be	O
aſsured	O
I	O
woud	O
tell	O
it	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
years	O
&	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
and	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Friends	O
a	O
more	O
strictly	O
honest	O
man	O
does	O
not	O
exist	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Naples	B-place
Friends	O
that	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
venture	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
first	O
a	O
little	O
difficult	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
relish	O
the	O
Naples	B-place
life	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
two	O
she	O
will	O
like	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
when	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
introduce	O
a	O
little	O
Cleanlineſs	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
of	O
which	O
no	O
Neapolitan	O
has	O
has	O
the	O
least	O
idea	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
My	O
family	O
will	O
contribute	O
all	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
to	O
her	O
happineſs	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
W.H	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
E.H	B-pers
.	I-pers
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
seperate	O
Must	O
be	O
so	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
bring	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Man	O
&	O
Maid	O
Servants	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
explain	O
the	O
whole	O
but	O
you	O
afraid	O
Emma	B-pers
woud	O
not	O
be	O
If	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
explain	O
all	O
to	O
y	O
satisfaction	O
--	O
I	O
flatter	O
myse	O
lf	O
will	O
think	O
her	O
worthy	O
of	O
every	O
I	O
coud	O
poſsibly	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
yo	O
u	O
comprehend	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
W.H	I-pers
is	O
one	O
and	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Minister	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
another	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
Yrs	O
.	O
very	O
affecly	O
WH	B-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
all	O
your	O
family	O
--	O
Palombo	B-pers
is	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
a	O
Travelling	O
chaise	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
