TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1793	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
much	O
concerned	O
to	O
hear	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
not	O
such	O
,	O
as	O
those	O
who	O
esteem	O
her	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
would	O
wish	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
proper	O
subjection	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
hardly	O
dare	O
to	O
be	O
Nervous	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
therefore	O
remind	O
You	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
adage	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Chesterfield	I-pers
)	O
A	O
Woman	O
a	O
Spaniel	O
&	O
a	O
Walnut	O
Tree	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
they	O
're	O
beat	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
they	O
'll	O
be	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
English	O
Judges	O
,	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Judge	O
Thumb	O
,	O
allows	O
of	O
gentle	O
correction	O
,	O
perhaps	O
a	O
little	O
Hazel	O
Castigation	O
might	O
be	O
as	O
effectual	O
a	O
Prescription	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
may	O
propose	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
œconomical	O
.	O
My	O
poor	O
Wife	O
,	O
dare	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
be	O
Nervous	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
boiled	O
Pig	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
next	O
April	O
,	O
having	O
then	O
been	O
Nine	O
Years	O
married	O
.	O
One	O
gleam	O
of	O
consolation	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
still	O
seems	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
permitted	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
London	B-place
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
agree	O
to	O
allow	O
Me	O
to	O
sit	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
almost	O
wish	O
their	O
Lordships	O
may	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
lose	O
my	O
Election	O
,	O
than	O
my	O
boiled	O
Pig	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
recovered	O
at	O
some	O
future	O
period	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
never	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
patience	O
with	O
You	O
for	O
selling	O
Taxal	B-place
.	O
Such	O
a	O
Manoeuvre	O
is	O
directly	O
in	O
opposition	O
to	O
every	O
principle	O
of	O
Liberty	O
&	O
Equality	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
right	O
have	O
You	O
to	O
better	O
your	O
Income	O
,	O
when	O
mine	O
grows	O
worse	O
every	O
day	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
really	O
unpardonable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
hate	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
doubt	O
,	O
of	O
its	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Scheme	O
of	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
originated	O
with	O
Yourself	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
every	O
sensible	O
Man	O
knows	O
,	O
that	O
Money	O
is	O
the	O
Root	O
of	O
all	O
Evil	O
.	O
I	O
presume	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Sense	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
your	O
Rib	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
hesitate	O
to	O
declare	O
my	O
abhorrence	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
wearers	O
of	O
Blue	O
Stockings	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
adorn	O
my	O
Limbs	O
with	O
white	O
Cotton	O
,	O
manufactured	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
Village	O
.	O
Having	O
now	O
covered	O
two	O
Pages	O
with	O
Nonsense	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
read	O
over	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
blushing	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
would	O
give	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
more	O
real	O
pleasure	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
secure	O
You	O
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
at	O
our	O
Farm	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
really	O
hope	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
very	O
long	O
delay	O
giving	O
us	O
that	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
The	O
Mothers	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
Vanity	O
,	O
comparing	O
the	O
Accomplishments	O
of	O
their	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
You	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
may	O
entertain	O
ourselves	O
laughing	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
very	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Yours	O
very	O
faithfully	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
forgive	O
You	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
like	O
the	O
Witches	O
,	O
your	O
petition	O
is	O
written	O
backwards	O
.	O
My	O
worthy	O
Mate	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
Greek	O
&	O
was	O
astounded	O
with	O
your	O
Learning	O
,	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
.	O
Be	O
good	O
,	O
get	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
come	O
to	O
Us	O
soon	O
.	O
But	O
remember	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
teach	O
my	O
Wife	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
naughty	O
tricks	O
.	O
She	O
proposes	O
,	O
submitting	O
to	O
a	O
temporary	O
confinement	O
,	O
next	O
July	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
very	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
Twenty	O
Second	O
Janry-	O
1793	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr=	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel-le	B-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
by	O
Carlisle	B-place
Napier	B-pers
