TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
Oct	O
r	O
-	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
London	B-place
Plan	O
arranged	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
most	O
happy	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
civilities	O
to	O
You	O
in	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
surprised	O
that	O
You	O
should	O
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
that	O
Situation	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
attractive	O
Charms	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Wimpole	O
Street	O
,	O
will	O
certainly	O
carry	O
off	O
Your	O
Husband	O
from	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
Yesterday	O
from	O
celebrating	O
the	O
Jubilee	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Instant	O
at	O
Selkirk	B-place
.	O
The	O
day	O
was	O
made	O
doubly	O
interesting	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
Son	O
Lieutenant	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
contriving	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
there	O
from	O
London	B-place
.	O
He	O
has	O
just	O
got	O
his	O
promotion	O
from	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
added	O
to	O
his	O
Dignities	O
by	O
making	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Deputy	O
Lieutenants	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
him	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
whacking	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Riots	O
,	O
appears	O
well	O
calculated	O
to	O
thrash	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Idea	O
of	O
meeting	O
him	O
at	O
Selkirk	B-place
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
,	O
he	O
croſsed	O
over	O
from	O
Newcastle	B-place
,	O
to	O
meet	O
and	O
afforded	O
me	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
introducing	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
23	O
,	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
After	O
remaining	O
here	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
again	O
get	O
afloat	O
.	O
His	O
Mother	O
&	O
c	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
They	O
still	O
stare	O
at	O
his	O
size	O
.	O
As	O
He	O
is	O
just	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
&	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
neither	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
composure	O
enough	O
to	O
write	O
more	O
.	O
Best	O
love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
live	O
here	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
old	O
Blue	O
Stocking	O
Ladies	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
,	O
wished	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
is	O
not	O
the	O
Notorious	O
Waddington	B-pers
of	O
Hop	O
Celebrity	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
You	O
can	O
tell	O
me	O
?	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Seventh	O
October	O
1809	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
