TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
July	O
ye	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
——	I-pers
The	O
Letters	O
arrived	O
here	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
packet	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
yours	O
of	O
June	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
reach	O
'd	O
me	O
no	O
sooner	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
June	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
of	O
July	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
sooner	O
acknowledged	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
's	O
2	O
delightful	O
ones	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
deliver	O
the	O
enclosed	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
feel	O
her	O
kindneſs	O
in	O
writing	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
post	O
thank	O
my	O
dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
for	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
myself	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
inclosed	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Land	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
received	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
Surprized	O
and	O
pleas	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
s	O
Appearance	O
in	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Ball	O
on	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
particular	O
in	O
your	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Dreſs	O
Looks	O
and	O
Manner	O
on	O
the	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Universal	O
Approbation	O
and	O
Admiration	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
amends	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
ill	O
fortune	O
in	O
being	O
absent	O
on	O
so	O
Interesting	O
an	O
Occasion	O
pray	O
make	O
my	O
Affecate	O
.	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
nothing	O
hinder	O
'd	O
you	O
from	O
being	O
an	O
Eye	O
Witneſs	O
of	O
it	O
it	O
must	O
give	O
us	O
both	O
such	O
singular	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
feel	O
delighted	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
what	O
pleasure	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
given	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
to	O
see	O
her	O
Acquit	O
herself	O
so	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
answer	O
every	O
wish	O
they	O
could	O
form	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
Day	O
we	O
celebrated	O
here	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
power	O
,	O
carrying	O
our	O
Band	O
of	O
Musick	O
to	O
a	O
Beautiful	O
Wood	O
about	O
5	O
Miles	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
stands	O
on	O
a	O
Lake	O
which	O
we	O
croſs	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
our	O
number	O
of	O
little	O
boats	O
,	O
the	O
Musick	O
accompanying	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Dinner	O
Cold	O
and	O
Hot	O
was	O
served	O
on	O
a	O
stone	O
Table	O
under	O
the	O
Shade	O
of	O
the	O
Trees	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Table	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
an	O
Inscription	O
near	O
it	O
on	O
Stone	O
John	B-pers
4th	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portugal	I-pers
(	O
in	O
whose	O
Person	O
this	O
Crown	O
was	O
restored	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Bragenze	B-place
)	O
dined	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1645	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
Succeſsors	O
John	B-pers
5th	I-pers
.	I-pers
which	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Sons	O
dined	O
here	O
in	O
1714	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Table	O
has	O
Obtain	O
'd	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mesa	O
Real	O
in	O
Portuguese	O
.	O
here	O
we	O
all	O
drank	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
our	O
Royal	O
Family	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accompanied	O
with	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Viva	O
's	O
from	O
our	O
Guests	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
as	O
many	O
English	O
and	O
Portuguese	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
aſsemble	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Scene	O
was	O
beautiful	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
concluded	O
with	O
a	O
Universal	O
dancing	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
could	O
attempt	O
it	O
.	O
Poor	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
could	O
not	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
determin	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
on	O
a	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
anxious	O
to	O
celebrate	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
as	O
Spectators	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
but	O
am	O
still	O
every	O
moment	O
expecting	O
her	O
from	O
Porto	B-place
.	O
Your	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
situation	O
and	O
Disposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
pleas	O
'd	O
me	O
vastly	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
and	O
am	O
glad	O
Madlle-	B-pers
Moula	I-pers
is	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
Looks	O
and	O
Spirits	O
.	O
I	O
form	O
every	O
day	O
stronger	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
by	O
some	O
good	O
Opportunity	O
that	O
shall	O
offer	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
where	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
is	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
begin	O
the	O
Baths	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
now	O
think	O
him	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
venture	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
certainly	O
mended	O
lately	O
in	O
that	O
respect	O
;	O
but	O
is	O
still	O
subject	O
to	O
the	O
swelling	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
free	O
from	O
Pains	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
happier	O
than	O
by	O
writing	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Hart	B-pers
.	I-pers
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
most	O
Affectly	O
.	O
and	O
sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
C.	I-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
F——	I-pers
