TOKEN	NE
4	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
20	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
1802	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Had	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
lived	O
,	O
poſsibly	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
sent	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
Name	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
really	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
leisure	O
to	O
hunt	O
out	O
Dutcheſses	O
,	O
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
obeying	O
your	O
Commands	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
for	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
's	O
death	O
,	O
because	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Valuable	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
visited	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
married	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
,	O
no	O
longer	O
lives	O
in	O
South	O
Audley	O
Street	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
sold	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
to	O
Wimpole	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
fatigue	O
her	O
with	O
Visits	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Definitive	O
Treaty	O
is	O
arrived	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leveé	O
tomorrow	O
has	O
been	O
announced	O
in	O
this	O
Evening	O
's	O
Gazette	O
.	O
As	O
an	O
old	O
Courtier	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
know	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
hold	O
one	O
in	O
this	O
holiday	O
Week	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
likewise	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
the	O
Official	O
Notification	O
of	O
my	O
new	O
Dignity	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
arrives	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
shall	O
kiſs	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
Leveé	O
.	O
Next	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
go	O
North	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
my	O
Miſs	O
will	O
return	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayors	O
Ball	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
three	O
hours	O
on	O
her	O
progreſs	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
Pannel	O
of	O
the	O
Carriage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
shattered	O
to	O
peices	O
.	O
Providentially	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
hurt	O
by	O
the	O
accident	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Wednesday	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
April	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
returned	O
from	O
kiſsing	O
the	O
Royal	O
Paw	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
shall	O
fill	O
up	O
my	O
time	O
till	O
Dinner	O
,	O
in	O
scribbling	O
.	O
Adieu	O
London	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
First	O
April	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
