TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
&	O
highly	O
approve	O
your	O
judicious	O
management	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
troublesome	O
busineſs	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
do	O
credit	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
daughter	O
's	O
memory	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
all	O
her	O
debts	O
may	O
be	O
faithfully	O
discharged	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
explained	O
herself	O
most	O
explicitly	O
to	O
good	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Mann	O
&	O
to	O
Doctor	B-pers
Whalley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
&	O
will	O
agree	O
to	O
everything	O
she	O
may	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
dying	O
requests	O
transmitted	O
to	O
me	O
through	O
Dr.	B-pers
Whalley	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
was	O
not	O
privy	O
to	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
perceive	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
arrangements	O
made	O
with	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
all	O
these	O
I	O
hold	O
most	O
sacred	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
strictly	O
complied	O
with	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
dictated	O
in	O
perfect	O
equity	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
referrd	O
to	O
money	O
absolutely	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
free	O
gift	O
.	O
I	O
regret	O
that	O
I	O
dared	O
not	O
encourage	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
's	O
visit	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
desirous	O
beyond	O
measure	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
meeting	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
invariably	O
approved	O
of	O
her	O
conduct	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
generosity	O
&	O
unwearied	O
affection	O
to	O
my	O
late	O
dear	O
daughter	O
,	O
who	O
conceal	O
'd	O
nothing	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
busineſs	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
premised	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
point	O
neceſsary	O
without	O
which	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
proceed	O
,	O
the	O
acknowledgement	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
£4000	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
portion	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
having	O
aſsented	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
£2111	O
.	O
11	O
15	O
in	O
balance	O
of	O
£6000	O
her	O
portion	O
which	O
depended	O
solely	O
upon	O
my	O
verbal	O
agreement	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
never	O
sign	O
any	O
contract	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
general	O
discharge	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
demands	O
whatever	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
had	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
a	O
different	O
conduct	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
to	O
appeal	O
to	O
my	O
aſsurance	O
generosity	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
absurd	O
harangue	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
marriage	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
deplorable	O
situation	O
,	O
urging	O
me	O
to	O
entitle	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
£2000	O
settled	O
on	O
my	O
daughter	O
&	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
receivd	O
You	O
may	O
believe	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
impudent	O
proposal	O
an	O
absolute	O
negative	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
taking	O
leave	O
,	O
he	O
desird	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
short	O
answer	O
,	O
Sir	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
communicating	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
in	O
person	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
mode	O
preferable	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
propose	O
your	O
busineſ	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
beat	O
over	O
the	O
old	O
ground	O
by	O
an	O
appeal	O
to	O
my	O
generosity	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
retain	O
'd	O
the	O
Annuity	O
I	O
might	O
let	O
him	O
partake	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
put	O
an	O
abrupt	O
conclusion	O
to	O
our	O
conference	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
thought	O
all	O
connexion	O
between	O
us	O
is	O
now	O
totally	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
;	O
for	O
shou	O
'd	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
force	O
a	O
correspondence	O
he	O
will	O
receive	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
his	O
letters	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
replete	O
with	O
impertinence	O
&	O
fallacy	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
obliged	O
humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
June	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
24	O
June	O
1810	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
