TOKEN	NE
Windsor	O
Castle	O
Sund	O
ay	O
Dcr	O
23	O
d	O
My	O
Dea	O
rest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
red	O
your	O
valuable	O
Manuscript	O
yester	O
day	O
Eg	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
on	O
my	O
following	O
all	O
your	O
injunctions	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
Time	O
yet	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pages	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
delighted	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
will	O
one	O
you	O
call	O
my	O
Pet	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
worthy	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
My	O
delayed	O
my	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Portrait	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
Dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
having	O
been	O
seriosly	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
write	O
word	O
She	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constant	O
anxiety	O
She	O
naturally	O
lives	O
in	O
,	O
retards	O
Her	O
Recovery	O
&	O
this	O
added	O
to	O
all	O
Her	O
unremitted	O
attendance	O
upon	O
Her	O
poor	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
which	O
had	O
affected	O
Her	O
Health	O
,	O
yet	O
prevents	O
Her	O
even	O
reading	O
and	O
writing	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
Her	O
ocupations	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
had	O
returned	O
to	O
when	O
this	O
illneſs	O
began	O
--	O
From	O
what	O
I	O
remember	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
Picture	O
is	O
like	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
good	O
bree	O
ding	O
&	O
c	O
was	O
perfect	O
,	O
&	O
great	O
remains	O
of	O
Beauty	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
a	O
Picture	O
drawn	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
Her	O
Death	O
which	O
is	O
charming	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
inclose	O
it	O
your	O
Portrait	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Frank	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
great	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
you	O
shall	O
recive	O
it	O
by	O
some	O
safe	O
conveyance	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
now	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
true	O
Old	O
fashioned	O
Stile	O
&	O
Old	O
fashioned	O
Friendship	O
most	O
sincerly	O
do	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
Compliments	O
of	O
this	O
Bleſsed	O
Season	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
many	O
Happy	O
ones	O
--	O
My	O
Friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gomm	I-pers
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
will	O
be	O
in	O
Town	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
meet	O
often	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
Cousin	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
for	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
The	O
only	O
words	O
we	O
could	O
speak	O
was	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
Chapel	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
left	O
Windsor	B-place
very	O
soon	O
after	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Ever	O
Your	O
Affly	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
you	O
find	O
my	O
Hand	O
writing	O
improved	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
