TOKEN	NE
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
formal	O
Note	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
your	O
obliging	O
Invitation	O
for	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
July	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
accept	O
,	O
as	O
next	O
Thursday	O
Jy	O
5	O
th	O
,	O
We	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
answer	O
also	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gomm	I-pers
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
who	O
desire	O
their	O
kind	O
Comps	O
)	O
go	O
to	O
Place	O
to	O
spend	O
some	O
Days	O
with	O
Him	O
&	O
his	O
Sister	O
before	O
Her	O
Wedding	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Malmesbury	I-pers
's	O
Park	O
Place	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
returned	O
by	O
Jy	O
11	O
th	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
when	O
we	O
do	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
long	O
illneſs	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
bishop	O
es	O
have	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
have	O
prevented	O
our	O
doing	O
in	O
so	O
in	O
comfort	O
I	O
was	O
sory	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
&	O
equally	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yours	O
Affly	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
Hill	O
Street	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
20	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
--	O
