TOKEN	NE
June	O
27	O
--	O
89	O
--	O
Bath	B-place
The	O
party	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
invited	O
consisted	O
only	O
of	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
--	O
sister	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
--	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
sickly	O
,	O
peevish	O
resemblance	O
--	O
the	O
Air	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
walk	O
to	O
Lincom	B-place
&	O
the	O
Strawberry	O
eating	O
was	O
deferred	O
--	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
and	O
parted	O
--	O
28	O
.	O
yesterday	O
I	O
sent	O
off	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
take	O
Castor	O
Oil	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
was	O
prevented	O
from	O
joining	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
stayed	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
and	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
left	O
so	O
agreeable	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
uncommon	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
extreme	O
reluctanc	O
e	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
recieved	O
a	O
general	O
invitation	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
shewed	O
us	O
several	O
beautiful	O
drawings	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
's	O
who	O
has	O
taught	O
the	O
young	O
Ladies	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
school	O
for	O
9	O
Years	O
--	O
He	O
was	O
originally	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
naturally	O
a	O
turn	O
for	O
drawing	O
upon	O
receiving	O
proper	O
encouragement	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
he	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
prefer	O
drawing	O
Veſsels	O
to	O
navigating	O
them	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
--	O
where	O
his	O
genius	O
will	O
now	O
doubt	O
be	O
rewarded	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
shewed	O
a	O
drawing	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
which	O
She	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
return	O
for	O
several	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
humblest	O
of	O
human	O
beings	O
--	O
,	O
”	O
that	O
,	O
“	O
he	O
will	O
take	O
one	O
of	O
Smith	B-pers
s	O
drawings	O
&	O
copy	O
it	O
with	O
infinite	O
pleasure	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
in	O
her	O
Opinion	O
he	O
far	O
excells	O
him	O
”	O
,	O
--	O
She	O
read	O
us	O
two	O
very	O
sensible	O
letters	O
from	O
the	O
younger	O
Cox	B-pers
who	O
is	O
commenced	O
a	O
Travelling	O
Tutor	O
&	O
i	O
s	O
now	O
abroad	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
--	O
he	O
describ	O
ed	O
a	O
canton	O
in	O
Swiſserland	B-place
where	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
liberty	O
&	O
harmony	O
reigns	O
amongst	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
.	O
The	O
greatest	O
simplicity	O
of	O
dreſs	O
&	O
manners	O
--	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
feast	O
held	O
under	O
the	O
Shade	O
of	O
an	O
immense	O
tree	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
musick	O
&	O
dancing	O
--	O
the	O
fiddle	O
is	O
not	O
used	O
there	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
musick	O
was	O
so	O
plaintive	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
powerful	O
Effect	O
both	O
upon	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
pupil	O
--	O
from	O
wch	O
,	O
he	O
concluded	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
affect	O
the	O
Natives	O
still	O
more	O
;	O
which	O
no	O
doubt	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
the	O
Swiſs	O
are	O
never	O
allowed	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
ab	O
sent	O
from	O
their	O
own	O
country	O
)	O
to	O
tune	O
their	O
native	O
strains	O
--	O
lest	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
kindle	O
that	O
amor	O
patriae	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
wonderful	O
power	O
over	O
their	O
minds	O
--	O
he	O
related	O
a	O
story	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
--	O
A	O
woman	O
of	O
fortune	O
in	O
the	O
Canton	B-place
of	I-place
Berne	I-place
at	O
ye	O
age	O
of	O
76	O
having	O
conceived	O
a	O
maternal	O
affection	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
wishing	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
her	O
fortune	O
,	O
married	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
allowed	O
no	O
other	O
connection	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
beautiful	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
whom	O
She	O
knew	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
attached	O
--	O
upon	O
a	O
solemn	O
promise	O
being	O
mutually	O
given	O
between	O
this	O
young	O
couple	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
lawfully	O
married	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
She	O
died	O
--	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
as	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
&	O
bore	O
him	O
4	O
Children	O
--	O
the	O
extreme	O
felicity	O
of	O
this	O
family	O
was	O
interrupted	O
by	O
malice	O
or	O
envy	O
&	O
totally	O
destroyed	O
by	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Instance	O
of	O
Tyranny	O
in	O
the	O
magistrates	O
of	O
(	O
what	O
is	O
extolled	O
as	O
)	O
a	O
free	O
State	O
--	O
The	O
Man	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
connection	O
was	O
compelled	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
Love	O
which	O
was	O
almost	O
the	O
immediate	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
--	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
destroyed	O
himself	O
--	O
The	O
good	O
old	O
Woman	O
died	O
shortly	O
from	O
exceſsive	O
grief	O
&	O
despair	O
and	O
The	O
poor	O
little	O
orphans	O
of	O
this	O
illfated	O
connection	O
were	O
reduced	O
to	O
Beggary	O
==	O
last	O
night	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
sharp	O
frost	O
with	O
Hail	O
Storms	O
--	O
to	O
day	O
it	O
has	O
snowed	O
twice	O
--	O
29	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
drawing	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
by	O
Sir	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
really	O
a	O
treat	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
any	O
Master	O
's	O
yt	O
pleased	O
me	O
more	O
--	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
the	O
dear	O
Object	O
of	O
my	O
Love	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
votre	O
mari	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
nervous	O
lately	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
felt	O
so	O
uncomfortable	O
at	O
being	O
separated	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
You	O
are	O
every	O
instant	O
before	O
my	O
Eyes	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
for	O
you	O
every	O
moment	O
&	O
am	O
really	O
unhappy	O
to	O
be	O
without	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
Nothing	O
will	O
ever	O
happen	O
to	O
remove	O
me	O
again	O
to	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
dear	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
advantages	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
derive	O
from	O
my	O
sejour	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
will	O
compensate	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
my	O
Absence	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
u	O
p	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
--	O
at	O
6	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
's	O
&	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
(	O
She	O
goes	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Sandleford	B-place
)	O
--	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vanbrugh	I-pers
,	O
all	O
alive	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Meynell	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
,	O
who	O
reproached	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
havg	O
called	O
upon	O
them	O
--	O
The	O
younger	O
Mr.	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sweet	O
creature	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
younger	O
Brother	O
&	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
Card	O
players	O
who	O
's	O
names	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
glymse	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
likneſs	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veſsie	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
friendly	O
invitation	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
quite	O
en	O
famille	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
She	O
loves	O
reasonable	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
great	O
curiosities	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
&	O
begs	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
t	O
w	O
o	O
ago	O
he	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Gloucester	B-place
Cathedrall	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
dismal	O
sight	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
low	O
lands	O
in	O
that	O
Country	O
&	O
in	O
Worcestershire	B-place
deluged	O
with	O
Water	O
to	O
an	O
amazing	O
extent	O
--	O
one	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Tewksbury	B-place
has	O
had	O
a	O
1000£	O
worth	O
of	O
Hay	O
destroyed	O
&	O
the	O
loſs	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
country	O
will	O
be	O
immense	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
came	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
home	O
&	O
then	O
ing	O
Miſs	B-pers
took	O
my	O
Arm	O
&	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
's	O
where	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
sup	O
--	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
enquiries	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
--	O
She	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
paſsage	O
with	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Acct	O
.	O
indeed	O
--	O
“	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
by	O
the	O
last	O
Acct	O
.	O
was	O
speechleſs	O
&	O
the	O
faculty	O
had	O
pronounced	O
that	O
her	O
death	O
must	O
happen	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
”	O
--	O
This	O
I	O
fear	O
will	O
overset	O
our	O
Friend	O
/	O
--	O
30	O
--	O
After	O
my	O
Leſsons	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
infamous	O
paper	O
The	O
Herald	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
scandalous	O
allusion	O
to	O
our	B-pers
worthy	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
under	O
the	O
title	O
of	O
Insanity	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
paragraph	O
mentioned	O
that	O
Marchesi	B-pers
had	O
been	O
uncommonly	O
noticed	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
wonderful	O
what	O
means	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
gain	O
such	O
influence	O
over	O
the	O
fair	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
S.	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
afternoon	O
--	O
about	O
5	O
OClock	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
She	O
had	O
just	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
whh-	O
wd	O
.	O
hasten	O
her	O
departure	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
&	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
suspecting	O
what	O
was	O
really	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
services	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
posted	O
away	O
directly	O
&	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
things	O
about	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
giving	O
every	O
aſsistance	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
could	O
not	O
stay	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
most	O
of	O
Sally	B-pers
's	O
Matters	O
--	O
This	O
diverted	O
me	O
exceſsively	O
,	O
for	O
Sally	B-pers
's	O
Maid	O
is	O
a	O
stiff	O
Methodist	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
thoug	O
ht	O
it	O
an	O
Abomination	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
shd	O
.	O
to	O
uch	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Womans	O
dreſs	O
I	O
repeatedly	O
called	O
for	O
her	O
Smickets	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
hardly	O
create	O
a	O
smile	O
Sally	B-pers
was	O
pleased	O
as	O
neither	O
She	O
or	O
her	O
maid	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
half	O
the	O
Clothes	O
into	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
moment	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
cram	O
their	O
odd	O
matters	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
cd	O
.	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
her	O
Laces	O
&	O
best	O
things	O
properly	O
--	O
like	O
a	O
great	O
Simpleton	O
She	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
but	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
bank	O
bills	O
--	O
which	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
her	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Banks	O
were	O
shut	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
change	O
for	O
two	O
&	O
with	O
some	O
trouble	O
got	O
the	O
rest	O
converted	O
into	O
Cash	O
--	O
thō	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
She	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
securing	O
places	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
running	O
about	O
for	O
this	O
crazy	O
Creature	O
and	O
was	O
quite	O
tired	O
July	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wake	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
,	O
for	O
thō	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
Sally	B-pers
was	O
off	O
about	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
t	O
o	O
the	O
Inn	O
--	O
which	O
vexed	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
She	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
Ingles	B-pers
called	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
at	O
one	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
&	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
The	O
town	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
bathed	O
last	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
corporation	O
Baths	O
which	O
are	O
very	O
pleasant	O
.	O
thō	O
more	O
expensive	O
for	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
too	O
cold	O
to	O
bathe	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
immediately	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
profuse	O
perspiration	O
came	O
on	O
wh	O
.	O
continued	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
encouraged	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
pains	O
in	O
my	O
limbs	O
since	O
the	O
former	O
bathing	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
attribute	O
to	O
the	O
coldneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Atmosphere	O
at	O
that	O
tim	O
e	O
I	O
din	O
ed	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
's	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
Lady	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
flights	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Sweden	B-place
.	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
afternoon	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bolingbroke	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
half	O
Sister	O
&	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
had	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Norwich	B-place
--	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Milnes	B-pers
's	O
at	O
8	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Ingles	B-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
stayed	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
with	O
a	O
Lady	O
to	O
a	O
Cardparty	O
--	O
/	O
2	O
.	O
/	O
This	O
morng	O
Ingles	B-pers
called	O
upon	O
me	O
by	O
Appointment	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
walked	O
round	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
New	O
Buildings	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
it	O
made	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
proposals	O
of	O
Excursions	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
stated	O
objections	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
consented	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
where	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
against	O
the	O
grain	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lose	O
a	O
Leſson	O
upon	O
the	O
Violincello	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
regret	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
'm	O
anxious	O
to	O
get	O
all	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
more	O
difficulties	O
on	O
that	O
instrument	O
than	O
on	O
a	O
piano	O
forte	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
momentary	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
Ingles	B-pers
&	O
am	O
writing	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
send	O
this	O
off	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
ridiculous	O
Idea	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
(	O
whose	O
ideas	O
of	O
things	O
differ	O
from	O
ours	O
upon	O
most	O
subjects	O
)	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
proposal	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
trip	O
into	O
Lancashire	B-place
whilst	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
--	O
to	O
this	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
had	O
insuperable	O
Objections	O
,	O
which	O
still	O
remain	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
Body	O
compliments	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Improvement	O
of	O
my	O
Looks	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
lucky	O
that	O
Bath	B-place
is	O
so	O
thin	O
of	O
Company	O
or	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
make	O
sad	O
Havoc	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
Hearts	O
as	O
my	O
Beauty	O
would	O
be	O
irresistable	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
in	O
charming	O
Spirits	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
Write	O
to	O
me	O
my	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
soon	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'm	O
impatient	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
of	O
f	O
you	O
.	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Isaac	B-pers
is	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Ingles	B-pers
--	O
hang	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
go.	O
,	O
adieu	O
,	O
adieu	O
a	O
thousand	O
good	O
wishes	O
attend	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Affy	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
J.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
2	O
d	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
tolerable	O
fine	O
day	O
--	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
rain	O
yesterday	O
Adieu	O
--	O
God	O
bless	O
my	O
Love	O
&	O
our	O
dear	O
li	O
t	O
tle	O
Darling	O
--	O
Kiſses	O
100.	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
from	O
Papa	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
Post	O
.	O
