TOKEN	NE
¼	O
to	O
5	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
for	O
one	O
moment	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Dockyard	O
--	O
&	O
Mount	O
Edcumbe	O
&	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
b	O
m	O
ust	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Commiſsioner	O
's	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
me	O
wth	O
great	O
Civility	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
did	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Edgcumbe	I-pers
I	O
have	O
not	O
sat	O
down	O
before	O
since	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
No	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
today	O
Encore	O
Adieu	O
JD	B-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
J.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
from	O
Oakford	B-place
to	O
his	O
wife	O
