TOKEN	NE
Naples	B-place
Augt	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1785	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
a	O
Tour	O
of	O
the	O
Islands	B-place
of	I-place
Ischia	I-place
,	O
Ventotiene	B-place
,	O
Ponza	B-place
,	O
Palmarole	B-place
Zanone	B-place
&	O
c	O
all	O
Volcanick	O
,	O
and	O
Ponza	B-place
is	O
so	O
curious	O
as	O
to	O
furnish	O
matter	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
R	O
.	O
Society	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
lay	O
aside	O
the	O
idleneſs	O
which	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
fasten	O
upon	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
bewitching	O
Climate	O
Otiosa	O
Napoli	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
its	O
Epithet	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
sincerely	O
congratulate	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
Marriage	O
I	O
have	O
such	O
an	O
opinion	O
of	O
your	O
judgements	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
merit	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
not	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
him	O
pray	O
tell	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
moment	O
hi	O
of	O
His	O
marriage	O
I	O
am	O
become	O
his	O
humble	O
Servant	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
when	O
an	O
opportunity	O
shall	O
offer	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
lucky	O
Man	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
swear	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Women	O
on	O
Earth	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
one	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
woud	O
make	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
wife	O
as	O
yourself	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
your	O
Uncle	O
I	O
shoud	O
have	O
been	O
apt	O
to	O
have	O
proposed	O
to	O
you	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
little	O
too	O
old	O
.	O
You	O
joke	O
about	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
propose	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
did	O
&	O
answerd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
determined	O
never	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
State	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
fair	O
enough	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
seemd	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
many	O
domestick	O
qualities	O
&	O
her	O
taste	O
for	O
musick	O
was	O
so	O
perfect	O
&	O
my	O
present	O
Situation	O
so	O
desolate	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
willing	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
what	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
world	O
wou	O
'd	O
call	O
a	O
folly	O
--	O
however	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
best	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
W	O
hen	O
the	O
Court	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
their	O
Sicilian	O
Majesties	O
but	O
now	O
They	O
are	O
absent	O
I	O
paſs	O
my	O
time	O
rather	O
dully	O
--	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
a	O
home	O
without	O
a	O
bosom	O
friend	O
&	O
Companion	O
?	O
My	O
Books	O
,	O
pictures	O
--	O
musick	O
,	O
prospect	O
are	O
certainly	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Soul	O
to	O
all	O
is	O
wanting	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Your	O
most	O
affecly	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
via	O
Mantua	B-place
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
No	O
27	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Chesterfield	B-place
Taxal	B-place
Daschau	O
Daeskeu	O
