TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
25	O
th	O
:	O
Janry-	O
1784	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
once	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
'till	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
next	O
June	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
beleive	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
altered	O
my	O
resolution	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
severe	O
cold	O
confined	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Tired	O
therefore	O
of	O
reading	O
,	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
You	O
merely	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
falling	O
asleep	O
.	O
My	O
letter	O
perhaps	O
may	O
bring	O
on	O
You	O
that	O
Inclination	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
drive	O
from	O
myself	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
ill	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
at	O
present	O
is	O
extremely	O
Cold	O
,	O
hard	O
frost	O
&	O
snow	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
feet	O
wet	O
which	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
a	O
Sore	O
throat	O
&	O
Toothach	O
.	O
Loyalty	O
to	O
my	O
Royal	O
Mistreſs	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
Aſsembly	O
on	O
her	O
birthday	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
increased	O
my	O
complaints	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
prudently	O
confined	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
church	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
To	O
punish	O
You	O
for	O
your	O
saucineſs	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
copy	O
one	O
single	O
Sheet	O
of	O
my	O
Journal	O
to	O
the	O
Highlands	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
treated	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
on	O
that	O
subject	O
with	O
the	O
attention	O
it	O
merited	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
induced	O
to	O
expose	O
my	O
remarks	O
even	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Blue	O
Stocking	O
Tribe	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
remarked	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
perfect	O
Indigo	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
confeſses	O
to	O
have	O
sojourned	O
with	O
the	O
Empreſs	O
of	O
Shells	O
&	O
Mother	O
Delany	B-pers
for	O
a	O
long	O
period	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
.	O
Now	O
Madam	O
as	O
to	O
your	O
Quarterly	O
Communications	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
follow	O
your	O
own	O
inclination	O
.	O
If	O
writing	O
pleases	O
You	O
,	O
Write	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
contrary	O
is	O
agreable	O
,	O
tant	O
mieux	O
,	O
the	O
leſs	O
trouble	O
shall	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
answering	O
your	O
letters	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
convinced	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
indifferent	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
being	O
thoroughly	O
satisfied	O
that	O
Friendship	O
is	O
a	O
mere	O
word	O
without	O
any	O
meaning	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Every	O
body	O
makes	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
body	O
would	O
wish	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
beleive	O
that	O
they	O
really	O
felt	O
that	O
Quality	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Song	O
“	O
Friendship	O
for	O
Interest	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
Name	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Country	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
Politicians	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
avowed	O
Reprobater	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
's	O
East	O
India	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
wishing	O
for	O
a	O
Diſsolution	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
event	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
considerable	O
changes	O
among	O
st	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Peers	O
&	O
Commoners	O
.	O
Seven	O
new	O
Candidates	O
for	O
the	O
Honour	O
of	O
representing	O
the	O
Peerage	O
have	O
already	O
declared	O
themselves	O
,	O
Viz	O
--	O
The	O
Earls	O
of	O
Murray	B-pers
,	O
Balcarres	B-pers
,	O
Kellie	B-pers
Dumfries	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Hopetoun	B-pers
,	O
Lords	B-pers
Cranstoun	I-pers
&	O
Kinnaird	B-pers
--	O
Whether	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
expects	O
to	O
be	O
turned	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
however	O
been	O
particularly	O
attentive	O
to	O
strengthen	O
his	O
Interest	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
but	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
Letters	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
likewise	O
begging	O
my	O
Vote	O
&	O
Interest	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Many	O
people	O
would	O
have	O
refused	O
their	O
request	O
considering	O
the	O
style	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
behaved	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
His	O
Grace	O
,	O
His	O
Lordship	O
&	O
Her	O
Ladyship	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
support	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
whether	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
feel	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
however	O
thought	O
it	O
expedient	O
to	O
thank	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Civility	O
,	O
mais	O
je	O
les	O
meprise	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Be	O
a	O
good	O
Girl	O
&	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
take	O
you	O
into	O
favour	O
again	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
Affece	O
.	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
My	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
I	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pulteney	I-pers
has	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Convent	O
--	O
