TOKEN	NE
daughter	O
of	O
Rev	B-pers
Fredk	I-pers
Jane	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
afterwards	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
Portman	O
Square	O
London	B-place
.	O
December	O
27	O
th	O
:	O
-	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
begin	O
to	O
suspect	O
me	O
of	O
having	O
forgotten	O
my	O
Promise	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
deferr	O
'd	O
it	O
purposely	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
got	O
into	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
above	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Our	O
unsettled	O
State	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
Excuse	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
more	O
immediately	O
.	O
--	O
Before	O
I	O
proceed	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
many	O
Thanks	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Hare	O
that	O
we	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
however	O
,	O
fancy	O
that	O
it	O
reminded	O
me	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
like	O
this	O
House	O
extremely	O
;	O
its	O
Situation	O
is	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
We	O
inhabit	O
the	O
Parlours	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
Drawing-Room	O
not	O
being	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
quite	O
finish	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
when	O
once	O
we	O
become	O
entirely	O
settled	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
find	O
ourselves	O
as	O
comfortably	O
lodged	O
as	O
ever	O
we	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
little	O
Daughter	O
is	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
understand	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
remarkably	O
clever	O
,	O
and	O
agreeable	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
introducing	O
this	O
little	O
Cousin	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
Chance	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Spring	O
.	O
London	B-place
is	O
very	O
pleasant	O
at	O
that	O
Season	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
but	O
convenient	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
graceleſs	O
Creature	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
without	O
enquiring	O
after	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
old-	O
fashion	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
wish	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
our	O
Names	O
,	O
a	O
merry	O
Christmas	O
,	O
a	O
happy	O
New-Year	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Returns	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
will	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
good	O
Wishes	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
hundred	O
ingenious	O
Devices	O
for	O
making	O
long	O
Christmas	O
Evenings	O
short	O
.	O
You	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
famous	O
Collection	O
of	O
Riddles	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Kind	O
of	O
Purpose	O
,	O
often	O
prove	O
an	O
Aſsistance	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Play	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Busineſs	O
of	O
our	O
moving	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
continue	O
to	O
amuse	O
myself	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
with	O
Music	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Opera	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
entertained	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
Her	O
Daughter	O
is	O
much	O
improved	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
little	O
Girl	O
.	O
The	O
Boys	O
are	O
likewise	O
,	O
grown	O
,	O
and	O
improved	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
remarkably	O
gay	O
Season	O
among	O
the	O
fine	O
People	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
yet	O
--	O
I	O
understand	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
amiable	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Beauty	O
.	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Acquisition	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
Princeſses	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
stand	O
more	O
in	O
Need	O
than	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
young	O
Friend	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
may	O
go	O
into	O
Public	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
may	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
--	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
my	O
long	O
Silence	O
prevent	O
your	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Our	O
best	O
Regards	O
attend	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
truly	O
and	O
affectely	O
:	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
