TOKEN	NE
The	O
Inclosed	O
Lines	O
muſt	O
plead	O
my	O
Excuse	O
for	O
not	O
waiting	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
tomorrow	O
Evening	O
.	O
Underſtanding	O
his	O
Disgrace	O
is	O
no	O
ſecret	O
in	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
better	O
than	O
join	O
in	O
the	O
Laugh	O
againſt	O
himself	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
can	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
receives	O
Letters	O
from	O
Town	B-place
,	O
that	O
will	O
ſhew	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Intention	O
to	O
abſcond	O
from	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
their	O
own	O
advice	O
&	O
concurrence	O
he	O
left	O
London	B-place
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
I	O
am	O
happy	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
ſome	O
good	O
News	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
bad	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
friend	O
s	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
can	O
feel	O
in	O
either	O
.	O
--	O
Peruſe	O
the	O
Inclosed	O
from	O
Amſterdam	B-place
&	O
return	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
ſome	O
conſolation	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
thoſe	O
who	O
know	O
me	O
moſt	O
beſt	O
,	O
as	O
Companions	O
,	O
are	O
more	O
my	O
frie	O
nds	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
Relations	O
.	O
Indeed	O
they	O
know	O
no	O
m	O
little	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
ſpent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
Œconomy	O
comprehends	O
every	O
ſin	O
.	O
--	O
For	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
