TOKEN	NE
1st	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
from	O
Naples	B-place
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
in	O
law	O
Mrs	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
before	O
1771	O
My	O
Dr	O
Sister	O
I	O
have	O
waited	O
long	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
impatience	O
hoping	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
but	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
Vain	O
I	O
can	O
resist	O
no	O
longer	O
&	O
must	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
real	O
Mortification	O
both	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Myself	O
not	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
however	O
this	O
will	O
put	O
you	O
both	O
in	O
Mind	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
Land	O
of	O
the	O
Living	O
&	O
that	O
both	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
have	O
not	O
forgot	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
Attentions	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
be	O
assured	O
we	O
never	O
shall	O
,	O
particularly	O
my	O
self	O
--	O
therefore	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
needleſs	O
to	O
repeat	O
that	O
we	O
beg	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
both	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
health	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
point	O
gain	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Society	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
like	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
procure	O
it	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
contented	O
for	O
while	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Company	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
other	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
disgusted	O
with	O
the	O
Neapolitan	O
Manners	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
we	O
therefore	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
proper	O
Ceremonys	O
of	O
his	O
Situation	O
will	O
permit	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
ever	O
omits	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
offending	O
--	O
our	O
house	O
is	O
very	O
comfortable	O
it	O
is	O
without	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gates	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
&	O
so	O
retird	O
from	O
all	O
noise	O
.	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
fancy	O
ourselves	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Bay	B-place
of	I-place
Naples	I-place
(	O
which	O
is	O
just	O
under	O
our	O
Window	O
)	O
&	O
the	O
Island	O
of	O
Capria	B-place
,	O
in	O
short	O
the	O
Air	O
&	O
Situation	O
is	O
certainly	O
very	O
fine	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
would	O
come	O
&	O
try	O
it	O
--	O
at	O
present	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
diversions	O
going	O
forward	O
except	O
one	O
two	O
little	O
Vile	O
theatres	O
leſs	O
than	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
haymarket	O
where	O
people	O
sit	O
five	O
hours	O
to	O
hear	O
very	O
pretty	O
Musick	O
very	O
ill	O
perform	O
'd	O
&	O
Nonsensical	O
Works	O
acted	O
with	O
the	O
lowest	O
Buffoonery	O
--	O
but	O
such	O
is	O
the	O
Neapolitan	O
taste	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
look	O
upon	O
a	O
good	O
Punchinello	O
as	O
a	O
most	O
Respectable	O
Character	O
,	O
next	O
Monday	O
the	O
great	O
theatre	O
begins	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
large	O
that	O
with	O
difficulty	O
you	O
hea	O
r	O
the	O
Voices	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
altogether	O
in	O
th	O
is	O
Country	O
of	O
Musick	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
li	O
ttle	O
Good	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Churches	O
which	O
is	O
really	O
charming	O
--	O
&	O
Now	O
My	O
Dr	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
will	O
bid	O
you	O
Adieu	O
&	O
only	O
Add	O
Hamilton	B-pers
s	O
&	O
My	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Self	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
your	O
daughter	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
soon	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
Sister	O
Yr	O
Most	O
Affecte	O
&	O
Obligd	O
humble	O
Servt	O
C.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Naples	B-place
Octber	O
.	O
ye	O
29	O
th	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Northampton	B-place
in	O
Inghilterra	B-place
Northamptonshire	B-place
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
