TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
Portman	O
Sqr	O
Dec	O
:	O
17	O
th	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
A	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
must	O
alway	O
increase	O
the	O
joy	O
of	O
a	O
recent	O
happy	O
event	O
,	O
or	O
revive	O
that	O
of	O
of	O
a	O
former	O
one	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
my	O
felicity	O
increased	O
by	O
the	O
part	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
therefore	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
Mrs	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
health	O
is	O
not	O
impaired	O
by	O
the	O
present	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
jolly	O
boy	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
herself	O
,	O
The	O
Parents	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Babe	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Southampton	B-place
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
out	O
of	O
health	O
all	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
advised	O
by	O
his	O
Physician	O
pretty	O
late	O
in	O
ye	O
Autumn	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
Sea	O
bathing	O
,	O
they	O
prudently	O
fixd	O
on	O
Southampton	B-place
as	O
affording	O
a	O
comfort	O
able	O
retreat	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
benefit	O
enough	O
from	O
bathing	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
continue	O
it	O
during	O
that	O
Season	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
at	O
the	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
Parliament	O
much	O
improved	O
in	O
health	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
ye	O
Child	O
at	O
Southampton	B-place
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
trusty	O
Servant	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
returnd	O
thither	O
with	O
a	O
resolution	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
H	O
:	O
of	O
Commons	O
meets	O
after	O
the	O
holy	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
delighted	O
to	O
find	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
unfashionable	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
before	O
XmaſsChristmaſs	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
it	O
best	O
in	O
its	O
demi	O
Saison	O
character	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
neither	O
a	O
Solitude	O
nor	O
a	O
Crowd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
indeed	O
a	O
great	O
mortification	O
at	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
finding	O
my	O
amiable	O
Friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
in	O
a	O
most	O
declining	O
condition	O
.	O
your	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
s	O
humane	O
attentions	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
comfort	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
minds	O
like	O
hers	O
,	O
like	O
Aromatick	O
Herbs	O
,	O
&	O
sweet	O
flowers	O
,	O
even	O
when	O
wither	O
'd	O
&	O
decay	O
'd	O
retain	O
a	O
sweet	O
odour	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
still	O
affectionate	O
to	O
her	O
Friends	O
,	O
&	O
benevolent	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
mental	O
powers	O
are	O
sadly	O
impaired	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
introduced	O
to	O
dear	O
little	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
from	O
every	O
reason	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
amiable	O
.	O
All	O
reports	O
,	O
true	O
,	O
or	O
untrue	O
,	O
are	O
so	O
circulated	O
by	O
the	O
news	O
papers	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
poſsible	O
to	O
send	O
ones	O
Correspondents	O
any	O
news	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
said	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pulteney	I-pers
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Lord	B-pers
Ancram	I-pers
,	O
if	O
Cupid	O
advises	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
even	O
the	O
Goddeſs	O
of	O
Prudence	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Objection	O
to	O
the	O
Union	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
compliments	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
kiſs	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Lady	O
in	O
token	O
of	O
future	O
friendship	O
With	O
perfect	O
esteem	O
I	O
am	O
dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
&	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Eliz	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
