TOKEN	NE
July	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
:	O
1790	O
.	O
Stanton	B-place
.	O
Bury	B-place
St	I-place
:	I-place
Edmund	I-place
's	I-place
Suffolk	B-place
.	I-place
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
Habitation	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
perceive	O
by	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
near	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
with	O
our	O
little	O
Place	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
pleasant	O
either	O
for	O
walking	O
or	O
riding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
very	O
comfortable	O
.	O
We	O
proposing	O
propose	O
staying	O
here	O
till	O
November	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
all	O
our	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Election	O
has	O
much	O
engaged	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
hitherto	O
.	O
That	O
Busineſs	O
is	O
terminated	O
now	O
,	O
however	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Rous	I-pers
and	O
Sir	B-pers
Chas	I-pers
:	I-pers
Bunbury	I-pers
,	O
carried	O
the	O
Election	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
Majority	O
,	O
against	O
Sir	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
Vanneck	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
went	O
to	O
Ipswich	B-place
to	O
vote	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Bunbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
last	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
pretty	O
little	O
Cousin	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
improves	O
daily	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
with	O
his	O
Regiment	O
(	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
:	O
Dragoons	O
--	O
)	O
at	O
Croydon	B-place
.	O
The	O
Fatigue	O
of	O
military	O
Duty	O
disagreed	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
and	O
believe	O
,	O
will	O
find	O
no	O
more	O
Inconvenience	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
were	O
well	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
are	O
quite	O
pleased	O
with	O
this	O
Place	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
makes	O
some	O
Amends	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
disadvantageous	O
Exchange	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
,	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
perilous	O
State	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
vastly	O
better	O
;	O
and	O
Sir	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
says	O
she	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Kemble	I-pers
is	O
now	O
,	O
Proprietor	O
of	O
the	O
Theatre	O
at	O
Liverpool	B-place
;	O
so	O
,	O
Summer	O
brings	O
no	O
Rest	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
goes	O
through	O
all	O
his	O
Occupations	O
very	O
succeſsfully	O
.	O
The	O
Operas	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
over	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
The	O
Number	O
subscribed	O
for	O
,	O
is	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
Gallini	B-pers
has	O
a	O
few	O
Nights	O
exclusive	O
of	O
the	O
Subscription	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
is	O
clear	O
Gain	O
.	O
He	O
really	O
ought	O
to	O
make	O
something	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
last	O
Season	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
profitable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
smallneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Theatre	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
Price	O
he	O
gave	O
Marchesi	B-pers
I	O
fear	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
Marchesi	B-pers
next	O
is	O
engaged	O
at	O
Venice	B-place
.	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
England	B-place
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wish	O
much	O
,	O
to	O
renew	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Have	O
I	O
any	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Season	O
?	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
happy	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
likewise	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Regards	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
remain	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
sincerely	O
&	O
affectionately	O
yours	O
.	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
