TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
August	O
11	O
th	O
1770	O
Though	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
ceases	O
to	O
Answer	O
my	O
Letters	O
&	O
denies	O
me	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Hearing	O
how	O
she	O
her	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
do	O
:	O
yet	O
(	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
miscarriage	O
of	O
yr	O
Letters	O
)	O
I	O
write	O
this	O
to	O
Notiffie	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
them	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
Daughter	O
on	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
July	O
&	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
familly	O
are	O
well	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
has	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
Summer	O
at	O
Litchfield	B-place
with	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
home	O
in	O
Octr	O
:	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
are	O
all	O
much	O
yours	O
--	O
they	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
compts	O
to	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
whose	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
Politeneſs	O
can	O
never	O
be	O
forgot	O
by	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
Affect	O
Cousin	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
The	B-place
Abbey	I-place
Edinburgh	B-place
