TOKEN	NE
Uppingham	B-place
May	O
21	O
st	O
1	O
80	O
2	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
inform	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
Katherine	B-pers
was	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
this	O
morning	O
safely	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
--	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
expectation	O
of	O
herself	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
not	O
I	O
beli	O
eve	O
their	O
wishes	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
quite	O
indifferent	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
or	O
a	O
boy	O
But	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
been	O
prepared	O
for	O
--	O
my	O
sister	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
remarkably	O
el	O
well	O
&	O
they	O
say	O
had	O
an	O
uncommon	O
good	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
is	O
also	O
well	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
this	O
morning	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
--	O
with	O
Kindest	O
remembrance	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Affly	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Excuse	O
great	O
haste	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
other	O
letters	O
to	O
write	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Platt	B-place
nearBedfordshire	I-place
