TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
We	O
are	O
all	O
much	O
obliged	O
by	O
your	O
kind	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
full	O
of	O
Invalids	O
&	O
poor	O
Mr	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
I	O
fear	O
very	O
seriously	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
hear	O
.	O
My	O
Cold	O
is	O
very	O
troublesome	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
unwell	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
little	O
Sophie	B-pers
I	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
high	O
Fever	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
tollerable	O
Night	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
day	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
Seen	O
her	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
make	O
me	O
wish	O
to	O
postpone	O
a	O
little	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Seeing	O
you	O
here	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Juliana	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
who	O
has	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
reserve	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
Evening	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
She	O
sets	O
out	O
for	O
Paris	B-place
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
&	O
remain	O
ever	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Most	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Sunday	O
Morng	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
