TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
When	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
yr	O
.	O
kind	O
Letter	O
at	O
Falmouth	B-place
we	O
were	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
embark	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
wrote	O
from	O
hence	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
spirits	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
happy	O
about	O
both	O
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
my	O
Brother	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
seize	O
this	O
opportunity	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
sensibly	O
I	O
feel	O
your	O
kind	O
participation	O
in	O
our	O
bitter	O
distreſs	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
spirits	O
are	O
exceedingly	O
low	O
but	O
in	O
her	O
health	O
she	O
is	O
certainly	O
mending	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
whenever	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
recovery	O
makes	O
a	O
quicker	O
progreſs	O
than	O
it	O
does	O
at	O
present	O
her	O
cheerfulneſs	O
will	O
return	O
--	O
if	O
lovely	O
views	O
&	O
bright	O
sunshine	O
cd	O
.	O
give	O
them	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
spirits	O
now	O
for	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
both	O
in	O
an	O
elevated	O
pleasant	O
situation	O
just	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
&	O
over	O
look	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
shipping	O
in	O
the	B-place
Tagus	I-place
--	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
shall	O
rather	O
be	O
losers	O
in	O
this	O
respect	O
by	O
removing	O
50	O
Miles	O
up	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
the	O
Caldas	B-place
Baths	I-place
wch	O
.	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
beautifully	O
situated	O
as	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
hardly	O
admit	O
any	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
&	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
flat	O
Country	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
opposite	O
to	O
our	O
situation	O
here	O
where	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
common	O
visit	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
without	O
going	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
hills	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
built	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
are	O
all	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
us	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
easy	O
about	O
our	O
two	O
dear	O
Invalids	O
as	O
to	O
trouble	O
to	O
return	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
England	O
in	O
June	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
writing	O
the	O
whole	O
E	O
.	O
&	O
my	O
hand	O
&	O
Eyes	O
wd	O
.	O
fail	O
me	O
for	O
saying	O
more	O
than	O
this	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sincerely	O
&	O
affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
S.	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
&	O
Sister	O
desire	O
their	O
kind	O
love	O
&	O
compts	O
.	O
Buenos	B-place
Ayres	I-place
April	O
28	O
.	O
1781	O
