TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
take	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
to	O
remind	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
yours	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Dr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
dines	O
at	O
the	O
Club	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
send	O
yr	O
letter	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
keep	O
mine	O
til	O
Tuesday	O
if	O
Hartly	B-pers
does	O
not	O
bring	O
yours	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
Cold	O
is	O
quite	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
I	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
innocent	O
Cause	O
of	O
yr	O
Catching	O
one	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
is	O
by	O
our	O
Servant	O
as	O
G	B-pers
:	I-pers
Grote	I-pers
is	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
continue	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Cart	O
.	O
with	O
so	O
feeble	O
a	O
support	O
as	O
poor	O
old	O
higins	O
--	O
the	O
Coach	O
man	O
is	O
yet	O
an	O
Invalid	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
drive	O
us	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
I	O
hope	O
you	O
&	O
yr	O
charming	O
circle	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
.	O
&	O
if	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
good	O
humour	O
this	O
foggy	O
Weather	O
.	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
sans	O
Pareil	O
I	O
delight	O
in	O
yr	O
Father	O
in	O
Law	O
&	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
in	O
these	O
strange	O
regions	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Heir	O
apparent	O
.	O
we	O
read	O
the	O
Papers	O
&	O
are	O
quite	O
Sanguine	O
.	O
that	O
all	O
is	O
over	O
with	O
France	B-place
&	O
our	O
fears	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
--	O
so	O
adieu	O
.	O
with	O
love	O
from	O
all	O
to	O
all	O
yrs	O
ever	O
affecly	O
DBlosset	B-pers
Novr	O
.	O
12	O
