TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
All	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
certainly	O
go	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
sometime	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Orders	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
so	O
ask	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
hear	O
it	O
from	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
CFinch	B-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
