TOKEN	NE
I	O
am	O
infinitely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
being	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
me	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
present	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
fine	O
Chalk	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
deserving	O
of	O
that	O
precious	O
commodity	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
inflammation	O
in	O
your	O
Eyes	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
perfectly	O
well	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
friends	O
at	O
Bulstrode	B-place
I	O
believe	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Father	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
making	O
a	O
visit	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
is	O
returned	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
yesterday	O
&	O
we	O
got	O
here	O
to	O
dinner	O
to	O
day	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Aunts	O
quite	O
well	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remembered	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
accept	O
my	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
your	O
sincere	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
Kenwood	O
Octr	O
.	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
forget	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
Plants	O
are	O
safely	O
arrived	O
here	O
&	O
are	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
