TOKEN	NE
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
14	O
th	O
-	O
Novr	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
received	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
s	O
Letter	O
,	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
which	O
have	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
surprised	O
me	O
.	O
Whatever	O
your	O
motives	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
prudent	O
ones	O
.	O
The	O
Salary	O
of	O
your	O
Place	O
was	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
a	O
recompence	O
for	O
the	O
Confinement	O
&	O
neceſsary	O
Expences	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
the	O
only	O
inducement	O
I	O
can	O
discover	O
for	O
your	O
remaining	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
was	O
the	O
Gracious	O
attention	O
of	O
your	O
Royal	O
Mistreſs	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
satisfied	O
with	O
your	O
reasons	O
for	O
resigning	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
from	O
riding	O
with	O
my	O
fingers	O
so	O
cold	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
hold	O
my	O
Pen	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
soon	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
but	O
should	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
you	O
leave	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
Now	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
more	O
leisure	O
,	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
often	O
--	O
and	O
beleive	O
your	O
removal	O
from	O
the	O
Ear	O
of	O
a	O
Queen	O
will	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
alteration	O
in	O
the	O
Esteem	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
profeſsed	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
and	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
The	O
Old	O
Lady	O
sends	O
her	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
You	O
--	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
convinced	O
You	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
Court	O
,	O
unleſs	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
.	O
