TOKEN	NE
22	O
Feby	O
1786	O
--	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Letter	O
of	O
this	O
date	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
yr-	O
dear	O
friend	O
added	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
--	O
the	O
Company	O
were	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Watt	I-pers
,	O
Commodore	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
's	O
Birthday	O
--	O
after	O
Tea	O
we	O
played	O
at	O
pope	O
Joan	O
--	O
whenever	O
I	O
speak	O
to	O
yr	O
dear	O
friend	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
her	O
Eyes	O
sparkle	O
and	O
she	O
seems	O
to	O
devour	O
every	O
word	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
happy	O
opportunity	O
of	O
establishing	O
myself	O
in	O
her	O
good	O
opinion	O
,	O
and	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
double	O
satisfaction	O
from	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
--	O
the	O
Evg	O
being	O
very	O
wet	O
Lady	B-pers
C——	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
brot	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
and	O
yr	O
D——	B-pers
home	O
--	O
21	O
st	O
Call	O
'd	O
this	O
morng	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
vastly	O
well	O
--	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
rather	O
low	O
--	O
I	O
stayed	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
seemed	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
an	O
hour	O
an	O
half	O
--	O
several	O
times	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
interrupt	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
writing	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
prevented	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
“	O
must	O
you	O
go	O
--	O
well	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
stay	O
any	O
longer	O
--	O
but	O
do	O
come	O
and	O
breakfast	O
wh-	O
me	O
before	O
you	O
leave	O
town	B-place
”	O
--	O
She	O
looks	O
melancholy	O
--	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
shd-	O
do	O
,	O
were	O
I	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
--	O
She	O
appears	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
some	O
great	O
diſappointment	O
--	O
surely	O
her	O
heart	O
is	O
affected	O
--	O
otherwise	O
,	O
a	O
handsome	O
woman	O
--	O
in	O
ye-	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
poſsest	O
of	O
great	O
resources	O
within	O
herself	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
tolerable	O
State	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
fall	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
world	O
and	O
be	O
really	O
unhappy	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
realy	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
the	O
short	O
Absence	O
of	O
a	O
dear	O
sister	O
,	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
cause	O
for	O
the	O
indulgence	O
of	O
melancholy	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
satisfy	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
sensibility	O
and	O
common	O
affections	O
are	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
whenever	O
she	O
sees	O
a	O
certain	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
enquires	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
lately	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
actually	O
married	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
certain	O
Lady	O
(	O
who	O
entre	O
nous	O
,	O
has	O
wounded	O
her	O
reputation	O
by	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
she	O
knows	O
lives	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
and	O
avowed	O
state	O
of	O
adultery	O
)	O
lately	O
gave	O
a	O
trifling	O
present	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Egremont	I-pers
a	O
souvenir	O
d'amit	O
ié	O
--	O
in	O
Steel	O
ye-	O
same	O
day	O
she	O
gave	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
one	O
in	O
Diamonds	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
Temple	B-place
Bar	I-place
--	O
so	O
I	O
petitioned	O
for	O
a	O
seat	O
--	O
&	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
her	O
busineſs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
s	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
constantly	O
engaged	O
since	O
September	O
in	O
arranging	O
the	O
shells	O
&	O
c	O
under	O
their	O
different	O
claſses	O
and	O
affixing	O
the	O
Linean	O
names	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
arduous	O
work	O
--	O
every	O
Claſs	O
is	O
a	O
separate	O
Lot	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Levers	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
vase	O
and	O
Jupiter	O
Serapis	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
wch	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
a	O
1000	O
Guineas	O
--	O
the	O
pictures	O
and	O
many	O
valuable	O
things	O
are	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
melancholy	O
sight	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
thō	O
a	O
beautiful	O
one	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
looks	O
vastly	O
well	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
we	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
fever	O
or	O
some	O
severe	O
illneſs	O
--	O
I	O
either	O
heard	O
it	O
or	O
dreamt	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
Catalogues	O
are	O
5	O
Shillings	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
croſs	O
'd	O
thrō	O
the	O
horse	O
guards	O
and	O
the	O
park	O
to	O
ye-	O
Queens	O
house	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
received	O
me	O
very	O
graciously	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
speeches	O
yo	O
.	O
desired	O
abt	O
.	O
P.	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
she	O
said	O
She	O
wd-	O
inform	O
her	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
made	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
after	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
P.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
remembered	O
you	O
wth	O
great	O
affection	O
wch	O
I	O
allowed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
fair	O
paſsage	O
thrō	O
the	O
opposite	O
Ear	O
,	O
recollecting	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
--	O
after	O
staying	O
20	O
minutes	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
her	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
sending	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
--	O
She	O
wd	O
.	O
talk	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
P	O
.	O
who	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
positive	O
,	O
is	O
married	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
your	O
dear	O
letter	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
lay	O
upon	O
my	O
table	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
that	O
my	O
poor	O
fingers	O
cd	O
.	O
hardly	O
hold	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
add	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
mine	O
more	O
welcome	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
in	O
hight	O
spirits	O
and	O
like	O
herself	O
--	O
she	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Nanny	B-pers
tomorrow	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
H——	I-pers
is	O
weak	O
yet	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
not	O
exert	O
herself	O
too	O
much	O
--	O
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
home	O
--	O
22	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
sally	O
forth	O
--	O
Andrew	B-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
he	O
begins	O
to	O
grumble	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ansr-	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
cd	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
just	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
who	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
then	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murrays	I-pers
were	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
Ld	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
--	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
doing	O
myself	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
waiting	O
upon	O
them	O
this	O
morning	O
after	O
paying	O
my	O
Respects	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
they	O
desired	O
their	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
return	O
in	O
the	O
Evg	O
--	O
I	O
croſsed	O
the	O
park	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
s	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
who	O
desired	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
is	O
vastly	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
Toy	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newport	O
Street	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Chalk	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
this	O
plan	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
--	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
likely	O
person	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
procure	O
the	O
best	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Sir	B-pers
Jos	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
ill	O
of	O
ye-	O
Rhumatism	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
looks	O
very	O
pretty	O
&	O
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
angry	O
that	O
you	O
dont	O
come	O
to	O
town	B-place
--	O
she	O
says	O
Husbands	O
are	O
alike	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
's	O
pictures	O
--	O
Dr-	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Stratford	O
place	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
recd	O
me	O
very	O
graciously	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Clarendon	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
were	O
there	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
beautiful	O
drawing	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
are	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Marlborough	I-pers
's	O
Gems	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
vastly	O
well	O
executed	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
suspect	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
has	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
concerned	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Macartney	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honor	O
to	O
his	O
Country	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
proved	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
fine	O
prints	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wals	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
collected	O
--	O
She	O
desired	O
her	O
Comps	O
.	O
and	O
wished	O
you	O
cd	O
.	O
see	O
those	O
prints	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Wimpole	O
Street	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
at	O
home	O
She	O
looked	O
beautiful	O
--	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
are	O
arrived	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
hoped	O
the	B-pers
Cathcarts	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
who	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
when	O
I	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
negative	O
,	O
yr	O
sweet	O
Cousin	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
invite	O
him	O
--	O
how	O
kind	O
&	O
obliging	O
are	O
her	O
great	O
attentions	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
She	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
yt-	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
but	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
send	O
it	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
frank	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
immediately	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
&	O
finding	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
sent	O
a	O
cover	O
to	O
him	O
wch	O
.	O
conveys	O
this	O
scrawl	O
to	O
my	O
estimable	O
wife	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Ly	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
who	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
civilly	O
--	O
Clarkes	O
is	O
11	O
£	O
-9	O
s	O
-0	O
--	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
money	O
--	O
give	O
her	O
7	O
Guineas	O
or	O
the	O
whole	O
--	O
our	O
Interest	O
now	O
due	O
is	O
26	O
£	O
-0-0	O
--	O
The	O
first	O
bell	O
is	O
ringing	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Wife	O
continue	O
to	O
Love	O
yr-	O
affct	O
.	O
Husband	O
JDickenson	B-pers
I	O
will	O
anon	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
perhaps	O
I	O
can	O
prevail	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
to	O
write	O
a	O
Line	O
--	O
My	O
Love	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Comp	O
.	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
--	O
Memm	O
:	O
27	O
£	O
Memm	O
:	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
it	O
is	O
27	O
£	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
Eating	O
Parlour	O
Wednesday	O
Afternoon	O
5	O
oclock	O
Your	O
beloved	O
being	O
just	O
arrived	O
here	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
dined	O
,	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
not	O
quite	O
filled	O
up	O
,	O
inviting	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
on	O
this	O
blank	O
Page	O
.	O
The	O
temptation	O
of	O
conversing	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
moments	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
resisted	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
we	O
wish	O
for	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
making	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
dear	O
Vesey	B-pers
's	O
little	O
Table	O
!	O
mais	O
le	O
tems	O
viendra	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
comfort	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
with	O
your	O
Husband	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
grudge	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
knows	O
your	O
value	O
and	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
grudge	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
man	O
who	O
ever	O
wore	O
a	O
head	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
fortune	O
in	O
poſseſsing	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
your	O
absence	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
truly	O
perfidious	O
rival	O
and	O
am	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
supplant	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
heart	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
as	O
fast	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
cruel	O
confinement	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
long	O
evening	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
envited	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
reputation	O
,	O
I	O
discreetly	O
admitted	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
.	O
We	O
