TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
Novr	O
.	O
1801	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
conscience	O
checked	O
,	O
I	O
hasten	O
to	O
relieve	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
repeat	O
the	O
Absolution	O
formerly	O
given	O
You	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
Epistolising	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
known	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bear	O
You	O
no	O
ill	O
will	O
,	O
hatred	O
,	O
or	O
Malice	O
whatever	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
and	O
Yours	O
,	O
are	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
ever	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
high	O
in	O
my	O
gracious	O
favour	O
and	O
esteem	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
same	O
happy	O
distinction	O
,	O
whether	O
You	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
ample	O
,	O
categorical	O
,	O
and	O
sincere	O
Declaration	O
will	O
set	O
your	O
Mind	O
at	O
rest	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
Not	O
having	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
likely	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
prudently	O
determined	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Lords	O
squabble	O
about	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
without	O
personally	O
aſsisting	O
at	O
their	O
deliberations	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
finger	O
in	O
Pye	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
my	O
Proxy	O
to	O
the	O
Magnanimous	O
,	O
Magnificent	O
,	O
and	O
Courtly	O
Baron	B-pers
of	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
expreſses	O
the	O
great	O
sense	O
he	O
entertains	O
of	O
the	O
honour	O
&	O
confidence	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
reposed	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
amiable	O
Style	O
you	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
imagine	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
beating	O
up	O
your	O
Quarters	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
never	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
Archy	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
when	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
plans	O
so	O
constantly	O
deranged	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
must	O
content	O
yourself	O
with	O
the	O
hopes	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Chapter	O
of	O
Accidents	O
may	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
,	O
when	O
you	O
least	O
expect	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
delightful	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
plentiful	O
Crops	O
of	O
Grain	O
,	O
Potatoes	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
reduced	O
our	O
Markets	O
to	O
reasonable	O
terms	O
.	O
This	O
plenty	O
,	O
followed	O
by	O
Peace	O
,	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
everybody	O
here	O
,	O
very	O
happy	O
.	O
The	O
joy	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbouring	O
Village	O
was	O
testified	O
by	O
illuminations	O
&	O
c.	O
If	O
we	O
can	O
but	O
keep	O
Frenchmen	O
,	O
Frenchwomen	O
,	O
&	O
French	O
Principles	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
our	O
own	O
Men	O
&	O
Women	O
out	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
all	O
may	O
go	O
well	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
although	O
I	O
love	O
,	O
and	O
approve	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
much	O
sorrow	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Alien	O
Bill	O
is	O
repealed	O
.	O
The	O
French	O
Princes	O
are	O
to	O
return	O
this	O
Month	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
dull	O
residence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
be	O
any	O
advantage	O
to	O
the	O
Society	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Antigallican	O
,	O
and	O
grow	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
My	O
Seven	O
home	O
Brats	O
have	O
been	O
laid	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Blibes	O
,	O
Water	O
Jags	O
,	O
or	O
Chicken	O
pox	O
,	O
whichever	O
You	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
eldest	O
Girl	O
is	O
still	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
dangerous	O
disorder	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
affected	O
their	O
Spirits	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
bodies	O
are	O
perfect	O
Leopards	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
Lepers	O
)	O
.	O
A	O
cargo	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
this	O
forenoon	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
since	O
their	O
confinement	O
,	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
which	O
seems	O
to	O
transport	O
them	O
mightily	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
Love	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
the	O
fair	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Yours	O
very	O
Affectionately	O
Napier	B-pers
Is	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
married	O
,	O
or	O
dead	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
dont	O
mention	O
her	O
?	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Ninth	O
Novr	O
.	O
1801	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
7	O
”	O
3	O
1	O
”	O
3	O
8	O
”	O
6	O
