TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
have	O
only	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
are	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
bear	O
their	O
Affliction	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
edifying	O
manner	O
.	O
Ill	O
send	O
an	O
ansr	O
:	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
when	O
I	O
return	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
settle	O
nothing	O
now	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
soon	O
--	O
Yrs	O
:	O
sincerely	O
PD	B-pers
Windsor	B-place
Sunday	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1783	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
dr	B-pers
Mrs	I-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
soon	O
after	O
my	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
dreſs	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
Court	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
&	O
She	O
wld	O
.	O
call	O
on	O
Me	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
ye	O
:	O
sweet	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Sophia	I-pers
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
looks	O
charmingly	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
near	O
Piccadilly	B-place
London	B-place
