TOKEN	NE
Cumberland	O
Street	O
Novr	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1798	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
should	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
require	O
reminding	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
heart	O
sufficiently	O
grateful	O
to	O
remember	O
and	O
--	O
ever	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
kind	O
treatment	O
I	O
received	O
during	O
my	O
stay	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
was	O
so	O
anxious	O
for	O
us	O
all	O
to	O
accompany	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
(	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
left	O
us	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
strong	O
mark	O
of	O
inattention	O
in	O
me	O
had	O
I	O
remained	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
indeed	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
have	O
returned	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
that	O
evening	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
our	O
Post	O
goes	O
out	O
--	O
earlier	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
grieved	O
that	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
should	O
have	O
suffered	O
so	O
much	O
after	O
parting	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
her	O
I	O
often	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
happy	O
hours	O
we	O
spent	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
thankful	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
standing	O
my	O
Advocate	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
to	O
plead	O
my	O
own	O
cause	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
from	O
yours	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
befriended	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
surprised	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
did	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
part	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
read	O
her	O
my	O
excuse	O
)	O
she	O
will	O
in	O
future	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
opinion	O
of	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
best	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
and	O
also	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
my	O
reason	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
sooner	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
lose	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
friendship	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
vain	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
's	O
wish	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
left	O
Leighton	B-place
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
disapointed	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
M	O
rs	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Sisters	O
agree	O
with	O
every	O
one	O
that	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
much	O
taller	O
but	O
not	O
fatter	O
.	O
Fanny	B-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
so	O
nearly	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
height	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
rather	O
a	O
dispute	O
whic	O
h	O
is	O
the	O
tallest	O
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
more	O
croſs	O
on	O
Sunday	O
then	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
as	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
unpleasant	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
day	O
interrupted	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
if	O
length	O
of	O
letters	O
are	O
to	O
compensate	O
for	O
my	O
having	O
paſsed	O
so	O
many	O
agreeable	O
months	O
under	O
his	O
roof	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
them	O
long	O
enough	O
.	O
--	O
Fanny	B-pers
is	O
so	O
fearful	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
pretty	O
work-bag	O
which	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
mentioning	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
aſsu	O
re	O
you	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
introduced	O
to	O
all	O
our	O
Friends	O
that	O
have	O
visited	O
us	O
since	O
my	O
return	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
admired	O
,	O
F	B-pers
is	O
making	O
one	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
occurences	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
ten	O
days	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
of	O
much	O
importance	O
)	O
may	O
still	O
be	O
again	O
agreeable	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
I	O
shall	O
communicate	O
them	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sisters	O
&	O
my	O
sisters	O
to	O
ask	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
little	O
else	O
the	O
first	O
--	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
last	O
Week	O
we	O
drank	O
Tea	O
with	O
Col	B-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Treeme	I-pers
in	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
Mr	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
's	O
Wednesday	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
walk	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Thursday	O
Mrs	B-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
spent	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Saturday	O
we	O
paid	O
a	O
morning	O
visit	O
s	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
Monday	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
and	O
her	O
three	O
daughters	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
My	O
Aunt	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
Bromley	B-place
with	O
Katherine	B-pers
where	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Basket	O
of	O
provision	O
you	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bad	O
memory	O
--	O
My	O
Sisters	O
have	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
we	O
are	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
good	O
things	O
it	O
--	O
contained	O
,	O
Fanny	B-pers
feasts	O
on	O
the	O
walnuts	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
does	O
indulge	O
poor	O
Katherine	B-pers
with	O
an	O
onion	O
sometimes	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
seldom	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ka	I-pers
had	O
quite	O
She	O
has	O
at	O
last	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
eat	O
salt	O
with	O
her	O
meat	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
used	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
few	O
patches	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
has	O
promised	O
to	O
collect	O
some	O
more	O
amongst	O
her	O
Friends	O
you	O
may	O
rely	O
on	O
my	O
sending	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
procure	O
them	O
--	O
give	O
my	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
and	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
write	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
letter	O
:	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
not	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
receiving	O
.	O
Fanny	B-pers
unites	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
love	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bate	I-pers
's	I-pers
best	O
regards	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
every	O
sense	O
of	O
gratitude	O
Yrs	O
ever	O
affecy	O
M.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
and	O
all	O
enquiring	O
Friends	O
single	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Norman	O
Jobs	O
&	O
c	O
}	O
1-12:4	O
