TOKEN	NE
Dear	B-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Accept	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
two	O
most	O
obliging	O
letters	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
son	O
has	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
understanding	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
great	O
cunning	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
succeeds	O
in	O
duping	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
disposed	O
to	O
give	O
credit	O
to	O
his	O
sincerity	O
.	O
The	O
consciousneſs	O
of	O
having	O
acted	O
below	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
reproaches	O
he	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
such	O
conduct	O
give	O
him	O
no	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
he	O
writes	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Taxal	B-place
with	O
all	O
poſsible	O
chearfulneſs	O
forgetting	O
that	O
the	O
impreſsions	O
he	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
were	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Impostor	O
&	O
these	O
impreſsions	O
are	O
further	O
confirmed	O
by	O
discoveries	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
thus	O
much	O
painful	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
to	O
put	O
you	O
upon	O
your	O
guard	O
.	O
As	O
no	O
Person	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
clearer	O
in	O
sight	O
into	O
his	O
real	O
character	O
&	O
disposition	O
than	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
the	O
greatest	O
perplexity	O
in	O
forming	O
any	O
reasonable	O
plan	O
for	O
his	O
future	O
life	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
no	O
plan	O
cou	O
'd	O
succeed	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
perfectly	O
clear	O
then	O
that	O
unleſs	O
an	O
amendment	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
can	O
be	O
brought	O
about	O
&	O
some	O
ideas	O
of	O
a	O
moral	O
sense	O
be	O
given	O
him	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
totally	O
destitute	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
reformation	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
candor	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
never	O
upbraided	O
him	O
for	O
follies	O
natural	O
to	O
young	O
men	O
.	O
my	O
remonstrances	O
&	O
invectives	O
have	O
been	O
pointed	O
only	O
against	O
falsehood	O
&	O
dishonesty	O
those	O
poisonous	O
qualities	O
if	O
not	O
eradicated	O
must	O
destroy	O
my	O
feelings	O
as	O
a	O
Parent	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
very	O
kindly	O
preſs	O
'd	O
his	O
visit	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
never	O
have	O
proposed	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
unfit	O
for	O
your	O
society	O
.	O
I	O
perfectly	O
recollected	O
your	O
partiality	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
from	O
thence	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
hopes	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
enter	O
into	O
his	O
situation	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
give	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
wou	O
'd	O
even	O
startle	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
too	O
far	O
gone	O
for	O
slight	O
hints	O
to	O
have	O
effect	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
fear	O
to	O
preſs	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
more	O
conversant	O
in	O
the	O
modes	O
of	O
persuasive	O
advice	O
than	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
to	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
a	O
case	O
that	O
will	O
indeed	O
try	O
your	O
skill	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
repeat	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
patience	O
to	O
too	O
long	O
a	O
trial	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
has	O
a	O
promised	O
visit	O
upon	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Daniell	I-pers
at	O
Lichfield	B-place
,	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
my	O
Friend	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
interested	O
for	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
it	O
will	O
perhaps	O
be	O
lucky	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
build	O
upon	O
your	O
foundations	O
raise	O
an	O
Edifice	O
between	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
Architects	O
will	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
my	O
utmost	O
gratitude	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
I	O
say	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
W.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
?	O
nothing	O
to	O
his	O
credit	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
therefore	O
better	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
request	O
you	O
make	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
upon	O
a	O
certain	O
occasion	O
,	O
were	O
it	O
the	O
only	O
test	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
give	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
&	O
regard	O
for	O
you	O
&	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
it	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
consolatory	O
the	O
satisfactions	O
given	O
by	O
my	O
B.r	O
may	O
be	O
to	O
palliate	O
the	O
proposed	O
union	O
,	O
I	O
sincerely	O
confeſs	O
that	O
my	O
private	O
sentiments	O
are	O
so	O
averse	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
more	O
improper	O
person	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
well	O
be	O
chosen	O
for	O
the	O
proposed	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
my	O
excuse	O
in	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
friendship	O
with	O
Palombi	B-pers
from	O
my	O
Br	O
.	O
's	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
disgust	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
tell	O
busineſs	O
in	O
London	B-place
prevented	O
my	O
attendance	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
agree	O
in	O
the	O
reason	O
aſsigned	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
taken	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
House	O
on	O
Lease	O
in	O
Portman	O
Square	O
but	O
my	O
occupations	O
preparatory	O
to	O
my	O
going	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
be	O
till	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
are	O
not	O
given	O
in	O
excuse	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
conceive	O
in	O
what	O
a	O
dilemma	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
respecting	O
my	O
conduct	O
to	O
some	O
Friends	O
who	O
have	O
lately	O
left	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
fear	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
Robt	O
in	O
a	O
Post	O
or	O
two	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Sert	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
August	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1791	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
19	O
Orchard	O
St	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
in	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
