TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dearest	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
News	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
to	O
entertain	O
you	O
with	O
,	O
no	O
Events	O
interesting	O
or	O
uninteresting	O
to	O
relate	O
but	O
t	O
o	O
w	O
o	O
lines	O
I	O
scrawl	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
thought	O
frequently	O
of	O
your	O
fall	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sincerly	O
hope	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
attended	O
with	O
any	O
bad	O
consequences	O
.	O
The	O
Weather	O
except	O
to	O
Chapel	O
has	O
not	O
allowed	O
us	O
to	O
stir	O
out	O
till	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
from	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
½	O
pt	O
Seven	O
yesterday	O
I	O
paſsed	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
and	O
Genl	B-pers
Freitag	I-pers
&	O
to	O
compleat	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
hour	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
additional	O
happineſs	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bludworth	I-pers
s	O
Company	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
wonder	O
then	O
my	O
Dear	O
at	O
the	O
total	O
anihilation	O
of	O
every	O
bright	O
Idea	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
last	O
long	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
unfit	O
for	O
Society	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dearest	O
I	O
still	O
have	O
Life	O
enough	O
left	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
Sincere	O
Affection	O
--	O
MC	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Mond	O
a	O
y	O
Morg	O
Love	O
to	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
Affte	O
Duty	O
to	O
dear	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
