TOKEN	NE
De	O
ar	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
goes	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
gave	O
m	O
e	O
the	O
tickets	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
s	O
benefit	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
like	O
anecdotes	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
two	O
gen	O
tlemen	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
othe	O
r	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dunford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
busy	O
meddling	O
man	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
always	O
finding	O
fault	O
with	O
his	O
neighbour	O
--	O
The	O
late	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
Mr	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
man	O
)	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
his	O
Mayoralty	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
acco	O
unt	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dunford	I-pers
who	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
not	O
allowing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Newgate	O
what	O
was	O
their	O
due	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
brought	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
Butchers	O
&	O
Bakers	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
their	O
account	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
defrauding	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
is	O
usual	O
&	O
chiefly	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
expence	O
;	O
the	O
court	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
about	O
180	O
citizens	O
,	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
rebuke	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dunford	I-pers
very	O
severely	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
rebuke	O
I	O
would	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
paſs	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
......	I-pers
When	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
thirteen	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
left	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
me	O
an	O
apprentice	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Tom	B-pers
,	O
their	O
are	O
three	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
always	O
to	O
bear	O
in	O
your	O
mind	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
is	O
to	O
remember	O
that	O
whatsoever	O
money	O
paſses	O
through	O
your	O
hands	O
is	O
sacred	O
&	O
let	O
yr	O
.	O
diſstreſses	O
be	O
what	O
they	O
will	O
must	O
never	O
be	O
touch	O
'd	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
secondly	O
speak	O
not	O
ill	O
nor	O
do	O
no	O
mischief	O
to	O
thy	O
neighbour	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
speak	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
or	O
can	O
help	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
thirdly	O
try	O
to	O
make	O
yourself	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
people	O
in	O
general	O
try	O
to	O
make	O
themselves	O
Miserable	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
happy	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
Affected	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dunford	I-pers
so	O
much	O
that	O
he	O
burst	O
into	O
tears	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
were	O
so	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
really	O
went	O
an	O
without	O
being	O
further	O
rebuked	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
..	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Affectionate	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
your	O
ever	O
obliged	O
&	O
affectionate	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
G——r	I-pers
Let	O
me	O
have	O
an	O
answer	O
about	O
Sally	B-pers
as	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
interested	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Sir	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northampton	B-place
