TOKEN	NE
Octr	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
--	O
1779	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
chide	O
you	O
for	O
not	O
answering	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
ago	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
post	O
brought	O
me	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Septr	O
wherein	O
you	O
seem	O
surprised	O
at	O
my	O
silence	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
actually	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
my	O
debt	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
stood	O
upon	O
that	O
ceremony	O
with	O
one	O
I	O
love	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
you	O
if	O
my	O
natural	O
indolence	O
had	O
not	O
totally	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ashamed	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
ground	O
it	O
has	O
gain	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
endeavour	O
to	O
combat	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
eloquent	O
&	O
plausible	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
resisting	O
,	O
this	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
little	O
share	O
of	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
my	O
own	O
has	O
kept	O
me	O
silent	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
follow	O
my	O
bad	O
example	O
,	O
letters	O
from	O
the	O
friends	O
we	O
love	O
are	O
always	O
valuable	O
;	O
but	O
particularly	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
and	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
oftener	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
terrible	O
eruption	O
of	O
Mount	O
Vesuvius	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Augst	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
suppose	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
little	O
drawing	O
which	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
which	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
exaggerated	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
horrid	O
&	O
the	O
confusion	O
it	O
occasion	O
'd	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
more	O
horrid	O
,	O
the	O
Yells	O
&	O
screams	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
Proceſsion	O
with	O
torches	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
Genaro	O
made	O
one	O
shudder	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
evident	O
that	O
terror	O
having	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
as	O
drunkeneſs	O
,	O
had	O
rais	O
'd	O
their	O
minds	O
to	O
a	O
pitch	O
of	O
Madneſs	O
capable	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
undertakings	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
s	O
Palace	O
&	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
S	O
t	O
Genaro	O
brought	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
his	O
refusal	O
to	O
comply	O
they	O
sett	O
fire	O
to	O
his	O
Gate	O
&	O
were	O
now	O
succeeding	O
in	O
forcing	O
the	O
Saint	O
out	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
must	O
have	O
then	O
been	O
attended	O
with	O
bad	O
consequences	O
)	O
when	O
some	O
one	O
very	O
happily	O
thought	O
of	O
applying	O
to	O
a	O
Dominican	O
Friar	O
called	O
Padre	B-pers
Rocca	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
popular	O
Preacher	O
(	O
owing	O
to	O
his	O
adapting	O
his	O
Sermons	O
to	O
the	O
understandings	O
,	O
education	O
,	O
&	O
language	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
immediately	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
perceiving	O
they	O
had	O
prepared	O
common	O
pitch	O
torches	O
to	O
accompany	O
their	O
Saint	O
,	O
he	O
reproach	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
want	O
of	O
respect	O
in	O
coming	O
so	O
ill	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
persuaded	O
them	O
to	O
retire	O
till	O
they	O
could	O
procure	O
white	O
wax	O
torches	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
--	O
to	O
this	O
they	O
listen	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
time	O
being	O
gain	O
'd	O
the	O
fever	O
of	O
the	O
Mountain	O
subsided	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
minds	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
course	O
became	O
more	O
calm	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
afterwards	O
another	O
fit	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
grown	O
used	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
inspire	O
them	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
terror	O
--	O
since	O
this	O
the	O
mouth	O
has	O
been	O
stopp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
till	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
point	O
fell	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
now	O
smokes	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
it	O
gave	O
two	O
groans	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
quite	O
like	O
particularly	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
our	O
Villa	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
Vesuvius	O
,	O
but	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Mountain	O
Doctor	O
)	O
aſsures	O
me	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
fear	O
;	O
since	O
the	O
eruption	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
shock	O
of	O
an	O
earthquake	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
done	O
no	O
damage	O
;	O
this	O
however	O
makes	O
me	O
think	O
many	O
months	O
will	O
not	O
paſs	O
without	O
another	O
eruption	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
leſs	O
violent	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
in	O
that	O
Almighty	O
Providence	O
which	O
has	O
hitherto	O
preserv	O
'd	O
us	O
in	O
numberleſs	O
occasions	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
under	O
that	O
persuasion	O
I	O
rest	O
as	O
quietly	O
here	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
elsewhere	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Court	O
of	O
last	O
Year	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
Caserta	B-place
where	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
join	O
it	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
one	O
Month	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
Parsano	O
a	O
Hunting	O
Seat	O
about	O
fifty	O
Miles	O
off	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
them	O
as	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
has	O
appointed	O
him	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
hunting	O
Seats	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
really	O
feel	O
quite	O
abandon	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
Naples	B-place
without	O
him	O
--	O
the	O
footing	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
upon	O
at	O
this	O
Court	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Ministre	O
de	O
Famille	O
while	O
the	O
French	O
Ambaſsador	O
(	O
who	O
has	O
managed	O
his	O
Affairs	O
exceedingly	O
ill	O
)	O
is	O
treated	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
with	O
civility	O
)	O
with	O
great	O
distance	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
soon	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
,	O
unleſs	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
first	O
Minister	O
in	O
France	B-place
;	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
all	O
the	B-pers
French	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Ministers	O
were	O
like	O
him	O
--	O
the	O
change	O
in	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
character	O
is	O
amazing	O
since	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
,	O
it	O
has	O
made	O
an	O
impreſsion	O
upon	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
incapable	O
of	O
,	O
hardly	O
a	O
day	O
paſses	O
that	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
shed	O
floods	O
of	O
tears	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
only	O
happy	O
hours	O
she	O
seems	O
to	O
paſs	O
is	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Daughters	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
whom	O
are	O
most	O
charming	O
Children	O
The	O
poor	O
little	O
Prince	O
Royal	O
is	O
no	O
comfort	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
her	O
Ambitions	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
predominant	O
paſsion	O
)	O
&	O
Vanity	O
,	O
are	O
perpetually	O
mortified	O
thro	O
'	O
him	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
little	O
weakly	O
unpromising	O
Child	O
,	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
large	O
head	O
&	O
a	O
rickety	O
look	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
at	O
times	O
so	O
hurt	O
about	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
lamenting	O
his	O
great	O
backwardneſs	O
in	O
too	O
Strong	O
terms	O
.	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
now	O
gives	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
time	O
to	O
busineſs	O
of	O
works	O
with	O
The	O
Ministers	O
,	O
who	O
make	O
all	O
their	O
reports	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
who	O
seems	O
(	O
in	O
general	O
)	O
very	O
glad	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
burthen	O
off	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
grown	O
(	O
in	O
private	O
)	O
very	O
devout	O
(	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
superstitious	O
)	O
for	O
she	O
lately	O
sent	O
in	O
Secret	O
a	O
Nightgown	O
of	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
to	O
a	O
famous	O
relick	O
to	O
touch	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
his	O
recovery	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
mistaken	O
(	O
as	O
Years	O
come	O
on	O
)	O
if	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
grow	O
in	O
that	O
respect	O
like	O
The	B-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
I	O
thought	O
these	O
circumstances	O
might	O
amuse	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
write	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Post	O
at	O
Rome	B-place
where	O
it	O
is	O
sure	O
of	O
not	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
.	O
--	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
delighted	O
with	O
the	O
accts	O
.	O
of	O
H	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
story	O
in	O
the	O
Newspaper	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
&	O
preparing	O
for	O
the	O
engagement	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
charming	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
him	O
&	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chartres	I-pers
whose	O
conduct	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
applauded	O
otherwise	O
qu	O
'	O
a	O
l'Opera	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Song	O
upon	O
that	O
Glorious	O
occasion	O
.	O
can	O
not	O
finish	O
my	O
letter	O
without	O
rejoicing	O
with	O
you	O
afresh	O
upon	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
yr	O
situation	O
,	O
&	O
or	O
the	O
constant	O
goodness	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
your	O
combined	O
