TOKEN	NE
Wednesday	O
8	O
th	O
Sepr	O
1784	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
so	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
busineſs	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
seeing	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
pedestal	O
for	O
the	O
Vase	O
for	O
the	O
D	B-pers
of	I-pers
P——	I-pers
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
will	O
think	O
well	O
contrived	O
it	O
was	O
Crighton	B-pers
my	O
cabinet	O
maker	O
maker	O
in	O
in	O
Kings	O
Street	O
Soho	B-place
that	O
made	O
it	O
&	O
he	O
can	O
repair	O
it	O
&	O
fit	O
the	O
glaſses	O
as	O
I	O
intended	O
if	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
chooses	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
remarkable	O
for	O
obbs	O
--	O
To	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
will	O
c	O
sometime	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
&	O
most	O
affly	O
.	O
W	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
Sepr	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
.	O
84	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
