TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
Febry	O
:	O
10	O
th	O
:	O
1772	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
may	O
justly	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
neglect	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
civility	O
most	O
demanded	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
myself	O
so	O
lately	O
drank	O
of	O
the	O
bitter	O
Cup	O
of	O
Affliction	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
of	O
adding	O
to	O
yours	O
,	O
by	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
my	O
Heart	O
wou	O
'd	O
dictate	O
to	O
my	O
Pen	O
,	O
too	O
feellingly	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
Sensibility	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
good	O
Sen	O
s	O
e	O
has	O
enabled	O
you	O
to	O
resume	O
your	O
wonted	O
Chearfulneſs	O
,	O
&	O
agreeable	O
employments	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
Your	O
little	O
Friend	O
(	O
who	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
partial	O
to	O
)	O
desires	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
grows	O
fast	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
exceſsively	O
fond	O
of	O
Books	O
.	O
much	O
more	O
than	O
her	O
Needle	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
propose	O
in	O
Spring	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
boarding	O
School	O
.	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
high	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
almost	O
ran	O
wild	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
well	O
.	O
please	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
most	O
respectful	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H——	I-pers
Your	O
sincere	O
Friend	O
&	O
obliged	O
Humble	O
:	O
Servt	O
:	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
