TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
My	O
Mother	O
Com̄iſsions	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
(	O
with	O
her	O
Love	O
)	O
the	O
Letter	O
that	O
goes	O
with	O
this	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Elisabeth	I-pers
requesting	O
you	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
R	O
H	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
myself	O
by	O
having	O
ye	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
Calling	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wet	O
weather	O
prevents	O
me	O
--	O
Kew	B-place
Sepr	O
.	O
1779	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
