TOKEN	NE
Kinsale	B-place
,	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Novr	O
.	O
1786	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
would	O
have	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
Divorce	O
.	O
Pray	O
has	O
not	O
your	O
husband	O
an	O
undoubted	O
right	O
to	O
tumble	O
down	O
Stairs	O
whenever	O
he	O
pleases	O
,	O
without	O
your	O
presuming	O
to	O
be	O
alarmed	O
?	O
I	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Jerry	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
of	O
Dublin	B-place
by	O
Six	O
footpads	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
draw	O
my	O
Sword	O
when	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Carriage	O
&	O
we	O
got	O
away	O
without	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
She	O
durst	O
as	O
soon	O
have	O
eat	O
my	O
Sword	O
as	O
played	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
Trick	O
,	O
as	O
You	O
did	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
.	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
proper	O
Advice	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
true	O
mode	O
of	O
managing	O
Wives	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
however	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
You	O
have	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
disappointing	O
him	O
,	O
be	O
the	O
production	O
Male	O
or	O
Female	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
You	O
can	O
effectively	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
by	O
presenting	O
him	O
with	O
Twins	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
sight	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
gratified	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
dancing	O
your	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
You	O
will	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
as	O
my	O
Wife	O
did	O
viz	O
.	O
As	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
she	O
begins	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
touch	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
made	O
of	O
Glaſs	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
whole	O
Nursery	O
in	O
proper	O
Awe	O
&	O
subjection	O
.	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
for	O
a	O
multitude	O
of	O
good	O
reasons	O
.	O
The	O
Cathcart	O
's	O
can	O
aſsist	O
in	O
Nursing	O
You	O
&	O
the	O
Air	O
of	O
Dallington	B-place
may	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
afterwards	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
you	O
propose	O
nursing	O
yourself	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C——	I-pers
is	O
I	O
find	O
a	O
Candidate	O
to	O
succeed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Scotch	O
Peers	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
called	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
by	O
new	O
Titles	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
word	O
he	O
intended	O
going	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
to	O
canvaſs	O
in	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
Succeſs	O
&	O
with	O
all	O
due	O
deference	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
wisdom	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
Journey	O
be	O
no	O
means	O
prudent	O
.	O
He	O
&	O
his	O
family	O
seem	O
to	O
exist	O
more	O
in	O
Post	O
Chaises	O
,	O
than	O
in	O
comfortable	O
houses	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
unfavourable	O
accounts	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
's	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
ever	O
considered	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
amiable	O
of	O
that	O
set	O
of	O
my	O
Cousins	O
.	O
I	O
suspect	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
saved	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
with	O
credit	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Officer	O
of	O
Rank	O
who	O
is	O
lately	O
come	O
home	O
told	O
Me	O
that	O
Charles	B-pers
wasted	O
all	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
Journey	O
's	O
between	O
or	O
rather	O
Voyages	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Country	O
's	O
.	O
His	O
constitution	O
has	O
been	O
bad	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
recollect	O
before	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
India	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
tormented	O
with	O
a	O
spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Graham	O
's	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
.	O
Your	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
has	O
I	O
suppose	O
imagine	O
taken	O
a	O
new	O
lease	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Bedford	B-place
Square	O
House	O
might	O
have	O
contented	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
poſsibly	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
his	O
disposition	O
to	O
be	O
contented	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pechell	I-pers
returned	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
from	O
his	O
Royal	O
Visit	O
,	O
has	O
since	O
that	O
been	O
appointed	O
one	O
of	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Ushers	O
&	O
obtained	O
excellent	O
Rooms	O
in	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Pechell	I-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
straw	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suspect	O
bids	O
fair	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
next	O
Summer	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
Winter	O
in	O
France	B-place
.	O
They	O
have	O
taken	O
their	O
Son	O
with	O
them	O
&	O
left	O
their	O
daughter	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
removed	O
her	O
abode	O
to	O
Clar	O
ges	O
Street	O
Lady	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
tried	O
some	O
experiment	O
of	O
rearing	O
a	O
Girl	O
she	O
produced	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
ago	O
with	O
spoon	O
meat	O
only	O
,	O
which	O
ended	O
in	O
the	O
Infant	O
's	O
departure	O
from	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
&	O
brats	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
is	O
called	O
William	B-pers
John	I-pers
after	O
his	O
two	O
Grandfathers	O
.	O
We	O
propose	O
innoculating	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
An	O
operation	O
I	O
would	O
allways	O
recommend	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
old	O
&	O
which	O
is	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
children	O
,	O
who	O
like	O
ours	O
,	O
are	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
moved	O
at	O
a	O
moments	O
warning	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mansell	O
Park	O
in	O
your	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
for	O
Sale	O
&	O
was	O
half	O
inclined	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
is	O
discontinued	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
poſsible	O
wish	O
for	O
your	O
Safety	O
,	O
welfare	O
&	O
happineſs	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
personally	O
unknown	O
to	O
Us	O
,	O
has	O
his	O
full	O
share	O
of	O
our	O
Affections	O
;	O
his	O
having	O
chosen	O
You	O
to	O
torment	O
him	O
is	O
a	O
convincing	O
proof	O
to	O
Us	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
love	O
him	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
faithfull	O
friend	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
JD	O
desires	O
Love	O
&	O
kindest	O
respects	O
Beech	O
Sat	O
.	O
going	O
to	O
return	O
home	O
alone	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
KINSALE	B-place
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
By	O
Derbyshire	B-place
.	O
6½	O
41-	O
10-10	O
51-10	O
7	O
18	O
59-8-6½	O
