TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
that	O
you	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
displeased	O
with	O
my	O
conduct	O
towards	O
you	O
;	O
&	O
particularly	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
show	O
that	O
confidence	O
in	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
just	O
a	O
claim	O
to	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
some	O
appearance	O
of	O
foundation	O
for	O
a	O
censure	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
reflexion	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
candor	O
&	O
humanity	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
reasonable	O
allowances	O
for	O
the	O
caution	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
be	O
observed	O
in	O
my	O
perplex	O
'd	O
&	O
unfortunate	O
circumstances	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
conscious	O
to	O
myself	O
of	O
being	O
incapable	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
reserve	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
imprudent	O
to	O
communicate	O
by	O
letter	O
;	O
let	O
me	O
therefore	O
finally	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
intreat	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
me	O
having	O
never	O
yet	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
silence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
upon	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
can	O
proceed	O
from	O
no	O
other	O
reasons	O
than	O
those	O
I	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
already	O
unfortunate	O
enough	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
therefore	O
feel	O
the	O
most	O
sensible	O
regret	O
in	O
being	O
deprived	O
of	O
your	O
friendship	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
relied	O
&	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
be	O
a	O
real	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
paſs	O
my	O
time	O
here	O
but	O
very	O
heavily	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
change	O
the	O
scene	O
is	O
as	O
yet	O
very	O
uncertain	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
determin	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
reside	O
here	O
much	O
longer	O
.	O
My	O
presence	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
will	O
I	O
fear	O
be	O
soon	O
indispensably	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
affairs	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
as	O
bad	O
a	O
state	O
as	O
poſsible	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Buttle	I-pers
's	O
having	O
totally	O
neglected	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
now	O
condescend	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
my	O
letters	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
added	O
to	O
this	O
the	O
chance	O
of	O
losing	O
my	O
Manager	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
who	O
I	O
hear	O
is	O
very	O
ill.	O
Let	O
me	O
caution	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
employ	O
Mr.	B-pers
Buttle	I-pers
any	O
more	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Papers	O
.	O
Your	O
Leases	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
whose	O
honesty	O
I	O
can	O
answer	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
caution	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
trust	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
without	O
your	O
positive	O
orders	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
remember	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
to	O
my	O
Niece	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
and	O
Affectionately	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
York	B-place
Novr	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1763	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Nov	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
1763	O
.	O
from	O
York	B-place
