TOKEN	NE
Deal	B-place
Apr	O
,	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
Believe	O
me	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
that	O
nothing	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
greater	O
pleaſure	O
than	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
only	O
this	O
day	O
by	O
mistake	O
of	O
the	O
postmaster	O
of	O
Canterbury	B-place
not	O
forwarding	O
my	O
letters	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
buſineſs	O
&	O
return	O
to	O
Canterbury	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
this	O
short	O
affair	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
reſolved	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
greatly	O
concerned	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
health	O
and	O
indeed	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
reaſon	O
I	O
was	O
ſorry	O
to	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
canterbury	B-place
at	O
this	O
time	O
however	O
thank	O
God	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
that	O
all	O
danger	O
is	O
over	O
&	O
may	O
she	O
enjoy	O
the	O
health	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
continually	O
.	O
You	O
deſire	O
my	O
intructions	O
to	O
calm	O
your	O
spirits	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
advice	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
give	O
.	O
Viz	O
Remember	O
always	O
we	O
are	O
poor	O
worms	O
that	O
we	O
dont	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
best	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
ſure	O
whatever	O
our	O
almighty	O
Creator	O
orders	O
must	O
be	O
for	O
our	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
so	O
wisely	O
ordered	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
preſumption	O
in	O
us	O
to	O
repine	O
at	O
his	O
just	O
decrees	O
&	O
let	O
us	O
always	O
be	O
prepared	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
own	O
,	O
&	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
that	O
whatever	O
is	O
,	O
is	O
right	O
These	O
thoughts	O
are	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
calm	O
the	O
spirits	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
follow	O
the	O
above	O
you	O
'll	O
always	O
find	O
yourself	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
or	O
worst	O
that	O
may	O
happen	O
trust	O
in	O
God	O
&	O
he	O
never	O
will	O
forsake	O
th	O
em	O
that	O
puts	O
his	O
trust	O
in	O
him	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
most	O
Affctly-	O
W.N	B-pers
--	O
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
congratulate	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
recovery	O
but	O
tell	O
Buxton	B-place
is	O
the	O
place	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
