TOKEN	NE
29	O
March	O
1793	O
That	O
a	O
man	O
should	O
write	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
spirits	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
would	O
surprize	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
things	O
--	O
your	O
letter	O
entertained	O
me	O
greatly	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
Taxal	B-place
man	O
you	O
surprize	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
could	O
spin	O
out	O
such	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
matter	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
odious	O
odious	O
tract	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
surprized	O
,	O
sameneſs	O
will	O
tire	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
last	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
purr	O
away	O
life	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
corner	O
--	O
society	O
is	O
the	O
zest	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
but	O
vegetables	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
avast	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
the	O
inceſsant	O
changes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mere	O
profeſſional	O
friendships	O
which	O
engage	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
fashio	O
na	O
ble	O
folk	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
far	O
more	O
tiresome	O
than	O
even	O
the	O
repeated	O
strol	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
path	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
river	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
--	O
my	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
state	O
is	O
this	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
happyest	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
smallest	O
ground	O
for	O
regret	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
to	O
being	O
always	O
in	O
love	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
something	O
like	O
being	O
always	O
hungry	O
which	O
is	O
impoſſible	O
--	O
now	O
says	O
H.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
filthy	O
fellow	O
,	O
does	O
he	O
call	O
that	O
love	O
?	O
softly	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
S	O
t	O
Peter	O
and	O
the	O
sheet	O
?	O
besides	O
think	O
of	O
little	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
but	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
people	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
always	O
tired	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
are	O
thousands	O
who	O
regard	O
a	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Sense	O
as	O
they	O
do	O
a	O
cane	O
,	O
a	O
cork	O
:	O
skrew	O
a	O
snufbox	O
,	O
only	O
because	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
so	O
long	O
--	O
Darby	O
&	O
Joan	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
described	O
a	O
paragon	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
worth	O
20	O
golden	O
fleeces	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
wrong	O
Louisa	B-pers
in	O
your	O
heart	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
old	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
smooth	O
his	O
road	O
to	O
Heaven	O
,	O
than	O
be	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Herculanium	O
crockery	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
tolerable	O
good	O
purr	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
hate	O
myself	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
the	O
older	O
tabby	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
--	O
it	O
wd	O
not	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
cure	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
damn	O
that	O
fellow	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D——	I-pers
with	O
his	O
gout	O
in	O
the	O
Nerves	O
are	O
not	O
we	O
all	O
nerves	O
--	O
let	O
Turton	B-pers
take	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Knighton	O
Ginger	O
bread	O
for	O
break	O
fast	O
with	O
a	O
glaſs	O
of	O
sack	O
or	O
old	O
Madeira	O
--	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
air	O
in	O
dry	O
weather	O
,	O
or	O
use	O
a	O
Swing	O
within	O
doors	O
in	O
damp	O
Weather	O
,	O
dine	O
at	O
her	O
hungry	O
hour	O
,	O
use	O
brisk	O
exercise	O
in	O
a	O
ca	O
r	O
riage	O
,	O
sup	O
early	O
,	O
drink	O
draught	O
Porter	O
banish	O
tea	O
,	O
rise	O
early	O
,	O
my	O
life	O
against	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
she	O
will	O
grow	O
a	O
stout	O
woman	O
.	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
rather	O
have	O
a	O
beef	O
Steak	O
Wife	O
than	O
a	O
water	O
gruel	O
one	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
walks	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
hungred	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
snap	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
oysters	O
&	O
a	O
morsel	O
of	O
bread	O
--	O
if	O
milk	O
agrees	O
with	O
her	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
disposes	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
whereof	O
exercise	O
is	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
machine	O
--	O
Delicacy	O
of	O
the	O
Sex	O
!	O
fiddlesticks	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
dance	O
,	O
rake	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
children	O
--	O
delicate	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
!	O
A	O
certain	O
Turton	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Imperial	O
service	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Taafe	I-pers
how	O
he	O
was	O
enabled	O
to	O
make	O
so	O
gallant	O
a	O
defence	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
post	O
with	O
so	O
few	O
men	O
.	O
plase	O
your	O
Majesty	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
wifes	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
ridgementals	O
on	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gived	O
a	O
whirelock	O
to	O
ivery	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bitches	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Jas	O
Jesus	O
,	O
plase	O
your	O
Majesty	O
the	O
bitches	O
kipt	O
up	O
sich	O
a	O
whireing	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
kipt	O
the	O
innemy	O
off	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
reinforcement	O
.	O
delicacy	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
an	O
enemy	O
to	O
milk	O
chocolate	O
,	O
depend	O
on	O
it	O
Women	O
are	O
ruined	O
by	O
slops	O
&	O
medicine	O
,	O
make	O
them	O
hungry	O
by	O
air	O
and	O
exercise	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
live	O
generously	O
,	O
then	O
no	O
pimples	O
,	O
then	O
no	O
vapors	O
,	O
no	O
yawnings	O
,	O
no	O
halfsleeps	O
--	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
Geo	B-pers
:	I-pers
2d	I-pers
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
aſſent	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
clever	O
fellow	O
)	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
physician	O
for	O
me	O
or	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Turton	B-pers
does	O
not	O
know	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
gout	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
arisen	O
from	O
my	O
bed	O
having	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
both	O
feet	O
,	O
both	O
ancles	O
,	O
both	O
k	O
n	O
ees	O
,	O
both	O
elbows	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
left	O
crupper	O
--	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
having	O
found	O
it	O
imprudent	O
to	O
brave	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
yielded	O
to	O
flannel	O
,	O
to	O
slops	O
,	O
sweating	O
,	O
low	O
diet	O
while	O
the	O
Fever	O
with	O
delirium	O
lasted	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
trial	O
)	O
great	O
relief	O
from	O
rubbing	O
the	O
painful	O
part	O
with	O
Opodeldoc	O
,	O
which	O
never	O
repelled	O
the	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
this	O
bout	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
complaint	O
in	O
head	O
or	O
Stomach	O
on	O
former	O
occasions	O
I	O
plyed	O
my	O
gentleman	O
in	O
head	O
or	O
Stomach	O
with	O
Tinc	O
.	O
Rhab	O
.	O
ȝ	O
.	O
S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
relieved	O
from	O
pain	O
,	O
walk	O
pretty	O
hobbling	O
,	O
write	O
as	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
pretty	O
legible	O
hand	O
like	O
yours	O
,	O
eat	O
what	O
pleases	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Madeira	O
&	O
a	O
fig	O
for	O
the	O
Doctor	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
my	O
own	O
Esculapius	O
--	O
Nervous	O
gout	O
indeed	O
--	O
a	O
novel	O
term	O
well	O
done	O
Master	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
--	O
4	O
Weeks	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
total	O
of	O
my	O
confinement	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
gout	O
since	O
1769	O
--	O
what	O
say	O
you	O
,	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
?	O
I	O
am	O
within	O
3	O
years	O
of	O
60	O
--	O
what	O
say	O
you	O
Master	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
de	O
tirte	O
a	O
fuera	O
of	O
cursed	O
Anguera	B-place
--	O
si	O
quid	O
novisti	O
rectius	O
I	O
beg	O
youll	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
for	O
War	O
here	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
gueſs	O
by	O
my	O
date	O
(	O
March	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1793	O
)	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
must	O
cripple	O
about	O
more	O
or	O
leſs	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
happy	O
mortal	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
tho	O
there	O
be	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
your	O
England	B-place
and	O
my	O
Ireland	B-place
whom	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
aye	O
and	O
embrace	O
s	O
in	O
ner	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
equally	O
surprized	O
&	O
grieved	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
niece	O
Mr	B-pers
Doctor	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
is	O
not	O
made	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
mysteries	O
,	O
because	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
dont	O
suppose	O
she	O
would	O
ride	O
astride	O
to	O
Gretna	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
yet	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
like	O
to	O
yield	O
to	O
the	O
soft	O
impulse	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
gentle	O
legal	O
force	O
was	O
used	O
--	O
She	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
choice	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
judge	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
wou	O
l	O
d	O
make	O
her	O
election	O
sure	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
notion	O
of	O
such	O
fruit	O
hanging	O
Summer	O
after	O
Summer	O
--	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
altogether	O
deserve	O
the	O
favorable	O
opinion	O
she	O
entertains	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
deserve	O
certainly	O
about	O
19	O
/	O
20	O
ths	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
so	O
will	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
shant	O
die	O
yet	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Cervantes	B-pers
England	B-place
Mary	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derby	B-place
Shire	I-place
