TOKEN	NE
Wing	B-place
Janry	O
2	O
d	O
1800	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
At	O
last	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
Magazines	O
--	O
&	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
intelligence	O
which	O
is	O
so	O
new	O
to	O
us	O
both	O
that	O
we	O
conclude	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
has	O
Avow	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
the	O
Authoreſs	O
of	O
the	O
Series	O
of	O
P	O
lays	O
--	O
&	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
preparation	O
at	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
had	O
this	O
Country	O
has	O
taken	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
under	O
its	O
immediate	O
Protection	O
--	O
pray	O
asſure	O
Grand	O
in	O
yr	O
next	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
Subscribe	O
my	O
pittance	O
toward	O
this	O
new	O
Tax	O
--	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
Submiſsion	O
.	O
but	O
with	O
cheerfulneſs	O
.	O
&	O
readineſs	O
--	O
did	O
John	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
tell	O
you	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
Claim	O
the	O
Dukedom	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
--	O
from	O
the	O
Stories	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
the	B-pers
poor	I-pers
Cardinal	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
&	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
from	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
duke	O
(	O
which	O
Stories	O
differ	O
'd	O
materially	O
as	O
how	O
&	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
Lord	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
became	O
Duke	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
conceive	O
that	O
the	O
lawyers	O
wd	O
Easily	O
make	O
out	O
a	O
Case	O
which	O
may	O
fill	O
their	O
pockets	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
glad	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
these	O
Young	O
ladies	O
will	O
never	O
forget	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
&	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Shewed	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
melancholy	O
circumstances	O
--	O
I	O
Hope	O
this	O
for	O
their	O
sakes	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
wish	O
them	O
well	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
I	O
think	O
their	O
prospect	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
gloomy	O
one	O
.	O
it	O
requires	O
not	O
only	O
Steadineſs	O
--	O
but	O
great	O
good	O
Sense	O
.	O
for	O
a	O
Young	O
pretty	O
Girl	O
with	O
the	O
Talents	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Edwin	I-pers
to	O
Conduct	O
her	O
self	O
with	O
Prudence	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
World	O
,	O
as	O
London	B-place
contains	O
--	O
she	O
,	O
a	O
perfect	O
Stranger	O
--	O
of	O
an	O
Age	O
to	O
believe	O
any	O
Profeſsion	O
of	O
regard	O
made	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
most	O
Selfish	O
.	O
&	O
often	O
the	O
most	O
Unworthy	O
--	O
in	O
Short	O
.	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
nothing	O
Short	O
of	O
a	O
Miraculous	O
interference	O
can	O
save	O
those	O
poor	O
innocents	O
&	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
wonderful	O
instance	O
of	O
divine	O
Mercy	O
may	O
be	O
shewn	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
--	O
is	O
the	O
sincere	O
wish	O
of	O
yr	O
ever	O
Affect	O
Friend	O
Dr	B-pers
Milman	I-pers
Love	O
from	O
all	O
to	O
both	O
lord	B-pers
something	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
is	O
better	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
