TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
1803	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Immediately	O
on	O
receiving	O
your	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Man	O
with	O
that	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
this	O
moment	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
melancholy	O
accounts	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
event	O
happened	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
Ten	O
,	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
loved	O
Your	O
Uncle	O
,	O
I	O
regret	O
the	O
feelings	O
You	O
will	O
experience	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
Love	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
I	O
trust	O
this	O
fine	O
weather	O
will	O
remove	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Cough	O
.	O
Every	O
Mortal	O
h	O
as	O
er	O
e	O
almost	O
ha	O
ve	O
s	O
suffered	O
from	O
the	O
Influenza	O
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Sixth	O
April	O
1803	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
