TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Enclosed	O
to	O
P	B-pers
Ernest	I-pers
&	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
&	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
indulge	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Line	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
all	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
yourself	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
has	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
Manuscript	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
add	O
so	O
will	O
only	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
&	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C.Finch	B-pers
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
P.	B-pers
Ernest	I-pers
I	O
will	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
desires	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
but	O
can	O
not	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
Harleyford	B-place
.	O
March	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
House	O
London	B-place
Hon	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
