TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
April	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
on	O
friday	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
this	O
Morning	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
if	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
Inst-	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
You	O
seem	O
to	O
reproach	O
my	O
want	O
of	O
distinctneſs	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
explaining	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
poſsible	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
deserve	O
the	O
rebuke	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
write	O
on	O
one	O
subject	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
are	O
thinking	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
My	O
mind	O
has	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
tormented	O
both	O
with	O
public	O
&	O
private	O
Matters	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
say	O
nothing	O
except	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
addition	O
to	O
my	O
Salary	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
leave	O
You	O
to	O
gueſs	O
whether	O
the	O
present	O
Times	O
promise	O
much	O
hope	O
to	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
private	O
matters	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
Slough	O
of	O
despond	O
.	O
My	O
John	B-pers
,	O
my	O
faithful	O
&	O
attached	O
John	B-pers
,	O
is	O
no	O
longer	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
Service	O
.	O
That	O
Devil	O
Cupid	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
worse	O
devil	O
,	O
a	O
torment	O
of	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
has	O
separated	O
us	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
She	O
plagued	O
him	O
till	O
she	O
extinguished	O
all	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
frail	O
Mortality	O
shewed	O
itself	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
's	O
Maid	O
had	O
charms	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
approach	O
of	O
a	O
living	O
Witneſs	O
of	O
their	O
indiscretion	O
,	O
obliged	O
her	O
to	O
quit	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
,	O
&	O
me	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
John	B-pers
.	O
So	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
four	O
people	O
have	O
been	O
rendered	O
uncomfortable	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
two	O
good	O
Servants	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
have	O
lost	O
their	O
peace	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
slightest	O
suspicion	O
of	O
this	O
connexion	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
told	O
her	O
Mistreſs	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
departure	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
now	O
,	O
almost	O
weep	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
John	B-pers
fixed	O
(	O
I	O
hope	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Scottish	O
Baronet	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
bring	O
him	O
immediately	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
when	O
he	O
will	O
fix	O
on	O
some	O
place	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
three	O
Children	O
to	O
move	O
to	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
Place	O
is	O
mine	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
decamp	O
.	O
My	O
Rib	O
&	O
Children	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
to	O
fix	O
on	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
expect	O
to	O
return	O
here	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Week	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
moment	O
we	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
all	O
will	O
be	O
hurry	O
&	O
confusion	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
again	O
in	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
by	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
or	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
General	O
Aſsembly	O
opens	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
look	O
round	O
this	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
operation	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
in	O
packing	O
up	O
my	O
Books	O
,	O
&	O
no	O
John	B-pers
to	O
aſsist	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
absolutely	O
makes	O
me	O
melancholy	O
.	O
For	O
these	O
last	O
twelve	O
Years	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
book	O
has	O
been	O
dusted	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
rational	O
looking	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Livery	O
.	O
He	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
commenced	O
our	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
I	O
seldom	O
ever	O
speak	O
in	O
a	O
Carriage	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
inclined	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Companion	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
me	O
a	O
rare	O
sulky	O
fellow	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
probably	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
at	O
least	O
Six	O
Months	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
then	O
addreſs	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
exhibited	O
the	O
Portrait	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
my	O
Rib	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
original	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
rashly	O
promised	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
that	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Trip	O
I	O
make	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Love	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
from	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
myself	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Countrywoman	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Fourth	O
April	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
