TOKEN	NE
I	O
congratulate	O
you	O
most	O
sincerely	O
my	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
upon	O
the	O
happy	O
event	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
disappointments	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
those	O
relating	O
to	O
a	O
former	O
seemingly	O
splendid	O
situation	O
,	O
borne	O
without	O
complaint	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
turn	O
to	O
enjoy	O
some	O
tranquillity	O
and	O
happineſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
greatest	O
reason	O
to	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
turn	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
always	O
disposed	O
to	O
see	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
favorable	O
point	O
of	O
view	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
certainly	O
the	O
truest	O
and	O
most	O
profitable	O
philosophy	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
transplanted	O
into	O
another	O
Family	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
assure	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
affectionate	O
interest	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
concern	O
your	O
happineſs	O
will	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
ever	O
attend	O
you	O
in	O
all	O
situations	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
another	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Agent	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
upon	O
the	O
busineſs	O
of	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
,	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
enter	O
upon	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
quit	O
the	O
subject	O
without	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
settled	O
to	O
your	O
entire	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
affectionate	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
with	O
my	O
congratulations	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
your	O
mutual	O
happineſs	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
c	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Teingmouth	B-place
--	O
Devon	B-place
June	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
In	O
your	O
next	O
please	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
how	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
trespaſs	O
further	O
upon	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S——t	I-pers
's	O
indulgence	O
