TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
No	O
words	O
can	O
expreſs	O
my	O
gratitude	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
your	O
unwearied	O
attention	O
to	O
my	O
dearest	O
daughter	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
former	O
occasion	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
visited	O
with	O
a	O
similar	O
affliction	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
her	O
perilous	O
state	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
very	O
evident	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
command	O
over	O
my	O
grief	O
,	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
her	O
present	O
case	O
is	O
still	O
much	O
more	O
desperate	O
not	O
having	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
a	O
ray	O
of	O
hope	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
dread	O
of	O
meeting	O
her	O
cruel	O
husband	O
prevents	O
my	O
setting	O
out	O
immediately	O
for	O
London	B-place
but	O
if	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
sufferer	O
shoud	O
even	O
be	O
alive	O
at	O
my	O
arrival	O
,	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
answer	O
it	O
to	O
myself	O
to	O
disturb	O
her	O
last	O
moments	O
.	O
shoud	O
she	O
be	O
capable	O
of	O
receiving	O
comfort	O
from	O
her	O
Father	O
s	O
bleſsing	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
after	O
having	O
received	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
convey	O
it	O
I	O
beseech	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
impreſsive	O
terms	O
You	O
poſeſs	O
your	O
self	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
daughter	O
&	O
thereforefore	O
you	O
can	O
duely	O
estimate	O
my	O
feelings	O
at	O
this	O
perilous	O
crisis	O
.	O
My	O
head	O
is	O
too	O
confused	O
to	O
dwell	O
longer	O
upon	O
this	O
painful	O
subject	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
further	O
period	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
wanting	O
in	O
every	O
possible	O
demonstration	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
kindest	O
remembrance	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
much	O
obliged	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bath	B-place
May	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
49	O
.	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
