TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
Feby	O
6	O
th	O
1801	O
Chere	O
Amie	O
Many	O
Thanks	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
your	O
good	O
Husband	O
for	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
Cottage	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
advis	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
to	O
Employ	O
Major	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
s	O
Workmen	O
.	O
but	O
Alas	O
!	O
what	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
female	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
quite	O
alone	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
ready	O
at	O
hand	O
to	O
advise	O
with	O
.	O
the	O
temptation	O
was	O
to	O
save	O
carriage	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
between	O
our	O
selves	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
having	O
paid	O
18	O
S	O
.	O
for	O
Carriage	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
trust	O
my	O
Credit	O
is	O
good	O
,	O
having	O
paid	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
--	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
Employ	O
his	O
own	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
&	O
desire	O
Mr	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
my	O
little	O
Stoves	O
&	O
the	O
Copper	O
&	O
have	O
them	O
put	O
up	O
.	O
the	O
Stoves	O
rumfordiz	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
greatly	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
hasten	O
matters	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
putting	O
any	O
one	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
must	O
then	O
pay	O
the	O
Taxes	O
&	O
to	O
own	O
the	O
truth	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
advisable	O
upon	O
all	O
accounts	O
to	O
have	O
every	O
thing	O
ready	O
before	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
furniture	O
to	O
Avoid	O
disputes	O
--	O
which	O
frighten	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wits	O
--	O
if	O
Sharpe	B-pers
has	O
not	O
sold	O
Mr	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
s	O
parlour	O
Stove	O
he	O
may	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
for	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
that	O
rumfordis	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
sure	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
return	O
to	O
Wing	B-place
--	O
but	O
I	O
gueſs	O
within	O
three	O
Weeks	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
Baily	B-pers
to	O
fetch	O
home	O
the	O
Whisky	O
the	O
first	O
Leisure	O
day	O
--	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
written	O
to	O
Stevens	B-pers
--	O
&	O
she	O
informs	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
rest	O
satisfied	O
that	O
all	O
shall	O
go	O
well	O
.	O
however	O
she	O
will	O
write	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
divert	O
you	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
with	O
an	O
Artifice	O
which	O
exceeds	O
all	O
belief	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
Answer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
Apology	O
from	O
Either	O
Party	O
I	O
neither	O
expect	O
it	O
or	O
desire	O
it	O
--	O
both	O
father	O
&	O
daughter	O
had	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
to	O
sneer	O
at	O
me	O
--	O
for	O
granting	O
Anne	O
her	O
Pardon	O
.	O
&	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
understand	O
without	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
a	O
misconception	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fool	O
very	O
likely	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
Either	O
father	O
or	O
daughter	O
,	O
are	O
usually	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
information	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
highly	O
approve	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
--	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
forwarder	O
in	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
than	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
3	O
Months	O
with	O
Mandaist	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
place	O
the	O
outside	O
is	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
importance	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalebert	I-pers
does	O
all	O
she	O
can	O
to	O
Encourage	O
dreſsing	O
very	O
constantly	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
place	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
however	O
high	O
in	O
situation	O
can	O
be	O
too	O
well	O
Acquainted	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
Household	O
Economy	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
is	O
not	O
quite	O
19	O
--	O
has	O
however	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
every	O
Egg	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
spent	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
the	O
Honours	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
table	O
since	O
15	O
--	O
she	O
Carves	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
Father	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
young	O
Lady	O
--	O
quite	O
Youthful	O
--	O
not	O
Precieuse	O
--	O
but	O
of	O
a	O
serious	O
turn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
convinc	O
'd	O
that	O
indulgence	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
plan	O
for	O
Education	O
--	O
that	O
these	O
Leper	O
Children	O
are	O
more	O
Noisy	O
than	O
many	O
others	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
confeſs	O
--	O
but	O
amongst	O
the	O
Seven	O
--	O
not	O
one	O
nor	O
two	O
a	O
fit	O
--	O
or	O
have	O
the	O
smallest	O
particle	O
of	O
jealousy	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
their	O
disposition	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jelabert	I-pers
does	O
not	O
get	O
well	O
but	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
high	O
Spirits	O
--	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
dupe	O
of	O
the	O
reports	O
which	O
are	O
so	O
industriously	O
circulated	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
without	O
a	O
Civil	O
War	O
(	O
which	O
God	O
avert	O
.	O
)	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
present	O
Vile	O
adminestration	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
places	O
--	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
however	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
us	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Ministers	O
bought	O
the	O
Union	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Cornwallis	I-pers
that	O
the	O
roman	O
Catholicks	O
should	O
be	O
prefered	O
--	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
this	O
agreement	O
without	O
consulting	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
--	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
appris	O
'd	O
of	O
this	O
measure	O
he	O
flew	O
out	O
&	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
consent	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
Coronation	O
oath	O
for	O
any	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
set	O
of	O
Men	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
consulted	O
the	B-pers
Arch	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
&	O
also	O
the	O
Speaker	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
a	O
great	O
favourite	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
extremely	O
positive	O
upon	O
this	O
Subject	O
--	O
the	O
Ministers	O
say	O
on	O
their	O
part	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Cornwallis	I-pers
will	O
resign	O
--	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
recollect	O
Lord	O
Fitzwilliam	B-pers
s	O
was	O
recall	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
upon	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Countenancing	O
the	O
roman	O
Catholic	O
Cause	O
.	O
this	O
new	O
Scheme	O
has	O
offended	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
off	O
in	O
opposition	O
&	O
gratton	B-pers
the	O
Irish	O
Orator	O
&	O
Patriot	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
Ponsoby	B-pers
's	O
Borough	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
chosen	O
for	O
Wicklow	B-place
in	O
opposition	O
to	O
the	O
Buckingham	B-place
Alias	O
Nugent	O
interest	O
this	O
last	O
piece	O
of	O
News	O
will	O
interest	O
Sir	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Lovett	I-pers
--	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Lambton	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
in	O
this	O
Days	O
paper	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
of	O
or	O
more	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
s	O
death	O
behave	O
respectably	O
,	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
our	O
frail	O
Sex	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
reflections	O
which	O
will	O
recur	O
to	O
the	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Creation	O
--	O
&	O
how	O
they	O
will	O
again	O
revive	O
the	O
Story	O
of	O
the	O
Ephesian	O
Matron	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
your	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
hurt	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
any	O
Answer	O
from	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
:	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
her	O
Letter	O
of	O
to	O
morrow	O
I	O
shall	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
dispatches	O
--	O
I	O
trust	O
her	O
eyes	O
are	O
opening	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
their	O
Material	O
Advantage	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
open	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
yesterday	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
she	O
seems	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
but	O
is	O
in	O
great	O
anxiety	O
.	O
indeed	O
I	O
may	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Equally	O
in	O
Trouble	O
.	O
our	O
worthy	O
&	O
excellent	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
D'Oyly	I-pers
is	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
death	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
account	O
,	O
her	O
desorder	O
is	O
a	O
Pleurisy	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
getting	O
better	O
but	O
has	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
relapses	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
five	O
Times	O
bled	O
.	O
at	O
past	O
70.	O
that	O
I	O
dread	O
to	O
morrow	O
I	O
wrote	O
yesterday	O
to	O
a	O
Confidential	O
upper	O
Man	O
servant	O
,	O
&	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
us	O
all	O
in	O
any	O
Situation	O
,	O
Either	O
in	O
Affliction	O
.	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Calmer	O
moments	O
of	O
our	O
lives	O
,	O
a	O
fast	O
,	O
a	O
faithful	O
&	O
a	O
tender	O
friend	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
Love	O
her	O
sincerely	O
--	O
besides	O
all	O
these	O
excellent	O
qualities	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
an	O
irreparable	O
Loſs	O
--	O
for	O
her	O
goodneſ	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
verbal	O
kindneſs	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
pecuniary	O
loſs	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
large	O
presents	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
Money	O
--	O
but	O
What	O
saved	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
--	O
&	O
made	O
her	O
appear	O
more	O
decent	O
than	O
she	O
could	O
or	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Mendip	I-pers
my	O
Heart	O
bleeds	O
in	O
pints	O
.	O
never	O
were	O
two	O
Sisters	O
,	O
more	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
her	O
Lord	O
at	O
87	O
or	O
8	O
is	O
wonderful	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Understanding	O
&	O
appearance	O
--	O
but	O
extremely	O
Croſs	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
snaps	O
her	O
every	O
word	O
he	O
speaks	O
.	O
with	O
all	O
this	O
attendance	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
requires	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
s	O
Society	O
was	O
a	O
cordial	O
&	O
one	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
.	O
if	O
in	O
Case	O
she	O
sld	O
survive	O
her	O
Lord	O
--	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
Grieve	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
but	O
such	O
is	O
this	O
melancholy	O
fate	O
of	O
humanity	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
is	O
also	O
very	O
much	O
indispos	O
'd	O
&	O
confin	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
will	O
find	O
a	O
resource	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
--	O
Adieu	O
Love	O
to	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
the	O
dear	O
Lou	B-pers
--	O
believe	O
me	O
truly	O
yrs	O
DB	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walden	B-place
Feby	O
Eight	O
1801	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	I-pers
2nd	I-pers
Baron	I-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
