TOKEN	NE
in	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
be	O
typed	O
King	O
's	O
Street	O
Novr	O
.	O
20-	O
th	O
1783	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
It	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
in	O
this	O
diſsipated	O
Town	B-place
to	O
do	O
what	O
one	O
wishes	O
or	O
likes	O
best	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
every	O
moment	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
Town	B-place
and	O
was	O
always	O
prevented	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
has	O
received	O
your	O
Note	O
and	O
desires	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
His	O
respectfull	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
accompany	O
me	O
to	O
Bullstrode	B-place
on	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
and	O
where	O
we	O
propose	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
Dinner	O
time	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
there	O
is	O
busineſs	O
in	O
the	O
H	O
.	O
of	O
Commons	O
&	O
my	O
private	O
busineſs	O
will	O
require	O
my	O
returning	O
to	O
Town	B-place
that	O
day	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
require	O
Charles	B-pers
attendance	O
in	O
the	O
H	O
.	O
of	O
C	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
this	O
arrangement	O
is	O
not	O
perfectly	O
agreable	O
at	O
Bullstrode	B-place
let	O
us	O
know	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
alter	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
write	O
I	O
shall	O
conclude	O
all	O
is	O
settled	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
us	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
yours	O
most	O
affectioly	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
W.H	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
