TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
it	O
is	O
now	O
more	O
Time	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
reckon	O
--	O
since	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
leave	O
Margate	B-place
without	O
knowing	O
in	O
what	O
situation	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
Find	O
you	O
a	O
ll	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
out	O
wandering	O
in	O
the	O
Derbysh	B-place
Caverns	O
whether	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
has	O
another	O
Child	O
whether	O
your	O
agreeable	O
Companions	O
are	O
in	O
C	O
largis	O
Street	O
or	O
improving	O
the	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Country	O
friends	O
of	O
a	O
ll	O
this	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
ignorant	O
as	O
a	O
Post	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
a	O
is	O
a	O
point	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
interested	O
&	O
anxious	O
for	O
the	O
Health	O
of	O
the	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
thing	O
or	O
Person	O
--	O
interesting	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
Margate	B-place
but	O
that	O
yr	O
flirt	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
his	O
f	O
Wife	O
&	O
Friend	O
paſses	O
the	O
Evenings	O
much	O
oftener	O
ofter	O
more	O
to	O
to	O
their	O
mind	O
by	O
a	O
Solitary	O
Candle	O
than	O
in	O
Crowded	O
Rooms	O
where	O
the	O
re	O
are	O
such	O
multitudes	O
pour	O
'd	O
in	O
from	O
Sea	O
&	O
Land	O
you	O
would	O
think	O
yrself	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
grea	O
t	O
mask	O
'd	O
Ball	O
of	O
Europe	B-place
West	B-place
&	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
&	O
yet	O
very	O
few	O
na	O
mes	O
famil	O
iar	O
in	O
the	O
Aſsemblys	O
you	O
frequent	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
abominably	O
I	O
write	O
so	O
you	O
must	O
thank	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
thrown	O
my	O
Scratch	O
es	O
at	O
your	O
Head	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
--	O
you	O
wil	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
is	O
rather	O
better	O
--	O
alas	O
my	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
now	O
with	O
them	O
embarks	O
at	O
Margate	B-place
for	O
France	B-place
alas	O
this	O
P	O
l	O
ace	O
so	O
welcome	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
world	O
is	O
very	O
mischievous	O
to	O
me	O
happy	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
some	O
more	O
such	O
tho	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Claſs	O
send	O
th	O
eir	O
minds	O
abroad	O
are	O
Clipt	O
in	O
Wing	O
some	O
how	O
when	O
their	O
attempt	O
to	O
transfer	O
their	O
Person	O
&	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
their	O
talents	O
into	O
foreign	O
La	O
nds	O
how	O
can	O
I	O
refrain	O
when	O
the	O
word	O
talents	O
starts	O
up	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
in	O
perspective	O
,	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
so	O
vain	O
that	O
I	O
venture	O
to	O
scratch	O
to	O
to	O
right	O
&	O
left	O
as	O
you	O
see	O
tho	O
I	O
only	O
intended	O
a	O
Billet	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
charming	O
Letter	O
--	O
whether	O
that	O
fine	O
Poem	O
will	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Preſs	O
we	O
shall	O
talk	O
off	O
--	O
When	O
we	O
meet	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
joined	O
the	O
added	O
lines	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
3	O
to	O
4	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
flirting	O
upon	O
--	O
the	O
Pantiles	B-place
of	O
Tunbridge	B-place
be	O
it	O
so	O
let	O
us	O
meet	O
a	O
les	O
Soupé	O
?	O
en	O
d	O
i	O
shabille	O
&	O
yu	O
y	O
u	O
ou	O
not	O
tire	O
of	O
yr	O
friends	O
Handcock	B-pers
&	O
Veseys	B-pers
Margate	B-place
is	O
sad	O
without	O
the	B-pers
d	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
how	O
does	O
she	O
Margate	B-place
for	O
this	O
month	O
at	O
least	O
15	O
To	O
Vesey	B-pers
