TOKEN	NE
11	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1779	O
Windsor	B-place
My	O
Dear	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
Necklace	O
as	O
you	O
desired	O
&	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
was	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
&	O
admired	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
Nothing	O
facetious	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
has	O
hitherto	O
happened	O
what	O
this	O
day	O
&	O
to	O
morrow	O
may	O
produce	O
you	O
shall	O
certainly	O
know	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bludworth	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Arnald	I-pers
&	O
Genl	B-pers
Freitag	I-pers
are	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Chase	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
compleat	O
day	O
the	O
Lord	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
think	O
how	O
Lovely	O
the	O
Musick	O
Room	O
was	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bludworth	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
,	O
&	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
pity	O
me	O
?	O
&	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
did	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
force	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
before	O
he	O
compaſsed	O
it	O
for	O
I	O
tried	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
submit	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
grace	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Princes	O
are	O
arrived	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Affy	O
Y-	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
My	O
Love	O
to	O
Moumou	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
½	O
pt	O
two	O
Monday	O
--	O
