TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	B-place
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
1789	O
Dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
recieved	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Letter	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
writing	O
You	O
from	O
Bristol-Wells	B-place
,	O
in	O
compliance	O
with	O
your	O
request	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
returned	O
several	O
Packets	O
of	O
the	O
Manuscripts	O
which	O
You	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
since	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
Two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
divided	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Rev	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mr-	I-pers
Collier	I-pers
's	O
Sonnets	O
in	O
Two	O
Franks	O
,	O
&	O
enclosed	O
them	O
also	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
arrived	O
safely	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
shall	O
interest	O
your	O
Concern	O
by	O
telling	O
You	O
that	O
my	O
excellent	O
Father	O
,	O
whom	O
You	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
so	O
much	O
admired	O
,	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
shocking	O
fall	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
which	O
has	O
confined	O
him	O
now	O
near	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
weight	O
on	O
his	O
Hip	O
&	O
Thigh	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
or	O
dislocate	O
any	O
bone	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Muscles	O
recieved	O
such	O
a	O
violent	O
bruise	O
&	O
general	O
Shock	O
,	O
that	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
any	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Leg	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
his	O
Bed	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Rhumatism	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
part	O
affected	O
,	O
added	O
very	O
considerably	O
to	O
his	O
Sufferings	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
come	O
down-stairs	O
only	O
within	O
these	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
moves	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
two	O
Men-Servants	O
&	O
his	O
Crutches	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
from	O
Andover	B-place
,	O
&	O
another	O
of	O
great	O
repute	O
,	O
from	O
Winchester	B-place
,	O
attend	O
him	O
;	O
They	O
do	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
irrecoverable	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
hold	O
out	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
yet	O
be	O
tedious	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Spirits	O
are	O
extremely	O
dejected	O
from	O
the	O
total	O
alteration	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
which	O
You	O
know	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
active	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
perswasion	O
that	O
He	O
never	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
leg	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
He	O
has	O
returns	O
frequently	O
of	O
violent	O
fits	O
of	O
Pain	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
sympathise	O
with	O
us	O
all	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
&	O
particularly	O
with	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
's	O
tender	O
feelings	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
She	O
exerts	O
herself	O
wonderfully	O
&	O
her	O
tranquil	O
mind	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Support	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
her	O
charming	O
&	O
just	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
trying	O
Events	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
You	O
the	O
Riddles	O
,	O
the	O
Quipos	O
,	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
french	O
Songs	O
;	O
Over	O
the	O
aria	O
d'anfoſsi	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
misfortune	O
with	O
my	O
Ink	O
has	O
befallen	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
scarcely	O
dare	O
venture	O
to	O
excuse	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
rely	O
on	O
the	O
Generosity	O
of	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
Mind	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
knows	O
how	O
to	O
forgive	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
He	O
will	O
accept	O
of	O
my	O
best	O
Thanks	O
for	O
his	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
Mischief	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
presume	O
You	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
your	O
elegant	O
Poet	O
&	O
Philosopher	O
of	O
Derby	B-place
,	O
Dr-	B-pers
Darwin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
so	O
highly	O
charmed	O
us	O
with	O
his	O
“	O
Botanical	O
Garden	O
or	O
the	O
Loves	O
of	O
the	O
Plants	O
”	O
.	O
Surely	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
to	O
boast	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
ingenious	O
Production	O
for	O
many	O
long	O
Years	O
!	O
so	O
novel	O
in	O
it	O
's	O
Imagination	O
,	O
&	O
such	O
beautiful	O
Lines	O
!	O
How	O
charmingly	O
too	O
has	O
He	O
introduced	O
your	O
Friend	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
!	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
join	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Compliments	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Little	O
Catherine	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
sends	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
lively	O
friend	O
your	O
Darling	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
You	O
will	O
naturally	O
allow	O
of	O
my	O
concluding	O
Abruptly	O
in	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
Trouble	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
frequently	O
called	O
off	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
must	O
now	O
subscribe	O
myself	O
Your	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
E——	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
&	O
gt	O
;	O
Chester	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
