TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
only	O
within	O
this	O
Hour	O
my	O
dr	O
Friend	O
red	O
y	O
--	O
Note	O
wc̅h	O
is	O
dated	O
yesterday	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
when	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
about	O
find	O
me	O
generally	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
&	O
four	O
&	O
always	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
morrow	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
at	O
three	O
if	O
it	O
y	O
ou	O
can	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
alone	O
at	O
two	O
,	O
when	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
generally	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
)	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
Every	O
Body	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
deliver	O
your	O
Love	O
&	O
Comps	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
may	O
return	O
them	O
warmly	O
.	O
Me	B-pers
de	I-pers
La	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
intended	O
calling	O
upon	O
you	O
this	O
Morg	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Cough	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
the	O
Cold	O
that	O
every	O
body	O
has	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
thank	O
God	O
otherways	O
well	O
--	O
very	O
Affly	O
my	O
dr	O
Yr	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
½	O
pt	O
3	O
Sunday	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
