TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
arrived	O
here	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
long	O
in	O
settling	O
our	O
busineſs	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
every	O
thing	O
arranged	O
in	O
so	O
clear	O
a	O
manner	O
&	O
so	O
corresponding	O
with	O
your	O
account	O
that	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
difficulty	O
occurrd	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
event	O
great	O
expence	O
must	O
be	O
incurrd	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
good	O
management	O
considerable	O
abuses	O
were	O
prevented	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
his	O
his	O
Wife	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
keys	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
drawers	O
£100	O
belong	O
ing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
£30	O
in	O
a	O
draft	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
mention	O
to	O
me	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
his	O
laying	O
hands	O
upon	O
the	O
£100	O
was	O
certainly	O
improper	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
none	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
expences	O
.	O
Since	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
s	O
arrival	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
impertinent	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
complaining	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
disappointed	O
in	O
his	O
late	O
meeting	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
expected	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
gift	O
to	O
ameliorate	O
his	O
circumstances	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
intend	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
ill	O
founded	O
expectations	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
engage	O
in	O
no	O
further	O
correspondence	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
expect	O
in	O
future	O
every	O
instance	O
of	O
hostility	O
against	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
returning	O
you	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
a	O
Deed	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
£200	O
as	O
a	O
testimony	O
of	O
my	O
regard	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
her	O
fidelity	O
&	O
attachment	O
to	O
my	O
late	O
dear	O
daughter	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miss	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
to	O
aſure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
oliged	O
&	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
Bath	B-place
July	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mostly	O
Mr	B-pers
Fredk	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
30	O
July	O
1810	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
