TOKEN	NE
11	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
1799	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Having	O
in	O
due	O
form	O
spit	O
on	O
the	O
Green	O
Wafer	O
,	O
and	O
closed	O
your	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
commanded	O
my	O
Man	O
John	B-pers
to	O
carry	O
it	O
himself	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
allow	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
Creature	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
Me	O
the	O
pretence	O
for	O
Your	O
gadding	O
abroad	O
.	O
The	O
Archy	O
Cathcarts	O
have	O
likewise	O
had	O
the	O
humanity	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
The	O
He	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
soon	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
She	O
one	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
You	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
Dinner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Greville	O
Mansfields	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Card	O
to	O
feast	O
with	O
the	O
Portland	O
Place	O
Mansfields	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	B-pers
of	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
is	O
confined	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
Cold	O
,	O
or	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
of	I-pers
Ditto	I-pers
,	O
in	O
attendance	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
I	O
,	O
inadvertently	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
disobedience	O
to	O
your	O
commands	O
,	O
betrayed	O
your	O
intention	O
of	O
being	O
here	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
But	O
,	O
as	O
your	O
determination	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
point	O
,	O
is	O
fixed	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
much	O
consequence	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Best	O
Love	O
and	O
Affections	O
to	O
the	O
Leighton	O
Houseites	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affecte	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
To	O
convince	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
Wafers	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
practice	O
is	O
filthy	O
London	B-place
,	O
Eighth	O
April	O
1799	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
