TOKEN	NE
21	O
st	O
.	O
May	O
1780	O
Sunday	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
love	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
happy	O
by	O
recg	O
your	O
little	O
note	O
--	O
pray	O
explain	O
--	O
you	O
have	O
rais	O
'd	O
my	O
curiosity	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
highest	O
pitch	O
--	O
&	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
low	O
--	O
surely	O
my	O
Friend	O
could	O
not	O
in	O
those	O
few	O
hours	O
of	O
Yesterday	O
find	O
cause	O
to	O
injure	O
both	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
repose	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q	I-pers
last	O
night	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
T——	B-place
she	O
said	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
kindest	O
manner	O
imaginable	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
drawing	O
Room	O
will	O
not	O
last	O
long	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
late	O
before	O
Miſs	B-pers
G——	I-pers
sets	O
out	O
--	O
Adieu	O
for	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
shall	O
begin	O
from	O
yesterday	O
--	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
journal	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
too	O
sincerely	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
interested	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
trifling	O
occurrence	O
Adieu	O
