TOKEN	NE
Paris	B-place
Augst	O
:	O
17	O
th	O
:	O
1787	O
Whilst	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Boy	O
is	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
&	O
kind	O
Friend	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
worthy	O
Husband	O
,	O
how	O
very	O
very	O
much	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
Him	O
for	O
the	O
friendly	O
offer	O
you	O
made	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Plan	O
as	O
you	O
see	O
is	O
changed	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
can	O
never	O
forgot	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
intended	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
Line	O
from	O
Calais	B-place
--	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
much	O
Comfort	O
or	O
indeed	O
any	O
to	O
have	O
sent	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
--	O
The	O
Dr	O
:	O
Boy	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
Amiens	B-place
,	O
&	O
my	O
days	O
Time	O
is	O
past	O
in	O
constant	O
anxiety	O
,	O
&	O
earnest	O
Endeavours	O
to	O
become	O
resigned	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
that	O
gracious	O
&	O
all	O
wise	O
Being	O
,	O
who	O
alone	O
knows	O
what	O
is	O
but	O
for	O
his	O
poor	O
dependent	O
Creatures	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
change	O
of	O
Climate	O
will	O
do	O
no	O
good	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Air	O
is	O
delicious	O
for	O
those	O
who	O
can	O
bear	O
heat	O
(	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
wd	O
enjoy	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
enjoy	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Boy	O
is	O
not	O
overcome	O
as	O
I	O
sd	O
:	O
have	O
expected	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
is	O
thinner	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
Calais	B-place
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
his	O
Cough	O
is	O
certainly	O
leſs	O
frequent	O
&	O
his	O
Pulse	O
better	O
--	O
his	O
great	O
thinneſs	O
&	O
Looks	O
are	O
very	O
alarming	O
--	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
my	O
anxious	O
Eyes	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
all	O
around	O
me	O
--	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
heavy	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
asleep	O
after	O
his	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
looks	O
make	O
my	O
Heart	O
sink	O
within	O
me	O
.	O
Last	O
post	O
brought	O
me	O
an	O
acct	O
:	O
of	O
Dr	O
:	O
Lord	B-pers
C——	I-pers
being	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
Cold	O
&	O
Fever	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
complains	O
of	O
the	O
sultry	O
Weather	O
,	O
I	O
trimble	O
lest	O
She	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
her	O
bilious	O
Fever	O
--	O
do	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
She	O
is	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
She	O
promises	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
--	O
She	O
complains	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
&	O
Eyes	O
&	O
bids	O
me	O
not	O
be	O
alarmed	O
if	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
writes	O
for	O
her	O
next	O
.	O
I	O
pray	O
God	O
She	O
may	O
be	O
soon	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
&	O
yr	O
:	O
best	O
Friend	O
&	O
your	O
Dr	O
:	O
little	O
Marianne	B-pers
are	O
well	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
pray	O
kiſs	O
the	O
little	O
Dear	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
sake	O
.	O
My	O
p	O
oor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
has	O
still	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
is	O
better	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
sadly	O
wretched	O
about	O
our	O
poor	O
Boy	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
seem	O
inured	O
to	O
anxiety	O
&	O
sorrow	O
--	O
&	O
If	O
I	O
cd	O
:	O
think	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Husband	O
being	O
better	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
his	O
Trials	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
paſs	O
my	O
future	O
Life	O
in	O
tranquil	O
sorrow	O
&	O
resignation	O
--	O
God	O
grant	O
I	O
may	O
poſseſs	O
the	O
last	O
bleſsing	O
Sunday	O
Augt	O
:	O
19	O
.	O
Another	O
kind	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
kind	O
Friend	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
10000	O
Thanks	O
&	O
tell	O
you	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Boy	O
has	O
been	O
better	O
those	O
2	O
last	O
Days	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
a	O
lovely	O
Villa	O
at	O
Paſsy	B-place
--	O
sweet	O
Air	O
&	O
near	O
the	O
Bois	B-place
de	I-place
Boulogne	I-place
--	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
find	O
benefit	O
--	O
if	O
it	O
please	O
God	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
yrs	O
:	O
very	O
gratefully	O
&	O
affly	O
:	O
Louisa	B-pers
we	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
better	O
Spirits	O
.	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
.	O
--	O
PC	B-pers
&	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
kind	O
Love	O
They	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
grateful	O
Acknowledgements	O
to	O
yr	O
good	O
&	O
worthy	O
Husband	O
.	O
pray	O
tell	O
Him	O
how	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
we	O
are	O
&	O
to	O
you	O
Dr	O
:	O
kind	O
Friend	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Angleterre	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
