TOKEN	NE
At	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
's	O
Newsells	O
.	O
Royston	B-place
Deceb	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
Alth	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Frank	O
for	O
this	O
Letter	O
--	O
yet	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
leaves	O
us	O
tomorrow	O
for	O
London	B-place
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
the	O
desire	O
I	O
feel	O
to	O
remind	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
of	O
her	O
late	O
Solitary	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
Glad	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
alth	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Carriage	O
for	O
8	O
by	O
the	O
day	O
till	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
safely	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
most	O
cordially	O
&	O
kindly	O
received	O
by	O
my	O
Host	O
.	O
&	O
Hosteſs	O
.	O
also	O
by	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
&	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Emigrant	O
of	O
distinction	O
a	O
Count	B-pers
Abi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
a	O
miserable	O
object	O
.	O
having	O
been	O
terrified	O
almost	O
to	O
Anihilation	O
by	O
the	O
Virgins	O
&	O
their	O
daughter	O
.	O
whose	O
disappointment	O
of	O
their	O
Pleas	O
made	O
them	O
so	O
outrageous	O
that	O
I	O
actually	O
fear	O
'd	O
they	O
wd	O
seize	O
their	O
Prey	O
--	O
&	O
not	O
suffer	O
her	O
or	O
me	O
to	O
depart	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
my	O
departure	O
a	O
secret	O
til	O
the	O
Sunday	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
troubled	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Note	O
.	O
Which	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Westminster	O
Magazine	O
Parcel	O
stating	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
that	O
the	O
dates	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
I	O
therin	O
begg	O
'd	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
suffer	O
my	O
Letters	O
&	O
my	O
Servant	O
s	O
Letters	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
cd	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
forward	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
giving	O
the	O
direction	O
as	O
above	O
--	O
I	O
likewise	O
stated	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
sending	O
any	O
letters	O
to	O
Wing	B-place
.	O
but	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
orders	O
with	O
Baily	B-pers
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
this	O
trouble	O
.	O
&	O
grant	O
me	O
my	O
Petition	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
real	O
pleasure	O
.	O
comfort	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
add	O
Luxury	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
.	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
Library	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Choice	O
Collection	O
of	O
Books	O
--	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Illustrious	O
finely	O
engraved	O
Prints	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
any	O
Collection	O
&	O
remarkably	O
interesting	O
.	O
for	O
are	O
not	O
very	O
illustrious	O
People	O
of	O
Antient	O
,	O
times	O
.	O
but	O
all	O
those	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
times	O
&	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
our	O
remembrances	O
,	O
Buonaparté	B-pers
,	O
Washington	B-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
these	O
give	O
in	O
to	O
pleasant	O
discourse	O
.	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
that	O
Buonaparté	B-pers
is	O
not	O
what	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Man	O
.	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
inconsistent	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Majority	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
.	O
Washington	B-pers
was	O
certainly	O
good	O
&	O
Great	O
.	O
Count	B-pers
Abi	I-pers
.	O
was	O
not	O
only	O
happy	O
in	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
lady	O
whose	O
namesakes	O
he	O
is	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
Acquainted	O
with	O
in	O
France	B-place
.	O
but	O
with	O
one	O
who	O
certainly	O
agrees	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Buonaparté	B-pers
will	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
restore	O
the	O
Monarchy	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
persuaded	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Powers	O
in	O
Europe	O
will	O
Laſser	O
lui	O
faire	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
French	O
Man	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
quiet	O
--	O
he	O
spends	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
drawing	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
Artist	O
--	O
he	O
last	O
Night	O
drew	O
his	O
own	O
Chateau	O
.	O
at	O
Abi	O
.	O
&	O
he	O
would	O
describe	O
it	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
zeres	O
ze	O
Bed	O
.	O
zere	O
s.	O
ze	O
shiminé	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
perspiration	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
perceive	O
it	O
--	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
always	O
wish	O
for	O
your	O
company	O
.	O
is	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
strange	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
this	O
morning	O
told	O
Mrs	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
that	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
for	O
your	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Walking	O
over	O
the	O
very	O
pretiest	O
kitchen	O
Garden	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
--	O
Great	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
surrounded	O
by	O
a	O
rich	O
Bank	O
finely	O
planted	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
entirely	O
Picturesque	O
The	O
Plots	O
for	O
common	O
garden	O
stuff	O
.	O
are	O
array	O
'd	O
like	O
Parterres	O
&	O
the	O
same	O
for	O
Pot	O
herbs	O
.	O
Sallading	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
has	O
all	O
compartment	O
.	O
a	O
lovely	O
green	O
House	O
.	O
well	O
stoc	O
'd	O
.	O
&	O
also	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Grape	O
House	O
.	O
Peach	O
House	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
Hot	O
House	O
.	O
in	O
their	O
different	O
appartments	O
.	O
I	O
there	O
saw	O
several	O
curiosity	O
,	O
the	O
Cotton	O
tree	O
Inc.	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Cane	O
.	O
these	O
were	O
new	O
to	O
my	O
ignorant	O
Eyes	O
--	O
tho	O
What	O
wd	O
I	O
give	O
for	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
all	O
this	O
managed	O
into	O
the	O
greatest	O
order	O
.	O
&	O
at	O
an	O
Expence	O
which	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Trifling	O
in	O
comparison	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
sld	O
have	O
suppos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
had	O
heard	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
.	O
what	O
Mr	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
has	O
done	O
for	O
his	O
daughters	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
has	O
£300	O
per	O
annum	O
.	O
his	O
2	O
other	O
daughters	O
the	O
same	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Moiety	O
of	O
a	O
real	O
Estate	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
his	O
other	O
daughters	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
.	O
no	O
one	O
knows	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
but	O
the	O
Chere	O
Amie	O
has	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
quite	O
decided	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
H——n	I-pers
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
at	O
Court	O
.	O
yr	O
Uncle	O
was	O
Invited	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Grenville	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
absurd	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
bring	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Itallian	O
Ladies	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
knew	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
sent	O
word	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Convenient	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
to	O
come	O
that	O
day	O
--	O
he	O
wd	O
take	O
some	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Man	O
dinner	O
--	O
some	O
people	O
have	O
sent	O
excuses	O
when	O
they	O
hear	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
like	O
Mr	B-pers
P	I-pers
I	O
sd	O
never	O
ask	O
these	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
again	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
my	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
concludes	O
me	O
most	O
truly	O
&	O
affecly	O
yrs	O
DBloſset	B-pers
I	O
go	O
to	O
Audley	O
End	O
on	O
fridy	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
til	O
the	O
Post	O
arrives	O
here	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
Letters	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
.	O
before	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
received	O
here	O
--	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Hoble	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
,	O
Audley	O
End	O
.	O
Saffron	B-place
Walden	I-place
Eſsex	B-place
.	O
Single	O
Sheet	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
