TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Hammy	B-pers
Will	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
order	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
Dinner	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
till	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
till	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
their	O
Majesties	O
do	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
&	O
seen	O
Turton	B-pers
(	O
who	O
enquired	O
very	O
kindly	O
after	O
you	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
no	O
Blister	O
yet	O
thank	O
God	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
dear	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizt	I-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
kiſs	O
Pſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	O
love	O
to	O
Moumou	B-pers
&	O
Che	B-pers
Che	I-pers
&	O
aſsure	O
yr	O
self	O
my	O
Dearest	O
of	O
my	O
truly	O
Maternal	O
affection	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
my	O
Brother	O
left	O
Coxheath	B-place
this	O
Morg	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
their	O
Majesties	O
a	O
charming	O
acc̅t	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
Thursday	O
pt	O
2	O
--	O
5	O
th	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1788	O
Queens	O
House	O
