TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
13	O
th	O
:	O
Novr-	O
1780	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
next	O
I	O
propose	O
leaving	O
this	O
agreable	O
City	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
intention	O
of	O
paying	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
You	O
in	O
person	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Birthday	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
at	O
last	O
suspend	O
your	O
joy	O
at	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
seeing	O
me	O
'till	O
that	O
distant	O
period	O
.	O
You	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
occupied	O
with	O
attendance	O
on	O
the	B-pers
P.	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
leſs	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
preparing	O
for	O
my	O
departure	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
not	O
improbable	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
visit	O
the	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
before	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
and	O
still	O
am	O
occupied	O
very	O
busy	O
arranging	O
my	O
Affairs	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
arrival	O
at	O
Welwyn	B-place
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
'till	O
I	O
do	O
so	O
shall	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
This	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
be	O
idle	O
,	O
will	O
I	O
suspect	O
be	O
perfectly	O
agreable	O
to	O
your	O
lazyneſs	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
people	O
south	O
of	O
Tweed	B-place
distracted	O
?	O
What	O
did	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Beaulieu	I-pers
mean	O
by	O
his	O
behaviour	O
to	O
the	B-pers
D	I-pers
of	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
He	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
forbid	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
Royal	O
presence	O
--	O
Prince	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
's	O
military	O
promotion	O
&	O
intended	O
journey	O
pleases	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
both	O
he	O
&	O
the	B-pers
P.	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
have	O
sensible	O
men	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Young	O
ones	O
will	O
ruin	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
arrived	O
here	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
at	O
Shaw	O
Park	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
expect	O
them	O
in	O
Edinr-	B-place
tomorrow	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
a	O
Beauty	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
something	O
very	O
pleasing	O
in	O
her	O
Countenance	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
seem	O
happy	O
&	O
conten	O
d	O
ted	O
.	O
The	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
proposes	O
to	O
loiter	O
away	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
till	O
after	O
Christmaſs	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
your	O
character	O
of	O
Mr-	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
formerly	O
liked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
really	O
long	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
forgot	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
is	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
s	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
much	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
threatens	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
goes	O
to	O
England	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
yours	O
very	O
sincerely	O
&	O
affectionately	O
N——	B-pers
