TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
yesterday	O
has	O
reliev	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
much	O
anxiety	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
;	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
attention	O
that	O
you	O
experience	O
is	O
highly	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
your	O
Friends	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
must	O
esteem	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
testimony	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
conduct	O
is	O
approved	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
settled	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
within	O
3	O
miles	O
of	O
Dublin	B-place
since	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
&	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
&	O
convenient	O
residence	O
,	O
the	O
situation	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
excell	O
'd	O
as	O
it	O
commands	O
the	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Bay	B-place
of	I-place
Dublin	I-place
with	O
the	O
opposite	O
Hills	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Villas	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
farm	O
of	O
about	O
fifty	O
English	O
Acres	O
,	O
the	O
half	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
Lawn	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
pastur	O
'd	O
by	O
sheep	O
&	O
other	O
cattle	O
,	O
which	O
enliven	O
the	O
scene	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
other	O
respects	O
.	O
With	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
small	O
Parish	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
so	O
eligible	O
an	O
acquisition	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
justifying	O
my	O
absenting	O
myself	O
from	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
North	B-place
of	I-place
Ireland	I-place
,	O
of	O
all	O
places	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
the	O
most	O
detestable	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
present	O
any	O
chance	O
of	O
attaining	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
without	O
my	O
apprehensions	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
last	O
reduced	O
to	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
giving	O
up	O
that	O
Living	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
residence	O
there	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
insisted	O
upon	O
;	O
this	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
distreſsing	O
reduction	O
of	O
my	O
income	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
of	O
two	O
evils	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
has	O
met	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
affliction	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
second	O
within	O
these	O
few	O
years	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
remember	O
right	O
he	O
loſs	O
'd	O
a	O
son	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
a	O
horse	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
has	O
transmitted	O
me	O
the	O
Papers	O
you	O
mention	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
returned	O
them	O
signed	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
must	O
enjoy	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
connections	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
must	O
feel	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
your	O
society	O
very	O
severely	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
enjoy	O
a	O
good	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
favor	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
has	O
disposed	O
of	O
herself	O
very	O
unfortunately	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
fortune	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
wretched	O
a	O
being	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
any	O
intercourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
daughter	O
about	O
eight	O
months	O
old	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
adding	O
to	O
his	O
family	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
second	O
Daughter	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
Child	O
now	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
&	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
more	O
fortunate	O
than	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
is	O
at	O
last	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
bad	O
consequences	O
of	O
the	O
inoculation	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
well	O
looking	O
boy	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
mentioning	O
some	O
particulars	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
we	O
mean	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
our	O
constant	O
residence	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
next	O
winter	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
expence	O
in	O
the	O
purchase	O
,	O
additions	O
furnishing	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
matter	O
more	O
of	O
prudence	O
than	O
of	O
choice	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Compts	O
.	O
&	O
every	O
good	O
wish	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
August	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
1778	O
Latour	O
--	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
