TOKEN	NE
2	O
d	O
April	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
obliging	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
&	O
wou	O
'd	O
soon	O
have	O
known	O
at	O
Your	O
Door	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
worthy	O
of	O
yr	O
kind	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
heard	O
Yesterday	O
with	O
much	O
Satisfaction	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
More	I-pers
that	O
You	O
were	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
took	O
a	O
Mem̄	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
You	O
,	O
&	O
promis	O
'd	O
myself	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
You	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
great	O
Regard	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
yr	O
faithfull	O
hum	O
ble	O
Servant	O
F.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
