TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
At	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
;	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
pray	O
God	O
send	O
it	O
may	O
turn	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
future	O
happineſs	O
;	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
sincere	O
wish	O
of	O
your	O
constant	O
friend	O
.	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
line	O
by	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
most	O
convenient	O
to	O
your	O
Self	O
;	O
I	O
come	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
musling	O
.	O
--	O
They	O
all	O
join	O
in	O
due	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
your	O
Affct	O
friend	O
.	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Novbr	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
