TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
30	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1784	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Tho	O
'	O
you	O
obstinately	O
persisted	O
in	O
refusing	O
to	O
write	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bachelor	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
flattered	O
myself	O
the	O
respect	O
due	O
to	O
my	O
exalted	O
Station	O
as	O
a	O
Benedict	O
would	O
have	O
induced	O
You	O
to	O
throw	O
away	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
your	O
leisure	O
Minutes	O
in	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Having	O
been	O
disappointed	O
in	O
this	O
hope	O
&	O
Providence	O
having	O
pleased	O
to	O
decree	O
that	O
this	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
rainy	O
Morning	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
Pen	O
to	O
aſsure	O
You	O
that	O
You	O
have	O
frequently	O
been	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
my	O
thoughts	O
and	O
Conversation	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
My	O
Maria	B-pers
loves	O
&	O
esteems	O
You	O
and	O
regrets	O
much	O
the	O
distance	O
which	O
prevents	O
her	O
cultivating	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
and	O
friendship	O
with	O
You	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
the	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
of	O
both	O
of	O
Us	O
--	O
Our	O
journey	O
we	O
made	O
out	O
easily	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
Weather	O
proved	O
favourable	O
,	O
pleasantly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
approved	O
of	O
My	O
choice	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
Seven	O
Weeks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
once	O
experienced	O
an	O
unpleasant	O
Moment	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
's	O
temper	O
is	O
calm	O
and	O
equal	O
,	O
accommodating	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
whims	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
few	O
.	O
She	O
appears	O
contente	O
d	O
with	O
everything	O
and	O
studies	O
to	O
do	O
everything	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
happy	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
myself	O
&	O
Wife	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
expects	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
every	O
hour	O
.	O
A	O
t	O
present	O
her	O
circumference	O
more	O
resembles	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
object	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
Harriot	B-pers
is	O
the	O
happies	O
t	O
creature	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
and	O
paſses	O
mos	O
t	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
with	O
Us	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
has	O
taken	O
a	O
particular	O
Attachment	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
,	O
for	O
entre	O
Nous	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
's	O
hands	O
and	O
to	O
fix	O
her	O
with	O
Us	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
however	O
mention	O
this	O
Scheme	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Parties	O
'till	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
The	O
style	O
of	O
Company	O
She	O
sees	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
's	I-pers
is	O
not	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
chuse	O
a	O
Helpmate	O
from	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
long	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
everything	O
about	O
Yourself	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
very	O
sincere	O
and	O
a	O
ffecti	O
onate	O
friend	O
&	O
brother	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarge	O
s	O
Street	O
London	B-place
