TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
12	O
th	O
-	O
1790	O
Buxton	B-place
My	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
have	O
spent	O
an	O
uncomfortable	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
Father	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
--	O
Not	O
poſseſsing	O
much	O
Sensibility	O
himself	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
judge	O
how	O
cruelly	O
he	O
acts	O
in	O
trifling	O
with	O
other	O
's	O
--	O
he	O
hates	O
to	O
argue	O
upon	O
a	O
Subject	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
playing	O
the	O
same	O
game	O
as	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Jeopardy	O
--	O
Money	O
unfortunately	O
is	O
of	O
t	O
oo	O
precious	O
a	O
Quality	O
in	O
my	O
Father	O
s	O
Eyes	O
&	O
between	O
ourselves	O
to	O
a	O
rich	O
Jew	O
or	O
Jeweſs	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
married	O
us	O
all	O
--	O
Seeing	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
for	O
this	O
Connection	O
he	O
is	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
dilemma	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
surprised	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
Birch	B-place
he	O
has	O
avoided	O
my	O
looks	O
all	O
day	O
&	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
speaking	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
poring	O
his	O
Eyes	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
some	O
sort	O
--	O
several	O
times	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
this	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
interrupted	O
by	O
some	O
Fool	O
or	O
other	O
&	O
I	O
determined	O
upon	O
a	O
conversation	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
to	O
Church	O
&	O
from	O
there	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Longden	I-pers
--	O
Consent	O
he	O
must	O
&	O
will	O
in	O
time	O
--	O
Pray	O
tell	O
Eliza	B-pers
if	O
you	O
think	O
proper	O
that	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
propose	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
give	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
upon	O
ye-	O
marriage	O
1500	O
£	O
,	O
one	O
thousand	O
of	O
which	O
/that	O
in	O
yr-	O
Uncle	O
s	O
hands	O
I	O
will	O
transfer	O
to	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
join	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
in	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
500	O
£	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
sum	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
immediately	O
raised	O
--	O
As	O
She	O
knows	O
our	O
Situation	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
She	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
fortune	O
is	O
&	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
upon	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
our	O
present	O
humour	O
we	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
civil	O
or	O
escape	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
--	O
If	O
Cr	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
of	O
whom	O
&	O
his	O
Connections	O
we	O
certainly	O
know	O
but	O
little	O
)	O
will	O
be	O
properly	O
communicate	O
,	O
He	O
can	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
warmer	O
friend	O
than	O
he	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Chaise	O
and	O
flown	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
on	O
a	O
conversation	O
this	O
morng	O
And	O
my	O
heart	O
rebels	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
must	O
forbid	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
your	O
Husband	O
--	O
Sarah	B-pers
only	O
wanted	O
a	O
knowled	O
ge	O
of	O
herself	O
to	O
have	O
behaved	O
always	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
to	O
deserve	O
yr-	O
warmest	O
Affections	O
&	O
tho	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
painful	O
leſson	O
,	O
She	O
now	O
sees	O
her	O
er	O
ror	O
in	O
idolizing	O
an	O
Object	O
--	O
not	O
quite	O
deserving	O
of	O
that	O
unbounded	O
degree	O
of	O
affectn	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
gain	O
the	O
intelligence	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
send	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
ye-	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
pains	O
in	O
drying	O
the	O
Wafer	O
of	O
my	O
last	O
--	O
Hang	O
Peggy	B-pers
!	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
months	O
notice	O
--	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chetham	I-pers
will	O
make	O
enquiries	O
for	O
a	O
Cook	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
he	O
advises	O
a	O
continuance	O
of	O
the	O
use	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Bath	O
&	O
he	O
's	O
sent	O
me	O
two	O
prescriptions	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
,	O
thō	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
well	O
without	O
them	O
--	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
pain	O
&	O
feel	O
very	O
little	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
well	O
again	O
&	O
restored	O
to	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
nostro	O
Fratello	O
&	O
his	O
Dulcinea	B-pers
del	I-pers
Toboso	I-pers
To	O
Sarah	B-pers
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
before	O
Timothy	B-pers
came	O
&	O
meant	O
to	O
sen	O
d	O
it	O
by	O
ye-	O
Joiner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
