TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
ye	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
Decr	O
.	O
1777	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
My	O
own	O
recovery	O
since	O
my	O
arrival	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
hath	O
not	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
satiſfaction	O
without	O
alloy	O
to	O
myſelf	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
growing	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
mortification	O
of	O
seeing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
invalid	O
tranſferr	O
'd	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
two	O
companions	O
,	O
poor	O
wife	O
and	O
poor	O
dove	O
.	O
Confin	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
week	O
by	O
severe	O
colds	O
,	O
one	O
hung	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
dropp	O
'd	O
her	O
wing	O
;	O
the	O
moſt	O
brilliant	O
sunſhine	O
would	O
often	O
entice	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
which	O
command	O
the	O
whole	O
extent	O
of	O
our	O
delightful	O
situation	O
in	O
the	O
Circus	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
large	O
circumference	O
all	O
alive	O
&	O
crouded	O
with	O
hats	O
,	O
cloaks	O
,	O
capuchins	O
,	O
petticoats	O
,	O
ribbons	O
and	O
shoestrings	O
of	O
all	O
colours	O
in	O
sprightly	O
motion	O
to	O
the	O
morning	O
diverſions	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
repeated	O
cry	O
of	O
chair	O
,	O
chair	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
balls	O
,	O
concerts	O
,	O
theatre	O
,	O
cards	O
&	O
c	O
a	O
:	O
they	O
saw	O
,	O
&	O
each	O
sat	O
like	O
a	O
Patience	O
on	O
a	O
monument	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
always	O
smiling	O
on	O
grief	O
;	O
they	O
heard	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
tir	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
were	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
me	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
plied	O
the	O
needle	O
.	O
A	O
propos	O
;	O
what	O
book	O
think	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
,	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
your	O
most	O
devoted	O
though	O
utterly	O
forgotten	O
slave	O
?	O
The	O
life	O
&	O
adventures	O
of	O
Robinſon	O
Cruſoe	O
--	O
The	O
wolves	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
firſt	O
volume	O
;	O
Miranda	B-pers
hath	O
loſt	O
her	O
wager	O
;	O
she	O
hath	O
not	O
paid	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
worſe	O
,	O
my	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
pen	O
firſt	O
irretrievably	O
diſables	O
her	O
from	O
ever	O
diſcharging	O
an	O
obligation	O
of	O
juſtice	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
conſcience	O
.	O
Sweet	O
saint	O
!	O
have	O
no	O
recourſe	O
to	O
juſtification	O
Truſt	O
to	O
penitence	O
alone	O
,	O
whoſe	O
healing	O
dews	O
can	O
remove	O
the	O
only	O
speck	O
upon	O
your	O
purity	O
in	O
this	O
firſt	O
inſtance	O
of	O
tranſgreſsion	O
!	O
To	O
my	O
rightful	O
claim	O
the	O
governeſs	O
of	O
this	O
houſe	O
,	O
and	O
Miranda	B-pers
join	O
their	O
fervent	O
petition	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
us	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
attonement	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
gratification	O
to	O
their	O
affectionate	O
solicitude	O
.	O
All	O
unite	O
in	O
compliments	O
to	O
Lieutenant	B-pers
governeſs	I-pers
Dove	I-pers
&	O
you	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
moſt	O
faithful	O
&	O
cordial	O
friend	O
&	O
servt	O
.	O
Miranda	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
If	O
lovely	O
R	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
be	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
embrace	O
her	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
all	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
my	O
own	O
houſe	O
,	O
not	O
all	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
we	O
are	O
too	O
much	O
diſpos	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
to	O
ourſelves	O
Catherine	B-pers
Author	O
of	O
Leonidas	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
1777	O
R.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Esqr-	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
London	B-place
