TOKEN	NE
Albemarle	O
Street	O
May	O
2	O
d	O
:	O
1786	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
am	O
well	O
pleased	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
like	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
hopes	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
suit	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
diffident	O
&	O
a	O
sweet	O
temper	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
two	O
great	O
qualities	O
in	O
a	O
servant	O
what	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
ladies	O
maid	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
true	O
meaning	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
's	O
verses	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
I	O
will	O
ask	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eton	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
recommend	O
a	O
printer	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
honest	O
man	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
imploy	O
him	O
the	O
Provost	O
was	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Your	O
Old	O
Friend	O
&	O
Lover	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
has	O
been	O
in	O
france	B-place
for	O
these	O
last	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
surprized	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
continue	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
shamefully	O
treated	O
by	O
his	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
Town	B-place
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
his	O
daughters	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Hughes	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
sent	O
spies	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
woman	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
wretch	O
&	O
abused	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
Phillipa	B-pers
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
sons	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
even	O
Hariot	B-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
sensible	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
led	O
away	O
in	O
this	O
instance	O
by	O
his	O
sister	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
sorry	O
no	O
w	O
that	O
matters	O
went	O
so	O
far	O
;	O
his	O
son	O
Bourdieu	B-pers
reproach	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
living	O
with	O
their	O
mother	O
before	O
he	O
married	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
father	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
rage	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
glaſs	O
of	O
wine	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
disenherit	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
meaning	O
James	B-pers
&	O
John	B-pers
James	B-pers
&	O
John	B-pers
,	O
Phillipa	B-pers
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scrape	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
abroad	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
&	O
my	O
Mother	O
s	O
godchild	O
Hariot	B-pers
is	O
still	O
at	O
Nancy	B-pers
s	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
girl	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
intends	O
writing	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
to	O
request	O
his	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
during	O
the	O
holiydays	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
goes	O
home	O
her	O
morals	O
will	O
be	O
quite	O
corrupted	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
wants	O
steadineſs	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
naturally	O
a	O
sweet	O
disposition	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
himself	O
wants	O
steadineſs	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
have	O
suffer	O
'd	O
his	O
children	O
to	O
have	O
behav	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
they	O
have	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
's	O
benefit	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
she	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
this	O
season	O
)	O
&	O
caught	O
a	O
cold	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
every	O
night	O
between	O
six	O
&	O
seven	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
hoarseneſs	O
&	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
short	O
cough	O
,	O
Kemble	B-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
have	O
been	O
uneas	O
ie	O
y	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
this	O
day	O
seven-night	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
so	O
unhappy	O
about	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
..	I-pers
on	O
Sunday	O
&	O
thought	O
her	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
hoarse	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
herself	O
too	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
much	O
improved	O
this	O
winter	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
inclose	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H——	I-pers
to	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
kind	O
epistle	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
remember	O
that	O
last	O
year	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
debt	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
will	O
he	O
very	O
particularly	O
mentions	O
it	O
as	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
five	O
thousand	O
more	O
,	O
Since	O
his	O
death	O
the	O
bond	O
which	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
is	O
miſsing	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
it	O
no	O
where	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
visit	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burges	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burges	I-pers
paid	O
us	O
this	O
winter	O
my	O
mother	O
mentioned	O
the	O
bond	O
which	O
Mr	B-pers
acknowledged	O
,	O
still	O
I	O
received	O
no	O
interest	O
from	O
him	O
though	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
was	O
due	O
last	O
Lady	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Strothoff	I-pers
who	O
is	O
our	O
solicitor	O
&	O
our	O
my	O
trustee	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
&	O
mention	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
interest	O
upon	O
the	O
bond	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Strothoff	I-pers
said	O
their	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
show	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
&	O
that	O
indeed	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
the	O
same	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
S	I-pers
..	I-pers
said	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
case	O
he	O
should	O
file	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
chancery	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
they	O
both	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
thursday	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
weak	O
woman	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
her	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
no	O
w	O
think	O
her	O
both	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
visit	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
we	O
call	O
&	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
to	O
our	O
faces	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
will	O
going	O
into	O
chancery	O
that	O
the	O
executors	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
very	O
short	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
angry	O
)	O
they	O
have	O
then	O
used	O
us	O
very	O
ill	O
Madam	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
act	O
as	O
the	O
will	O
then	O
stood	O
,	O
finding	O
me	O
very	O
positive	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
mistook	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
beneath	O
either	O
my	O
mother	O
or	O
myself	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
our	O
leaves	O
&	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
my	O
Mother	O
that	O
nothing	O
should	O
ever	O
tempt	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
within	O
their	O
door	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
McKonochie	I-pers
is	O
very	O
much	O
alter	O
'd	O
we	O
never	O
see	O
meet	O
,	O
surely	O
their	O
never	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
family	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
I	O
think	O
as	O
bad	O
a	O
disposition	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Richd	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
mine	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
very	O
Affectionate	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
