TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
September	O
2	O
d	O
1788	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
arrived	O
in	O
Town	O
this	O
Evening	O
&	O
found	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
receive	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
your	O
existence	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
of	O
your	O
recollection	O
--	O
the	O
comfortable	O
letter	O
I	O
promised	O
you	O
from	O
Horton	B-place
waited	O
for	O
one	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
never	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
even	O
one	O
line	O
?	O
however	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
nothing	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
reproach	O
each	O
other	O
on	O
that	O
of	O
our	O
corresponding	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
very	O
idle	O
,	O
every	O
body	O
complains	O
of	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
already	O
chargé	O
ed	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
scolding	O
meſsage	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
fortunately	O
for	O
you	O
she	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
several	O
tim	O
es	O
during	O
my	O
stay	O
there	O
--	O
&	O
dined	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
my	O
departure	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
entre	O
nous	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
much	O
like	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
is	O
an	O
absolute	O
Dwarf	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
all	O
like	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
more	O
&	O
more	O
every	O
time	O
we	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
Papa	O
is	O
absolutely	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
explain	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
disappeari	O
n	O
g	O
so	O
immediatly	O
from	O
Richmond	B-place
after	O
having	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
stay	O
there	O
&	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
proposed	O
spending	O
my	O
first	O
fortnight	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
return	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
till	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Park	O
&	O
my	O
next	O
at	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
--	O
but	O
upon	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
at	O
Court	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
home	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
unleſs	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
immediatly	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
determined	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
already	O
engaged	O
myself	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
)	O
just	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
after	O
her	O
very	O
long	O
absence	O
&	O
illneſs	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
to	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
--	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
left	O
Richmond	B-place
I	O
think	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
at	O
Church	O
&	O
desired	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
&	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
immeddeatly	O
&	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
till	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
just	O
returned	O
,	O
after	O
paſsing	O
the	O
pleasantest	O
week	O
I	O
almost	O
ever	O
remember	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
beautiful	O
charmi	O
n	O
g	O
Place	O
!	O
the	O
Owners	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
love	O
,	O
how	O
ungrateful	O
should	O
I	O
be	O
to	O
her	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
as	O
a	O
Mother	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
her	O
from	O
my	O
Soul	O
!	O
The	O
society	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
pleasantest	O
poſsible	O
--	O
all	O
the	O
Lennoxes	B-pers
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
is	O
the	O
cleverest	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
humoured	O
&	O
the	O
most	O
sensible	O
Woman	O
--	O
more	O
true	O
drollery	O
&	O
humour	O
than	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
in	O
any	O
person	O
--	O
the	O
Girls	O
are	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
beautiful	O
&	O
as	O
pleasing	O
as	O
good	O
--	O
so	O
much	O
simplicity	O
,	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
sence	O
&	O
good	O
humou	O
r	O
they	O
are	O
indeed	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
is	O
charmi	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
amiable	O
&	O
my	O
heart	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
&	O
sad	O
when	O
we	O
separated	O
yesterday	O
--	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elisabeth	I-pers
is	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
very	O
ill	O
again	O
,	O
Blisters	O
--	O
all	O
her	O
old	O
Complaints	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
is	O
appointed	O
,	O
Friend	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
with	O
500£	O
a	O
year	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
did	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
handsomest	O
,	O
most	O
flattering	O
manner	O
--	O
&	O
inded	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
flattering	O
appointment	O
--	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
this	O
favour	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
put	O
out	O
her	O
hand	O
&	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
be	O
my	O
Friend	O
”	O
--	O
So	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Kingston	I-pers
is	O
dead	O
--	O
17000£	O
a	O
year	O
goes	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
&	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
much	O
to	O
Evelyn	B-pers
--	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
left	O
all	O
her	O
Jewels	O
,	O
divided	O
between	O
or	O
rather	O
amongst	O
,	O
the	O
Pope	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
whom	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ruſsia	I-pers
--	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
further	O
particulars	O
of	O
this	O
strang	O
will	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Binning	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
Lodge	O
on	O
Monday	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
duri	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
time	O
&	O
at	O
as	O
early	O
a	O
period	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
morni	O
n	O
g	O
I	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
,	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
then	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
&	O
shall	O
return	O
there	O
about	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
or	O
10	O
th	O
of	O
November	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
delighted	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
&	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
--	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
look	O
to	O
your	O
bein	O
g	O
as	O
a	O
most	O
comfortable	O
&	O
delightful	O
Circums	O
tance	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
angel	O
is	O
well	O
--	O
adieu	O
once	O
more	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Richmond	B-place
Surry	B-place
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Sepr	O
.	O
1788	O
