TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Will	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
inclosed	O
L	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
I	O
expected	O
some	O
Franks	O
from	O
the	O
Bishop	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
sent	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
wait	O
&	O
must	O
trouble	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
Hercules	O
,	O
the	O
not	O
being	O
dragged	O
for	O
two	O
Hot	O
Hours	O
upon	O
the	O
Terrace	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
July	O
27	O
,	O
1780	O
will	O
contribute	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
wore	O
out	O
by	O
Wednesdy	O
but	O
Wednesday	O
Evening	O
recruits	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
Start	O
again	O
on	O
Frid	O
a	O
y	O
,	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
do	O
not	O
judge	O
of	O
my	O
Friendship	O
by	O
my	O
Silence	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
gives	O
me	O
no	O
time	O
for	O
writing	O
--	O
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Thursd	O
a	O
y	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
July	O
1780	O
