TOKEN	NE
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
.	O
April	O
23	O
d	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
surprized	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
Understanding	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
received	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
trouble	O
you	O
by	O
writing	O
again	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
day	O
was	O
so	O
perfectly	O
alike	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
really	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
communicate	O
.	O
My	O
poor	O
dear	O
Father	O
grew	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
affectionately	O
solicitous	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
comfort	O
;	O
towards	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
convinced	O
,	O
the	O
rejoining	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
.	O
Till	O
we	O
know	O
whether	O
his	O
engagement	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
would	O
be	O
continued	O
for	O
the	O
ensuing	O
season	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
act	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
state	O
of	O
affairs	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
of	O
the	O
Dublin	B-place
Theatre	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
upon	O
busineſs	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
then	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
much	O
regretted	O
parting	O
with	O
me	O
)	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
best	O
seize	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
having	O
an	O
interview	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
light	O
into	O
my	O
future	O
prospects	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
may	O
see	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
You	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
all	O
violence	O
about	O
the	O
unlucky	O
transaction	O
I	O
formerly	O
explained	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
has	O
subsided	O
,	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
really	O
very	O
kind	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
occasion	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
learn	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
retains	O
his	O
present	O
situation	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
me	O
over	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
this	O
Summer	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
should	O
travel	O
with	O
every	O
comfort	O
.	O
Meanwhile	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
an	O
anxious	O
state	O
of	O
suspense	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
even	O
should	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
intentions	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
consult	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
before	O
I	O
proceed	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
write	O
again	O
,	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
here	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
at	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
receive	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Best	I-pers
's	O
affairs	O
are	O
in	O
so	O
lamentable	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
derangement	O
,	O
that	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
occasionally	O
occupies	O
the	O
only	O
spare	O
room	O
the	O
house	O
affords	O
.	O
Plainly	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Best	I-pers
has	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
for	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
fear	O
West	B-place
India	I-place
property	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
way	O
.	O
Having	O
given	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
chapter	O
of	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
now	O
wish	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
senr	O
:	O
,	O
I	O
conclude	O
,	O
is	O
recovered	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
his	O
son	O
and	O
daughter	O
's	O
tender	O
attentions	O
.	O
The	O
extract	O
you	O
transmitted	O
me	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
affords	O
a	O
strong	O
proof	O
(	O
were	O
any	O
wanting	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
were	O
kindly	O
attentive	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
communication	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
they	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
.	O
--	O
Poor	O
the	B-pers
Cathcarts	I-pers
has	O
been	O
,	O
twice	O
,	O
so	O
extremely	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
danger	O
of	O
losing	O
her	O
.	O
Thank	O
God	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
.	O
She	O
desires	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
such	O
of	O
your	O
other	O
neighbours	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
poor	O
dear	O
Father	O
in	O
amended	O
health	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
depreſsed	O
spirits	O
.	O
I	O
sadly	O
want	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
for	O
a	O
little	O
change	O
of	O
scene	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
doubtful	O
of	O
succeeding	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
.	O
With	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
truly	O
obliged	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
.	O
