TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
have	O
this	O
instant	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
--	O
&	O
will	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
to	O
enclose	O
with	O
one	O
from	O
My	O
Aunt	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
herself	O
--	O
She	O
will	O
probably	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Bp	I-pers
is	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
pretty	O
well	O
but	O
at	O
times	O
very	O
low	O
spirited	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Aunt	I-pers
returned	O
here	O
from	O
Gloucester	B-place
Yesterday	O
Mong	O
early	O
and	O
is	O
Still	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
She	O
goes	O
this	O
morng	O
to	O
Brompton	B-place
--	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
dawdling	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
adjoining	O
--	O
She	O
seems	O
perfectly	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Spirits	O
&	O
leaves	O
Bromley	B-place
at	O
latest	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
-	O
of	O
May	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
neither	O
time	O
or	O
space	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Mary	B-pers
but	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
She	O
most	O
sincerely	O
regrets	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
--	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
consider	O
it	O
a	O
happy	O
release	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
dear	O
letter	O
very	O
impatiently	O
&	O
beg	O
She	O
will	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
No	O
60	O
High	O
Street	O
Cheltenham	B-place
--	O
remember	O
kindly	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
&	O
all	O
the	O
dear	O
dumb	O
animals	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Yr	O
affte-	O
&	O
obliged	O
--	O
F.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Our	O
Estate	O
Our	O
fate	O
,	O
respecting	O
y	O
:	O
Estate	O
is	O
still	O
undecided	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
a	O
much	O
longer	O
Letter	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
when	O
I	O
receive	O
it	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Beds——	B-place
