TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
July	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
1786	O
The	O
melancholy	O
contents	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
break	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
manner	O
he	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
his	O
amiable	O
wife	O
,	O
Alas	O
,	O
my	O
once	O
lov	O
'd	O
&	O
dearest	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
is	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
she	O
departed	O
from	O
this	O
world	O
of	O
sorrow	O
&	O
anxiety	O
on	O
Monday	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
better	O
after	O
her	O
first	O
attack	O
&	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
though	O
I	O
feel	O
much	O
better	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
relapse	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
sacrament	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
bore	O
her	O
journey	O
to	O
Harwood	B-place
last	O
thursday	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
was	O
expected	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
arrived	O
there	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
her	O
death	O
continued	O
very	O
bad	O
indeed	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
wrote	O
to	O
dear	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
yesterday	O
to	O
beg	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
wth	O
:	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
Nanny	B-pers
is	O
a	O
saint	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
Almighty	O
shower	O
down	O
his	O
bleſsing	O
on	O
her	O
&	O
still	O
inable	O
her	O
to	O
support	O
herself	O
through	O
this	O
this	O
dreadful	O
scene	O
of	O
affliction	O
.	O
I	O
hardly	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
wish	O
&	O
my	O
hand	O
trembles	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
degree	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
scarcely	O
hold	O
my	O
pen	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
might	O
see	O
it	O
unexpectedly	O
in	O
a	O
newspaper	O
;	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
billious	O
fever	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
desire	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remembered	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
Ever	O
oblig	O
'd	O
friend	O
M	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
P.S	O
..	O
Let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
,	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
what	O
will	O
she	O
not	O
feel	O
,	O
I	O
pity	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
pity	O
myself	O
for	O
I	O
dearly	O
lov	O
'd	O
the	O
dear	O
Catherine	B-pers
;	O
but	O
my	O
dearest	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
but	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
angel	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
happier	O
than	O
this	O
world	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
illneſs	O
would	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
been	O
present	O
to	O
her	O
imagenation	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Welsbourne	O
Warwickshire	B-place
