TOKEN	NE
Accept	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
sincerest	O
wishes	O
an	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
can	O
form	O
for	O
your	O
mutual	O
Happineſs	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
my	O
Compts	O
&	O
Congratulations	O
acceptable	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
&	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
future	O
plans	O
&	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
partaker	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
present	O
the	O
amendment	O
is	O
so	O
slow	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
perceive	O
I	O
gain	O
strength	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
can	O
no	O
longer	O
hold	O
my	O
pen	O
but	O
most	O
affectly	O
&	O
Faithfully	O
Yrs	O
MC	B-pers
Portland	I-pers
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
Dowr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
June	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
