TOKEN	NE
Copied	O
by	O
E	O
G	O
A	O
in	O
manuscript	O
Willingham	B-place
Augt	O
2	O
d	O
1772	O
Immediately	O
upon	O
my	O
getting	O
to	O
Town	B-place
My	O
dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
made	O
enquiresy	O
about	O
my	O
Globes	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
ſome	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
gone	O
however	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
Second	O
Waggon	O
You	O
will	O
recieve	O
the	O
World	O
which	O
I	O
lay	O
most	O
ſincerely	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
only	O
Young	O
Lady	O
who	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
deſerves	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
convince	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
lay	O
more	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
immediately	O
done	O
The	O
2	O
&	O
4	O
volumes	O
of	O
la	O
vie	O
des	O
peintres	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
short	O
time	O
I	O
stayed	O
in	O
Town	B-place
but	O
have	O
left	O
a	O
com̅ission	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
ſoon	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
ſend	O
you	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
little	O
book	O
of	O
Poems	O
whither	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
get	O
those	O
not	O
printed	O
from	O
her	O
for	O
you	O
must	O
depend	O
on	O
time	O
,	O
tho	O
did	O
she	O
know	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
obliging	O
her	O
Sister	O
Excellence	O
Please	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
forgiven	O
her	O
uſuage	O
of	O
m	O
y	O
e	O
at	O
Newport	B-place
Pagnell	I-place
nor	O
shall	O
I	O
till	O
we	O
meet	O
there	O
again	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
My	O
Compliments	O
to	O
the	O
Kitten	O
&	O
pray	O
pull	O
off	O
her	O
Cap	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
ſee	O
her	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
I	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
Canterbury	B-place
where	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
always	O
look	O
on	O
me	O
as	O
her	O
most	O
ſincere	O
friend	O
&	O
who	O
may	O
believe	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
aſsure	O
her	O
she	O
has	O
none	O
more	O
than	O
her	O
most	O
affct	O
Couſin	O
Wm	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
The	O
post	O
is	O
just	O
going	O
otherwise	O
this	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
longer	O
.	O
pray	O
write	O
Soon	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
The	B-pers
Honble-	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
