TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
1	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
confeſs	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
did	O
surprise	O
me	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
You	O
mention	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
naturally	O
concluded	O
the	O
Letter	O
you	O
wrote	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
had	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
his	O
Hopes	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
consulted	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
expediency	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
the	O
Match	O
,	O
I	O
fairly	O
,	O
candidly	O
&	O
honestly	O
gave	O
you	O
my	O
Opinion	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
again	O
as	O
open	O
and	O
not	O
hesitate	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
present	O
conduct	O
seems	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
strictly	O
sincere	O
in	O
his	O
Attachment	O
to	O
You	O
and	O
perfectly	O
disinterested	O
in	O
repeating	O
his	O
Proposals	O
.	O
Removed	O
from	O
your	O
Office	O
near	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
your	O
Royal	O
Mistreſs	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
ambitious	O
views	O
of	O
increasing	O
his	O
fortune	O
from	O
your	O
Interest	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Your	O
own	O
private	O
fortune	O
is	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
great	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
temptation	O
.	O
Your	O
own	O
worth	O
and	O
intrinsic	O
merit	O
can	O
alone	O
be	O
the	O
inducements	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
had	O
to	O
appear	O
once	O
more	O
as	O
an	O
humble	O
supplicant	O
on	O
your	O
Imperial	O
Will	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
therefore	O
be	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
your	O
friends	O
can	O
not	O
disapprove	O
of	O
your	O
making	O
choice	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
your	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Seige	O
of	O
Troy	B-place
has	O
been	O
a	O
Joke	O
to	O
the	O
Seige	O
poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
rightly	O
understand	O
your	O
letter	O
You	O
intend	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
unmercifull	O
as	O
to	O
prolong	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
Winter	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
is	O
perhaps	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
advise	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
most	O
earnestly	O
to	O
You	O
not	O
to	O
delay	O
this	O
matter	O
but	O
to	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
think	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
expect	O
after	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
waited	O
for	O
Your	O
Ladyship	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
expedition	O
in	O
these	O
matters	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
on	O
your	O
paying	O
implicit	O
obedience	O
to	O
my	O
Commands	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
find	O
all	O
your	O
ideas	O
of	O
Matrimonial	O
felicity	O
compleatly	O
answered	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
add	O
my	O
wishes	O
for	O
your	O
being	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
Maria	B-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
tell	O
You	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
said	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
thoroughly	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
You	O
think	O
of	O
becoming	O
One	O
of	O
Us	O
,	O
being	O
confident	O
that	O
few	O
people	O
poſseſs	O
the	O
qualities	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
render	O
Matrimony	O
happy	O
in	O
a	O
greater	O
degree	O
than	O
You	O
do	O
--	O
My	O
Commiſsion	O
as	O
Captain	O
in	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
or	O
Kings	O
Own	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Foot	O
is	O
at	O
last	O
Signed	O
.	O
The	O
Regiment	O
is	O
now	O
on	O
Dublin	B-place
Duty	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Review	O
is	O
over	O
for	O
this	O
Year	O
I	O
have	O
applied	O
for	O
leave	O
of	O
Absence	O
for	O
as	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
my	O
Commanding	O
Officer	O
may	O
think	O
fit	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
inconvenient	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
Britain	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
have	O
busineſs	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peers	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
my	O
Entailed	O
Estate	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
make	O
my	O
presence	O
in	O
London	B-place
neceſsary	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
then	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
only	O
introduced	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
My	O
Sisters	O
are	O
both	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
produced	O
another	O
Daughter	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
fine	O
Child	O
&	O
promises	O
to	O
be	O
handsome	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Write	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
leisure	O
and	O
beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
sincerely	O
interested	O
in	O
your	O
happineſs	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
July	O
1784	O
