TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Balfour	I-pers
my	O
agent	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
having	O
been	O
advised	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
busineſs	O
I	O
formerly	O
troubled	O
you	O
upon	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
better	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
laid	O
aside	O
the	O
Deed	O
of	O
Conveyance	O
of	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
signed	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Deed	O
which	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
favor	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
execute	O
exactly	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
he	O
has	O
directed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
a	O
cornetcy	O
in	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Dragoons	O
for	O
m	O
whi	O
ch	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
do	O
on	O
the	O
security	O
of	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
for	O
which	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Dickens	O
on	O
&	O
you	O
upon	O
receiving	O
the	O
money	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
discharge	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
requires	O
more	O
formalities	O
,	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Deed	O
is	O
meant	O
to	O
certify	O
your	O
having	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
further	O
claim	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
Bond	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
,	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Ox	O
ford	O
Street	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
249	O
June	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
Directions	O
to	O
be	O
carefully	O
attended	O
to	O
in	O
executing	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Deed	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
separte	O
Ratification	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
therefore	O
please	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
one	O
is	O
subjoined	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Page	O
of	O
the	O
Deed	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
a	O
Notary	O
Publick	O
,	O
&	O
Two	O
Witneſses	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
signs	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
croſs	O
--	O
The	O
Justice	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
adding	O
“	O
J	O
.	O
P.	O
”	O
after	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
&	O
the	O
Notary	O
at	O
the	O
Third	O
Croſs	O
prefixing	O
ie	O
before	O
to	O
his	O
name	O
the	O
Words	O
Præmiſsa	O
eſse	O
vera	O
attestor	O
--	O
And	O
the	O
Two	O
Witneſses	O
at	O
these	O
Marks	O
__	O
__	O
,	O
And	O
please	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
the	O
Date	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
residence	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
&	O
the	O
Designation	O
of	O
the	O
Witneſs	O
es	O
to	O
the	O
Ratification	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Deed	O
each	O
Page	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
first	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
by	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Croſs	O
&	O
by	O
the	O
Witneſses	O
at	O
these	O
Marks	O
__	O
__	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Page	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
for	O
giving	O
you	O
all	O
this	O
trouble	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
undertake	O
as	O
much	O
for	O
you	O
Return	O
the	O
Deed	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
by	O
a	O
safe	O
conveyance	O
or	O
by	O
Post	O
London	B-place
June	O
Sixteen	O
Seventeen	O
1789	O
John	B-pers
Dickenſon	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Greville	B-pers
