TOKEN	NE
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
Dus	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
happy	O
you	O
who	O
will	O
receive	O
what	O
I	O
lose	O
every	O
Day	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
more	O
&	O
as	O
her	O
conversation	O
grows	O
every	O
day	O
more	O
delightful	O
my	O
every	O
all	O
Happynes	O
atend	O
you	O
my	O
sweet	O
Friend	O
it	O
woud	O
be	O
charity	O
to	O
enliven	O
with	O
a	O
line	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
to	O
the	O
dull	O
Shore	O
before	O
a	O
storm	O
&	O
a	O
wreck	O
is	O
an	O
object	O
it	O
agrees	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
which	O
is	O
a	O
pardon	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
hor	O
dullnes	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
tho	O
unreasonable	O
whe	O
n	O
stands	O
quivering	O
before	O
you	O
may	O
it	O
give	O
you	O
every	O
happynes	O
wish	O
'd	O
by	O
yr	O
Vesey	B-pers
Dark	O
&	O
grimy	O
is	O
yr	O
friend	O
Mar	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
from	O
Margate	B-place
August	O
1784	O
