TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
immediatly	O
on	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
Day	O
sev'night	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
ones	O
purposes	O
are	O
seldom	O
put	O
in	O
execution	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
London	B-place
till	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
you	O
know	O
to	O
have	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Brother	O
had	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
his	O
ague	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
&	O
another	O
Fit	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
which	O
detained	O
&	O
alarmed	O
us	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
him	O
a	O
moment	O
Day	O
or	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
anxiety	O
and	O
fatigue	O
made	O
me	O
ill	O
for	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
again	O
,	O
especially	O
since	O
the	O
violent	O
thunder=Storm	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
relieved	O
the	O
air	O
&	O
our	O
lungs	O
of	O
that	O
dreadful	O
weight	O
which	O
was	O
become	O
quite	O
oppreſsive	O
,	O
we	O
pray	O
for	O
more	O
rain	O
,	O
everything	O
is	O
burnt	O
up	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
Cattle	O
absolutely	O
starving	O
,	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
their	O
lament	O
ation	O
&	O
cries	O
for	O
food	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
's	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
we	O
are	O
better	O
off	O
than	O
our	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
off	O
the	O
fever	O
with	O
Bark	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
hanging	O
upon	O
him	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
quite	O
well	O
till	O
he	O
has	O
another	O
regular	O
Fit	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Father	O
thank	O
God	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
my	O
dear	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
meet	O
after	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
absence	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
improving	O
journey	O
but	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
illneſs	O
who	O
kept	O
his	O
bed	O
three	O
Weeks	O
at	O
Fairfield	B-place
--	O
however	O
they	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
Lakes	O
in	O
Cumberland	B-place
&	O
Westmoreland	B-place
&	O
my	O
Brother	O
gives	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
excites	O
my	O
curiosity	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
inclination	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
tour	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nobody	O
yet	O
--	O
except	O
Mr	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
who	O
dined	O
here	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
let	O
us	O
into	O
all	O
the	O
private	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
at	O
Northamton	B-place
&	O
c.	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
visiting	O
this	O
Summer	O
thank	O
God	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
quite	O
cruel	O
to	O
be	O
routed	O
from	O
ones	O
comfortable	O
home	O
&	O
occupations	O
,	O
to	O
stuff	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
broiling	O
in	O
the	O
heat	O
I	O
must	O
regret	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Throckmortons	I-pers
who	O
are	O
both	O
the	O
best	O
&	O
pleasantest	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
&	O
who	O
I	O
fear	O
will	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
Weston	B-place
again	O
--	O
I	O
begin	O
my	O
visits	O
beyond	O
Northamton	B-place
tomorrow	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Suttons	I-pers
Thursby	B-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Days	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Langham	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
over	O
--	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
my	O
dear	O
sure	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
that	O
hot	O
dusty	O
place	O
any	O
longer	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
haste	O
you	O
will	O
certainly	O
have	O
a	O
wet	O
bad	O
Season	O
for	O
your	O
tour	O
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
,	O
besides	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
are	O
we	O
all	O
very	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
,	O
1000	O
things	O
may	O
happen	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
go	O
to	O
Wakefield	B-place
to	O
Weston	B-place
in	O
Staffordshire	B-place
Sir	B-pers
H.	I-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
s	O
,	O
inshort	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
of	O
you	O
whilst	O
we	O
are	O
stationary	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
pray	O
pray	O
come	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
wish	O
much	O
to	O
introduce	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
Beauty	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
now	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
than	O
most	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
here	O
the	O
verdure	O
is	O
gone	O
--	O
the	O
Severity	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
has	O
killed	O
all	O
the	O
Green	O
House	O
plants	O
and	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Shrubs	O
in	O
my	O
Flower	O
Garden	O
which	O
being	O
only	O
in	O
its	O
first	O
infancy	O
has	O
felt	O
the	O
cold	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
however	O
a	O
great	O
amusement	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
watch	O
the	O
progreſs	O
of	O
every	O
plant	O
--	O
We	O
play	O
&	O
sing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
occupied	O
2	O
hours	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
Child	O
Charlotte	B-pers
who	O
is	O
pretty	O
&	O
very	O
good	O
--	O
&	O
will	O
I	O
daresay	O
turn	O
out	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
time	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
pray	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
to	O
fix	O
your	O
coming	O
,	O
adieu	O
your	O
affecte	O
:	O
CMG	B-pers
Horton	B-place
July	O
17	O
th	O
1785	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
No	O
27	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
London	B-place
