TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
Feby	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
delightful	O
place	O
&	O
still	O
more	O
delightful	O
.	O
family	O
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
&	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
delightful	O
place	O
&	O
a	O
delightful	O
society	O
--	O
yet	O
these	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
mine	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
a	O
heavy	O
Heart	O
.	O
I	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
my	O
forward	O
direction	O
--	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
John	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
's	O
Newsells	O
.	O
Royston	B-place
--	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Braybrook	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
states	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
Cold	O
is	O
so	O
serious	O
that	O
People	O
go	O
to	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
to	O
Enquire	O
after	O
his	O
Health	O
--	O
I	O
dread	O
the	O
fatal	O
humour	O
falling	O
on	O
his	O
Lungs	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
time	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
Awful	O
Event	O
--	O
the	O
real	O
Love	O
&	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
his	O
Subjects	O
towards	O
him	O
keeps	O
them	O
quiet	O
now	O
all	O
their	O
Grievances	O
--	O
but	O
if	O
a	O
Change	O
was	O
to	O
happen	O
now	O
at	O
this	O
Crisis	O
--	O
no	O
one	O
Can	O
Calculate	O
what	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Consequences	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
frd	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
of	O
two	O
very	O
kind	O
letters	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
at	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
repine	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
feel	O
my	O
self	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
in	O
speaking	O
to	O
H	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
her	O
word	O
what	O
I	O
felt	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
.	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
--	O
my	O
Letter	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
answer	O
'd	O
by	O
Young	B-pers
.	O
or	O
Woodacre	B-pers
&	O
then	O
the	O
whole	O
village	O
wd	O
have	O
been	O
Acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Contents	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
kind	O
in	O
you	O
--	O
at	O
no	O
time	O
shall	O
I	O
ever	O
forget	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
Clock	O
warns	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
ready	O
for	O
dinner	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
concludes	O
me	O
Yrs	O
most	O
Affecly	O
DBloſset	B-pers
--	O
London	B-place
Feby	O
twenty	O
five	O
1801	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Griffin	B-pers
Braybrooke	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
