TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
June	O
1799	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
your	O
post	O
Office	O
people	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
can	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
your	O
Letter	O
went	O
to	O
Harwich	B-place
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
four	O
days	O
deprived	O
of	O
the	O
superlative	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
knowing	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
existence	O
.	O
This	O
peice	O
of	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Graciousness	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
learned	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
Kitten	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
are	O
amongst	O
the	O
Living	O
,	O
I	O
sincerely	O
congratulate	O
You	O
all	O
,	O
particularly	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
You	O
,	O
again	O
fixed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
When	O
Wives	O
gad	O
about	O
Town	B-place
,	O
they	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
become	O
unmanageable	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
good	O
reason	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
special	O
care	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
Rib	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Though	O
to	O
convince	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
confidence	O
in	O
her	O
Discretion	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
permitted	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Trip	O
,	O
acroſs	O
the	O
Mountains	O
,	O
to	O
Newcastle	B-place
,	O
without	O
my	O
attending	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
is	O
fixed	O
for	O
her	O
departure	O
.	O
In	O
return	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
She	O
brings	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
honour	O
Us	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
during	O
his	O
holidays	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
are	O
ended	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
all	O
well	O
,	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
She	O
still	O
has	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
uncertain	O
weather	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
get	O
quit	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
this	O
little	O
Jaunt	O
may	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
Exercise	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
.	O
How	O
I	O
shall	O
contrive	O
to	O
keep	O
all	O
the	O
Seven	O
Children	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
during	O
her	O
Absence	O
,	O
rather	O
puzzles	O
Me	O
.	O
Every	O
thing	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
is	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
Month	O
later	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
melancholy	O
sort	O
of	O
Comfort	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Comfort	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
our	O
Neighbours	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
are	O
not	O
better	O
off	O
than	O
ourselves	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Hay	O
will	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
cutting	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
my	O
Wheat	O
,	O
Barley	O
,	O
an	O
Oats	O
are	O
fairly	O
in	O
the	O
Barn	O
Yard	O
by	O
November	O
,	O
my	O
expectations	O
will	O
be	O
answered	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
our	O
Beef	O
and	O
Mutton	O
,	O
the	O
poor	O
Animals	O
are	O
half	O
starved	O
.	O
The	O
Store	O
Farmers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sheep	O
Farms	O
,	O
have	O
lost	O
almost	O
all	O
their	O
Lambs	O
from	O
the	O
severity	O
of	O
the	O
Weather	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
even	O
of	O
more	O
consequence	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Mortality	O
amongst	O
the	O
old	O
Sheep	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
serious	O
to	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
like	O
myself	O
,	O
draw	O
our	O
Rents	O
from	O
Sheep	O
Farms	O
.	O
When	O
Rent	O
Day	O
arrives	O
,	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
treated	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
List	O
of	O
Loſses	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
.	O
The	O
Japan	O
Warehouse	O
cost	O
me	O
some	O
trouble	O
to	O
comprehend	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
She	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
great	O
Grief	O
for	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
attached	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
Accounts	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
s	O
death	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sudden	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
Road	O
North	O
.	O
To	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
loſs	O
is	O
considerable	O
,	O
as	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
spent	O
most	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
Admiral	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
house	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
second	O
home	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Maria	B-pers
used	O
to	O
be	O
frequently	O
there	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
has	O
left	O
her	O
property	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
equally	O
between	O
her	O
Daughters	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Carnegie	I-pers
.	O
What	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fancy	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
something	O
handsome	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
Lady	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
has	O
at	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Eighty	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
,	O
removed	O
from	O
this	O
World	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
.	O
Her	O
Son	O
Tommy	B-pers
is	O
with	O
his	O
Regiment	O
at	O
Minorca	B-place
.	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
Your	O
Roads	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Bone	O
in	O
my	O
Body	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
perfectly	O
convinced	O
of	O
their	O
Execrability	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
vowed	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
do	O
penance	O
on	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
if	O
You	O
wish	O
that	O
We	O
should	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
remove	O
Your	O
Establishment	O
to	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
could	O
meet	O
without	O
being	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
breaking	O
our	O
Necks	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
be	O
an	O
admirable	O
acquisition	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Harpsichord	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
groan	O
forth	O
an	O
Accompaniment	O
on	O
the	O
Violoncello	O
,	O
while	O
You	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
disputing	O
in	O
a	O
sharper	O
Key	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Monboddo	I-pers
's	O
proposal	O
of	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
But	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
high	O
time	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
superannuated	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Selkirk	I-pers
left	O
one	O
Son	O
,	O
the	O
present	O
Earl	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Daughters	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Daughter	O
married	O
Sir	B-pers
James	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
as	O
notorious	O
a	O
Republican	O
as	O
her	O
Father	O
.	O
Four	O
Sons	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Selkirk	I-pers
died	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
grew	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
Men	O
.	O
The	O
present	O
Lord	O
was	O
the	O
youngest	O
Boy	O
.	O
If	O
his	O
political	O
principles	O
are	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
weep	O
on	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
Coat	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Love	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
Sincerely	O
Napier	B-pers
Remember	O
Me	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Thirteenth	O
June	O
1799	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
