TOKEN	NE
Type	O
portions	O
letter	O
in	O
book	O
not	O
typed	O
Newberry	B-place
Tuesday	O
Night	O
June	O
8	O
th	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
intended	O
calling	O
upon	O
you	O
yesterday	O
&	O
this	O
morning	O
but	O
busineſs	O
increased	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
degree	O
that	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
moment	O
for	O
as	O
the	O
Ship	O
goes	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
before	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
London	B-place
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
my	O
heavy	O
baggage	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
off	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
for	O
Wales	B-place
&	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
we	O
shall	O
go	O
over	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Ground	O
before	O
we	O
return	O
to	O
London	B-place
early	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
August	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
stay	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
in	O
London	B-place
before	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Naples	B-place
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
sensible	O
of	O
your	O
affection	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
away	O
by	O
my	O
numerous	O
acquaintance	O
from	O
seeing	O
you	O
often	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
most	O
sincere	O
&	O
true	O
affection	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
Cipriani	B-pers
sent	O
me	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
drawings	O
of	O
the	O
Vase	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
exquisite	O
the	O
whole	O
will	O
be	O
finished	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
)	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Vase	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
convey	O
it	O
secretly	O
to	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
therefore	O
Cipriani	B-pers
is	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
brings	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
safely	O
lodged	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
uneasy	O
till	O
I	O
hear	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
.	O
Send	O
your	O
letter	O
to	O
Nerots	O
Hotel	O
as	O
I	O
leave	O
two	O
Servants	O
there	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
sent	O
after	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
most	O
affly	O
Yrs	O
.	O
W	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
excuſe	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
Sent	O
your	O
covers	O
.	O
by	O
sending	O
the	O
encloſed	O
you	O
will	O
much	O
oblige	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
Servant	O
will	O
receive	O
his	O
orders	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
you	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
Notwithſtanding	O
my	O
remiſsneſs	O
.	O
which	O
gives	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
exerciſing	O
towards	O
me	O
your	O
Charity	O
&	O
beneVolence	O
very	O
Sincerely	O
yours	O
.	O
CFG	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
Greville	B-pers
London	B-place
