TOKEN	NE
(	O
1	O
Novbr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Bulstrode	O
Park	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
on	O
prosperously	O
wth	O
.	O
Coxe	B-pers
in	O
being	O
355	O
Page	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
Vol	O
.	O
--	O
sometimes	O
he	O
amuses	O
me	O
,	O
sometimes	O
informs	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
sometimes	O
makes	O
me	O
yawn	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
appears	O
an	O
air	O
of	O
veracity	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
he	O
relates	O
,	O
what	O
court	O
he	O
pays	O
to	O
the	O
Empress	O
of	O
Russia	B-place
?	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
view	O
returning	O
to	O
that	O
Country	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Whitebread	I-pers
(	O
the	O
great	O
Brewer	O
s	O
Son	O
)	O
--	O
They	O
are	O
to	O
travel	O
Through	O
the	O
Northern	O
Courts	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
allows	O
Mr.	B-pers
Coxe	I-pers
£	O
800	O
per	O
An	O
:	O
besides	O
paying	O
all	O
travelling	O
&	O
other	O
expences	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
was	O
here	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
&	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
curious	O
characteristic	O
anecdote	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
.	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
know	O
He	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
when	O
their	O
daughter	O
was	O
dying	O
&	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Dancer	O
to	O
Italy	B-place
,	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
was	O
dead	O
--	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
always	O
affected	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
fond	O
--	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
&	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
of	O
losing	O
her	O
Daughter	O
he	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
receive	O
a	O
natural	O
Daughter	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
handsome	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
charming	O
Girl	O
&	O
would	O
console	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
company	O
would	O
console	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
she	O
had	O
sustained	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
said	O
Lady	B-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
consented	O
to	O
receive	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
under	O
her	O
her	O
protection	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
expected	O
in	O
England	B-place
this	O
Month	O
July	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
There	O
are	O
few	O
People	O
remaining	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
care	O
Much	O
abt	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ancaster	I-pers
gives	O
Balls	O
,	O
as	O
does	O
Lady	B-pers
North	I-pers
at	O
Bushey	O
Park	O
--	O
others	O
too	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
2	O
)	O
of	O
&	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
o	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
interested	O
,	O
I	O
neither	O
went	O
nor	O
made	O
inquiries	O
abt	O
.	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
entirely	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
10	O
days	O
of	O
her	O
confinement	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walshingham	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
in	O
London	B-place
both	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
finished	O
the	O
second	O
Vol	O
:	O
of	O
Madame	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
's	O
Veillées	O
du	O
Chateau	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
like	O
her	O
Adêle	O
et	O
Theodore	O
&	O
c	O
?	O
I	O
allow	O
she	O
has	O
genius	O
&	O
imagination	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
approve	O
her	O
method	O
of	O
instructing	O
Children	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
oldest	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
7	O
10	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
youngest	O
7	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
--	O
More	O
of	O
this	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Consistency	O
,	O
Consistency	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
!	O
even	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
as	O
odious	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
croaking	O
Raven	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
repeat	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
continue	O
to	O
love	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
now	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
doing	O
.	O
Alas	O
!	O
poor	O
human	O
Nature	O
,	O
how	O
easily	O
led	O
astray	O
,	O
by	O
even	O
what	O
we	O
in	O
the	O
sober	O
sadneſs	O
of	O
reflecting	O
moments	O
most	O
heartily	O
despise	O
,	O
--	O
why	O
will	O
you	O
,	O
--	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
aſsociate	O
with	O
Ladies	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
wrong	O
,	O
else	O
why	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
from	O
others	O
--	O
and	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
praise	O
my	O
resolution	O
for	O
keeping	O
steadily	O
to	O
my	O
purpose	O
in	O
refusing	O
invitations	O
to	O
such	O
Houses	O
of	O
diſsipation	O
,	O
,	O
pardon	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
also	O
say	O
of	O
profligate	O
infamy	O
&	O
vice	O
--	O
With	O
The	O
Poet	O
Young	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Vice	O
seen	O
to	O
is	O
a	O
Monster	O
of	O
such	O
frightful	O
mien	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
hated	O
,	O
needs	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
yet	O
seen	O
too	O
oft	O
,	O
familiar	O
with	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
we	O
first	O
endure	O
,	O
then	O
pity	O
,	O
then	O
embrace	O
.	O
Passage	O
from	O
Alexander	O
Pope	O
's	O
Essay	O
on	O
Man	O
,	O
Epistle	O
II	O
.	O
3	O
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
8	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
1782	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
heard	O
that	O
their	O
Majesties	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
therefore	O
put	O
off	O
dining	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
night	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
,	O
in	O
attendance	O
,	O
you	O
dine	O
with	O
your	O
Sisters	O
The	O
Maids	O
of	O
Honor	O
at	O
your	O
their	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
polite	O
&	O
proper	O
excuse	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
I	O
shall	O
merely	O
get	O
a	O
glimpse	O
of	O
you	O
This	O
time	O
for	O
we	O
return	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
excursion	O
we	O
make	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
most	O
probably	O
till	O
Easter	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
had	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
(	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
hearing	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
voice	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
&	O
pleasure	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
work	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
in	O
friendly	O
converse	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
The	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
does	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
The	O
Play	O
Therefore	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
gain	O
an	O
Evg	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
through	O
Luc	O
i	O
an	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
--	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
July	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1780	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Beachey	B-place
head	I-place
,	O
would	O
I	O
could	O
convey	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
sensations	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
sight	O
of	O
ye	O
Stupendous	O
scene	O
made	O
more	O
awful	O
than	O
any	O
idea	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
formed	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
these	O
Cliffs	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
to	O
advantage	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
advantage	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
tide	O
had	O
prevented	O
our	O
going	O
far	O
enough	O
--	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
ever	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
gratefully	O
sensible	O
--	O
You	O
warn	O
me	O
to	O
guard	O
against	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
Ah	O
my	O
Dr-	O
why	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
good	O
&	O
amiable	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
loved	O
her	O
since	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
true	O
friendship	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
she	O
has	O
,	O
--	O
it	O
surely	O
must	O
be	O
perfectly	O
disinterested	O
.	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
mine	O
for	O
her	O
is	O
&	O
ever	O
shall	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
this	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
me	O
not	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd-	O
4/	O
The	O
fatigue	O
of	O
standing	O
upwards	O
of	O
3	O
hours	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
paſs	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
sleepleſs	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
up	O
but	O
I	O
roused	O
myself	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
earliest	O
intelligence	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
use	O
Leeches	O
to	O
your	O
gums	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
prove	O
a	O
certain	O
remedy	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
did	O
so	O
yesterday	O
&	O
it	O
removed	O
the	O
pain	O
she	O
had	O
suffered	O
for	O
10	O
days	O
.	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
1782	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
August	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
1780	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
ride	O
of	O
12	O
Miles	O
yesterday	O
afternoon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Esquire	O
,	O
we	O
attended	O
my	O
kind	O
Friends	O
who	O
came	O
here	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
visit	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
--	O
viz	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Genl-	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
tired	O
wch	O
:	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
had	O
I	O
walked	O
only	O
two	O
miles	O
--	O
Mrr	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
for	O
you	O
from	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tuffnel	I-pers
--	O
he	O
appears	O
an	O
amiable	O
young	O
Man	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
think	O
both	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
himself	O
are	O
equally	O
deserving	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
great	O
friends	O
wch	O
:	O
is	O
a	O
happy	O
circumstance	O
--	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
an	O
insolent	O
overbearing	O
Man	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
Governor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
better	O
calculated	O
for	O
a	O
negro	O
driver	O
than	O
the	O
situation	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
--	O
The	O
Man	O
however	O
is	O
not	O
unpleasant	O
in	O
his	O
manners	O
to	O
Ladies	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
superiors	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
&	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
society	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
enlivens	O
conversation	O
by	O
anecdotes	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
when	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lieutenant	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
I	O
believe	O
Aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
went	O
to	O
Italy	B-place
&	O
c.	O
with	O
the	O
rich	O
Young	O
Pelham	B-pers
.	O
5	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1780	O
Friday	O
Eveg	O
I	O
expect	O
you	O
early	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
what	O
times	O
what	O
dreadful	O
times	O
,	O
what	O
horrid	O
Riots	O
--	O
The	O
Dear	O
King	B-pers
!	O
how	O
does	O
he	O
shine	O
like	O
a	O
constellation	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
say	O
like	O
a	O
true	O
Christian	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
firmly	O
persuaded	O
Lord	B-pers
George	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
is	O
insane	O
--	O
my	O
heart	O
has	O
ached	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
pen	O
to	O
paper	O
--	O
twenty	O
times	O
have	O
I	O
begun	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
happier	O
than	O
myself	O
--	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Eastbourne	B-place
at	O
5	O
o	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morng	O
.	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
kindly	O
wished	O
(	O
this	O
a	O
secre	O
t	O
)	O
to	O
detain	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
she	O
should	O
chuse	O
either	O
to	O
have	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
or	O
myself	O
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
chusing	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
yet	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
was	O
affectionately	O
pleased	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
Sea	O
air	O
&	O
Bathing	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
good	O
&	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
corresponding	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
convince	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
real	O
sensibility	O
--	O
23	O
d	O
S	O
.	O
Eastbourne	B-place
23	O
d	O
.	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
1780	O
An	O
expreſs	O
arrived	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
was	O
safely	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
also	O
of	O
information	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
in	O
11	O
days	O
--	O
do	O
not	O
my	O
lovely	O
friend	O
let	O
your	O
family	O
jarring	O
take	O
such	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
spirits	O
Pardon	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
all	O
seem	O
to	O
contrive	O
to	O
torment	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
most	O
strange	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
extremely	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
uncommonly	O
attached	O
.	O
6	O
)	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Janry	O
1782	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
you	O
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
yr-	O
face	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
afford	O
me	O
great	O
happineſs	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
new	O
Year	O
smiles	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
enter	O
upon	O
it	O
in	O
Health	O
&	O
spirits	O
--	O
May	O
you	O
,	O
from	O
henceforth	O
,	O
enjoy	O
every	O
happineſs	O
Virtue	O
&	O
goodneſs	O
merit	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
deserve	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
our	O
friendship	O
will	O
continue	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
quit	O
it	O
may	O
we	O
hope	O
to	O
meet	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
&	O
may	O
we	O
merit	O
that	O
Heaven	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
the	O
reward	O
of	O
the	O
righteous	O
.	O
tenderly	O
Yours	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
Suſsex	B-place
8	O
th	O
June	O
1780	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Herts	O
Herstmonceux	B-place
it	O
is	O
about	O
10	O
Miles	O
from	O
hence	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
rail	O
at	O
the	O
ravages	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
mean	O
wretch	O
who	O
destroyed	O
this	O
noble	O
Pile	O
of	O
Building	O
,	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
the	I-pers
6th-	I-pers
till	O
within	O
these	O
4	O
Years	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
habitable	O
repair	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
outside	O
walls	O
are	O
left	O
standing	O
wch	O
:	O
while	O
they	O
last	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Monument	O
of	O
shame	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hare	I-pers
--	O
it	O
is	O
situated	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
Park	O
well	O
wooded	O
,	O
the	O
Ground	O
is	O
finely	O
disposed	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Ocean	O
crowns	O
the	O
prospect	O
,	O
the	O
Present	O
owner	O
has	O
just	O
finished	O
a	O
Modern	O
House	O
near	O
this	O
once	O
Noble	O
Castellated	O
Masion	O
with	O
its	O
Materials	O
--	O
the	O
Architect	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
was	O
Mr-	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Vogue	O
:	O
Herstmonceux	O
was	O
built	O
by	O
Sir	B-pers
Roger	I-pers
Fiennes	I-pers
in	O
1423	O
.	O
The	O
dimensions	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
noble	O
lofty	O
spacious	O
Room	O
is	O
still	O
to	O
be	O
traced	O
.	O
Addison	B-pers
wrote	O
his	O
comedy	O
of	O
the	O
7	O
Drummer	O
or	O
Haunted	O
House	O
when	O
on	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
this	O
Mansion	O
--	O
a	O
suitable	O
place	O
to	O
create	O
such	O
ideas	O
--	O
The	O
ancient	O
Furniture	O
&	O
curious	O
carved	O
woodwork	O
of	O
this	O
room	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
House	O
.	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
August	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
1780	O
I	O
feel	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
that	O
I	O
sincerely	O
regret	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
aſsist	O
you	O
in	O
attendance	O
on	O
your	O
worthy	O
Father	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Sister	O
is	O
very	O
attentive	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
doubt	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
--	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
one	O
feels	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
love	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
owe	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
should	O
lose	O
--	O
endeavour	O
Dear	O
friend	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
your	O
spirits	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
from	O
every	O
right	O
&	O
good	O
motive	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
of	O
our	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
excursion	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Ashburnham	O
,	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
's	O
abt	O
.	O
14	O
Miles	O
from	O
hence	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
situation	O
--	O
the	O
Park	O
is	O
7	O
Miles	O
in	O
circumference	O
--	O
the	O
Ground	O
finely	O
disposed	O
by	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
highly	O
improved	O
by	O
15	O
years	O
labour	O
&	O
skill	O
of	O
Mr-	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
--	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
employer	O
of	O
Brown	B-pers
I	O
should	O
suggest	O
some	O
alterations	O
wch	O
.	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
accordant	O
to	O
my	O
ideas	O
of	O
picturesque	O
beauty	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
great	O
Uncle	O
Charles	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
taste	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
this	O
place	O
more	O
renowned	O
for	O
true	O
simplicity	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
The	O
views	O
from	O
many	O
parts	O
the	O
views	O
are	O
extensive	O
--	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
one	O
might	O
see	O
to	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
60	O
miles	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
8	O
.	O
there	O
are	O
charming	O
rides	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
--	O
Water	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
Noble	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
easily	O
distinguished	O
Veſsels	O
sailing	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
Glaſses	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
crown	O
the	O
scene	O
the	B-place
Downs	I-place
rising	O
to	O
the	O
Clouds	O
Sky	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
distinct	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
ruins	O
of	O
Battle-Abbey	O
,	O
wch-	O
appeared	O
but	O
two	O
miles	O
distant	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
four	O
--	O
I	O
regretted	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
memorable	O
for	O
being	O
raised	O
upon	O
the	O
Spot	O
where	O
Harold	B-pers
s	O
Body	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
William	B-pers
stiled	O
ye-	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
pretended	O
attonement	O
for	O
the	O
horrid	O
quantity	O
of	O
human	O
Blood	O
shed	O
in	O
that	O
encounter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
Battle	O
Abbey	O
Called	O
the	O
Conquerors	O
Abbey	O
(	O
Built	O
by	O
William	B-pers
.	O
)	O
is	O
charmingly	O
situated	O
,	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
partly	O
inhabited	O
by	O
a	O
L	O
W	O
idow	O
Lady	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
pointed	O
to	O
our	O
observation	O
,	O
at	O
no	O
great	O
distance	O
,	O
an	O
eminence	O
called	O
Standard	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
William	B-pers
the	I-pers
invader	I-pers
,	I-pers
or	I-pers
Conqueror	I-pers
,	O
erected	O
his	O
Standard	O
on	O
landing	O
.	O
The	O
Abbey	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
magnificent	O
edifices	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
It	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
wreck	O
by	O
the	O
furious	O
zeal	O
of	O
the	O
Reformers	O
The	O
Gates	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
remain	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
very	O
grand	O
.	O
In	O
Ashburnham	O
Church	O
is	O
kept	O
the	O
Shirt	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Charles	B-pers
ye	I-pers
first	I-pers
wore	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
beheaded	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Sheet	O
wch	O
:	O
covered	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
An	O
Ancestor	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
was	O
Groom	O
of	O
the	O
Bedchamber	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
&	O
out	O
of	O
attachment	O
contrived	O
to	O
get	O
&	O
preserve	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
shirt	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
should	O
think	O
9	O
.	O
think	O
very	O
coarse	O
Linnen	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
Vandyke	B-pers
falling	O
down	O
collar	O
similar	O
to	O
what	O
we	O
see	O
in	O
the	O
Portraits	O
of	O
this	O
Monarch	O
--	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
costume	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
curiously	O
ornamented	O
with	O
variety	O
of	O
stiches	O
in	O
needlework	O
by	O
some	O
skillful	O
sempstreſs	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
Sailor	O
--	O
N	O
:	O
B	O
:	O
not	O
in	O
colors	O
but	O
white	O
Thread	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
saw	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
watch	O
wch	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Servant	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
his	O
execution	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
finely	O
enameled	O
in	O
colors	O
withing	O
(	O
on	O
Gold	O
)	O
withing	O
&	O
without	O
.	O
--	O
has	O
no	O
glaſs	O
but	O
shuts	O
up	O
like	O
a	O
Box	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
D	O
ai	O
ry	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
admired	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
furnished	O
with	O
fine	O
Old	O
Delf	O
,	O
China	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
in	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Milk	O
Pail	O
,	O
called	O
Queen	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
s	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
Greenwich	B-place
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
round	O
small	O
pail	O
of	O
white	O
wood	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
round	O
plain	O
silver	O
handle	O
,	O
&	O
broad	O
rims	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
encircle	O
the	O
top	O
&	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
pail	O
,	O
These	O
rims	O
are	O
engraved	O
,	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
arms	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
those	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
--	O
but	O
like	O
those	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Shirley	O
's	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
House	O
suits	O
the	O
situation	O
,	O
The	O
Rooms	O
are	O
Large	O
,	O
Light	O
,	O
&	O
handsome	O
;	O
--	O
the	O
furniture	O
neither	O
old	O
,	O
n	O
or	O
very	O
modern	O
,	O
n	O
or	O
elegant	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
had	O
intentions	O
of	O
new	O
furnishing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
poor	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
A	I-pers
's	O
miserable	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
preventing	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
distant	O
from	O
medical	O
advice	O
in	O
London	B-place
makes	O
him	O
defer	O
it	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
Ashburnham	O
without	O
seeing	O
the	O
Gardens	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
regret	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
stile	O
of	O
his	B-pers
Majesti	I-pers
es	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
--	O
but	O
wth	O
.	O
greater	O
natural	O
advantages	O
.	O
10	O
)	O
March	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
1780	O
--	O
To	O
what	O
my	O
friend	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
attribute	O
your	O
extroadinary	O
change	O
of	O
manner	O
&	O
coldness	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
Father	O
&	O
yourself	O
who	O
courted	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
I	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
sought	O
yours	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
remember	O
you	O
both	O
engaged	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
to	O
bring	O
you	O
to	O
my	O
apartments	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
-	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
Your	O
Father	O
almost	O
with	O
tears	O
intreated	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
you	O
be	O
rank	O
'd	O
among	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
&	O
I	O
recollect	O
paid	O
me	O
many	O
fine	O
compts	O
.	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
ever	O
since	O
(	O
till	O
your	O
return	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
)	O
--	O
expreſsed	O
in	O
the	O
warmest	O
terms	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
(	O
excepting	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Rt	I-pers
:	I-pers
your	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
Sister	O
)	O
the	O
dearest	O
to	O
your	O
heart	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
human	O
being	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
extroadinary	O
proofs	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
by	O
the	O
confidence	O
,	O
you	O
placed	O
in	O
me	O
I	O
really	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
become	O
a	O
votary	O
to	O
diſsipation	O
&	O
I	O
lament	O
to	O
observe	O
you	O
now	O
aſsociate	O
with	O
persons	O
I	O
shun	O
,	O
&	O
whose	O
conduct	O
you	O
have	O
condem̅ed	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
disappointed	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
grown	O
calous	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
wounded	O
;	O
--	O
In	O
you	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
find	O
steadineſs	O
of	O
character	O
superiour	O
to	O
those	O
Moths	O
whom	O
it	O
is	O
easy	O
to	O
predict	O
will	O
soon	O
or	O
late	O
fall	O
victims	O
to	O
dangers	O
they	O
seem	O
to	O
court	O
.	O
24	O
th	O
:	O
March	O
1780	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
receive	O
so	O
bad	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Health	O
&	O
spirits	O
,	O
one	O
should	O
imagine	O
the	O
diſsipation	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
constantly	O
engaged	O
in	O
(	O
11	O
in	O
would	O
rouse	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
however	O
prejudicial	O
it	O
may	O
&	O
must	O
be	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Eveg	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
removed	O
to	O
their	O
new	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
meet	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
stupid	O
&	O
sober	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
being	O
there	O
for	O
otherwise	O
I	O
despair	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
as	O
our	O
time	O
draws	O
near	O
for	O
my	O
quitting	O
Town	B-place
--	O
with	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
--	O
the	O
3	O
e	O
lder	O
Princes	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Augusta	B-pers
--	O
we	O
go	O
on	O
Sunday	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
shall	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
sennight	O
--	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Children	O
remain	O
in	O
Town	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
C——	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G——	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
Adieu	O
you	O
will	O
ever	O
find	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
My	O
excellent	O
friends	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1780	O
You	O
think	O
my	O
note	O
cruel	O
&	O
unkind	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
felt	O
even	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
expreſsed	O
--	O
I	O
require	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
than	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
consistent	O
--	O
let	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
be	O
the	O
guide	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
actions	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
an	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
too	O
honest	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
proportion	O
as	O
you	O
seemed	O
to	O
court	O
the	O
notice	O
&	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Great	O
the	O
Daſ	O
s	O
hers	O
of	O
the	O
hau	O
t-ton	O
you	O
shrank	O
from	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
such	O
painful	O
proofs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
mutability	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
human	O
heart	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
condemn	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
regretted	O
my	O
loſs	O
,	O
--	O
hence	O
I	O
justify	O
my	O
expreſsion	O
,	O
&	O
make	O
it	O
12	O
)	O
it	O
agreeable	O
to	O
my	O
feelings	O
ie	O
.	O
“	O
That	O
I	O
should	O
always	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
”	O
Come	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
embrace	O
you	O
with	O
tenderneſs	O
and	O
sincerity	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
with	O
your	O
Hungarian	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
from	O
the	O
conversation	O
of	O
such	O
persons	O
one	O
gains	O
what	O
Books	O
can	O
not	O
teach	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
keep	O
away	O
from	O
such	O
crowded	O
dinner	O
parties	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
,	O
with	O
your	O
very	O
delicate	O
health	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
make	O
you	O
ill	O
!	O
The	O
variety	O
also	O
of	O
smells	O
,	O
&	O
particularly	O
at	O
the	O
German	O
Tables	O
you	O
mention	O
--	O
A	O
Dish	O
of	O
smoking	O
Sour	O
Crout	O
will	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
affect	O
one	O
sufficiently	O
to	O
overcome	O
all	O
desire	O
of	O
eating	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Table	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
endure	O
it	O
--	O
The	O
worthy	O
Genl	B-pers
Freytag	I-pers
has	O
tried	O
to	O
bribe	O
me	O
various	O
ways	O
to	O
relish	O
it	O
but	O
without	O
suc̅eſs	O
we	O
are	O
great	O
friends	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shoud	O
be	O
still	O
a	O
greater	O
favorite	O
wth	O
him	O
could	O
I	O
conquer	O
my	O
dislike	O
to	O
Sour	O
Crout	O
.	O
(	O
13	O
Lady	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
Compton	I-pers
s	O
Gardens	O
,	O
Eastbourne	B-place
Sea	O
Seat	O
Septr	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
You	O
will	O
my	O
Dear	O
perceive	O
from	O
whence	O
this	O
is	O
dated	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
detirmined	O
this	O
post	O
should	O
not	O
depart	O
without	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
remained	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
,	O
--	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
&	O
my	O
sweet	O
engaging	O
Child	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
are	O
playing	O
about	O
like	O
innocent	O
Butterflies	O
in	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
&	O
culling	O
the	O
wild	O
flowers	O
on	O
the	O
Graſs	O
,	O
whilst	O
I	O
am	O
watching	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
yet	O
scribb	O
l	O
ing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
your	O
thinking	O
any	O
occupation	O
either	O
of	O
duty	O
,	O
or	O
pleasure	O
,	O
or	O
diſsipation	O
could	O
render	O
me	O
unmindful	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
earnestly	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
see	O
our	O
attentive	O
,	O
kind	O
&	O
skilful	O
Doct	B-pers
.	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
oftener	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
extremely	O
improper	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
continue	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
medicines	O
,	O
or	O
even	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
water	O
--	O
change	O
of	O
prescription	O
may	O
be	O
requisite	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
continuing	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
might	O
be	O
have	O
been	O
beneficial	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
perhaps	O
doing	O
yourself	O
great	O
injury	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
likewise	O
very	O
much	O
concerned	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
&	O
sincerely	O
glad	O
Dr	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
attends	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Physician	O
from	O
R	B-place
.	I-place
might	O
be	O
a	O
skilful	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
ha	O
d	O
s	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
chance	O
of	O
being	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Dr	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
by	O
knowing	O
his	O
constitution	O
can	O
prescribe	O
with	O
greater	O
certainty	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
you	O
without	O
fail	O
,	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
14	O
)	O
great	O
happineſs	O
of	O
the	O
proud	O
Parent	O
,	O
was	O
safely	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
on	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
had	O
an	O
expreſs	O
with	O
this	O
most	O
welcome	O
intelligence	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
never	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
before	O
,	O
my	O
most	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
&	O
her	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
worthy	O
Aunt	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
were	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
latter	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
is	O
recovered	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
her	O
favorite	O
Daughter	O
&	O
,	O
entre	O
nous	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
no	O
small	O
hardship	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
excused	O
by	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
attending	O
the	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
Eastbourne	B-place
,	O
&	O
though	O
I	O
so	O
very	O
highly	O
respect	O
&	O
love	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
I	O
think	O
as	O
she	O
enjoys	O
such	O
great	O
pecuniary	O
advantages	O
&	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
&	O
family	O
,	O
from	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
greatly	O
considered	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
regretted	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
exert	O
herself	O
more	O
for	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
children	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
You	O
will	O
rejoice	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
inform	O
you	O
my	O
friends	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
are	O
arrived	O
at	O
East-bourne	B-place
,	O
as	O
there	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
any	O
impropriety	O
in	O
their	O
visiting	O
their	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
joining	O
our	O
parties	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
heart	O
felt	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
often	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
persuade	O
them	O
to	O
remain	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
we	O
shall	O
--	O
They	O
have	O
their	O
sweet	O
Girl	O
with	O
them	O
(	O
15	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
gracious	O
&	O
affectionate	O
little	O
letter	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
she	O
tells	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
before	O
we	O
shall	O
m	O
e	O
et	O
,	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
wrote	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
&	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
sitting	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
last	O
year	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
have	O
had	O
an	O
open	O
rupture	O
(	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
sacred	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
blame	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
is	O
most	O
praiseworthy	O
and	O
indefatigable	O
in	O
the	O
duties	O
of	O
her	O
station	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
wants	O
softneſs	O
of	O
temper	O
&	O
manner	O
--	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
either	O
qualified	O
by	O
education	O
or	O
Birth	O
to	O
be	O
Subgoverness	O
to	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
a	O
Monarch	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
most	O
sincere	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
withstanding	O
--	O
&	O
flatter	O
myself	O
she	O
regards	O
me	O
equally	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
--	O
my	O
perpetual	O
torment	O
,	O
has	O
taken	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
strange	O
pate	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
Volume	O
of	O
incomprehensible	O
jargon	O
--	O
five	O
pages	O
of	O
Verse	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
much	O
in	O
prose	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
laugh	O
over	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
answer	O
his	O
letters	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
often	O
do	O
not	O
read	O
them	O
havg	O
many	O
packets	O
by	O
me	O
unsealed	O
.	O
Adieu	O
the	O
wind	O
blows	O
my	O
paper	O
about	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
Dear	O
Children	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
play	O
wth-	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
scribbled	O
so	O
rapidly	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
can	O
can	O
hardly	O
decypher	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
.	O
Ever	O
the	O
same	O
towards	O
you	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
--	O
Your	O
Br	O
.	O
&	O
Sister	O
.	O
16	O
)	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
1780	O
Eastbourne	B-place
I	O
am	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
scrap	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
God	O
grant	O
you	O
may	O
soon	O
be	O
enabled	O
to	O
write	O
longer	O
letters	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
is	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
suffers	O
much	O
--	O
I	O
trust	O
your	O
resentment	O
is	O
softened	O
,	O
for	O
though	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
offended	O
,	O
your	O
superiour	O
sense	O
&	O
the	O
uncommon	O
advantages	O
of	O
education	O
for	O
a	O
female	O
wch	O
your	O
Father	O
gave	O
you	O
,	O
ought	O
to	O
raise	O
your	O
ideas	O
above	O
such	O
miserable	O
trifles	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
will	O
never	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
--	O
no	O
account	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
day	O
.	O
A	O
shocking	O
&	O
most	O
awful	O
event	O
happened	O
yesterday	O
--	O
My	O
nerves	O
are	O
still	O
too	O
much	O
agitated	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
regular	O
acct	O
.	O
--	O
A	O
Thunder	O
storm	O
,	O
2	O
persons	O
were	O
killed	O
by	O
Lig	O
h	O
t	O
tning	O
Lightning	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
miraculous	O
from	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
we	O
escaped	O
--	O
those	O
also	O
that	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
occupied	O
was	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
direct	O
line	O
Adieu	O
the	O
Post	O
waits	O
--	O
Your	O
true	O
Friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
7	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
..	O
1780	O
--	O
——	B-pers
writes	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Lady	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
are	O
constant	O
in	O
their	O
attendance	O
on	O
Windsor	O
Terrace	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
much	O
wonder	O
at	O
,	O
as	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
does	O
not	O
invite	O
them	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Evening	O
parties	O
--	O
surely	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
particulary	O
mortifying	O
to	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
,	O
in	O
confidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
blame	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
's	O
manners	O
towards	O
her	O
(	O
17	O
her	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
grieve	O
to	O
sa	O
y	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
invariably	O
been	O
attentive	O
&	O
kind	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
affectionate	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
owed	O
,	O
whenever	O
I	O
expreſsed	O
my	O
acknowledgments	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
amiable	O
interference	O
in	O
persuading	O
his	O
Cousin	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
marry	O
her	O
--	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
repeatedly	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
history	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
par	O
enthesis	O
I	O
repeat	O
I	O
grieve	O
to	O
say	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
A	I-pers
:	I-pers
manners	O
towards	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
often	O
witneſs	O
to	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
provokingly	O
haughty	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
most	O
improperly	O
&	O
unprovokedly	O
insolent	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
many	O
other	O
letters	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
Yours	O
in	O
true	O
confidence	O
,	O
&	O
Sincerity	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
15	O
th	O
June	O
1780	O
Our	O
journey	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
fine	O
,	O
the	O
Roads	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
views	O
beautiful	O
,	O
particularly	O
from	O
East	B-place
Grinstead	I-place
to	O
Ukfield	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
prospect	O
was	O
more	O
confined	O
but	O
the	O
Fields	O
were	O
covered	O
with	O
charming	O
Verdure	O
bounded	O
by	O
luxuriant	O
Hedge-rows	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
Miles	O
from	O
East-bourne	B-place
it	O
is	O
barren	O
flat	O
,	O
&	O
dreary	O
.	O
Nothing	O
could	O
exceed	O
the	O
loyalty	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
This	O
circumstance	O
after	O
the	O
recent	O
melancholy	O
confusion	O
&	O
uproar	O
in	O
the	O
Capital	O
was	O
particularly	O
pleasing	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
highly	O
gratifying	O
to	O
their	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
's	O
.	O
every	O
Town	O
&	O
Village	O
through	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
paſsed	O
shewed	O
testimony	O
of	O
respect	O
&	O
attention	O
--	O
Bells	O
ringing	O
--	O
firing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
the	O
roads	O
lined	O
with	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
strewed	O
flowers	O
&	O
rushes	O
,	O
&	O
flung	O
Nosegays	O
into	O
the	O
Carriages	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
alighted	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
we	O
were	O
covered	O
with	O
the	O
flowers	O
which	O
the	O
poor	O
Women	O
showerd	O
over	O
us	O
--	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Governor	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
rewarded	O
them	O
by	O
throwing	O
Silver	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
gave	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Towns	O
&	O
Villages	O
for	O
the	O
Bell	O
ringers	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
abt	O
7	O
Miles	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
a	O
large	O
party	O
of	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
their	O
Wives	O
&	O
Daughters	O
behind	O
them	O
met	O
the	O
Royal	O
Children	O
&	O
after	O
giving	O
them	O
3	O
Chears	O
turned	O
their	O
Horses	O
&	O
escorted	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Habitation	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
neighbouring	O
Villages	O
--	O
The	O
Sailors	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Beach	O
fired	O
Cannon	O
at	O
intervals	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Cask	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
was	O
placed	O
there	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
orders	O
&	O
was	O
emptied	O
to	O
the	O
(	O
19	O
the	O
Healths	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Royal	B-pers
Family	I-pers
--	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
cheering	O
to	O
ones	O
spirits	O
after	O
the	O
horrid	O
transactions	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
The	O
reconciliation	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
the	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gloucester	I-pers
&	O
Cumberland	B-pers
is	O
now	O
made	O
public	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
introduced	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Princes	I-pers
&	O
Princeſs	B-pers
's	I-pers
with	O
the	O
restriction	O
that	O
their	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
's	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
's	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gloucester	I-pers
or	O
Cumberland	B-pers
--	O
They	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Elder	O
Princes	O
are	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
their	O
is	O
every	O
appearance	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
comfortable	O
here	O
&	O
spend	O
our	O
time	O
agreeably	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
as	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
always	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
affectionate	O
towards	O
me	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
R——	I-pers
&	O
love	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
.	O
June	O
1780	O
The	O
Birth	O
day	O
was	O
celebrated	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
Loyal	O
Manner	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Brother	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
played	O
at	O
Commerce	O
with	O
their	O
R	O
:	O
Highneſs	O
--	O
and	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
kept	O
them	O
to	O
sup	O
with	O
us	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
the	O
honor	O
&	O
gratification	O
of	O
another	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
she	O
informed	O
me	O
she	O
h	O
d	O
ad	O
not	O
seen	O
any	O
one	O
I	O
was	O
interested	O
about	O
,	O
except	O
yourself	O
at	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
near	O
Richmond	B-place
&	O
that	O
your	O
Father	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
writes	O
word	O
Lord	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
laughed	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
intention	O
,	O
of	O
20/	O
marrying	O
L	B-pers
MW	I-pers
.	I-pers
by	O
his	O
gay	O
companions	O
reminding	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
declarions	O
declarations	O
never	O
to	O
marry	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Egermont	I-pers
will	O
be	O
hurt	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
told	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
how	O
happy	O
&	O
pleased	O
she	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
intended	O
match	O
&	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Son	I-pers
would	O
marry	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
MH	B-pers
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
17	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1780	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.Budé	I-pers
has	O
written	O
you	O
a	O
Note	O
which	O
I	O
inclose	O
--	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
amiable	O
but	O
he	O
imagines	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
dupe	O
to	O
his	O
external	O
appearance	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Farhill	I-pers
are	O
very	O
ill	O
treated	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
are	O
all	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Domestic	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
hated	O
by	O
them	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
deservedly	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
your	O
Father	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
for	O
the	O
relief	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
Widow	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
raising	O
a	O
subscription	O
--	O
your	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
desired	O
I	O
would	O
never	O
would	O
scruple	O
applying	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
objects	O
of	O
real	O
distreſs	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
wished	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
him	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
left	O
an	O
amiable	O
beautiful	O
Wife	O
with	O
6	O
Children	O
--	O
from	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
circumstances	O
,	O
chiefly	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
illneſs	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sometime	O
deeply	O
involved	O
in	O
debt	O
.	O
The	O
Creditors	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
all	O
she	O
has	O
,	O
this	O
stroke	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
an	O
affectionate	O
Husband	O
has	O
overwhelmd	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
to	O
plead	O
for	O
my	O
poor	O
Widow	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
there	O
were	O
500	O
people	O
at	O
(	O
21	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Leeds	I-pers
's	O
Ball	O
at	O
Tunbridge	B-place
on	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
-	O
Tunbridge	B-place
is	O
quite	O
full	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
respecting	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
--	O
your	O
not	O
having	O
written	O
last	O
post	O
makes	O
me	O
fear	O
you	O
are	O
worse	O
than	O
you	O
represented	O
yourself	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
Queens	O
Upper	O
Lodge	O
Octbr	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1780	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
hour	O
to	O
myself	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
sitting	O
with	O
my	O
door	O
locked	O
to	O
prevent	O
intrusion	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
post	O
I	O
fear	O
will	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
haste	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
meeting	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
since	O
you	O
left	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
but	O
have	O
just	O
recd	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
tomorrow	O
&	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
its	O
contents	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
--	O
to	O
the	O
Younger	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
nor	O
never	O
could	O
bear	O
the	O
fatigue	O
of	O
much	O
walking	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
wondered	O
at	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Mother	O
never	O
hardly	O
let	O
me	O
walk	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
excercise	O
I	O
took	O
was	O
in	O
Carriages	O
&	O
sometimes	O
on	O
Horseback	O
--	O
Prince	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
will	O
soon	O
go	O
to	O
Hanover	B-place
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Granville	I-pers
,	O
aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
came	O
here	O
yesterday	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
orders	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Prince	O
also	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Malortie	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
England	B-place
about	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Granville	I-pers
s	O
manners	O
are	O
very	O
engaging	O
&	O
Gentleman	O
like	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
will	O
lose	O
his	O
Governors	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
&	O
have	O
22/	O
have	O
an	O
establishment	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
remain	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
in	O
Town	B-place
till	O
he	O
is	O
21	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
was	O
here	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Eveg	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
remarkably	O
polite	O
&	O
attentive	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
but	O
far	O
otherwise	O
to	O
——	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
foolish	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
piqued	O
at	O
--	O
The	O
reason	O
I	O
suppose	O
why	O
he	O
honored	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
prate	O
was	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
relations	O
&	O
c	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
is	O
fixed	O
for	O
the	O
Christening	O
--	O
Monday	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
In	O
the	O
Morng	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
,	O
as	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Sons	O
are	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
offering	O
before	O
they	O
quit	O
Windsor	B-place
therefore	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
say	O
Farewell	O
--	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
20	O
August	O
1781	O
Queens	O
Upper	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
(	O
To	O
ye	O
.	O
Honble	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
Horton	B-place
)	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
on	O
Friday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
frd	O
.	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
expects	O
you	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
delay	O
not	O
then	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
fix	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
week	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
absent	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
will	O
be	O
recovered	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
can	O
meet	O
--	O
for	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
from	O
7	O
till	O
11	O
three	O
Evegs	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
week	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
her	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
to	O
Kew	B-place
&	O
when	O
things	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
a	O
regu	O
r	O
lar	O
train	O
.	O
The	O
Féte	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	O
was	O
charming	O
--	O
The	O
Supper	O
was	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Georges	O
Hall	O
&	O
put	O
one	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
descriptions	O
in	O
The	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Genie	O
,	O
the	O
illuminations	O
&	O
decorations	O
of	O
the	O
Tables	O
was	O
so	O
brilliant	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
describe	O
(	O
23	O
my	O
dear	O
loved	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
is	O
now	O
under	O
this	O
Roof	O
&	O
will	O
remain	O
till	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
returns	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
expected	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
once	O
before	O
told	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
doing	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
I	O
was	O
certain	O
she	O
would	O
like	O
her	O
&	O
admire	O
her	O
character	O
&	O
manners	O
In	O
great	O
haste	O
ever	O
Yours	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
How	O
poor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
been	O
disappointed	O
!	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
friend	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
&	O
arrived	O
got	O
there	O
just	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
invitation	O
arrived	O
--	O
She	O
came	O
here	O
on	O
Friday	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
have	O
5	O
Minutes	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
alone	O
.	O
31	O
Octbr	O
1781	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Wednesday	O
night	O
¼	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
the	O
busineſs	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
is	O
in	O
bed	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
also	O
hasten	O
to	O
mine	O
as	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
steal	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
promise	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
--	O
My	O
Head	O
aches	O
--	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
worn	O
,	O
my	O
body	O
is	O
greatly	O
fatigued	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
has	O
been	O
confined	O
some	O
days	O
by	O
illneſs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
to	O
take	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
&	O
c	O
home	O
--	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
4	O
hours	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
Pſs-	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
giving	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
during	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
instead	O
of	O
remaining	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
with	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Augusta	B-pers
who	O
went	O
with	O
their	O
Majesties	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
--	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
from	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morng	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
running	O
24/	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
those	O
high	O
flights	O
of	O
stairs	O
&	O
so	O
on	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
finish	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
without	O
moving	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
my	O
fan	O
three	O
hours	O
&	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
to	O
add	O
as	O
the	O
Pſ	O
's	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
To	O
add	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
House	O
maid	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
for	O
myself	O
--	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
yet	O
had	O
any	O
aſsistance	O
from	O
poor	O
Goodyear	B-pers
--	O
all	O
this	O
will	O
convince	O
you	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
lay	O
down	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
Saty	O
3	O
d	O
--	O
Yesterday	O
was	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Birthday	O
Today	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
favorite	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
finished	O
painting	O
the	O
Satin	O
Border	O
&	O
even	O
I	O
myself	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
&	O
think	O
it	O
looks	O
elegant	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
color	O
'd	O
Sattin	O
Sliper	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
Lady	O
will	O
make	O
her	O
appearance	O
with	O
it	O
this	O
Eveg-	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
is	O
arrived	O
from	O
Holland	B-place
to	O
settle	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
she	O
will	O
belong	O
solely	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
be	O
in	O
quality	O
of	O
Lectrice	O
,	O
as	O
Mon̅	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
is	O
in	O
that	O
of	O
Lecture	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
I	O
suppose	O
only	O
read	O
French	O
&	O
German	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
generally	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
reading	O
english	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
's	O
Husband	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Preceptor	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Orange	I-pers
's	O
Children	O
.	O
(	O
Madme	O
.	O
has	O
brought	O
a	O
Child	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
Daughter	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
)	O
Se	O
is	O
extremely	O
plain	O
in	O
face	O
&	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
sensible	O
countenance	O
--	O
her	O
voice	O
not	O
pleasant	O
in	O
reading	O
--	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
has	O
undertaken	O
a	O
situation	O
she	O
appears	O
seems	O
to	O
(	O
25	O
to	O
me	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
calculated	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
bad	O
health	O
&	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
tender	O
constitution	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
very	O
weak	O
lungs	O
&	O
Eyes	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
concerned	O
for	O
this	O
Stranger	O
&	O
think	O
my	O
good	O
friend	O
De	B-pers
Luc	I-pers
has	O
judged	O
ill	O
to	O
transplant	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
native	O
Land	O
&	O
friends	O
--	O
particularly	O
too	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
young	O
--	O
she	O
looks	O
60	O
--	O
though	O
perhaps	O
not	O
near	O
so	O
old	O
--	O
as	O
her	O
complexion	O
,	O
grief	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
--	O
delicate	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
other	O
causes	O
may	O
make	O
her	O
appear	O
much	O
older	O
than	O
she	O
really	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pre-resolved	O
to	O
shew	O
this	O
poor	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
every	O
attention	O
--	O
for	O
though	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
will	O
be	O
most	O
kind	O
,	O
gracious	O
&	O
generous	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
others	O
will	O
slight	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
shew	O
her	O
moon	O
shine	O
civility	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
25	O
th	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
--	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
tomorrow	O
The	O
family	O
to	O
settle	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
return	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
to	O
attend	O
his	B-pers
Majesti	I-pers
es	O
hunting	O
party	O
These	O
excursions	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
from	O
Friday	O
ti	O
ll	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
delight	O
in	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
your	O
return	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
keep	O
your	O
word	O
,	O
&	O
arrive	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
then	O
see	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
-	O
time	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
as	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
Thursday	O
&	O
we	O
may	O
spend	O
that	O
Evg	O
together	O
--	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
26/	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
14	O
th	O
Jan	O
1782	O
--	O
I	O
suffered	O
many	O
hours	O
of	O
anxiety	O
on	O
your	O
acct	O
.	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
spared	O
had	O
your	O
letter	O
been	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
,	O
for	O
though	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
date	O
your	O
letter	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
had	O
so	O
seriously	O
promised	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
uneasineſs	O
I	O
suffered	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
particularly	O
too	O
as	O
no	O
post	O
went	O
form	O
hence	O
that	O
day	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
contrive	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
meſsenger	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
my	O
friend	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
place	O
any	O
faith	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
skill	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
--	O
You	O
aſsure	O
me	O
you	O
feel	O
“	O
rather	O
better	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
hope	O
you	O
neither	O
deceive	O
me	O
nay	O
yourself	O
.	O
--	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
not	O
free	O
from	O
one	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
they	O
will	O
venture	O
either	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
or	O
Opera	O
before	O
the	O
Great	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
enquired	O
after	O
your	O
health	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
melancholy	O
gloom	O
cast	O
over	O
our	O
whole	O
party	O
,	O
indeed	O
my	O
spirits	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
leisure	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
any	O
detail	O
--	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
who	O
this	O
day	O
week	O
was	O
under	O
this	O
Roof	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
good	O
spirits	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
deplorable	O
of	O
all	O
situations	O
,	O
--	O
confined	O
as	O
a	O
lunatic	O
&	O
raving	O
Mad	O
!	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Ever	O
most	O
Affy	O
.	O
Your	O
frd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
27	O
From	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Eſ	O
U	O
pshire	O
Farm	O
Eſsex	B-place
26	O
th	O
.	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
1783	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
unleſs	O
you	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
Courteenhall	O
--	O
this	O
requires	O
explanation	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
proposed	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
should	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
&	O
Mother	O
in	O
Yorkshire	B-place
,	O
&	O
my	O
amiable	O
friend	O
has	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
have	O
kindly	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
--	O
if	O
we	O
go	O
we	O
shall	O
stop	O
one	O
day	O
night	O
at	O
Courteenhall	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
busineſs	O
wch	O
will	O
detain	O
him	O
in	O
Eſsex	B-place
,	O
therefore	O
our	O
party	O
will	O
consist	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
her	B-pers
eldest	I-pers
Son	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Tutor	O
&	O
myself	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
stay	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
at	O
Mr-	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
attend	O
Northampton	B-place
Races	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
is	O
expected	O
back	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
bring	O
good	O
accts	O
.	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
,	O
&	O
that	O
his	O
Domestics	O
&	O
Neighbours	O
are	O
recovered	O
from	O
ye-	O
late	O
epidemic	O
disorder	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
not	O
seated	O
in	O
a	O
“	O
Proud	O
Alcove	O
”	O
or	O
Gothic	O
Temple	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
humble	O
shed	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
gratifying	O
the	O
wish	O
of	O
your	O
heart	O
in	O
hastening	O
on	O
to	O
a	O
beloved	O
Father	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
fine	O
a	O
day	O
for	O
your	O
Journey	O
--	O
Yesterday	O
the	O
weather	O
was	O
agreeably	O
pleasant	O
&	O
Dr	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
endulged	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
scheme	O
I	O
proposed	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
all	O
dine	O
in	O
the	O
Forest	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
day	O
.	O
--	O
pray	O
say	O
many	O
civil	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
Brother	O
&	O
aſsure	O
him	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
angry	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
I	O
certainly	O
would	O
have	O
spent	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
,	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
.	O
28	O
)	O
Bullstrode	O
Decbr	O
.	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
would	O
acquaint	O
you	O
why	O
I	O
prolonged	O
my	O
stay	O
with	O
the	O
Dr.	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
I	O
earnestly	O
wishd	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
so	O
warmly	O
&	O
affectionately	O
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
continue	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
that	O
it	O
was	O
hardly	O
im	O
poſsible	O
to	O
refuse	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
being	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
extremely	O
ill	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
longer	O
hesitate	O
--	O
These	O
two	O
Dear	O
friends	O
wanted	O
the	O
attention	O
&	O
friendly	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
their	O
spirits	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
my	O
endeavours	O
had	O
that	O
effect	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
touching	O
to	O
observe	O
their	O
tender	O
solicitude	O
for	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
exerting	O
herself	O
to	O
appear	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
alarm	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
,	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Dſs-	I-pers
using	O
every	O
effort	O
of	O
her	O
reason	O
to	O
conceal	O
from	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
her	O
anxiety	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
in	O
surprising	O
health	O
as	O
in	O
leſs	O
than	O
a	O
Month	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
84	O
--	O
her	O
birth	O
dates	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
year	O
--	O
Her	O
faculties	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
impaired	O
--	O
her	O
sight	O
only	O
excepted	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
been	O
failing	O
sometime	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
reads	O
,	O
&	O
writes	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
&	O
employs	O
herself	O
in	O
various	O
works	O
--	O
The	O
vigor	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
--	O
the	O
activity	O
of	O
her	O
limbs	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
sensibility	O
of	O
her	O
heart	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
young	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
n	O
veneration	O
&	O
love	O
for	O
this	O
most	O
excellent	O
of	O
women	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
talk	O
of	O
her	O
without	O
ceasing	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
every	O
day	O
more	O
charmed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
very	O
fortunate	O
in	O
having	O
had	O
opportunities	O
of	O
benifiting	O
by	O
the	O
contemplation	O
of	O
such	O
rare	O
human	O
perfection	O
,	O
&	O
receiving	O
instruction	O
by	O
listening	O
to	O
precepts	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
engraven	O
on	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
my	O
Dear	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Dowgr	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Carslisle	I-pers
is	O
returned	O
to	O
England	B-place
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
(	O
29	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
lose	O
many	O
pleasant	O
hours	O
at	O
Carlisle	O
House	O
--	O
for	O
you	O
certainly	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
infamous	O
,	O
&	O
,	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Carslisle	I-pers
,	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
has	O
shewn	O
her	O
great	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
probable	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
much	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
10	O
Decbr	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
sendg	O
.	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
thousand	O
things	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
Dr-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
has	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
time	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
indifferent	O
night	O
&	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
head	O
ach	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
attended	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
supper	O
just	O
ready	O
&	O
my	O
Dear	O
Ducheſs	O
will	O
wait	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
franks	O
send	O
your	O
letters	O
to	O
WhiteHall	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
left	O
us	O
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
three	O
days	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
here	O
again	O
next	O
Saturday	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
written	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
has	O
done	O
him	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
invite	O
him	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
for	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
the	O
18	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
your	O
plans	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
ever	O
Yours	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
This	O
date	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
correct	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
103	O
years	O
old	O
she	O
died	O
15	O
April	O
1788	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
1803	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G.Glover	I-pers
under	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
unpromising	O
exterior	O
poſseſses	O
every	O
good	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
heart	O
,	O
her	O
principles	O
are	O
founded	O
on	O
rectitude	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
warmest	O
&	O
most	O
steady	O
friend	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
to	O
esteem	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
deserves	O
one	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
opportunities	O
of	O
knowing	O
her	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
mere	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
manners	O
&	O
language	O
are	O
destitute	O
of	O
that	O
polish	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
requisite	O
in	O
that	O
society	O
to	O
which	O
her	O
Husband	O
belongs	O
,	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
Birth	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
from	O
her	O
education	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
30	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Farhill	I-pers
called	O
on	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
poem	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
written	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
printed	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Copies	O
printed	O
of	O
for	O
the	O
gratification	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
who	O
requested	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
imitation	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Juvenals	O
Satires	O
--	O
the	O
title	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
Nobility	O
we	O
will	O
read	O
it	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
Hour	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
this	O
morng	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
charming	O
spirits	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
chat	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
enquired	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
expreſsed	O
much	O
concern	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
entertained	O
by	O
the	O
prattle	O
of	O
Beau	B-pers
Tutteridge	I-pers
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guests	O
--	O
had	O
I	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
little	O
Burney	B-pers
's	O
talents	O
I	O
could	O
amuse	O
you	O
by	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
this	O
good	O
natured	O
coxcombical	O
being	O
.	O
He	O
boasted	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Original	O
from	O
whom	O
his	O
Royal	B-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
the	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
,	O
&	O
heir	O
apparent	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
England	B-place
copied	O
,	O
viz	O
his	O
Buckles	O
,	O
snuff	O
boxes	O
&	O
so	O
forth	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
Prince	O
unfortunately	O
does	O
not	O
have	O
his	O
hair	O
dreſsed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
stile	O
as	O
Tutteridge	B-pers
's	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
condemns	O
it	O
as	O
very	O
outre	O
&	O
unbecoming	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
old	O
Friend	O
Leonidas	B-pers
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
,	O
&	O
read	O
aloud	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
Manuscript	O
Comedy	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
wrote	O
30	O
years	O
ago	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
comedy	O
he	O
ever	O
wrote	O
--	O
The	O
Story	O
is	O
taken	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Arabian	O
nights	O
Entertainments	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Persian	O
Tales	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
entertaining	O
&	O
very	O
moral	O
--	O
interesting	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
dash	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
sentimental	O
--	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
in	O
16	O
days	O
&	O
though	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
corrected	O
it	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Preſs	O
.	O
(	O
31	O
1	O
st	O
-	O
July	O
1784	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
My	O
Dear	O
friend	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
pry	O
into	O
any	O
secret	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
communicate	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
require	O
is	O
the	O
continuance	O
of	O
the	O
affection	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
highest	O
opinion	O
of	O
your	O
understanding	O
&	O
well	O
know	O
how	O
inferior	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
judgment	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
visit	O
you	O
at	O
your	B-pers
Father	I-pers
s	O
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
engaged	O
me	O
to	O
execute	O
so	O
many	O
commiſsions	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
end	O
to	O
ym-	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
but	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Miles	O
from	O
Town	B-place
I	O
could	O
easily	O
go	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
could	O
return	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
commiſsion	O
is	O
to	O
superintend	O
the	O
progreſs	O
of	O
a	O
n	O
Drawg	O
&	O
engraving	O
by	O
Cipriani	B-pers
of	O
the	O
fine	O
Antique	O
Vase	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
Friday	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
has	O
just	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
had	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
on	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
North	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
waiting	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachel	I-pers
s	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
hourly	O
expects	O
,	O
&	O
after	O
ye	O
:	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
or	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
day	O
after	O
that	O
event	O
she	O
intends	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
now	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
posſibility	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
busineſs	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
train	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
finished	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
accompany	O
her	O
&	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
settled	O
this	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
&	O
you	O
must	O
inform	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
in	O
your	B-pers
Father	I-pers
s	O
carriage	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
&	O
where	O
the	O
Coach	O
sets	O
out	O
that	O
your	O
Servants	O
always	O
go	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
her	O
maid	O
by	O
that	O
conveyance	O
32/	O
conveyance	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
take	O
one	O
as	O
yours	O
or	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
can	O
dreſs	O
my	O
Hair	O
)	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
place	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
Chaise	O
--	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
is	O
to	O
accompany	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
we	O
shall	O
travel	O
with	O
post	O
horses	O
.	O
My	O
mind	O
is	O
quite	O
set	O
in	O
this	O
scheme	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
fears	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
manage	O
it	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Wm	B-pers
so	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
almost	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
humor	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
forced	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
Town	B-place
&	O
set	O
aside	O
all	O
my	O
Summer	O
engagements	O
&	O
disappoint	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
his	O
society	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
amends	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
rambling	O
over	O
the	O
Hills	O
&	O
far	O
away	O
I	O
was	O
my	O
dear	O
quite	O
affected	O
with	O
your	O
narrative	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
has	O
so	O
benevolently	O
taken	O
under	O
his	O
protection	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
astonished	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
has	O
acted	O
so	O
inconsiderately	O
as	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Guidance	O
at	O
Freestone	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
informs	O
me	O
she	O
dined	O
lately	O
at	O
Abington	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
party	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
acquitted	O
herself	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
this	O
Summer	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
interested	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
both	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
&	O
her	O
late	O
mother	O
s	O
sake	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
hoped	O
she	O
would	O
reap	O
great	O
advantage	O
by	O
forming	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
Isabella	B-pers
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
that	O
vile	O
Woman	O
the	B-pers
Dowg	I-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
what	O
a	O
dreadful	O
end	O
to	O
an	O
infamous	O
life	O
!	O
perhaps	O
you	O
(	O
33	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
the	O
following	O
particulars	O
33	O
concerning	O
her	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
relate	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
depend	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
person	O
who	O
informed	O
me	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
was	O
perfectly	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
high	O
spirits	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
,	O
was	O
out	O
all	O
Morning	O
&	O
dined	O
with	O
her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Abington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Actreſs	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
cause	O
of	O
displeasure	O
against	O
her	O
Porter	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
dreadful	O
paſsion	O
--	O
the	O
man	O
saw	O
her	O
stagger	O
&	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fall	O
--	O
he	O
caught	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
the	O
miserable	O
wretch	O
was	O
struck	O
wth-	O
death	O
,	O
all	O
she	O
said	O
after	O
the	O
Porter	O
had	O
placed	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
“	O
dont	O
leave	O
me	O
,	O
”	O
she	O
remained	O
there	O
two	O
hours	O
--	O
The	O
Apothecary	O
found	O
her	O
a	O
melancholy	O
object	O
,	O
her	O
tongue	O
hanging	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mouth	O
&	O
black	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
insensible	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
--	O
what	O
is	O
very	O
surprising	O
no	O
one	O
has	O
yet	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
order	O
respecting	O
the	O
Body	O
--	O
her	O
Servants	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Shell	O
in	O
wch-	O
they	O
have	O
placed	O
the	O
Corpse	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
dreſsed	O
in	O
White	O
Sattin	O
&	O
a	O
lace	O
Mob	O
cap	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
one	O
who	O
chuses	O
is	O
admitted	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
several	O
Young	O
Men	O
of	O
the	O
Haut-Ton	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
this	O
awful	O
spectacle	O
--	O
God	O
Grant	O
it	O
may	O
excite	O
some	O
profitable	O
and	O
lasting	O
impreſsions	O
on	O
their	O
minds	O
--	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Craggs	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
breathed	O
her	O
last	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
too	O
deeply	O
afflicted	O
34/	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
orders	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
also	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
her	O
Executor	O
Sir	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Crawford	I-pers
has	O
not	O
yet	O
acted	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
striking	O
leſson	O
might	O
this	O
event	O
be	O
to	O
the	O
vicious	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
do	O
not	O
strive	O
to	O
check	O
their	O
paſsions	O
--	O
how	O
dreadful	O
the	O
thought	O
that	O
a	O
human	O
creature	O
should	O
thus	O
unprepared	O
,	O
&	O
unrepenting	O
rush	O
into	O
an	O
awful	O
eternity	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
that	O
whenever	O
this	O
unhappy	O
creature	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
,	O
in	O
transports	O
of	O
despair	O
to	O
say	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
die	O
”	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
wont	O
die	O
”	O
--	O
enough	O
&	O
too	O
much	O
on	O
this	O
melancholy	O
subject	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
is	O
ill	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
yesterday	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
make	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
not	O
attending	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
indisposed	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
opp	O
r	O
eſsion	O
on	O
his	O
breath	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
this	O
my	O
worthy	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
told	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
is	O
so	O
ill	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Burrel	I-pers
&	O
her	B-pers
Mother	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
expreſs	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
--	O
the	O
Duke	O
is	O
drinking	O
himself	O
to	O
death	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
poſsible	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
who	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
l	O
a	O
y	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
always	O
joins	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
this	O
this	O
very	O
pleasant	O
,	O
Adieu	O
ton	O
chere	O
Amie	O
!	O
Mry	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
35	O
)	O
Monday	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1804	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
You	O
will	O
my	O
dearest	O
very	O
easily	O
comprehend	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
mortified	O
&	O
disappointed	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
too	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
concern	O
will	O
I	O
know	O
be	O
equally	O
so	O
!	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
accompany	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
tomorrow	O
&	O
I	O
also	O
greatly	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
Visit	O
you	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
however	O
still	O
hope	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
between	O
the	O
fortnight	O
Drawing	O
Rooms	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
then	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
has	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
most	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Sunday	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Saturday	O
at	O
her	O
Villa	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
&	O
I	O
returned	O
by	O
11	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
,	O
she	O
inquired	O
kindly	O
after	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Catherine	I-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mss	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boyle	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
him	O
--	O
(	O
notwithstanding	O
some	O
reports	O
I	O
have	O
certainly	O
heard	O
to	O
his	O
disadvantage	O
)	O
--	O
he	O
appears	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
sensible	O
,	O
&	O
polite	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
affectionate	O
terms	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
uncommonly	O
attentive	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
quite	O
adores	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
fond	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
a	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
enjoy	O
his	O
society	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
with	O
her	O
very	O
soon	O
again	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
run	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
intervals	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
affairs	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
in	O
for	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
.	O
People	O
may	O
say	O
what	O
they	O
please	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
,	O
even	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
steady	O
,	O
sincere	O
,	O
&	O
consistent	O
,	O
towards	O
myself	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
un-	O
36/	O
ungrateful	O
indeed	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
acknowle	O
g	O
d	O
ge	O
it	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
who	O
chuses	O
to	O
abuse	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
time	O
give	O
you	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
her	O
true	O
character	O
,	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
is	O
,	O
some	O
austerity	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
few	O
are	O
her	O
equals	O
in	O
strength	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
mental	O
acquirements	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
truth	O
maintain	O
she	O
is	O
truly	O
religious	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
devoid	O
of	O
benevolence	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
many	O
aſsert	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
acquainting	O
her	O
with	O
any	O
object	O
deserving	O
of	O
relief	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
feel	O
interested	O
for	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
was	O
seriously	O
displeased	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
applied	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
whom	O
she	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
anxious	O
about	O
--	O
&	O
without	O
my	O
asking	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
something	O
very	O
handsome	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
distreſsed	O
creatures	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
has	O
resigned	O
her	O
place	O
as	O
Lady	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bedchamber	O
to	O
her	O
Majesty	O
wch-	O
was	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
,	O
accepted	O
without	O
any	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
regret	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
succeeds	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
delighted	O
with	O
the	O
distinguished	O
honor	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
appointment	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
spend	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
tomorrow	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
obliged	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
--	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
people	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
dine	O
,	O
&	O
return	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morng	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
greatest	O
haste	O
having	O
a	O
thousand	O
things	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
letters	O
to	O
answer	O
Heaven	O
give	O
you	O
health	O
&	O
protect	O
you	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
frd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
37	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
My	O
dear	O
--	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
disappointed	O
in	O
seeing	O
my	O
,	O
delight	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cousin	O
Charles	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
--	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
bad	O
cold	O
by	O
walking	O
home	O
instead	O
of	O
having	O
my	O
Chair	O
,	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
feet	O
got	O
wet	O
--	O
O	O
how	O
I	O
lament	O
my	O
poor	O
dear	O
Parents	O
brought	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fine	O
Lady	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
last	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
his	O
friend	O
&	O
yours	O
was	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
heard	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
uncertain	O
if	O
any	O
letters	O
would	O
reach	O
him	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
has	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
further	O
information	O
before	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
very	O
highly	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
of	O
your	O
family	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
of	O
gratitude	O
&	O
sincere	O
affection	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Young	I-pers
is	O
now	O
at	O
Madrás	B-place
&	O
my	B-pers
Cousin	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
deteremination	O
respecting	O
his	O
continuance	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
would	O
be	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
more	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
I	O
must	O
conclude	O
,	O
Ever	O
tenderly	O
Yours	O
Mry	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Enclose	O
to	O
Viscount	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Portland	O
place	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
Sepbr-	O
1804	O
Harwood	B-place
Sunbury	B-place
Middlesex	B-place
My	O
Dearest	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
last	O
Sunday	O
&	O
am	O
engaged	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Monday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
two	O
Dear	O
Old	O
friends	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
where	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
a	O
long	O
Stay	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
is	O
at	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
s	O
Riddlesworth	O
Hall	O
Norfolk	B-place
she	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Governeſs	O
for	O
her	O
Daughters	O
,	O
I	O
38	O
)	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Dear	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
pray	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
immediately	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Madame	B-pers
Busche	I-pers
she	O
makes	O
me	O
many	O
apologies	O
and	O
entreats	O
the	O
continuance	O
of	O
my	O
friendship	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
The	O
worthy	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
confidant	O
i	O
f	O
n	O
this	O
strange	O
&	O
unexpected	O
conduct	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
has	O
cleared	O
up	O
the	O
mystery	O
,	O
but	O
under	O
promise	O
of	O
my	O
not	O
repeating	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Let	O
me	O
hear	O
very	O
particulary	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
your	O
Hip	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
doing	O
,	O
&	O
sometimes	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
think	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
graciously	O
inclined	O
enclose	O
your	O
Packets	O
to	O
Viscount	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
will	O
forward	O
them	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
am	O
gone	O
frm	O
.	O
thence	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Dſs-	I-pers
--	I-pers
Dog	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
quiet	O
comfortable	O
place	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
receive	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
observing	O
that	O
my	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
is	O
very	O
happy	O
as	O
a	O
Wife	O
&	O
Mother	O
she	O
has	O
3	O
sweet	O
little	O
Girls	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
the	O
means	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
an	O
hospitable	O
&	O
agreeable	O
stile	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
will	O
my	O
Dearest	O
,	O
write	O
longer	O
letters	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
ye	O
:	O
cold	O
&	O
inflammation	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
Octbr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
1804	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
been	O
surprised	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
frd-	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
so	O
bad	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Harwood	B-place
that	O
I	O
really	O
had	O
not	O
spirits	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
indeed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prudent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
use	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
--	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
arrived	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
&	O
he	O
kindly	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
the	O
eye	O
waters	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
recommended	O
to	O
use	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
too	O
strong	O
,	O
&	O
did	O
more	O
harm	O
than	O
good	O
--	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
1	O
Grain	O
(	O
or	O
2	O
at	O
most	O
)	O
of	O
White	O
Vitriol	O
in	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
Elder	O
flower	O
water	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
Bathe	O
my	O
eyes	O
with	O
this	O
mixture	O
several	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
&	O
refrained	O
much	O
from	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
&	O
my	O
(	O
39	O
my	O
eyes	O
are	O
now	O
well	O
--	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
recipe	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
prescribe	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
who	O
has	O
inflamed	O
Eye	O
lids	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
complaint	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
your	O
little	O
note	O
at	O
Harwood	B-place
&	O
your	O
letter	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
has	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
invitation	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
next	O
Saturday	O
at	O
her	O
Villa	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
accept	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Day	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
disappointed	O
her	O
by	O
not	O
going	O
6	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
going	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
fixt	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
resist	O
spending	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
happily	O
with	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
is	O
ordered	O
by	O
her	O
Physician	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Winter	O
at	O
Nice	B-place
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
this	O
Summer	O
he	O
thought	O
her	O
looking	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
grown	O
extremely	O
weak	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
concerned	O
she	O
in	O
so	O
declining	O
a	O
state	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
will	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
before	O
your	O
dinner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
not	O
dine	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Maids	O
of	O
Honor	O
's	O
table	O
--	O
&	O
If	O
I	O
dine	O
there	O
I	O
shall	O
offend	O
my	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
--	O
&	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
alone	O
at	O
home	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
receive	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
sent	O
word	O
he	O
intends	O
coming	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
provided	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
alone	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
father	O
has	O
been	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
you	O
free	O
from	O
complaint	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
general	O
state	O
of	O
suffering	O
as	O
Yours	O
!	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
intends	O
taking	O
me	O
&	O
his	O
Daughter	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Northumberland	O
s	O
fine	O
Villa	O
at	O
Sion	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
Belle	O
&	O
chere	O
Amie	O
Dure	O
á	O
jamais	O
notre	O
Amitie	O
!	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
X	O
This	O
mention	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
proves	O
that	O
this	O
letter	O
should	O
be	O
dated	O
1784	O
&	O
not	O
1804	O
see	O
page	O
42	O
40	O
Bullstrode	O
Park	O
19	O
th	O
:	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1784	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
yesterday	O
my	O
Dear	O
in	O
a	O
frank	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
--	O
how	O
unfortunate	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
spend	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
comfortable	O
hours	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
depended	O
on	O
doing	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
--	O
surely	O
my	O
Dear	O
aſsurances	O
of	O
friendship	O
from	O
me	O
must	O
be	O
wholly	O
unneceſsary	O
for	O
you	O
will	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
sincerely	O
attached	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
yet	O
the	O
conclusion	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
was	O
gratifying	O
to	O
my	O
feelings	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
was	O
here	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
charmed	O
in	O
contemplating	O
the	O
virtues	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
friends	O
--	O
you	O
would	O
delight	O
on	O
their	O
conversation	O
--	O
their	O
manners	O
--	O
&	O
you	O
wld-	O
be	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
living	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
around	O
you	O
--	O
here	O
you	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
constant	O
fund	O
of	O
rational	O
&	O
instructive	O
amusements	O
--	O
&	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
advanced	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
you	O
would	O
find	O
constant	O
good	O
humour	O
&	O
chearfulneſs	O
made	O
their	O
society	O
as	O
desirable	O
as	O
their	O
Virtues	O
,	O
good	O
sense	O
,	O
cultivated	O
minds	O
,	O
&	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
make	O
it	O
equally	O
instructive	O
&	O
entertaining	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
parties	O
took	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
agreeable	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
admired	O
by	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
with	O
the	O
most	O
comfortable	O
acts	O
.	O
of	O
herself	O
&	O
Marianne	B-pers
--	O
she	O
aſsures	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
suffered	O
in	O
health	O
by	O
the	O
anxiety	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
on	O
her	O
Dr	O
.	O
Girl	O
s	O
account	O
who	O
is	O
recovering	O
fast	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
also	O
was	O
getting	O
better	O
--	O
this	O
last	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
having	O
been	O
leſs	O
violent	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
does	O
not	O
mention	O
when	O
they	O
shall	O
leave	O
Riddlesworth	O
Hall	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
illneſs	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
has	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
their	O
going	O
into	O
Yorkshire	B-place
.	O
20	O
th	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
Christmas	O
when	O
she	O
settles	O
in	O
Town	B-place
(	O
41	O
Town	B-place
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
in	O
ye	O
most	O
friendly	O
manner	O
insisted	O
most	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
shall	O
make	O
his	O
intended	O
visit	O
to	O
me	O
here	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
your	O
question	O
when	O
our	O
affairs	O
will	O
draw	O
to	O
a	O
conclusion	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
believe	O
our	O
union	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
place	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
perhaps	O
some	O
Months	O
--	O
we	O
mutually	O
wish	O
to	O
shew	O
every	O
mark	O
of	O
deference	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Senior	I-pers
--	O
who	O
wishes	O
to	O
arrange	O
&	O
set	O
tle	O
every	O
thing	O
between	O
himself	O
Son	O
&	O
Daughters	O
before	O
we	O
are	O
united	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
Thursday	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
More	I-pers
writes	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
has	O
lately	O
made	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
a	O
poor	O
Creature	O
whose	O
whole	O
life	O
has	O
been	O
devoted	O
to	O
the	O
lowest	O
affairs	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Milking	O
Cows	O
,	O
selling	O
the	O
Milk	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
streets	O
of	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
&	O
feeding	O
Swine	O
,	O
to	O
support	O
a	O
miserable	O
existence	O
,	O
&	O
procure	O
food	O
for	O
6	O
small	O
Children	O
--	O
&	O
yet	O
who	O
writes	O
most	O
excellent	O
verses	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
fine	O
imagination	O
,	O
stored	O
with	O
abundance	O
of	O
images	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
poetical	O
expreſsion	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
ear	O
so	O
finely	O
tuned	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
500	O
lines	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
detect	O
an	O
unmusical	O
one	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
very	O
noble	O
sentiments	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
is	O
infinitely	O
better	O
good	O
principles	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
select	O
in	O
choosing	O
words	O
though	O
she	O
has	O
never	O
seen	O
a	O
Dictionary	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
this	O
poor	O
Creature	O
is	O
a	O
prodigy	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
has	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Verses	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
as	O
myself	O
I	O
will	O
copy	O
them	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
read	O
Coxe	B-pers
s	O
Tour	O
--	O
through	O
Poland	B-place
Ruſsia	B-place
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
you	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
reading	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
friends	O
in	O
an	O
Eveg	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
almost	O
got	O
through	O
the	O
first	O
Volume	O
,	O
I	O
like	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
&	O
He	O
appears	O
an	O
impartial	O
writer	O
.	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
occupied	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
room	O
left	O
on	O
this	O
sheet	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
how	O
&	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
desire	O
their	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
is	O
charming	O
well	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
not	O
contrive	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
Morng	O
visit	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
?	O
I	O
fear	O
frm	O
.	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
live	O
long	O
--	O
how	O
did	O
she	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
for	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
Ever	O
yor	O
.	O
friend	O
Mry	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
42	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
letters	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
evidently	O
copies	O
of	O
the	O
originals	O
,	O
&	O
apparently	O
in	O
the	O
handwriting	O
of	O
M	O
rs	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
née	O
Mary	O
Hamilton	O
)	O
are	O
dated	O
1803	O
and	O
1804	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
signed	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
she	O
married	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
became	O
engaged	O
on	O
18	O
th	O
June	O
1784	O
)	O
on	O
13	O
th	O
June	O
1785	O
This	O
must	O
be	O
incorrect	O
&	O
the	O
proper	O
dates	O
are	O
probably	O
1783	O
and	O
1784	O
and	O
the	O
se	O
date	O
183	O
or	O
1804	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
date	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
letters	O
were	O
copied	O
Besides	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
,	O
dated	O
1804	O
,	O
reference	O
is	O
made	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
who	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
1700	O
&	O
died	O
on	O
15	O
th	O
April	O
1788	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
letters	O
appear	O
among	O
the	O
original	O
letters	O
in	O
No-	O
15	O
.	O
A	B-pers
E	I-pers
H	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
“	O
Southfield	O
”	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
on	I-place
sea	I-place
7	O
March	O
1906	O
43	O
N	O
o	O
of	O
Letter	O
Year	O
Month	O
Page	O
1	O
1780	O
mar	O
24	O
th	O
10	O
2	O
“	O
“	O
“	O
10	O
3	O
“	O
“	O
“	O
11	O
4	O
“	O
June	O
8	O
th	O
5	O
5	O
“	O
“	O
“	O
6	O
6	O
“	O
“	O
15	O
th	O
18	O
7	O
“	O
“	O
“	O
19	O
8	O
“	O
July	O
23	O
rd	O
3	O
9	O
“	O
Augt	O
14	O
th	O
4	O
10	O
“	O
“	O
17	O
th	O
20	O
11	O
“	O
“	O
31	O
st	O
7	O
12	O
“	O
Septr	O
4	O
th	O
13	O
13	O
“	O
“	O
7	O
th	O
16	O
14	O
“	O
“	O
18	O
th	O
16	O
15	O
“	O
“	O
23	O
rd	O
5	O
16	O
“	O
Octr	O
23	O
rd	O
21	O
17	O
1781	O
Augt	O
20	O
th	O
22	O
18	O
“	O
Octr	O
31	O
st	O
23	O
19	O
“	O
Novr	O
3	O
rd	O
24	O
20	O
“	O
“	O
25	O
th	O
25	O
21	O
1782	O
Janr	O
1	O
st	O
6	O
22	O
“	O
“	O
8	O
th	O
3	O
23	O
“	O
“	O
14	O
th	O
26	O
24	O
“	O
“	O
4	O
25	O
1783	O
Janr	O
19	O
th	O
29	O
misdated	O
1803	O
26	O
“	O
Septr	O
26	O
th	O
27	O
27	O
“	O
Decr	O
9	O
th	O
28	O
28	O
1784	O
July	O
1	O
st	O
31	O
29	O
“	O
“	O
12	O
th	O
35	O
30	O
“	O
“	O
27	O
th	O
1	O
31	O
“	O
Augt	O
23	O
37	O
32	O
“	O
Septr	O
20	O
37	O
misdated	O
1804	O
33	O
“	O
Octr	O
5	O
38	O
34	O
“	O
“	O
19	O
40	O
35	O
“	O
“	O
20	O
40	O
36	O
“	O
“	O
21	O
41	O
37	O
“	O
Novr	O
5	O
1	O
44	O
.	O
These	O
letters	O
were	O
written	O
to	O
Miss	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
,	O
maid	O
of	O
Honour	O
to	O
Queen	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
between	O
24	O
th	O
March	O
1780	O
and	O
5	O
th	O
November	O
1784	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
who	O
was	O
minister	O
plenipotentiary	O
at	O
Berlin	B-place
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
1734	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
1816	O
.	O
Miss	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
married	O
Colonel	B-pers
the	I-pers
Honble-	I-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
in	O
1790	O
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
Barbara	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
Isabella	I-pers
(	O
referred	O
to	O
as	O
Bella	B-pers
in	O
these	O
letters	O
)	O
Married	O
General	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
the	O
widow	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Dean	O
of	O
Down	B-place
who	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
1686	O
&	O
died	O
in	O
1768	O
Miss	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
was	O
born	O
in	O
1752	O
,	O
married	O
General	B-pers
Darblay	I-pers
in	O
1793	O
&	O
died	O
in	O
1840	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Dr	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
a	O
music	O
master	O
&	O
french	O
refugee	O
.	O
The	O
letters	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
copied	O
in	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
their	O
dates	O
but	O
in	O
page	O
43	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
arranged	O
and	O
numbered	O
in	O
that	O
order	O
.	O
Found	O
this	O
parcel	O
among	O
my	O
Papers	O
after	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
as	O
requested	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
