TOKEN	NE
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
fr	O
om	O
Mr	B-pers
Fredk	I-pers
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
having	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
storms	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
safe	O
though	O
a	O
rough	O
paſsage	O
to	O
Holy	B-place
Head	I-place
;	O
we	O
ran	O
it	O
in	O
light	O
hours	O
from	O
Skerries	B-place
,	O
the	O
inundations	O
that	O
are	O
every	O
where	O
can	O
hardly	O
be	O
conceiv	O
'd	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
safe	O
in	O
port	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
be	O
satisfied	O
to	O
pospone	O
my	O
projects	O
to	O
a	O
more	O
favourable	O
opportunity	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
combination	O
of	O
unforeseen	O
croſs	O
circumstances	O
seem	O
to	O
conspire	O
against	O
my	O
carrying	O
them	O
into	O
execution	O
at	O
present	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
my	O
expedition	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
an	O
unprofitable	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
arranged	O
my	O
affairs	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
without	O
requiring	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
concluded	O
amicably	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Buttle	I-pers
&	O
discharged	O
his	O
Bill	O
of	O
Costs	O
,	O
which	O
for	O
doing	O
leſs	O
than	O
nothing	O
was	O
still	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fetherston	I-pers
in	O
Dublin	B-place
concluding	O
a	O
Purchase	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
;	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
make	O
no	O
fixt	O
agreement	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
knowing	O
what	O
trouble	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
upon	O
my	O
account	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
aſsured	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
properly	O
considered	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
directions	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Welldone	I-pers
to	O
send	O
the	O
Picture	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
notice	O
,	O
as	O
your	O
collection	O
increases	O
,	O
I	O
conclude	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
larger	O
apartments	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
much	O
greater	O
civilities	O
from	O
many	O
people	O
here	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
my	O
residence	O
here	O
much	O
more	O
agreeable	O
than	O
it	O
has	O
hitherto	O
been	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Niece	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
Yours	O
most	O
affectionately	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
York	B-place
Feby	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
th	O
1764	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
F	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
