TOKEN	NE
Tunbridge	B-place
Wells	I-place
19	O
July	O
1782	O
--	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
surprised	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	B-place
Mountains	I-place
of	I-place
Ephraim	I-place
;	O
&	O
I	O
daresay	O
will	O
not	O
scruple	O
paying	O
postage	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
promised	O
land	O
;	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
always	O
too	O
so	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
your	O
friends	O
:	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
apologise	O
for	O
intruding	O
on	O
your	O
time	O
,	O
unleſs	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
worth	O
amusing	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
arrived	O
here	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
,	O
since	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
tersian	O
Ague	O
,	O
and	O
continualy	O
spoils	O
our	O
prospect	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
making	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
beautifull	O
scene	O
interspersed	O
on	O
the	O
Hills	O
all	O
round	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
comfortable	O
House	O
(	O
for	O
this	O
place	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Mount	B-place
Ephraim	I-place
stone	O
inside	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
out	O
:	O
for	O
the	O
owners	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
too	O
fine	O
to	O
hide	O
in	O
the	O
parlours	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
little	O
paint	O
--	O
the	O
floors	O
partake	O
of	O
the	O
Hilly	O
situation	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
center	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
sit	O
or	O
walk	O
on	O
the	O
slope	O
--	O
the	O
outside	O
is	O
as	O
singular	O
as	O
the	O
in	O
;	O
having	O
no	O
top	O
,	O
or	O
roof	O
:	O
it	O
apears	O
very	O
odd	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
very	O
heavy	O
rain	O
and	O
found	O
ourselves	O
safe	O
from	O
the	O
storm	O
have	O
been	O
satisfied	O
we	O
are	O
well	O
secured	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
makes	O
no	O
figure	O
--	O
the	O
Hill	O
is	O
all	O
interspersed	O
with	O
Lumps	O
of	O
rock	O
among	O
which	O
are	O
squeezed	O
little	O
cottages	O
&	O
Hovels	O
which	O
form	O
a	O
picturesque	O
view	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
we	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
Well	O
,	O
Mount	O
Sion	O
,	O
Mount	O
Pleasant	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
views	O
is	O
rather	O
presumptious	O
who	O
walk	O
the	O
Terrace	O
and	O
commend	O
that	O
beautifull	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
raise	O
your	O
curiosity	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Les	O
Roché	O
tout	O
proche	O
;	O
which	O
are	O
so	O
celebrated	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
,	O
a	O
comfortable	O
room	O
and	O
sincere	O
welcome	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Tunbridge	O
Water	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
your	O
nerves	O
!	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
very	O
weak	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
already	O
found	O
great	O
Benefit	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
allowed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
We	O
flatter	O
ourselves	O
she	O
will	O
return	O
so	O
recruited	O
and	O
stout	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
quite	O
pleased	O
at	O
the	O
improvement	O
--	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Bowlby	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Darnley	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bows	I-pers
,	O
Heathcote	B-pers
,	O
Grosvenor	B-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
but	O
they	O
go	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
&	O
daughter	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wyndham	I-pers
,	O
Nisbett	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
curiosity	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
,	O
particularly	O
our	O
Beaus	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wont	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
great	O
Cheſs	O
Players	O
also	O
Dtr	B-pers
:	I-pers
DBowdler	I-pers
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
Count	B-pers
Bhruhl	I-pers
s	O
club	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
the	O
Phisician	O
we	O
left	O
here	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
Dtr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
has	O
left	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
tis	O
said	O
his	O
practice	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
line	O
of	O
matrimony	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
perhaps	O
you	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honour	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Late	I-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Orange	I-pers
and	O
Sister	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
James	I-pers
Gray	I-pers
:	O
her	O
Mother	O
who	O
is	O
lately	O
Dead	O
near	O
100	O
was	O
always	O
against	O
the	O
match	O
and	O
her	O
daught	O
er	O
tho	O
'	O
near	O
or	O
quite	O
70	O
was	O
too	O
dutifull	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
obstacle	O
being	O
removed	O
't	O
is	O
expected	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
very	O
soon	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
yet	O
?	O
Lady	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
complains	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
Letters	O
sadly	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Prince	B-pers
Caramanico	I-pers
Lays	O
abed	O
all	O
day	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
little	O
use	O
to	O
employ	O
about	O
sending	O
them	O
more	O
safely	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
now	O
we	O
are	O
removed	O
so	O
far	O
asunder	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
time	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
and	O
whether	O
you	O
aprove	O
our	O
hint	O
of	O
a	O
trip	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
I	O
hope	O
the	O
news	O
story	O
about	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
is	O
like	O
most	O
other	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
R	O
.	O
Familly	O
are	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
my	O
Sister	O
is	O
but	O
indifferent	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
since	O
here	O
,	O
so	O
only	O
my	O
Ly	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
attended	O
the	O
tea	O
drin	O
gs	O
ki	O
ngs	O
and	O
Pantiles	O
;	O
the	O
Balls	O
are	O
but	O
just	O
began	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
exhibited	O
there	O
as	O
yet	O
--	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
Sister	O
Joyn	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
and	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
these	O
were	O
acceptable	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yours	O
Sincerely	O
Wil	B-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
a	O
single	O
sheet	O
