TOKEN	NE
Kinsale	B-place
22	O
nd	O
:	O
July	O
1786	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
begun	O
Madam	O
--	O
for	O
on	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
your	O
last	O
Letter	O
I	O
find	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1786	O
staring	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Page	O
)	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
land	O
of	O
the	O
living	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
done	O
me	O
the	O
Honor	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
I	O
presume	O
the	O
cares	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
increased	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
a	O
moment	O
can	O
be	O
spared	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
your	O
wandering	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
desire	O
a	O
Categorical	O
Answer	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
Question	O
viz	O
--	O
Is	O
it	O
Peace	O
or	O
War	O
between	O
Us	O
?	O
If	O
War	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
If	O
Peace	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
directed	O
to	O
request	O
You	O
to	O
take	O
upon	O
Yourself	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
Sponsor	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
born	O
early	O
in	O
October	O
next	O
.	O
Harriot	B-pers
will	O
aſsist	O
You	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Brat	O
should	O
prove	O
a	O
Male	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
trust	O
him	O
to	O
your	O
Tuition	O
,	O
fearfull	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
by	O
following	O
your	O
example	O
become	O
as	O
Saucy	O
as	O
Yourself	O
,	O
the	O
natural	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
to	O
him	O
would	O
be	O
broken	O
bones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
apprehensions	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
a	O
Daughter	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
quite	O
fashionable	O
and	O
consequently	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
all	O
Miſses	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
pert	O
&	O
disagreable	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
the	O
abovenamed	O
Honor	O
is	O
unattended	O
with	O
the	O
usual	O
expence	O
as	O
all	O
Christening	O
Money	O
is	O
abolished	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
.	O
We	O
moved	O
our	O
Quarters	O
from	O
Cork	B-place
to	O
Charles	B-place
Fort	I-place
near	O
this	O
town	O
last	O
May	O
.	O
A	O
change	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
an	O
excellent	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
breathing	O
pure	O
Air	O
,	O
a	O
comfort	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
in	O
the	O
Town	B-place
of	I-place
Cork	I-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
without	O
exception	O
the	O
filthiest	O
hole	O
I	O
ever	O
put	O
my	O
foot	O
in	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
Us	O
next	O
Spring	O
is	O
very	O
uncertain	O
.	O
My	O
Regiment	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
ffor	O
foreign	O
Services	O
&	O
we	O
hope	O
it	O
's	O
destination	O
will	O
be	O
Canada	B-place
or	O
Nova	B-place
Scotia	I-place
.	O
If	O
my	O
Lt	O
Colonel	O
chuses	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Regt-	O
&	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
Maria	B-pers
will	O
accompany	O
Me	O
.	O
A	O
trip	O
acroſs	O
the	O
Atlantic	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
inconvenience	O
to	O
her	O
after	O
twice	O
croſsing	O
the	O
Pacific	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
however	O
regret	O
such	O
an	O
expedition	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
prolong	O
my	O
Absence	O
from	O
Britain	B-place
for	O
at	O
least	O
two	O
Years	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
begin	O
now	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Island	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
great	O
danger	O
of	O
Our	O
becoming	O
White	O
Boys	O
&	O
Savages	O
like	O
the	O
miserable	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
this	O
oppreſsed	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
common	O
people	O
is	O
miserable	O
beyond	O
conception	O
.	O
The	O
folly	O
,	O
extravagance	O
&	O
absurdity	O
of	O
their	O
betters	O
is	O
scandalous	O
.	O
I	O
honestly	O
confeſs	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
firm	O
beleive	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
convulsion	O
must	O
happen	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
before	O
many	O
years	O
paſs	O
on	O
.	O
Tythes	O
are	O
the	O
present	O
griev	O
an	O
ce	O
complained	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
White	O
Boys	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
these	O
deluded	O
people	O
are	O
supported	O
in	O
secret	O
to	O
by	O
persons	O
of	O
some	O
degree	O
of	O
consequence	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
otherways	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
collect	O
together	O
armed	O
in	O
such	O
large	O
Bodies	O
as	O
they	O
constantly	O
do	O
;	O
commit	O
depradations	O
on	O
their	O
peacable	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
&	O
escape	O
undiscovered	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
say	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
?	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
affectionate	O
Wish	O
for	O
Yourself	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ever	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithfull	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
IRELAND	B-place
KINSALE	B-place
Taxal	B-place
By	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
July	O
1786	O
