TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
Aprill	O
11	O
th	O
17	O
7	O
0	O
its	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
favourd	O
with	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
obliging	O
Letter	O
that	O
I	O
'm	O
almost	O
ashamed	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
your	O
well	O
known	O
good	O
Nature	O
&	O
justice	O
that	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
theyll	O
sugest	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
want	O
of	O
power	O
not	O
inclination	O
--	O
could	O
ever	O
cause	O
my	O
being	O
Sillent	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
so	O
much	O
esteem	O
&	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
Anxious	O
to	O
receive	O
Accounts	O
of	O
your	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
whom	O
I	O
hope	O
are	O
better	O
now	O
;	O
than	O
when	O
you	O
wrote	O
last	O
.	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
time	O
all	O
Enemy	O
's	O
Shift	O
their	O
Quarters	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Gout	O
is	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
disloged	O
:	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
soon	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
do	O
both	O
to	O
Satisfie	O
my	O
Anxiety	O
&	O
in	O
token	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
Angry	O
with	O
me	O
!	O
both	O
the	O
young	O
folks	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Ill	O
with	O
Violent	O
Colds	O
which	O
are	O
quite	O
Epidemicall	O
--	O
Harriot	B-pers
is	O
confined	O
wt	O
a	O
Cough	O
&	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
Cheast	O
but	O
begins	O
to	O
be	O
better	O
litle	O
Jane	B-pers
is	O
distrest	O
with	O
Cutting	O
Teeth	O
--	O
but	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Child	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
fine	O
Play	O
thing	O
for	O
you	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
Cousins	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remembred	O
to	O
You	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Mary	B-pers
sitts	O
by	O
me	O
talking	O
so	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
its	O
odds	O
if	O
I	O
dont	O
insert	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Pratle	O
:	O
she	O
asures	O
me	O
she	O
remembers	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
&	O
has	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
lost	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
&	O
all	O
his	O
Boys	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
've	O
just	O
sent	O
her	O
Away	O
&	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
compts	O
to	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
&	O
says	O
she	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
one	O
day	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
you	O
'll	O
pity	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
is	O
upon	O
his	O
March	O
with	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
to	O
Coventry	B-place
&	O
Warwick	B-place
--	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
best	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
&	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
that	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
their	O
Education	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
Interupted	O
--	O
I	O
willingly	O
make	O
that	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Sacriffice	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
but	O
I	O
asure	O
you	O
its	O
makeing	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
one	O
not	O
to	O
accompany	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
as	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
did	O
more	O
than	O
compensiate	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Disadvantages	O
attendant	O
on	O
my	O
hitherto	O
moveable	O
Situation	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
him	O
who	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
familly	O
Man	O
;	O
its	O
no	O
leſs	O
disagreeable	O
we	O
have	O
however	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
to	O
paſs	O
half	O
the	O
year	O
here	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
with	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
&	O
as	O
Winter	O
is	O
the	O
gloomiest	O
time	O
we	O
chose	O
to	O
be	O
together	O
then	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
paſs	O
more	O
Agreeably	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
Octr	O
:	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
The	O
Wing	O
I	O
realy	O
had	O
neither	O
Spiritts	O
nor	O
time	O
for	O
correspondance	O
--	O
since	O
he	O
's	O
been	O
gone	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
rather	O
worse	O
--	O
:	O
&	O
realy	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
Muster	O
up	O
resolution	O
enough	O
to	O
attempt	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
himself	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
when	O
People	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
dismalls	O
their	O
best	O
way	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Sillent	O
&	O
not	O
torment	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
Sorry	O
his	O
route	O
did	O
not	O
admitt	O
of	O
his	O
makeing	O
you	O
a	O
Visitt	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
gladly	O
do	O
whenever	O
its	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
perhaps	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
graciously	O
pleas	O
'd	O
once	O
more	O
to	O
Quarter	O
the	O
Greys	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
;	O
judge	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
then	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
or	O
Not	O
?	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
your	O
Pappa	O
will	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
regreating	O
the	O
Loſs	O
of	O
Jack	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
's	O
Ellection	O
--	O
or	O
rather	O
of	O
his	O
Seat	O
in	O
Parlt	O
:	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Hoptne	O
:	O
House	O
since	O
--	O
but	O
can	O
gueſs	O
they	O
are	O
as	O
litle	O
pleas	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
yr	O
Uncle	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
a	O
litle	O
beffore	O
he	O
left	O
this	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
since	O
from	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
ours	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
(	O
&	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
their	O
Civility	O
's	O
)	O
that	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
&	O
he	O
are	O
Well	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
later	O
than	O
Janry	O
:	O
last	O
our	O
friends	O
there	O
were	O
Well	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
Spiritts	O
then	O
--	O
but	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
leaveing	O
that	O
Country	O
than	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
there	O
--	O
.	O
My	O
Br	O
:	O
seldom	O
writes	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
!	O
but	O
is	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
grown	O
a	O
better	O
Correspondant	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
how	O
your	O
friends	O
at	O
Ipswich	B-place
go	O
on	O
.	O
Your	O
poor	O
Babylonians	O
will	O
be	O
quite	O
Moapt	O
for	O
meer	O
want	O
of	O
Society	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
kind	O
if	O
they	O
remove	O
themselves	O
at	O
this	O
rate	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
in	O
the	O
Pappers	O
,	O
the	O
remaining	O
Sister	O
&	O
Mother	O
will	O
now	O
doubly	O
feell	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graehme	I-pers
--	O
.	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
&	O
how	O
you	O
continue	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
your	O
Stupid	O
Town	O
--	O
surrounded	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
dull	O
sett	O
of	O
Mortals	O
?	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
yr	O
very	O
fatt	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
made	O
so	O
very	O
unsuccesfull	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
convin	O
ce	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
Visitt	O
;	O
by	O
comeing	O
to	O
the	O
Card	O
Aſsembly	O
but	O
above	O
all	O
tell	O
me	O
about	O
yourselves	O
which	O
is	O
what	O
Interests	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
Wishes	O
&	O
present	O
them	O
to	O
your	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mama	O
--	O
should	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
come	O
this	O
way	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
Seeing	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
Sincearly	O
felt	O
by	O
her	O
who	O
shall	O
ever	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Cousin	O
&	O
most	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
:	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
from	O
Durham	B-place
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
always	O
much	O
attatched	O
to	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
his	O
Son	O
is	O
no	O
leſs	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
buſsie	O
here	O
wt	O
a	O
Variety	O
of	O
Masters	O
&	O
grows	O
a	O
great	O
Boy	O
.	O
