TOKEN	NE
Q	O
.	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
30	O
August	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
What	O
can	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
not	O
much	O
indeed	O
!	O
but	O
to	O
wish	O
You	O
a	O
good	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
pretty	O
Blue	O
and	O
white	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
sit	O
and	O
read	O
with	O
You	O
the	O
Hermit	O
a	O
Poem	O
which	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
Favorite	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
it	O
twice	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
Oh	O
what	O
a	O
blessing	O
to	O
keep	O
good	O
Company	O
.	O
very	O
likely	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
either	O
Poet	O
or	O
Poem	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
The	O
season	O
continues	O
so	O
fine	O
that	O
Our	O
Terrace	O
is	O
constantly	O
filled	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
partake	O
of	O
that	O
amusement	O
and	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Spectator	O
.	O
all	O
alone	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
a	O
droll	O
Idea	O
started	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
which	O
by	O
any	O
cleaver	O
Person	O
my	O
be	O
made	O
much	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
my	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
dangerous	O
to	O
indulge	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
You	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
well	O
Madam	O
it	O
was	O
comparing	O
the	O
Terraſse	O
the	O
Royal	O
Terraſse	O
with	O
what	O
..	O
?	O
Patience	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Market	O
Oh	O
Fie	O
upon	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
.	O
Now	O
You	O
know	O
this	O
Wicked	O
thought	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
promise	O
You	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
and	O
You	O
promise	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
to	O
Yourself	O
.	O
Every	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
You	O
is	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
exepting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Veesy	I-pers
.	O
or	O
Weasy	B-pers
.	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
Neighborhood	O
and	O
come	O
twice	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
upon	O
the	O
Terrace	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
two	O
Courtsies	O
from	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
my	O
politeneſs	O
had	O
almost	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
mischief	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
scrawl	O
You	O
will	O
receive	O
from	O
me	O
till	O
we	O
meet	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
