TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
17	O
7	O
6	O
6	O
)	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
from	O
Ipswich	B-place
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
As	O
we	O
have	O
now	O
been	O
here	O
near	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
may	O
venture	O
to	O
affirm	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
last	O
fixed	O
upon	O
an	O
agreeable	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
so	O
I	O
find	O
Ipswich	B-place
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
The	O
country	O
about	O
it	O
is	O
charming	O
&	O
the	O
air	O
remarkably	O
good	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
are	O
remarkably	O
sociable	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
unanimous	O
in	O
showing	O
us	O
every	O
poſsible	O
civility	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
attribute	O
in	O
great	O
measure	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
who	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Estate	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
Ipswich	B-place
&	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
busineſs	O
to	O
recommend	O
me	O
very	O
particularly	O
to	O
every	O
Person	O
of	O
consequence	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Having	O
now	O
no	O
expectations	O
of	O
further	O
Preferment	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
more	O
expeditions	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
with	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
expence	O
&	O
trouble	O
of	O
moving	O
too	O
great	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Affairs	O
call	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
over	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
alone	O
,	O
without	O
very	O
great	O
inconvenience	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
enjoy	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
.	O
Finding	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
get	O
Lodgings	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
purchased	O
a	O
neat	O
small	O
House	O
&	O
Garden	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
which	O
I	O
intend	O
as	O
a	O
settlement	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
in	O
case	O
of	O
my	O
death	O
as	O
she	O
can	O
fix	O
in	O
no	O
place	O
with	O
equal	O
advantage	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
fortunately	O
that	O
event	O
is	O
prolongued	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
it	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
very	O
suitable	O
to	O
her	O
finances	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
residence	O
for	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
purchase	O
with	O
furniture	O
&	O
c	O
amounts	O
to	O
at	O
least	O
£	O
700	O
which	O
will	O
oblige	O
me	O
to	O
observe	O
a	O
very	O
strict	O
oeconomy	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
taken	O
possession	O
of	O
your	O
new	O
habitation	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
perfectly	O
to	O
your	O
mind	O
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
being	O
particularly	O
connected	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
Orwell	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
frequently	O
at	O
Ld	B-pers
Hallifax	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Jekyl	I-pers
called	O
upon	O
us	O
here	O
last	O
week	O
&	O
confirmed	O
the	O
news	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Beauchamp	I-pers
's	O
having	O
succeeded	O
his	O
Father	O
as	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lt	O
.	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
if	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
ever	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
totally	O
unqualified	O
for	O
that	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
owes	O
it	O
intirely	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bristol	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
pay	O
'd	O
court	O
for	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
us	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chatham	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
all	O
this	O
day	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
sore	O
throat	O
,	O
a	O
disorder	O
very	O
frequent	O
here	O
at	O
present	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
fevers	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
i	O
s	O
tolerably	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
her	O
friends	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
Adieu	O
Dr	O
.	O
Brother	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Yours	O
most	O
Affectionately	O
Betty	B-pers
Ipswich	B-place
September	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1766	O
.	O
Suffolk	B-place
