TOKEN	NE
copied	O
in	O
manuscript	O
E	O
G	O
A	O
St	B-place
Petersburg	I-place
16	O
N	O
S	O
Octr	O
.	O
1771	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
My	O
Brother	O
Frederick	B-pers
has	O
acquainted	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
received	O
yesterday	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
loſs	O
our	O
family	O
had	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
our	O
Eldest	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
too	O
affectionate	O
himself	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
regretted	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
very	O
sincerely	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
&	O
many	O
other	O
good	O
qualities	O
he	O
was	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
:	O
Your	O
Affliction	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
my	O
Brother	O
Frederick	B-pers
mentions	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
well	O
imagine	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
how	O
you	O
lived	O
together	O
:	O
No	O
circumstance	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
will	O
ever	O
escape	O
my	O
memory	O
:	O
Tis	O
in	O
that	O
View	O
that	O
I	O
offer	O
myself	O
to	O
your	O
remembrance	O
in	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
distreſs	O
,	O
desiring	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
aſsured	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
sympathy	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
ever	O
find	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
my	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
s	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
regard	O
and	O
good	O
wishes	O
for	O
yourself	O
&	O
your	O
daughter	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
hear	O
with	O
pleasure	O
from	O
Br	O
Fredy	B-pers
,	O
turns	O
out	O
an	O
Exceeding	O
good	O
young	O
Woman	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
had	O
time	O
before	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
recover	O
'd	O
your	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
your	O
health	O
has	O
not	O
suffer	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
shock	O
you	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
also	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
these	O
Compliments	O
of	O
regard	O
,	O
&	O
Condoleance	O
&	O
the	O
Children	O
desire	O
to	O
add	O
theirs	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
much	O
grown	O
you	O
would	O
Scarcely	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
Ever	O
your	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Catherine	B-pers
.	O
To	O
J.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
at	O
in	O
ST	B-place
PETERSBOVRG	I-place
Northampton	B-place
