TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
did	O
myself	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
acquainting	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
official	O
notice	O
of	O
a	O
vancancy	O
of	O
a	O
Cornetcy	O
in	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Dragoons	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
expected	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
immediately	O
make	O
a	O
deposite	O
of	O
the	O
purchase	O
money	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
regulated	O
price	O
;	O
without	O
which	O
the	O
recommendation	O
of	O
my	O
Son	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
given	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Secretary	O
at	O
War	O
,	O
for	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
approbation	O
.	O
Having	O
many	O
months	O
ago	O
obtain	O
'd	O
General	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
's	O
consent	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
Son	O
into	O
his	O
Regiment	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
unpleasant	O
situation	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
prepared	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
acceptance	O
of	O
your	O
most	O
obligi	O
n	O
g	O
offer	O
to	O
accommodate	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
security	O
of	O
an	O
Heritable	O
Bond	O
upon	O
my	O
Estate	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
which	O
my	O
Agent	O
informs	O
me	O
he	O
expects	O
to	O
receive	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
next	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
sufficient	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Taxal	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
uneasy	O
lest	O
it	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
remain	O
'd	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
from	O
Park	B-place
gate	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
directed	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
imagined	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
remained	O
there	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
account	O
for	O
my	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
daily	O
expectation	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
peremptory	O
order	O
to	O
lodge	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
your	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
letter	O
may	O
probably	O
be	O
on	O
its	O
way	O
,	O
yet	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
a	O
disappointment	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
advisable	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
second	O
application	O
,	O
directing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forwarded	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
your	O
absence	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
249	O
October	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1789	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Park	B-place
Gate	I-place
Chapel	B-place
de	I-place
la	I-place
Frith	I-place
to	O
be	O
forwarded	O
if	O
absent	O
John	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
esq	I-pers
Chester	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
.	O
Sat	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Oct	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
from	O
Oxford	O
St	O
.	O
