TOKEN	NE
A	O
letter	O
arriv	O
'd	O
for	O
you	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
postpon	O
'd	O
sending	O
it	O
till	O
to	O
day	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
frank	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
we	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
summer	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
By	O
way	O
of	O
news	O
I	O
inform	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
F	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
..	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
..	I-pers
were	O
hiſs	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Epsom	O
Course	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
disap	O
not	O
approving	O
his	O
supposed	O
marriage	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Abbey	O
last	O
tuesday	O
&	O
was	O
highly	O
entertain	O
'd	O
:	O
My	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
tell	O
her	O
I	O
am	O
rejoic	O
'd	O
she	O
likes	O
Sally	B-pers
--	O
The	O
coach	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
therefore	O
in	O
haste	O
I	O
conclude	O
myself	O
yr	O
much	O
obliged	O
M.	B-pers
G	I-pers
..	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
beg	O
their	O
remembrance	O
.	O
June	O
1786	O
London	B-place
Tenth	O
June	O
1786	O
J.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northamptonshe	B-place
Wfreedevaynes	B-pers
