TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
Street	O
3	O
April	O
1782	O
My	O
Dear	O
Will	B-pers
King	I-pers
considering	O
the	O
Storms	O
,	O
and	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Elements	O
;	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
,	O
enquiring	O
after	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
retired	O
into	O
Rural	O
felicity	O
;	O
to	O
expose	O
themselves	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
fury	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
catching	O
colds	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
return	O
safe	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
inconvenience	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
--	O
.	O
news	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
,	O
as	O
every	O
thing	O
Bon	O
Ton	O
has	O
left	O
the	O
regions	O
of	O
smoke	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
so	O
vulgar	O
as	O
to	O
remain	O
;	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
be	O
blown	O
or	O
wash	O
'd	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
few	O
odd	O
folks	O
that	O
remain	O
,	O
are	O
so	O
busy	O
talking	O
of	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
news	O
is	O
totaly	O
forgot	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
married	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Durham	I-pers
very	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
was	O
married	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Shirley	I-pers
Capt	B-pers
:	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
s	O
nephew	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
so	O
bad	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
Mr.	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
his	O
Deputy	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
daughter	O
away	O
--	O
so	O
matrimony	O
and	O
Gout	O
,	O
are	O
much	O
about	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
dated	O
the	O
3	O
rd	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
from	O
Caserta	B-place
,	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
mine	O
;	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
spight	O
of	O
all	O
our	O
acusations	O
,	O
declares	O
herself	O
not	O
guilty	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
acount	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
letters	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ours	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
seems	O
to	O
feel	O
herself	O
quite	O
inocent	O
:	O
and	O
says	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
complain	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
her	O
Debt	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
sincerely	O
loves	O
and	O
wishes	O
you	O
well	O
She	O
will	O
write	O
and	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
she	O
also	O
promises	O
,	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
her	O
old	O
correspondents	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
:	O
and	O
clears	O
herself	O
about	O
having	O
wrote	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
the	O
Court	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
gay	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Grand	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
's	O
being	O
there	O
but	O
that	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
winter	O
as	O
to	O
health	O
and	O
nerves	O
that	O
She	O
has	O
excused	O
herself	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
great	O
fêtes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
one	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Russia	I-pers
gave	O
them	O
and	O
at	O
which	O
She	O
did	O
her	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
describes	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
as	O
a	O
very	O
ugly	O
little	O
man	O
:	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
his	O
nose	O
to	O
his	O
upper	O
lip	O
,	O
longer	O
than	O
the	O
nose	O
itself	O
;	O
very	O
tottering	O
,	O
&	O
weak	O
in	O
make	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
constitution	O
;	O
which	O
one	O
expects	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
declared	O
incapable	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
ago	O
of	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ei	O
g	O
t	O
her	O
spirit	O
or	O
health	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
figure	O
--	O
his	O
Princeſs	O
has	O
person	O
enough	O
for	O
both	O
,	O
being	O
remarably	O
tall	O
and	O
large	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
their	O
apearance	O
must	O
be	O
rather	O
laughable	O
,	O
especialy	O
as	O
their	O
fondneſs	O
is	O
so	O
great	O
as	O
to	O
Kiſs	O
and	O
toy	O
in	O
public	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
occasion	O
her	O
Highneſs	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
stoop	O
or	O
the	O
little	O
Prince	O
could	O
never	O
reach	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
feeling	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
an	O
Awkward	O
one	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
as	O
the	O
Embaſsador	O
from	O
Ruſsia	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
favorite	O
with	O
his	O
first	O
wife	O
as	O
to	O
occasion	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
poisoned	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
that	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
his	O
second	O
it	O
pleads	O
some	O
excuse	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
fondneſs	O
She	O
shews	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
continual	O
dread	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
fate	O
--	O
this	O
acount	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
is	O
lately	O
returned	O
from	O
abroad	O
and	O
makes	O
me	O
no	O
way	O
envy	O
the	O
Brilliant	O
situation	O
of	O
of	O
such	O
great	O
Princes	O
and	O
Princeſses	O
--	O
after	O
all	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
Splendid	O
Misery	O
!	O
and	O
our	O
humbler	O
lot	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
happiest	O
at	O
least	O
having	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
chusing	O
our	O
situation	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
are	O
unhappy	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
leſs	O
room	O
for	O
compaſsion	O
--	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
bad	O
my	O
Mother	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
begun	O
Aſses	O
Milk	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
her	O
much	O
improved	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
joyn	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
and	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
with	O
Lillies	O
&	O
Roses	O
from	O
the	O
Charms	O
of	O
Country	O
Retirement	O
remains	O
Dear	O
the	B-pers
Great	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Wil	B-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
The	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
