TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sr	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
some	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
only	O
returned	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
have	O
suffered	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
have	O
remained	O
unanswered	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
&	O
Tuesday	O
we	O
are	O
particularly	O
engaged	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
every	O
thing	O
worth	O
seeing	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
propose	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
when	O
we	O
hope	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
paying	O
our	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Sr	O
.	O
Your	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servant	O
J	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
May	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
1788	O
