TOKEN	NE
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
1783	O
The	O
Day	O
you	O
left	O
London	B-place
I	O
received	O
a	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Chaise	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
Thursday	O
&	O
stay	O
till	O
Saturday	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
comply	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
request	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
engagements	O
but	O
agree	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
proposition	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Eveg	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
too	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
)	O
--	O
&	O
staying	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
could	O
return	O
to	O
Town	B-place
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G——	I-pers
who	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
day	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
--	O
our	O
Party	O
consisted	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
who	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G——	I-pers
before	O
we	O
parted	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
politely	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Villa	O
&	O
invited	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
week	O
--	O
upon	O
this	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
insisted	O
so	O
strongly	O
upon	O
my	O
remaining	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
refusing	O
--	O
besides	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
powerfull	O
inducement	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
dinner	O
tha	O
t	O
he	O
might	O
show	O
me	O
his	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
this	O
I	O
could	O
no	O
t	O
perhaps	O
have	O
managed	O
.	O
had	O
not	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
but	O
by	O
&	O
c	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
much	O
Hero	B-pers
has	O
made	O
of	O
me	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
her	O
guest	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
very	O
attentive	O
,	O
good	O
Humourd	O
&	O
polite	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
no	O
addition	O
to	O
my	O
pleasure	O
but	O
having	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
talk	O
'd	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
you	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
nay	O
many	O
times	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
da	O
y	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
at	O
it	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
ye	O
Castle	O
wth	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
restraint	O
wch	O
.	O
naturally	O
attends	O
such	O
a	O
situation	O
,	O
for	O
15	O
Years	O
--	O
here	O
she	O
is	O
sole	O
Mistreſs	O
--	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
around	O
her	O
being	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
interests	O
,	O
her	O
&	O
amuses	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
is	O
comfortable	O
&	O
chearful	O
--	O
The	O
Grounds	O
--	O
but	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
describe	O
(	O
I	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
clever	O
in	O
describing	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
much	O
interested	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
we	O
spend	O
our	O
time	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
accompanied	O
Hero	B-pers
&	O
Her	O
Daughter	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
D	I-place
:	I-place
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
H	B-pers
.	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
House	O
&	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
till	O
near	O
ten	O
--	O
at	O
that	O
hour	O
we	O
sup	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
after	O
Supper	O
Hero	B-pers
was	O
very	O
lively	O
,	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
retire	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
politely	O
conducted	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
6	O
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
was	O
heavenly	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
join	O
'd	O
by	O
H——	B-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
,	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
till	O
9	O
when	O
the	O
Bell	O
rings	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
we	O
separated	O
&	O
met	O
again	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Country	O
Church	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
decent	O
well	O
behaved	O
congregation	O
--	O
the	O
Clergyman	O
s	O
appearance	O
was	O
suited	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
an	O
amiable	O
looking	O
old	O
Man	O
with	O
Silver	O
Locks	O
,	O
he	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
prayers	O
devoutly	O
,	O
&	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
Sermon	O
--	O
the	O
Stile	O
unaffected	O
and	O
not	O
above	O
the	O
comprehension	O
of	O
his	O
country	O
parishioners	O
--	O
The	O
little	O
Band	O
of	O
Vocal	O
performers	O
quite	O
excelled	O
in	O
singing	O
the	O
Psalms	O
&	O
they	O
sang	O
an	O
Anthem	O
in	O
a	O
Manner	O
far	O
superior	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
heard	O
in	O
a	O
Village	O
Church	O
.	O
we	O
saunter	O
'd	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
domain	O
&	O
c	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Seat	O
wch	O
.	O
commands	O
a	O
fine	O
View	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Medallion	O
Seat	O
,	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
has	O
modelled	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
one	O
wch	O
.	O
hangs	O
in	O
the	O
Centre	O
Panel	O
--	O
the	O
Subject	O
is	O
,	O
Hippolytus	O
offering	O
a	O
Chapelet	O
to	O
Diana	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
Panels	O
are	O
written	O
these	O
beautiful	O
Lines	O
translated	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Hippolytus	O
of	O
Euripedes	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
.	O
To	O
thee	O
,	O
Bright	O
Goddeſs	O
,	O
these	O
fair	O
flowers	O
I	O
bring	O
:	O
A	O
Chapelet	O
woven	O
from	O
th	O
e	O
'	O
untainted	O
Mead	O
Thy	O
cool	O
sequester	O
'd	O
haunt	O
;	O
where	O
never	O
yet	O
Shepherd	O
approach	O
'd	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
rude	O
hind	O
ne'er	O
heav	O
'd	O
Th	O
'	O
unhallow	O
'd	O
axe	O
:	O
nor	O
voice	O
,	O
nor	O
sound	O
,	O
is	O
heard	O
Save	O
the	O
low	O
murmuring	O
of	O
the	O
vernal	O
Bee	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
The	O
day-spring	O
from	O
above	O
the	O
dew	O
distils	O
,	O
Genial	O
,	O
&	O
mild	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
pure	O
stream	O
exhal	O
'd	O
On	O
every	O
fragrant	O
herb	O
,	O
&	O
favorite	O
flower	O
.	O
The	O
original	O
of	O
this	O
Medallion	O
&	O
verses	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Ionick	O
Temple	O
at	O
Blenheim	B-place
.	O
The	O
Dinner	O
hour	O
is	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
and	O
the	O
hours	O
are	O
kept	O
to	O
strictly	O
--	O
we	O
separated	O
from	O
3	O
till	O
6	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
under	O
some	O
trees	O
upon	O
the	O
Terrace	O
wch-	O
has	O
the	O
Thames	O
running	O
under	O
it	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
Hero	B-pers
's	O
boat	O
&	O
were	O
row	O
'd	O
for	O
near	O
two	O
hours	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
deligh	O
t	O
ful	O
--	O
the	O
Eveg	O
was	O
serene	O
and	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
beautiful	O
Objects	O
there	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
Banks	O
of	O
this	O
River	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
fineneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Weather	O
tempted	O
us	O
to	O
walk	O
&	O
Hero	B-pers
took	O
me	O
round	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
grounds	O
wch	O
.	O
may	O
be	O
stild	O
ferme	O
Ornée	O
--	O
we	O
read	O
for	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
read	O
some	O
paſsages	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
life	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Marlbrough	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
as	O
late	O
after	O
supper	O
as	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
Hero	B-pers
pays	O
me	O
a	O
flattering	O
Compliment	O
in	O
sitting	O
up	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
conversation	O
kept	O
her	O
up	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
beyond	O
her	O
usual	O
time	O
.	O
Monday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
Hero	B-pers
had	O
the	O
complaisance	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
to	O
see	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
Palace	O
as	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Phaeton	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
also	O
)	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
in	O
seeing	O
many	O
fine	O
Pictures	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
understood	O
that	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
not	O
left	O
any	O
worth	O
notice	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
much	O
better	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
Palace	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
accustom	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
described	O
(	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
F	O
.	O
as	O
a	O
melancholy	O
uncomfortable	O
habitation	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
contrary	O
a	O
magnificent	O
and	O
chearful	O
one	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
terms	O
are	O
light	O
&	O
in	O
fine	O
proportion	O
the	O
situation	O
is	O
certainly	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Garden	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
Taste	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
might	O
be	O
improved	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
might	O
spend	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
if	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
King	O
or	O
Queen	O
three	O
Months	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
at	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
.	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
who	O
were	O
to	O
dine	O
here	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Maid	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
me	O
either	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
hers	O
attend	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
chose	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
most	O
agreeable	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Modest	O
pretty	O
Young	O
Woman	O
&	O
dreſses	O
hair	O
remarkably	O
well	O
(	O
yo	O
.	O
know	O
why	O
I	O
mention	O
this	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
entertain	O
'd	O
us	O
extremely	O
by	O
relating	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Burlington	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
up	O
--	O
the	O
Stile	O
of	O
life	O
she	O
led	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
reserve	O
for	O
you	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
Seat	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
I	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Cool	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
with	O
my	O
Book	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
retired	O
quiet	O
Seat	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
spend	O
some	O
happy	O
hours	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
one	O
I	O
have	O
chosen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
mine	O
.	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8.	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
a	O
Chapter	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Old	O
&	O
one	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
New	O
Testament	O
&	O
The	O
Psalms	O
--	O
this	O
she	O
always	O
does	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
read	O
these	O
appointed	O
--	O
but	O
regularly	O
through	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
we	O
separate	O
till	O
di	O
d	O
n	O
ner	O
time	O
unleſs	O
we	O
meet	O
accidentally	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Oatlands	O
--	O
saw	O
the	O
fine	O
Grotto	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
been	O
finish	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
4	O
years	O
--	O
it	O
cost	O
10,000	O
L	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
placed	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
extremely	O
beautiful	O
,	O
it	O
consists	O
of	O
four	O
Rooms	O
&	O
a	O
Cold	O
Bath	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
ornamented	O
wth	O
:	O
taste	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
decorated	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
profusion	O
of	O
beautiful	O
shells	O
&	O
spars	O
,	O
it	O
gives	O
one	O
ye	O
.	O
idea	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
desinge	O
was	O
intended	O
for	O
a	O
Mansion	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
of	O
the	O
Fairys	O
.	O
Hero	B-pers
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
far	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
more	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Place	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Grotto	O
upon	O
the	O
fine	O
Terrace	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
much	O
celebrated	O
,	O
it	O
looks	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Noble	O
piece	O
of	O
Water	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
in	O
length	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
.	O
made	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
expence	O
.	O
We	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
about	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
Hero	B-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Kitchen	O
Garden	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
&	O
Organ	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
Supper	O
--	O
after	O
supper	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Blair	B-pers
s	O
new	O
work	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Belles	O
Lettres	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
Book	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
comprehended	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
5	O
)	O
July	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
At	O
11	O
oClock	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
came	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
aſsist	O
at	O
her	O
leſson	O
of	O
Astronomy	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
this	O
leſson	O
wch	O
.	O
lasted	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
as	O
She	O
had	O
an	O
Head	O
ache	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
Dreſsing	O
Room	O
&	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Blair	B-pers
.	O
I	O
then	O
left	O
her	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Dinner	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
before	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Ferry	O
boat	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
River	O
where	O
she	O
waited	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriage	O
--	O
the	O
Ferry	O
boat	O
is	O
row	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
has	O
no	O
other	O
apparent	O
distinction	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sex	O
but	O
wearing	O
a	O
single	O
Petycoat	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
Mans	O
Hat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
&	O
Jacket	O
--	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
choose	O
this	O
employment	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
amusement	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
9	O
years	O
old	O
--	O
that	O
an	O
Uncle	O
then	O
obliged	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
16	O
,	O
&	O
since	O
then	O
,	O
neceſsity	O
forced	O
her	O
to	O
continue	O
it	O
--	O
she	O
appears	O
abt	O
.	O
40	O
&	O
a	O
most	O
truly	O
Masculine	O
figure	O
she	O
is	O
--	O
Phillis	B-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
drinks	O
&	O
swears	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
airing	O
to	O
Town	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
was	O
a	O
desire	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
seeing	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Warwick	B-pers
who	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
arrived	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
as	O
her	O
G	O
.	O
had	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
time	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Autumn	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
have	O
engaged	O
myself	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
Eveg	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Glovers	O
--	O
Veseys	O
--	O
Jacksons	O
aſsembled	O
to	O
receive	O
me	O
--	O
they	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Eveg	O
.	O
July	O
3	O
d	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Warwick	B-pers
--	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
to	O
dinner	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
setting	O
,	O
packing	O
up	O
furnit	O
u	O
re	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
up	O
her	O
apartments	O
to	O
his	B-pers
M——	I-pers
who	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
is	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Hero	B-pers
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
delighted	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
own	O
daughter	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
together	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
part	O
til	O
12	O
oClock	O
July	O
4	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
again	O
invited	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Globe	O
leſson	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
Astronomy	O
,	O
or	O
have	O
forgotten	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
once	O
learn	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
most	O
contemptible	O
figure	O
,	O
for	O
Hero	B-pers
wld	O
.	O
insist	O
upon	O
my	O
doing	O
some	O
Problems	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
myself	O
a	O
hundred	O
miles	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
detirmind	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
pains	O
in	O
learning	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
again	O
go	O
to	O
T	B-place
:	I-place
D	I-place
:	I-place
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
That	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
how	O
quick	O
,	O
how	O
clever	O
,	O
how	O
well	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
were	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eveg	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
Water	O
to	O
a	O
Meadow	O
wch	O
.	O
belongs	O
to	O
Hero	B-pers
--	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
Hay	O
Cocks	O
&	O
were	O
very	O
Rural	O
--	O
&	O
sentimental	O
--	O
repeating	O
Verses	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
Hero	B-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
Handle	B-pers
s	O
Leſsons	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Organ	O
before	O
Supper	O
&	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Critisms	O
of	O
ye	O
Reviewers	O
upon	O
Blair	B-pers
s	O
new	O
Work	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
Wrote	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
till	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
came	O
down	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
her	O
Chapters	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
employments	O
till	O
B——Breakfast	O
time	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
your	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
travel	O
'd	O
into	O
Eſsex	B-place
after	O
my	O
Sevt	O
.	O
had	O
pd	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
postage	O
,	O
so	O
your	O
scheme	O
of	O
Directing	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
my	O
house	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
Man	O
insisted	O
upon	O
being	O
Paid	O
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
the	O
Sevt	O
.	O
gave	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
aſsuring	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
--	O
Now	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
orders	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
also	O
told	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
yt	O
.	O
your	O
were	O
to	O
direct	O
your	O
letters	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
.	O
therefore	O
till	O
I	O
can	O
procure	O
franks	O
enclose	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
,	O
or	O
your	O
Maid	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
hurt	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
yours	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
again	O
tormented	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
tooth	O
ach	O
au	O
reste	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
pleased	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
comfort	O
about	O
my	O
coming	O
down	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
disappointed	O
in	O
my	O
hopes	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
writes	O
me	O
word	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
to	O
day	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
is	O
uncertain	O
when	O
he	O
can	O
leave	O
Eſsex	B-place
&	O
that	O
he	O
thinks	O
he	O
has	O
busineſs	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
to	O
come	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
dread	O
lest	O
ye	O
.	O
uncertainty	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
W.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
should	O
at	O
last	O
prevent	O
me	O
from	O
being	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
when	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
however	O
hope	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
s	O
and	O
got	O
Twickenham	B-place
at	O
½	O
past	O
2.	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
spend	O
in	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
Pictures	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
I	O
saw	O
--	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
impoſsib	O
ly	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
this	O
Villa	O
?	O
what	O
a	O
collection	O
!	O
such	O
Pictures	O
--	O
Miniatures	O
--	O
Antiques	O
--	O
relicks	O
--	O
China	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
what	O
wd	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
give	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Month	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
to	O
examine	O
ye	O
.	O
various	O
&	O
valuable	O
curiosities	O
it	O
contains	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
however	O
to	O
have	O
opportunities	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
has	O
politely	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
I	O
chose	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
had	O
only	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
transient	O
view	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
Young	O
Burke	B-pers
were	O
ye-	O
Party	O
at	O
Dinner	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
day	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
delighted	O
with	O
my	O
Visit	O
to	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
home	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
--	O
Hero	B-pers
had	O
so	O
obligingly	O
requested	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
Monday	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
refuse	O
--	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
Before	O
&	O
after	O
Supper	O
Hero	B-pers
treated	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
of	O
her	B-pers
Father	I-pers
s	O
Manuscripts	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
was	O
very	O
entertaining	O
full	O
of	O
anecdote	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
so	O
perfectly	O
agreeable	O
that	O
we	O
regretted	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
retire	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
July	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
Hero	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
breakfast	O
&	O
strongly	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
another	O
Week	O
of	O
my	O
company	O
but	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
without	O
entering	O
into	O
reasons	O
for	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
ym	O
of	O
weight	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
home	O
as	O
my	O
amiable	O
companion	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
to	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
&	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
we	O
parted	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
.	O
Hero	B-pers
did	O
not	O
appear	O
displeased	O
but	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
disappointed	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
seems	O
to	O
enjoy	O
himself	O
prodigiously	O
&	O
is	O
really	O
an	O
entertaining	O
companion	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
favorite	O
of	O
Hero	B-pers
's	O
.	O
After	O
Church	O
--	O
our	O
busineſs	O
was	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
Gardens	O
this	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Deſs	O
Dreſs	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
Water	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W.Wilmot	I-pers
looks	O
wretchedly	O
--	O
he	O
appeard	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
quite	O
won	O
his	O
heart	O
by	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
Dog	O
--	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
Shakespeares	O
Temple	O
and	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
merry	O
till	O
a	O
Shower	O
of	O
Rain	O
made	O
Hero	B-pers
look	O
grave	O
--	O
some	O
distreſs	O
's	O
in	O
our	O
return	O
home	O
will	O
make	O
us	O
laugh	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
to	O
talk	O
it	O
over	O
Typed	O
Charming	O
letter	O
from	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
or	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
June	O
29	O
to	O
July	O
3	O
1783	O
