TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
when	O
your	O
Letter	O
arrived	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
actually	O
meditating	O
the	O
fabrication	O
of	O
one	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
saucineſs	O
not	O
to	O
believe	O
me	O
.	O
Therefore	O
nothing	O
more	O
shall	O
be	O
written	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
.	O
Your	O
Letter	O
is	O
written	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Spirit	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
regained	O
your	O
health	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
anything	O
entertaining	O
in	O
return	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
thoughts	O
have	O
been	O
occupied	O
&	O
harraſsed	O
with	O
Bonds	O
,	O
Bills	O
,	O
&	O
Mortgages	O
ever	O
since	O
last	O
September	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
Irish	O
Gentry	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Dublin	B-place
to	O
settle	O
the	O
Claims	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
ruinous	O
nineteen	O
Years	O
Lawsuit	O
.	O
After	O
many	O
Pro	O
's	O
&	O
Con	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
my	O
Law	O
Agent	O
&	O
these	O
Vagabonds	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
compromised	O
matters	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
enormous	O
Sum	O
of	O
four	O
thousand	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
demands	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
Property	O
of	O
her	O
Sister	O
s	O
which	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
Interest	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Costs	O
of	O
Suit	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
paying	O
down	O
£2000	O
instantly	O
,	O
&	O
took	O
my	O
Bond	O
payable	O
in	O
Septr	O
1806	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
remaining	O
£2200	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fortunate	O
enough	O
to	O
procure	O
the	O
immediate	O
loan	O
of	O
£2000	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
quit	O
of	O
the	O
Harpies	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
reckoning	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Creditors	O
must	O
arrive	O
,	O
it	O
became	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
Me	O
to	O
consider	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
satisfy	O
all	O
their	O
cravings	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
has	O
occurred	O
but	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
determined	O
on	O
.	O
My	O
intention	O
has	O
been	O
notified	O
in	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
to	O
settle	O
all	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
Arrangements	O
for	O
the	O
Sale	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
with	O
my	O
Nose	O
to	O
the	O
Earth	O
by	O
pinching	O
poverty	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
step	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
about	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
clear	O
off	O
all	O
my	O
Incumbrances	O
,	O
personal	O
&	O
hereditary	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
nearly	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
My	O
personal	O
Engagements	O
are	O
about	O
£9500	O
(	O
including	O
the	O
Irish	O
4000	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
£2000	O
borrowed	O
from	O
the	O
Trustees	O
to	O
compleat	O
of	O
my	O
Marriage	O
Settlement	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
)	O
.	O
My	O
entailed	O
Debt	O
is	O
now	O
reduced	O
to	O
£2448	O
.	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
£6000	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
considered	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
bring	O
me	O
now	O
from	O
Ten	O
thousand	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
£12,000	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
allow	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
sanguine	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
therefore	O
not	O
count	O
on	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
10,000	O
Guineas	O
which	O
will	O
pay	O
off	O
all	O
my	O
personal	O
obligations	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
£1000	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
If	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
£12,000	O
should	O
be	O
obtained	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
more	O
independant	O
.	O
No	O
man	O
alive	O
abhors	O
being	O
in	O
debt	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
myself	O
once	O
free	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
arrive	O
at	O
great	O
felicity	O
indeed	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
naturally	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Resolution	O
of	O
quitting	O
a	O
Residence	O
where	O
we	O
have	O
lived	O
happily	O
&	O
comfortably	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
was	O
not	O
fixed	O
on	O
without	O
feeling	O
a	O
few	O
pangs	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
both	O
convinced	O
that	O
the	O
measure	O
is	O
proper	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
eventually	O
be	O
advantageous	O
to	O
Us	O
all	O
.	O
Having	O
stated	O
all	O
this	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
fair	O
that	O
You	O
should	O
be	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Leases	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
Entailed	O
Property	O
in	O
Selkirkshire	B-place
,	O
expire	O
at	O
Whitsunday	O
1807	O
.	O
That	O
Estate	O
is	O
now	O
let	O
at	O
£748	O
pr-	O
Ann	O
.	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
certainly	O
double	O
its	O
Rent	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
those	O
farms	O
,	O
now	O
let	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
at	O
£200	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
£80	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
been	O
offered	O
£540	O
for	O
.	O
My	O
plan	O
is	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
new	O
Leases	O
are	O
let	O
,	O
to	O
appropriate	O
a	O
Sum	O
annually	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
encreased	O
Rent	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
paying	O
off	O
the	O
£2448	O
,	O
still	O
remaining	O
for	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
debts	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
transmit	O
it	O
clear	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Estate	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
£500	O
pr	O
Ann	O
.	O
&	O
was	O
answerable	O
for	O
nearly	O
£6000	O
of	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
iniquities	O
.	O
By	O
taking	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
redeeming	O
the	O
Land	O
Tax	O
,	O
I	O
reduced	O
that	O
Debt	O
to	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
&	O
purchased	O
the	O
Land	O
Tax	O
,	O
by	O
selling	O
a	O
detached	O
farm	O
of	O
£130	O
pr-	O
Ann	O
.	O
for	O
4000	O
Guineas	O
.	O
If	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
produces	O
£12000	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
both	O
my	O
personal	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
debt	O
,	O
without	O
waiting	O
for	O
the	O
arrangement	O
I	O
propose	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
unleſs	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
deemed	O
more	O
expedient	O
to	O
purchase	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
my	O
family	O
in	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
As	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Parliament	O
last	O
Seſsion	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
attending	O
my	O
duty	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
ensuing	O
Session	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
arranged	O
my	O
other	O
matters	O
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
Mary	B-pers
accompanies	O
me	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
She	O
is	O
going	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
daughter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Moray	I-pers
,	O
where	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
elder	O
Sister	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
the	O
Fox	O
Hounds	O
are	O
sent	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
hate	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
barbarous	O
Story	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Newspaper	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
been	O
permitted	O
to	O
devour	O
a	O
Fox	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
having	O
given	O
excellent	O
sport	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
&	O
taken	O
shelter	O
in	O
your	O
Court	O
Yard	O
,	O
from	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
been	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
have	O
saved	O
poor	O
Reynards	O
life	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
risk	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Garrick	B-pers
,	O
nor	O
shall	O
I	O
attempt	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Young	O
Roscius	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
not	O
wishing	O
to	O
be	O
squeezed	O
or	O
trampled	O
to	O
death	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
fortunate	O
in	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Aldborough	I-pers
.	O
Every	O
body	O
speaks	O
well	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
grateful	O
for	O
her	O
recollection	O
of	O
Me	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
brother	O
would	O
get	O
himself	O
quietly	O
hanged	O
before	O
he	O
becomes	O
Earl	O
of	O
Selkirk	O
.	O
Arch	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
Yorkshire	B-place
Living	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
somewhere	O
near	O
Ferrybridge	B-place
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
bad	O
Man	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
hate	O
Dragoon	O
Parsons	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
the	O
Fox	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
wishing	O
every	O
thing	O
good	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
friend	O
and	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
34	O
each	O
}	O
Side	O
}	O
19	O
bottom	O
19	O
Do	O
8	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Fifth	O
Janry-	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
