TOKEN	NE
20	O
Febry	O
1790	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
St-	O
Saturday	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
post	O
arrived	O
with	O
yr-	O
much	O
wished	O
for	O
Letter	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
dispatched	O
mine	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
set	O
off	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
there	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
more	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
directions	O
to	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
about	O
Packing	O
Boxes	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
returned	O
to	O
town	B-place
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
yr-	O
Uncle	O
's	O
--	O
Pachierotti	B-pers
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
&	O
dined	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
paſsed	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Kilmore	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
ye	O
Bishopeſs	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Pi	B-pers
&	O
Miss	B-pers
H——	I-pers
sang	O
a	O
Duet	O
&	O
Piozzi	B-pers
joined	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
terzato	O
wch	O
.	O
far	O
exceeded	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
before	O
--	O
At	O
11	O
we	O
separated	O
I	O
desired	O
Ld	B-pers
W——	I-pers
to	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
and	O
he	O
good	O
naturedly	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
Sunday	O
--	O
This	O
morning	O
by	O
appointmt-	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kershaw	I-pers
my	O
Coach	O
Acquaintance	O
at	O
Old	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
then	O
walked	O
forth	O
--	O
&	O
called	O
first	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
's	O
who	O
's	O
paintings	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
's	O
we	O
obligingly	O
shewed	O
us	O
his	O
drawings	O
--	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
has	O
discovered	O
this	O
method	O
,	O
of	O
keeping	O
water	O
colors	O
wet	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
Oil	O
--	O
next	O
we	O
called	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
who	O
's	O
manner	O
of	O
Drawing	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
stile	O
--	O
he	O
very	O
obligingly	O
opened	O
all	O
his	O
Port	O
Folio	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
attended	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
's	O
,	O
another	O
Artist	O
,	O
who	O
accompanied	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
--	O
here	O
we	O
saw	O
another	O
manner	O
of	O
drawing	O
--	O
after	O
examining	O
his	O
portfolios	O
we	O
all	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandby	I-pers
's	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
at	O
old	O
Serres	B-pers
's	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
Vandervelt	B-pers
's	O
schetches	O
&	O
his	O
own	O
paintings	O
--	O
afterwards	O
we	O
separated	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kershaw	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
at	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
dined	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
7	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Cr	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
--	O
at	O
8	O
he	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
H——	I-pers
I	O
introduced	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
who	O
was	O
properly	O
attentive	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
desired	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
introduce	O
ye-	O
Cr	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
who	O
sat	O
next	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
exclaimed	O
“	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
dont	O
introduce	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
'm	O
sick	O
of	O
Foreigners	O
”	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
cooled	O
me	O
affectually	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
poor	O
Palombi	B-pers
remain	O
unpresented	O
--	O
that	O
Coxcomical	O
puppy	O
Pindemonte	B-pers
was	O
there	O
&	O
affected	O
to	O
treat	O
Palombi	B-pers
with	O
the	O
“	O
Haut	O
ten	O
bas	O
”	O
I	O
fancy	O
the	O
fellow	O
perceived	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
--	O
his	O
sagacity	O
was	O
sufft	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
that	O
--	O
thō	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
prompt	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
room	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
an	O
intruder	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
dont	O
wonder	O
at	O
people	O
's	O
dread	O
of	O
foreigners	O
--	O
for	O
they	O
stick	O
to	O
you	O
like	O
Bird	O
Lime	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
shaking	O
them	O
off	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
much	O
complained	O
of	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
Cr	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
Monday	O
--	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
paid	O
Owen	B-pers
's	O
bill	O
for	O
the	O
B	O
water	O
--	O
walked	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
useful	O
articles	O
of	O
Household	O
Luxuries	O
to	O
please	O
my	O
own	O
self	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Eagle	O
Stt	O
Holborn	B-place
about	O
my	O
picture	O
frame	O
--	O
from	O
there	O
we	O
walked	O
back	O
thrō	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
--	O
called	O
at	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
Caenwood	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
&	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
I	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
put	O
into	O
Cases	O
--	O
left	O
the	O
others	O
in	O
train	O
&	O
walked	O
to	O
town	B-place
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
,	O
dreſsed	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Portland	O
place	O
at	O
5	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
called	O
on	O
me	O
yesterday	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
out	O
her	O
fine	O
little	O
Girl	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
but	O
unfortunately	O
ye-	O
Damsel	O
was	O
sleepy	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
6	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
nearly	O
read	O
this	O
Pamphlet	O
agt	O
.	O
ye-	O
Test	O
Act	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
--	O
We	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
yet	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
ye-	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
reserved	O
a	O
ticket	O
for	O
Hastings	B-pers
's	O
trial	O
for	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
polite	O
attention	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
prolonged	O
my	O
stay	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
again	O
&	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
stairs	O
to	O
desire	O
his	O
beſ	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
civilities	O
to	O
me	O
are	O
particularly	O
flattering	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
owing	O
to	O
his	O
attachment	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
so	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
entertain	O
or	O
amuse	O
him	O
--	O
or	O
be	O
useful	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
it	O
began	O
to	O
rain	O
&	O
before	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
get	O
to	O
a	O
stand	O
of	O
Coaches	O
my	O
sweet	O
person	O
was	O
wet	O
to	O
the	O
Skin	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
trugged	O
on	O
to	O
Burlington	O
St	O
.	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
&	O
changed	O
my	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
AMaria	B-pers
's	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
engagement	O
of	O
meeting	O
Palombi	B-pers
at	O
her	O
house	O
to	O
breakfast	O
this	O
morng	O
as	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
at	O
9	O
&	O
they	O
men	O
must	O
be	O
attended	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
leave	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
men	O
to	O
themselves	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
J	I-pers
's	O
house	O
--	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
ye-	O
Bell	O
in	O
Wood	O
St	O
.	O
before	O
one	O
with	O
our	O
Goods	O
&	O
Chattels	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ben	I-pers
met	O
me	O
there	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
3	O
before	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
prevail	O
upon	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
weigh	O
ye	O
Goods	O
whch	O
they	O
evaded	O
by	O
one	O
excuse	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
I	O
know	O
was	O
to	O
charge	O
me	O
4	O
or	O
500	O
lb	O
wt	O
.	O
more	O
than	O
there	O
really	O
was	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
youll	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
quite	O
sufft-	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
safe	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
--	O
receive	O
great	O
pleasure	O
from	O
seeing	O
you	O
occupied	O
in	O
arranging	O
your	O
shells	O
,	O
foſsils	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
the	O
eagerneſs	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
Child	O
's	O
perplexing	O
aid	O
in	O
decomposing	O
yr-	O
management	O
--	O
Dear	O
little	O
Soul	O
,	O
How	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
--	O
not	O
entirely	O
for	O
herself	O
--	O
but	O
because	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
indeed	O
my	O
Love	O
the	O
only	O
merit	O
I	O
will	O
allow	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
poſseſs	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
having	O
discernment	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
yr-	O
very	O
superior	O
worth	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
loving	O
you	O
infinitely	O
more	O
than	O
every	O
earthly	O
consideration	O
--	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
at	O
4	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
employing	O
in	O
scribbling	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
improbable	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
--	O
In	O
case	O
that	O
should	O
not	O
happen	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
prevented	O
from	O
leaving	O
Town	B-place
--	O
before	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
will	O
arrive	O
at	O
Horridge	B-place
I	O
believe	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
--	O
when	O
a	O
Cart	O
must	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
meet	O
ye-	O
waggon	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
box	O
no	O
.	O
13	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
at	O
ten	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
's	O
--	O
he	O
&	O
all	O
yr-	O
family	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
bad	O
cold	O
that	O
every	O
body	O
complains	O
of	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
W——	I-pers
who	O
has	O
seen	O
nobody	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
principal	O
complaint	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Impertinent	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Children	O
--	O
&	O
without	O
exception	O
must	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
finest	O
family	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
all	O
equally	O
docile	O
good	O
tempered	O
&	O
affecte	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
W——	I-pers
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
very	O
friendly	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
then	O
called	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Foote	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
paſsed	O
an	O
agreeable	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
informed	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
had	O
highly	O
offended	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
by	O
keeping	O
them	O
waiting	O
for	O
2	O
hours	O
before	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
appearance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
their	O
respects	O
to	O
t	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
general	O
grumble	O
&	O
a	O
general	O
squeeze	O
--	O
many	O
talked	O
of	O
returning	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
a	O
mistake	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
all	O
were	O
dissatisfied	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
confined	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
together	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
made	O
some	O
seriously	O
ill	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
for	O
Ly	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
distreſsed	O
by	O
a	O
country	O
parson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
consulting	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
manuscript	O
which	O
lay	O
before	O
him	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
s	O
advice	O
wd	O
.	O
soon	O
have	O
driven	O
me	O
away	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
persevered	O
&	O
sat	O
me	O
out	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
said	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
for	O
you	O
&	O
sent	O
you	O
some	O
publication	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
--	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
even	O
the	O
title	O
page	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
judge	O
presently	O
--	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
Bloſsets	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
then	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Mr.-	B-pers
Mrs.-	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
--	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
's	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
--	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Acct	O
.	O
confirmed	O
of	O
the	O
complaint	O
agt	O
.	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
ten	O
thousand	O
things	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
but	O
her	O
eyes	O
were	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
--	O
her	O
general	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
is	O
certainly	O
better	O
than	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
looks	O
very	O
pretty	O
--	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
dined	O
wth-	O
them	O
today	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
AM——	B-pers
wd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
pleased	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
dine	O
once	O
wth-	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
fixed	O
on	O
--	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
's	I-pers
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
--	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Ly	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Camelford	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lewisham	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
said	O
many	O
civil	O
things	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
who	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
--	O
also	O
for	O
Ly	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
--	O
for	O
Cr	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
--	O
&	O
3	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
--	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
--	O
where	O
we	O
left	O
our	O
names	O
--	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Wimpole	O
St	O
.	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
&	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Longhams	O
--	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
for	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
--	O
then	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
--	O
was	O
admitted	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
and	O
am	O
now	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
AMaria	B-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
--	O
poor	O
Soul	O
(	O
--	O
she	O
dare	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
whh	O
is	O
a	O
serious	O
trouble	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
shall	O
now	O
have	O
the	O
Happineſs	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
my	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
arms	O
very	O
soon	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
not	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
surprising	O
you	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
awaken	O
yr-	O
affectionate	O
solicitude	O
for	O
my	O
safety	O
from	O
the	O
perils	O
of	O
a	O
stage	O
Coach	O
Adieu	O
best	O
of	O
Wifes	O
--	O
&	O
most	O
amiable	O
of	O
women	O
You	O
are	O
&	O
for	O
ever	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
tenderly	O
beloved	O
by	O
your	O
own	O
JD	B-pers
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
her	O
--	O
London	B-place
February	O
twenty	O
fourth	O
1790	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Warwick	O
