TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
Stt	O
.	O
Friday	O
.	O
n	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
take	O
Leave	O
of	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
--	O
arriv	O
'd	O
at	O
Her	O
Door	O
the	O
Rain	O
began	O
to	O
fall	O
&	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
run	O
wch	O
.	O
so	O
represented	O
to	O
Me	O
the	O
Storm	O
of	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
renew	O
'd	O
the	O
Terror	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Home	O
Home	O
tho	O
my	O
Coach	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
Out	O
&	O
wait	O
on	O
You	O
.	O
Cowards	O
there	O
always	O
were	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
be	O
not	O
in	O
Battle	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Harm	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
yr	O
Precious	O
Daur	O
looking	O
as	O
if	O
London	B-place
had	O
done	O
Her	O
no	O
Harm	O
.	O
If	O
before	O
You	O
leave	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
any	O
thing	O
shd	O
bring	O
You	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
or	O
Richmond	B-place
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
enquire	O
for	O
Rosedale	O
&	O
yr	O
Obedient	O
humble	O
Servant	O
F.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Half	O
Moon	O
Street	O
Boulton	O
Street	O
