TOKEN	NE
6	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Happy	O
should	O
I	O
be	O
could	O
I	O
answer	O
your	O
Que	O
ry	O
,	O
of	O
when	O
do	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
?	O
believe	O
me	O
as	O
ignorant	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
yourself	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
depend	O
upon	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
thinks	O
it	O
safe	O
for	O
Pennel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
to	O
see	O
his	O
Br	O
&	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
first	O
flattered	O
myself	O
a	O
Month	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
longest	O
Quarantine	O
,	O
I	O
now	O
Philosophically	O
resign	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
more	O
distant	O
Period	O
of	O
5	O
Weeks	O
&	O
happy	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
disapointed	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
know	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
my	O
dear	O
you	O
have	O
ſuch	O
causes	O
for	O
uneasineſs	O
this	O
Life	O
is	O
certainly	O
most	O
thoroughly	O
disguised	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
am	O
thankful	O
for	O
the	O
Bleſsings	O
I	O
receive	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
have	O
felt	O
many	O
better	O
moments	O
.	O
The	O
Society	O
of	O
P	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
has	O
kept	O
me	O
alive	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
lose	O
them	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
my	O
anxiety	O
is	O
thank	O
God	O
happily	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Dear	O
Children	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
bear	O
the	O
ennui	O
&	O
Solitude	O
with	O
calmneſs	O
I	O
have	O
pleasant	O
moments	O
to	O
look	O
back	O
to	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
painful	O
ones	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
dwell	O
upon	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Br	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
5	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
thing	O
which	O
has	O
entertained	O
me	O
beyond	O
description	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
kn	O
o	O
w	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
d	O
o	O
would	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Smelts	I-pers
's	O
Squire	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
aproaching	O
Installation	O
of	O
Knights	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
he	O
really	O
made	O
me	O
laugh	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
allmost	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
Idea	O
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
it	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Irwin	I-pers
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
will	O
enjoy	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
this	O
Letter	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
judge	O
of	O
my	O
beautiful	O
countenance	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
my	O
Br	O
thinks	O
I	O
look	O
remarkably	O
well	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
Friend	O
,	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
all	O
yr	O
kindneſs	O
the	O
last	O
Cheese	O
was	O
excellent	O
&	O
I	O
daresay	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
Affly	O
Your	O
Wm	B-pers
--	O
We	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
smart	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
tho	O
not	O
so	O
fine	O
as	O
you	O
Mesdames	O
habit	O
ant	O
de	O
la	O
Cour	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
new	O
Gowns	O
--	O
