TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Six	O
months	O
have	O
now	O
paſsed	O
without	O
my	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
mean	O
any	O
reproof	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
must	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
making	O
my	O
acknowledgements	O
for	O
your	O
last	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
perfectly	O
settled	O
and	O
happy	O
in	O
your	O
new	O
department	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
understand	O
your	O
disposition	O
,	O
trifling	O
difficulties	O
will	O
not	O
disturb	O
you	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
&	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
none	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
leſs	O
room	O
for	O
addreſs	O
&	O
ingenuity	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
little	O
ground	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
my	O
personal	O
application	O
to	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
may	O
very	O
properly	O
give	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
further	O
Preferment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
with	O
perfect	O
contentedness	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
paſsed	O
the	O
age	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
with	O
any	O
prospect	O
of	O
succeſs	O
attempt	O
to	O
create	O
an	O
interest	O
with	O
Men	O
in	O
power	O
,	O
besides	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
myself	O
totally	O
unprovided	O
with	O
the	O
indispensable	O
requisites	O
,	O
the	O
ability	O
of	O
making	O
them	O
any	O
return	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
age	O
in	O
which	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
very	O
credulous	O
indeed	O
,	O
will	O
expect	O
to	O
receive	O
favours	O
gratuitously	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
have	O
risen	O
here	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
past	O
in	O
my	O
Line	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
woud	O
seem	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
very	O
few	O
instances	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
Birth	O
and	O
liberal	O
sentiments	O
were	O
certain	O
disqualifications	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
my	O
mind	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
contented	O
state	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
believe	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
proceed	O
in	O
reflexions	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
My	O
Agent	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
died	O
lately	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
I	O
have	O
appointed	O
Mr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
Balfour	I-pers
writer	O
to	O
the	O
Signet	O
at	O
Edinburgh	B-place
to	O
manage	O
my	O
Affairs	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
directions	O
to	O
attend	O
properly	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
oftner	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
write	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
ease	O
such	O
letters	O
as	O
I	O
like	O
best	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
do	O
not	O
show	O
the	O
smallest	O
premeditation	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
with	O
my	O
Family	O
to	O
Latour	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
summer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
out	O
more	O
money	O
there	O
than	O
I	O
intended	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
altogether	O
injudiciously	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
prejudice	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
recommendation	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
has	O
operated	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
procured	O
me	O
the	O
smallest	O
notice	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
perceived	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
therefore	O
expected	O
that	O
her	O
application	O
to	O
the	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lt	O
.	O
wou	O
'd	O
correspond	O
with	O
her	O
regard	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
any	O
further	O
troublesome	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
candid	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
but	O
that	O
my	O
Line	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
department	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
continue	O
to	O
believe	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
truth	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sackville	O
Street	O
May	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
1781	O
.	O
