TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dr	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
forbid	O
my	O
coming	O
over	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
unpleasant	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
gracious	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
refuse	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Conversation	O
at	O
least	O
together	O
between	O
this	O
&	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
yourself	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
well	O
,	O
Thursday	O
Evg	O
.	O
believe	O
me	O
nobody	O
wishes	O
you	O
more	O
perfect	O
Health	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
than	O
yr-	O
Sincely	O
affe	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Saturday	O
Morg	O
23	O
d	O
Novbr	O
1782	O
Windsor	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
