TOKEN	NE
May	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
Dr	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
--	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
waiting	O
on	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
yesterday	O
Evening	O
;	O
believe	O
me	O
no	O
Syren	O
Songs	O
were	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
induce	O
me	O
to	O
much	O
wish	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
your	O
obliging	O
invitation	O
the	O
truth	O
is	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
remain	O
at	O
home	O
having	O
a	O
Swelled	O
face	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
venturd	O
to	O
have	O
shewn	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
H	O
.	O
of	O
Lords	O
whither	O
my	O
bounden	O
Duty	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
concerned	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
is	O
not	O
eſsentially	O
recovering	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
worst	O
may	O
be	O
Expected	O
your	O
kind	O
attention	O
must	O
be	O
highly	O
gratifying	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
inclined	O
to	O
do	O
all	O
I	O
poſsibly	O
can	O
to	O
relieve	O
his	O
Anxiety	O
&	O
distreſs	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
power	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Service	O
I	O
fear	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
always	O
Dr	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yours	O
sincerely	O
&	O
c	O
Warwick	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
desired	O
by	O
Ly	B-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
completely	O
tired	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
unfit	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
Nurse	O
herself	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
calls	O
of	O
Duty	O
which	O
indeed	O
seem	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
light	O
--	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
at	O
Thorncliff	B-place
with	O
his	O
miserable	O
reduced	O
Regt	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
French	O
fotilla	O
is	O
out	O
he	O
saw	O
22	O
Sail	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
prefers	O
staying	O
in	O
England	B-place
to	O
going	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
where	O
he	O
is	O
destined	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	O
Regt	O
.	O
is	O
fit	O
for	O
Service	O
he	O
hopes	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
more	O
--	O
Certain	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Signal	O
was	O
made	O
sent	O
&	O
Expreſs	O
sent	O
to	O
Admiral	O
in	O
the	O
Downs	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
ye	O
Alert	O
.	O
--	O
