TOKEN	NE
15	O
th	O
July	O
1783	O
8	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
Nine	O
o'clock	O
yet	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
this	O
Nights	O
post	O
go	O
out	O
without	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
My	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
A	O
vous	O
tranquiliser	O
l'Esprit	O
with	O
infinite	O
satisfaction	O
I	O
contradict	O
the	O
report	O
raised	O
about	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
's	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
appears	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
she	O
suffers	O
from	O
the	O
extreme	O
heat	O
of	O
the	O
Weather	O
.	O
but	O
in	O
every	O
other	O
respect	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
Princeſses	O
are	O
all	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
your	O
Dear	O
little	O
Darling	O
is	O
as	O
engaging	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
(	O
since	O
you	O
desire	O
it	O
)	O
of	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
your	O
an	O
xi	O
ety	O
about	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
Ladies	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
Madelle	B-pers
Moula	I-pers
has	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
indisposed	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
is	O
not	O
yet	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Germany	B-place
I	O
am	O
sure	O
You	O
would	O
find	O
him	O
improved	O
Farewell	O
My	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
unalterable	O
Affection	O
M.	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
July	O
ye	O
15	O
th	O
