TOKEN	NE
27	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
unexpectedly	O
hurried	O
away	O
from	O
Home	O
to	O
attend	O
Parliament	O
,	O
much	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
.	O
Fortunately	O
,	O
the	O
Frost	O
continued	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
my	O
Journey	O
.	O
The	O
Weather	O
since	O
my	O
arrival	O
has	O
been	O
most	O
execrable	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
raining	O
&	O
thawing	O
,	O
my	O
patience	O
is	O
almost	O
exhausted	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
chiefly	O
confined	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
except	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Aunts	O
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Cronies	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
You	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Genealogical	O
Paper	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
You	O
?	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
lazy	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
You	O
little	O
information	O
about	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
family	O
;	O
by	O
profeſsion	O
,	O
a	O
Writer	O
of	O
the	O
Signet	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
an	O
Attorney	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Claſs	O
;	O
&	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Apollo	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
or	O
wherefore	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
You	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
£12,000	O
,	O
in	O
six	O
Years	O
by	O
his	O
busineſs	O
.	O
He	O
may	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
speculating	O
in	O
buying	O
&	O
selling	O
Land	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
formerly	O
reported	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
leaving	O
Edinburgh	B-place
so	O
precipitately	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
importunity	O
of	O
this	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
You	O
no	O
News	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
first	O
Cousins	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Napier	O
in	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Corunna	B-place
.	O
Three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
Sons	O
of	O
my	O
Uncle	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
eldest	O
of	O
these	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
The	B-pers
rest	I-pers
escaped	O
unhurt	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
is	O
quite	O
blind	O
.	O
Her	O
feelings	O
are	O
warm	O
,	O
and	O
acute	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
blow	O
has	O
indeed	O
been	O
severe	O
,	O
She	O
shews	O
much	O
resignation	O
,	O
and	O
submiſsion	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
if	O
the	O
Almighty	O
,	O
and	O
appears	O
most	O
thankful	O
that	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
her	O
two	O
other	O
Sons	O
have	O
been	O
preserved	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
weather	O
will	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Cadogan	O
Place	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
great	O
Town	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
in	O
smaller	O
ones	O
,	O
no	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
can	O
be	O
got	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
rains	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
all	O
my	O
Garrison	O
well	O
in	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
From	O
my	O
Eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
for	O
Months	O
past	O
.	O
My	O
second	O
Boy	O
,	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
Plymouth	B-place
,	O
to	O
repair	O
some	O
damages	O
the	O
Resistance	O
met	O
with	O
lately	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Gale	O
of	O
Wind	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
returning	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
about	O
Easter	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
You	O
are	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
shall	O
beat	O
up	O
your	O
Quarters	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
With	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
and	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Sixth	O
January	O
1809	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
