TOKEN	NE
Wednesday	O
Octber	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
where	O
we	O
are	O
stop	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
days	O
rest	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
you	O
received	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
from	O
Mannheim	B-place
not	O
for	O
the	O
entertainment	O
it	O
contain	O
'd	O
(	O
for	O
in	O
that	O
respect	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
reading	O
)	O
but	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
my	O
affection	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
my	O
promise	O
--	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
wrote	O
that	O
letter	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
taken	O
in	O
airing	O
&	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
strength	O
for	O
my	O
journey	O
that	O
I	O
ha	O
d	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
I	O
liked	O
Spa	B-place
better	O
towards	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
than	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
I	O
lived	O
very	O
much	O
together	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Spencers	I-pers
took	O
to	O
her	O
very	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
likewise	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Drogheda	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Hertford	I-pers
s	O
daughter	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
amiable	O
woman	O
&	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
wch	O
.	O
made	O
me	O
paſs	O
my	O
time	O
very	O
agreably	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
--	O
one	O
circumstance	O
however	O
damp	O
'd	O
every	O
enjoyment	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
the	O
melancholy	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
Delewarr	B-pers
family	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
great	O
hopes	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
hopes	O
became	O
so	O
fluctuating	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
there	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
little	O
hopes	O
of	O
ever	O
getting	O
him	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
touching	O
as	O
the	O
Scenes	O
,	O
every	O
day	O
among	O
in	O
that	O
family	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
amiable	O
,	O
&	O
suffering	O
,	O
&	O
suffer	O
so	O
mildly	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
wishes	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
comfort	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
it	O
breaks	O
ones	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
comprehend	O
that	O
feel	O
.	O
--	O
From	O
Spa	B-place
we	O
came	O
to	O
Spa	B-place
&	O
from	O
thence	O
embarkd	O
on	O
the	O
Rhine	O
&	O
were	O
four	O
days	O
getting	O
to	O
Bonn	B-place
from	O
whence	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
land	O
to	O
Mayence	B-place
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Theatre	O
at	O
Manheim	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Elector	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
&	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
a	O
frock	O
in	O
the	O
Pit	O
)	O
he	O
did	O
him	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
first	O
Minister	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
both	O
he	O
&	O
I	O
,	O
would	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Manheim	B-place
where	O
the	O
Electreſs	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
at	O
Ogersheim	B-place
when	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
accepted	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
tired	O
with	O
my	O
journey	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
dreſs	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
days	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Elector	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Concert	O
given	O
us	O
at	O
Count	B-pers
Savioli	I-pers
's	O
the	O
Directeur	O
des	O
Spectacles	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
last	O
Night	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
)	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
concert	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
lodging	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
Polite	O
&	O
attentive	O
--	O
from	O
Swezinghe	B-place
we	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
pursuance	O
of	O
our	O
Plan	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
Manheim	B-place
by	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Yesterday	O
were	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
calld	O
Naples	B-place
by	O
meeting	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gloucester	I-pers
who	O
upon	O
hearing	O
we	O
were	O
changing	O
horses	O
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
obey	O
'd	O
his	O
R	O
Hſs-	O
s	O
commands	O
&	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
shock	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
legs	O
are	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
his	O
face	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Corpse	O
,	O
his	O
hair	O
almost	O
totally	O
fallen	O
off	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
remains	O
quite	O
red	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Children	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
with	O
tears	O
in	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
he	O
is	O
hopeleſs	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
with	O
reason	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
ever	O
will	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
his	O
illneſs	O
--	O
nature	O
is	O
worn	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Winter	O
will	O
finish	O
all	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
legs	O
&	O
is	O
carried	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
--	O
What	O
is	O
birth	O
?	O
What	O
is	O
greatneſs	O
?	O
all	O
All	O
,	O
a	O
prey	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
&	O
Subject	O
to	O
every	O
pain	O
&	O
distreſs	O
but	O
why	O
do	O
I	O
moralize	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
forget	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Marqse	B-pers
Trotti	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughters	O
at	O
Goppingen	B-place
who	O
love	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
liked	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
felt	O
I	O
liked	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
that	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
little	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
n	O
proper	O
Oppertunity	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
expreſs	O
my	O
respectfull	O
Duty	O
to	O
our	O
Charming	O
&	O
Valuable	O
Queen	B-pers
--	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
of	O
Sovereigns	O
&	O
princes	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
admire	O
&	O
love	O
her	O
&	O
think	O
you	O
happy	O
in	O
your	O
situation	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
interest	O
me	O
--	O
My	O
kind	O
love	O
attends	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
joins	O
in	O
his	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
Yr	O
truly	O
Affecte	O
Aunt	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
es	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Bonn	B-place
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Angleterre	B-place
