TOKEN	NE
Upshire	O
Farm	O
Eſsex	B-place
Wedy	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
Your	O
letter	O
my	O
Dear	O
dated	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
has	O
but	O
this	O
moment	O
reach	O
'd	O
me	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
then	O
easily	O
imagine	O
what	O
a	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
state	O
my	O
mind	O
is	O
in	O
--	O
as	O
in	O
that	O
letter	O
I	O
learn	O
that	O
My	O
dear	O
friend	O
is	O
ill	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
accounts	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
pray	O
fail	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
Post	O
--	O
&	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
Courteen	O
Hall	O
for	O
I	O
go	O
there	O
on	O
friday	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
concerning	O
her	O
Illneſs	O
&	O
conceal	O
nothing	O
from	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
glad	O
you	O
are	O
with	O
your	O
dear	O
Sister	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
tenderly	O
you	O
love	O
her	O
&	O
with	O
what	O
Care	O
you	O
will	O
attend	O
her	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Physician	O
--	O
and	O
whether	O
this	O
had	O
illneſs	O
has	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
old	O
complaint	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
.	O
I	O
intreat	O
,	O
once	O
more	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
true	O
&	O
faithful	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
your	O
Sister	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
&	O
hope	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
my	O
letter	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
been	O
confin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Gout	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
recovering	O
but	O
is	O
still	O
carried	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
stairs	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
but	O
her	O
spirits	O
are	O
much	O
depreſsed	O
by	O
the	O
constant	O
state	O
of	O
anxiety	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
on	O
her	O
Husband	O
s	O
account	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
only	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
four	O
days	O
only	O
;	O
--	O
Ldy.W——	B-pers
&	O
I	O
,	O
only	O
&	O
Richard	B-pers
go	O
into	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
journey	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
little	O
Richard	B-pers
to	O
School	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
endulge	O
me	O
by	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
post	O
a	O
duplicate	O
letter	O
directed	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
Waltham	O
Abbey	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
improbable	O
but	O
something	O
may	O
happen	O
to	O
prevent	O
our	O
going	O
the	O
day	O
at	O
present	O
fix	O
'd	O
on	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
depend	O
upon	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
detirminations	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
--	O
Adieu	O
,	O
embrace	O
your	O
dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yr	O
.	O
Sister	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
ill	O
again	O
Perhaps	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
tomorrow	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
Yr	O
.	O
sister	O
fatigue	O
herself	O
with	O
writing	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
London	B-place
Free	O
Wake	O
