TOKEN	NE
Burlington	O
Street	O
31	O
st	O
March	O
1789	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
write	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
busineſs	O
retards	O
my	O
intentions	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
fatigue	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
&	O
night	O
as	O
I	O
seldom	O
leave	O
of	O
until	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
as	O
much	O
tired	O
as	O
a	O
day	O
Labourer	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
account	O
of	O
Politicks	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
learn	O
from	O
the	O
newspapers	O
.	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
recovery	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
most	O
fortunate	O
circumstance	O
for	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
if	O
the	O
Outs	O
had	O
once	O
got	O
into	O
poſseſsion	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
without	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
likely	O
Orange	O
Capes	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
serious	O
struggle	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
Gentry	O
would	O
instead	O
of	O
Bludgeons	O
thrust	O
a	O
few	O
Bayonets	O
into	O
us	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
as	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
now	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
family	O
and	O
his	O
subjects	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
take	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Children	O
are	O
all	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
present	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
had	O
swelled	O
Necks	O
--	O
Katherine	B-pers
&	O
Mary	B-pers
are	O
almost	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
Fanny	B-pers
s	O
(	O
Higgins	B-pers
says	O
)	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
some	O
continuance	O
--	O
Henry	B-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
grows	O
a	O
fine	O
fellow	O
&	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
tempered	O
Children	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
Kath	B-pers
&	O
Mary	B-pers
are	O
much	O
improved	O
--	O
Fanny	B-pers
has	O
not	O
health	O
to	O
continue	O
at	O
School	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
very	O
tractable	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
advised	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
--	O
Jones	B-pers
has	O
certainly	O
done	O
Kath	B-pers
:	I-pers
much	O
service	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
your	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
continued	O
well	O
all	O
this	O
long	O
Winter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
now	O
be	O
soon	O
over	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
has	O
completely	O
Furnished	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Wimbledon	O
and	O
intends	O
remaining	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
until	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
--	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
most	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
least	O
three	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
sometimes	O
oftener	O
--	O
Sunday	O
is	O
my	O
the	O
only	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
myself	O
&	O
hitherto	O
for	O
these	O
four	O
last	O
Sundays	O
Nanny	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
have	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
they	O
intend	O
being	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
Nanny	B-pers
has	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Children	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
what	O
paſsed	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
think	O
of	O
relying	O
upon	O
her	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
most	O
astonishing	O
to	O
think	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
gives	O
up	O
her	O
life	O
to	O
Madneſs	O
&	O
folly	O
The	O
Westminster	B-place
Petition	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
next	O
friday	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
I	O
have	O
declined	O
acting	O
as	O
the	O
Agent	O
yet	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
giving	O
a	O
constant	O
daily	O
attendance	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
at	O
a	O
consultation	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
wish	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Right	O
of	O
Voting	O
established	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Inhabts	O
of	O
Westmr	B-place
only	O
have	O
the	O
right	O
?	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
those	O
residing	O
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
or	O
any	O
other	O
County	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Westmr	B-place
.	O
If	O
the	O
house	O
determine	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
then	O
give	O
ourselves	O
no	O
further	O
trouble	O
Nanny	O
has	O
very	O
lately	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
blue	O
meeting	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hear	O
went	O
of	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
inclinable	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
diſsolution	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
September	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
authority	O
for	O
saying	O
so	O
,	O
yet	O
every	O
thing	O
wears	O
that	O
appearance	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
always	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
leſs	O
expensive	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
God	O
permit	O
than	O
on	O
Horseback	O
Pray	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
obed	O
Sert	O
.	O
J.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
The	O
Pages	O
were	O
discharged	O
for	O
improper	O
behaviour	O
