TOKEN	NE
I	O
was	O
favour	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mr	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
s	O
second	O
Letter	O
late	O
last	O
night	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
answerd	O
yr	O
first	O
imeditly	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
Ill	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
incapable	O
of	O
Writeing	O
Your	O
Second	O
Letter	O
schocked	O
me	O
greatly	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
alow	O
me	O
to	O
hope	O
every	O
thing	O
may	O
yet	O
be	O
Setled	O
aimicably	O
&	O
to	O
yr	O
Wish	O
I	O
sent	O
imeditly	O
on	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
yours	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Written	O
to	O
the	O
Signet	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Argyle	O
Square	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
delliver	O
yr	O
Meſsage	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
(	O
&	O
they	O
say	O
)	O
does	O
not	O
return	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
but	O
as	O
at	O
present	O
no	O
Court	O
of	O
Law	O
is	O
sitting	O
it	O
makes	O
his	O
comeing	O
rather	O
precotious	O
.	O
for	O
which	O
reason	O
you	O
should	O
get	O
Mr	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
s	O
Man	O
of	O
Law	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
yr	O
orders	O
as	O
they	O
understand	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
stille	O
better	O
than	O
ones	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
consequently	O
are	O
fittest	O
to	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
all	O
Law	O
affairs	O
--	O
but	O
you	O
had	O
best	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
but	O
justice	O
in	O
bellieveing	O
me	O
yr	O
very	O
Sinceare	O
friend	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
heartily	O
Sympathize	O
with	O
you	O
both	O
!	O
excuse	O
a	O
short	O
Letter	O
I	O
realy	O
am	O
very	O
Ill	O
but	O
much	O
yours	O
:	O
do	O
write	O
as	O
often	O
&	O
fully	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
it	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
Agreeable	O
--	O
Accept	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
&	O
the	O
Young	O
folk	O
s	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
yourself	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
as	O
well	O
as	O
those	O
of	O
your	O
ever	O
Affect	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
both	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
&	O
you	O
are	O
better	O
