TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Novr	O
.	O
1794	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
-	O
Inst	O
.	O
has	O
arrived	O
safe	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
no	O
Deeds	O
or	O
Conveyances	O
have	O
yet	O
made	O
out	O
their	O
journey	O
hither	O
.	O
Pray	O
pull	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Cap	O
(	O
her	O
Ears	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
)	O
who	O
has	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
unaccountable	O
daudling	O
,	O
concealed	O
this	O
Paper	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
your	O
Commands	O
,	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
so	O
.	O
Regular	O
&	O
orderly	O
in	O
all	O
our	O
proceedings	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
at	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
so	O
much	O
resembles	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
all	O
the	O
occurrences	O
are	O
wonderfully	O
interesting	O
to	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
yet	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
afford	O
no	O
entertainment	O
to	O
others	O
.	O
A	O
O	O
ne	O
great	O
event	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
has	O
this	O
day	O
happened	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
having	O
again	O
taken	O
her	O
Seat	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Dining	O
Table	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
since	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
threatens	O
taking	O
a	O
Walk	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
or	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
will	O
execute	O
her	O
threats	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
You	O
Females	O
are	O
tolerably	O
inclined	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
own	O
Will	O
,	O
perhaps	O
she	O
may	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
hardly	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Boy	O
sleeps	O
&	O
sucks	O
wonderfully	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
squalls	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
torment	O
him	O
dreſsing	O
&	O
undreſsing	O
.	O
Would	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
Brats	O
were	O
equally	O
quiet	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
alas	O
,	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
the	O
terrificability	O
of	O
my	O
Countenance	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
indulge	O
their	O
own	O
little	O
Paſsions	O
,	O
&	O
distreſs	O
my	O
Nerves	O
,	O
by	O
irritating	O
mine	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
suppose	O
Louisa	B-pers
never	O
treated	O
You	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
You	O
may	O
scarcely	O
imagine	O
the	O
thing	O
to	O
be	O
poſsible	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
poſseſses	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
complaint	O
in	O
the	O
Song	O
,	O
a	O
Scolding	O
Jade	O
.	O
The	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
Six	O
Squalling	O
Brats	O
is	O
now	O
nearly	O
added	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
five	O
being	O
quite	O
perfect	O
in	O
the	O
Art	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
sixth	O
will	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
imitative	O
powers	O
,	O
soon	O
learn	O
to	O
join	O
their	O
Chorus	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
having	O
inked	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
Paper	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
pay	O
Sevenpence	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
add	O
one	O
solid	O
declaration	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Nonsense	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
sincere	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
good	O
wishes	O
ever	O
attend	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Maria	B-pers
desires	O
to	O
join	O
hers	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
pray	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
faithful	O
&	O
attached	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Pray	O
dont	O
forget	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
.	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
14	O
th	O
-	O
Novr-	O
1794	O
.	O
This	O
letter	O
was	O
sealed	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
Your	O
Settlement	O
after	O
Marriage	O
came	O
to	O
Me	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
It	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
returned	O
this	O
Evening	O
had	O
You	O
condescended	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Instructions	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
Me	O
whether	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
sign	O
seal	O
deliver	O
&	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
preservation	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
also	O
be	O
signed	O
&	O
c	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
I	O
observe	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
Witneſs	O
to	O
your	O
Signatures	O
.	O
Inform	O
me	O
whether	O
any	O
more	O
is	O
required	O
when	O
I	O
sign	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Country	O
we	O
never	O
use	O
leſs	O
than	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
apprehend	O
,	O
room	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
above	O
my	O
Signing	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Send	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
all	O
these	O
queries	O
,	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
Post	O
.	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchester	B-place
by	O
Carlisle	B-place
