TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	B-place
23	O
.	O
Apl	O
.	O
94	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
amie	O
to	O
date	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
to	O
dinner	O
yesterday	O
&	O
recd	O
.	O
that	O
kind	O
of	O
welcome	O
reception	O
which	O
affords	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
so	O
much	O
gratification	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
looks	O
vastly	O
well	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
lame	O
at	O
least	O
much	O
leſs	O
so	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
a	O
little	O
aged	O
Mr.	B-pers
Laſss-	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
looking	O
vastly	O
well	O
,	O
his	O
daughter	O
is	O
an	O
uncommon	O
size	O
for	O
her	O
Age	O
&	O
xtremely	O
lusty	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
I	I-pers
is	O
very	O
indifferent	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
carriage	O
lately	O
&	O
caught	O
cold	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
feverish	O
&	O
looks	O
ill	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
writing	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
desired	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
b	O
e	O
st	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lethelier	I-pers
is	O
here	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
by	O
the	O
Cover	O
&	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tighe	I-pers
niece	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Newspapers	O
arrived	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
&	O
have	O
brought	O
us	O
charming	O
tidings	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
--	O
I	O
feel	O
exceſsively	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
something	O
so	O
creditable	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
merit	O
of	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Action	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
lost	O
so	O
few	O
Men	O
&	O
only	O
one	O
Officer	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
gratification	O
to	O
the	O
King	B-pers
and	O
a	O
fine	O
stimulant	O
to	O
the	O
luke	O
warm	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
too	O
that	O
the	O
Emperor	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
an	O
Action	O
which	O
succeeded	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
Martinique	B-place
too	O
has	O
surrendered	O
&	O
forces	O
are	O
detached	O
against	O
Guadaloupe	B-place
&	O
St.	B-place
Lucia	I-place
--	O
&	O
our	O
forces	O
are	O
now	O
bombarding	O
Bastia	B-place
the	O
capital	O
of	O
Corsica	B-place
--	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
do	O
well	O
&	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
sit	O
down	O
quietly	O
in	O
peace	O
--	O
Another	O
division	O
of	O
Poland	B-place
is	O
expected	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
vill	O
a	O
inous	O
busineſs	O
--	O
I	O
delivered	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
's	O
meſsage	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
--	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Windsor	B-place
tomorrow	O
morng	O
&	O
shall	O
sleep	O
tomorr	O
ow	O
night	O
at	O
Bags	O
hot	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
rea	O
ch	O
Windsor	B-place
in	O
one	O
day	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
get	O
there	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
have	O
the	O
p	O
leasure	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
plaguer	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
with	O
good	O
Accts	O
.	O
o	O
f	O
you	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
fro	O
m	O
thence	O
--	O
This	O
place	O
looks	O
just	O
as	O
formerly	O
.	O
every	O
body	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
appear	O
comfortable	O
&	O
happy	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
french	O
say	O
--	O
peace	O
&	O
plenty	O
is	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
poor	O
Dad	B-pers
is	O
not	O
here	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunken	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
dismiſsed	O
--	O
A	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
here	O
now	O
lives	O
wh-	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bower	I-pers
as	O
batman	O
--	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
I.s	B-pers
had	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
s	O
ale	O
of	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
but	O
I	O
omitted	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
Spurs	O
which	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
yesterday	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
except	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
dearly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
&	O
shall	O
remain	O
pour	O
toujour	O
le	O
même	O
mari	O
tres	O
affectioné	O
et	O
fidele	O
J.D——	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Tighe	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
place	O
about	O
7	O
Miles	O
from	O
hence	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
suit	O
us	O
&	O
I	O
only	O
mention	O
it	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
just	O
been	O
talking	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
library	O
which	O
contains	O
7000	O
Volumes	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
laid	O
out	O
5000£	O
in	O
very	O
few	O
Years	O
in	O
Books	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Library	O
from	O
her	O
Grandfather	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
their	O
Rooms	O
filled	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Irem	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
the	O
library	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
Bugbear	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
where	O
Nobody	O
reads	O
--	O
They	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
near	O
Stourhead	B-place
where	O
Sir	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
has	O
given	O
them	O
a	O
house	O
--	O
in	O
his	O
Grounds	O
rent	O
free	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wishes	O
them	O
to	O
live	O
near	O
him	O
--	O
this	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
Object	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
fortune	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
people	O
dont	O
want	O
friends	O
,	O
Acts	O
of	O
friendship	O
are	O
forced	O
upon	O
&	O
the	O
Neceſsitous	O
may	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
most	O
people	O
feel	O
this	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
