TOKEN	NE
Get	O
up	O
at	O
7.	O
dreſs	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
poſsible	O
to	O
divide	O
myself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
between	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Augusta	B-pers
(	O
who	O
are	O
in	O
different	O
rooms	O
)	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
O'Clock	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chapel	O
Tuesdays	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
to	O
attend	O
their	O
R	O
H	O
:	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
room	O
--	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
am	O
dismis	O
'd	O
by	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
get	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
attend	O
During	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
s	O
leſsons	O
with	O
her	O
Masters	O
from	O
9	O
O'Clock	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
from	O
12	O
till	O
2	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
which	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
for	O
hair-dreſsing	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
4	O
divide	O
myself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
between	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Augusta	B-pers
--	O
a	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
comes	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
Lodge	O
&	O
remains	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Pſs	O
's	O
are	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
the	O
Dinner	O
hour	O
is	O
4	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
seldom	O
at	O
table	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
's	O
20	O
Min	O
;	O
½	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
sometimes	O
5	O
O'Clock	O
.	O
this	O
depends	O
upon	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
rides	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
dine	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
whose	O
dinner	O
hour	O
depends	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
their	O
Majes	O
ties	O
-	O
dine	O
.	O
--	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
reads	O
aloud	O
--	O
the	O
three	O
Eldest	O
Pſs's-	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sit	O
&	O
work	O
.	O
till	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
comes	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
walk	O
upon	O
the	O
terrace	O
--	O
return	O
to	O
Tea	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
get	O
a	O
dish	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Musick	O
Room	O
and	O
generally	O
finish	O
the	O
Eveng	O
with	O
Cards	O
--	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
their	O
M	O
.	O
&	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
R	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
go	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
attend	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
(	O
walking	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
lower	O
Lodge	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
ye	O
.	O
Pſs	O
's	O
come	O
up	O
&	O
I	O
divide	O
myself	O
between	O
their	O
rooms	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
are	O
undreſsing	O
till	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
in	O
bed	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
seldom	O
much	O
before	O
12	O
before	O
I	O
retire	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
The	O
only	O
difference	O
of	O
the	O
Eveng	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
waiting	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
walk	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Terrace	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
hour	O
is	O
uncertain	O
as	O
it	O
depends	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
they	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
about	O
8	O
7	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
carries	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
lower	O
lodge	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
lives	O
there	O
does	O
not	O
return	O
therefore	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
rec	O
eive	O
ye	O
.	O
Pſs	O
's	O
.	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
up	O
every	O
Night	O
--	O
Till	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlaiment	O
breaks	O
up	O
--	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
once	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
up	O
once	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
On	O
ye	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
Morng	O
.	O
after	O
Chapel	O
&	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Kew	B-place
--	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Thursday	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
full	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
about	O
one	O
O'Clock	O
.	O
return	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
to	O
Tea	O
--	O
&	O
on	O
Friday	O
Afternoon	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
N	O
B	O
.	O
during	O
these	O
3	O
days	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
an	O
instant	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
my	O
nominal	O
Evengs	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
waiting	O
are	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
&	O
Thursday	O
&	O
every	O
other	O
Saturday	O
--	O
If	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
is	O
Ill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
constant	O
attendance	O
.	O
--	O
