TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
December	O
5	O
th	O
a	O
rambling	O
life	O
and	O
a	O
teazing	O
painful	O
complaint	O
,	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
paſs	O
over	O
the	O
fortnight	O
you	O
had	O
prescribed	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
directi	O
n	O
g	O
my	O
letters	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
This	O
I	O
shall	O
addreſs	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
Courteenhall	O
aſsured	O
that	O
ere	O
now	O
you	O
are	O
settled	O
in	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
neighbourhood	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
good	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
&	O
transmit	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Unlucky	O
,	O
unfortunate	O
inded	O
am	O
I	O
in	O
again	O
miſsing	O
you	O
in	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
,	O
but	O
when	O
was	O
I	O
otherwise	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
absolulety	O
like	O
the	O
Man	O
&	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
weather	O
House	O
,	O
never	O
out	O
or	O
in	O
togethe	O
r	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
any	O
of	O
being	O
confined	O
at	O
Northamton	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
under	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
s	O
Eye	O
and	O
Care	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
then	O
but	O
feel	O
perfectly	O
comfortable	O
and	O
easy	O
about	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
even	O
a	O
hope	O
of	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
at	O
Northamton	B-place
by	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
settled	O
&	O
whether	O
comfortably	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
feels	O
of	O
home	O
&	O
recall	O
those	O
of	O
early	O
youth	O
and	O
enjoyment	O
!	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
represent	O
you	O
to	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Mother	O
and	O
a	O
nurse	O
,	O
or	O
fancy	O
you	O
making	O
all	O
your	O
little	O
caps	O
&	O
shirts	O
but	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
in	O
that	O
light	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
admire	O
and	O
love	O
you	O
at	O
least	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
I	O
have	O
hitherto	O
seen	O
you	O
--	O
The	O
alteration	O
in	O
my	O
Plan	O
&	O
arrangement	O
respecting	O
Horton	B-place
,	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
consequence	O
&	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Bell	B-pers
's	O
state	O
of	O
Health	O
which	O
required	O
her	O
absence	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
frequent	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
and	O
scene	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
always	O
intending	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
about	O
this	O
time	O
so	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Sister	O
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
returning	O
there	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
--	O
my	O
Sister	O
went	O
from	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Hill	I-place
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
sometime	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Father	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
--	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Brock	O
street	O
--	O
the	O
Town	O
is	O
very	O
full	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
their	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
imagine	O
they	O
will	O
both	O
like	O
their	O
sejour	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
the	O
early	O
&	O
regular	O
Hours	O
my	O
Sister	O
the	O
dancing	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
myself	O
I	O
detest	O
the	O
Place	O
dancing	O
is	O
not	O
absolute	O
ly	O
my	O
paſsion	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
often	O
pleasant	O
in	O
an	O
impromptu	O
private	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
early	O
hours	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
what	O
delightful	O
mild	O
weather	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
vexed	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
&	O
leav	O
e	O
my	O
pleasant	O
walks	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
pleasant	O
Society	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
flying	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
the	O
whole	O
Autumn	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
regrets	O
at	O
leaving	O
one	O
Friend	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
prospect	O
of	O
a	O
quick	O
return	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
s	O
,	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Ly	I-pers
Kerr	I-pers
's	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
danci	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
singi	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
good	O
sense	O
,	O
and	O
wit	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
laughi	O
n	O
g	O
and	O
merrine	O
ſs	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
at	O
Putney	B-place
again	O
--	O
with	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Reventelau	I-pers
--	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
at	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
--	O
sometimes	O
with	O
the	O
gay	O
,	O
then	O
with	O
the	O
wretched	O
--	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
is	O
still	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
not	O
soon	O
recover	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
an	O
amiable	O
,	O
beloved	O
Daughter	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
alternately	O
paſsed	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
serious	O
,	O
or	O
quiet	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
&	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
circle	O
of	O
20	O
People	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
gravely	O
playi	O
n	O
g	O
at	O
Whist	O
&	O
cribbagge	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
laughi	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
cheati	O
n	O
g	O
at	O
Pope	O
Joan	O
--	O
Inshort	O
whilst	O
I	O
tr	O
was	O
last	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
appointed	O
Lectrice	O
to	O
the	O
society	O
and	O
every	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
read	O
a	O
French	O
Drame	O
or	O
story	O
of	O
some	O
kind	O
,	O
loud	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
attentive	O
audience	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
generally	O
drew	O
tears	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
choice	O
of	O
the	O
lecture	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
left	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
serious	O
or	O
affecting	O
nature	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
drove	O
to	O
Town	O
by	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
face	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
which	O
concludi	O
n	O
g	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
toothache	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
teeth	O
drawn	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
awake	O
in	O
torture	O
so	O
many	O
nights	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
&	O
Stuart	B-pers
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thinks	O
it	O
is	O
rheuma	O
tism	O
from	O
my	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
almost	O
perfectly	O
free	O
from	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
he	O
comes	O
every	O
day	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
attentive	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
dear	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
myself	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
Friday	O
&	O
have	O
never	O
left	O
my	O
room	O
since	O
then	O
--	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
impatient	O
to	O
be	O
released	O
--	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
comfortable	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
clean	O
warm	O
chearful	O
habitation	O
,	O
with	O
Musick	O
,	O
Books	O
,	O
pen	O
&	O
ink	O
&	O
every	O
means	O
of	O
amusement	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
breathe	O
without	O
difficulty	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
when	O
one	O
is	O
sleepy	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
spared	O
the	O
misery	O
of	O
dreſsing	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
&	O
the	O
still	O
greater	O
one	O
of	O
keeping	O
1000	O
disagreeable	O
engagements	O
--	O
Those	O
Friends	O
who	O
care	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
care	O
will	O
certainly	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
all	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wish	O
now	O
to	O
set	O
my	O
eyes	O
on	O
them	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
pleasant	O
line	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
means	O
whate	O
ver	O
They	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Town	O
is	O
full	O
--	O
the	O
Play	O
Houses	O
--	O
Parties	O
every	O
night	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
only	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
the	O
amusement	O
in	O
the	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
Beaus	O
&	O
Belles	O
soi	O
disant	O
old	O
&	O
young	O
to	O
shoot	O
arrows	O
at	O
a	O
mark	O
!	O
at	O
night	O
they	O
all	O
play	O
at	O
Loo	O
--	O
&	O
have	O
a	O
uniform	O
!	O
I	O
fancy	O
the	B-pers
P.	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fit	I-pers
.	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
Man	O
&	O
Wife	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
tired	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
more	O
in	O
love	O
,	O
more	O
attracted	O
&	O
more	O
entirely	O
hers	O
than	O
ever	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
crush	O
of	O
all	O
confidences	O
,	O
probabilities	O
&	O
wise	O
predictions	O
!	O
je	O
n	O
'	O
y	O
comprens	O
rien	O
,	O
nor	O
does	O
anybody	O
else	O
I	O
believe	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
is	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
ago	O
,	O
fairly	O
well	O
--	O
v	O
astly	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
by	O
all	O
accounts	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
severe	O
weather	O
will	O
throw	O
he	O
r	O
back	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
relapse	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
t	O
he	O
utmost	O
danger	O
--	O
everybody	O
loves	O
her	O
--	O
adores	O
her	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
will	O
I	O
think	O
break	O
her	O
heart	O
if	O
she	O
dies	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
is	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
June	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
hear	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
has	O
been	O
extremely	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
rather	O
better	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
vastly	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
about	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
for	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Day	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
just	O
a	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
my	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
which	O
on	O
one	O
account	O
and	O
only	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
Health	O
makes	O
a	O
journey	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
unwell	O
lately	O
but	O
it	O
draws	O
too	O
near	O
the	O
Birthday	O
to	O
be	O
practicable	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
t	O
u	O
ndertaken	O
immediatly	O
--	O
I	O
conclude	O
Col.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
yet	O
,	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
or	O
to	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
attentions	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
call	O
here	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
&	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
c	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
promised	O
to	O
convey	O
to	O
India	B-place
--	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
ask	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
about	O
Mr	B-pers
Young	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hear	O
Ld	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
like	O
Dallington	B-place
--	O
my	O
sudden	O
disappearance	O
from	O
Horton	B-place
prevented	O
me	O
waiti	O
n	O
g	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
doi	O
n	O
g	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
has	O
just	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
and	O
tomorrow	O
goes	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
so	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
left	O
alone	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
illneſs	O
(	O
my	O
continued	O
complaint	O
in	O
my	O
stomack	O
excepted	O
)	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
my	O
Family	O
--	O
Charlotte	B-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
pretty	O
good	O
--	O
she	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
&	O
promises	O
me	O
great	O
comfort	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
very	O
clever	O
--	O
&	O
quick	O
--	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
work	O
--	O
T	O
hank	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
for	O
inquiri	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
Ad	O
ieu	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
hear	O
if	O
but	O
in	O
two	O
words	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
settled	O
comfortably	O
--	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
constant	O
&	O
ardent	O
prayers	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
your	O
confinement	O
may	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
every	O
favourable	O
circumstances	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
may	O
o'ercloud	O
the	O
joy	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
event	O
of	O
it	O
will	O
produce	O
to	O
both	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
may	O
every	O
bleſsi	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
every	O
happineſs	O
always	O
attend	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
unknown	O
&	O
expected	O
Bei	O
n	O
g	O
already	O
poſseſses	O
a	O
strong	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
hea	O
rt	O
of	O
your	O
affectionate	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northamton	B-place
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
1786	O
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
