TOKEN	NE
Accept	O
these	O
Dallington	B-place
Violets	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
offer	O
to	O
you	O
with	O
very	O
different	O
Sensations	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
experienced	O
twenty	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
despairing	O
Lover	O
--	O
but	O
now	O
am	O
the	O
happy	O
Husband	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
amiable	O
&	O
beloved	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
J	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
16	O
March	O
1802	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
enclosing	O
violets	O
from	O
Dallington	B-place
