TOKEN	NE
You	O
will	O
excuse	O
me	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
sure	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
wrote	O
before	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
scarce	O
had	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
myself	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
that	O
my	O
teizing	O
Cough	O
seized	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
foretold	O
the	O
Night	O
I	O
came	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
your	O
poor	O
Mama	O
has	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
fall	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
reestablished	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
mind	O
&	O
body	O
easy	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
who	O
I	O
hear	O
wants	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
his	O
Living	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
)	O
&	O
Hamilton	B-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
hurry	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
see	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
Gate	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
oppertunity	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
both	O
heartily	O
join	O
in	O
wishing	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
settled	O
to	O
your	O
satisfaction	O
--	O
Ly	O
Ly	B-pers
Helton	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
evening	O
always	O
enquires	O
very	O
kindly	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
--	O
Thursday	O
thus	O
far	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
wrote	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
;	O
since	O
which	O
my	O
nerves	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
resume	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
&	O
now	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
stomach	O
suffers	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
excuse	O
my	O
writing	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
letter	O
--	O
Hamilton	B-pers
begs	O
your	O
acceptance	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Florence	B-place
Sattin	O
with	O
the	O
trimming	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
Negligé	O
which	O
he	O
hopes	O
you	O
will	O
wear	O
for	O
his	O
Sake	O
--	O
I	O
intend	O
sending	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
pepper	O
mint	O
drops	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
send	O
but	O
few	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
now	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
--	O
Our	O
kind	O
love	O
attends	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
most	O
Affecte	O
Aunt	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kings	B-place
Mews	I-place
Thursday	O
Janry	O
.	O
ye	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
