TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
My	O
Daughter	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
sensible	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
deferr	O
'd	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
informed	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
proposed	O
myself	O
that	O
pleasure	O
immediately	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
your	O
very	O
great	O
attention	O
&	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
your	O
invitation	O
of	O
my	O
Son	O
to	O
paſs	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
find	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
proposes	O
setting	O
out	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
myself	O
unworthy	O
the	O
constant	O
attachment	O
&	O
friendship	O
I	O
have	O
experienced	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
were	O
I	O
silent	O
upon	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
your	O
Cousin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
a	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
utmost	O
distreſs	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
his	O
Commiſsion	O
in	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
light	O
Dragoons	O
,	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
generosity	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
yours	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
forget	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
join	O
'd	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
February	O
twelve	O
month	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
constantly	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
obtain	O
'd	O
leave	O
of	O
absence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
mortification	O
to	O
receive	O
constant	O
complaints	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
conduct	O
unbecoming	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
by	O
keeping	O
low	O
company	O
,	O
negligence	O
of	O
his	O
duty	O
,	O
contracting	O
debts	O
,	O
withdrawing	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Officers	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
avoid	O
drinking	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
all	O
occasions	O
having	O
a	O
dirty	O
slovenly	O
appearance	O
.	O
Under	O
these	O
circumstances	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
wonder	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
disliked	O
&	O
despised	O
by	O
almost	O
every	O
Officer	O
in	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
&	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
from	O
the	O
particular	O
friendship	O
of	O
General	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
Colonel	O
's	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
long	O
since	O
have	O
been	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
Having	O
by	O
an	O
uncommon	O
quick	O
succeſsion	O
attain	O
'd	O
the	O
Rank	O
of	O
eldest	O
Cornet	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
have	O
succeeded	O
by	O
purchase	O
to	O
a	O
Lieutenancy	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
decline	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Regt	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
apprehending	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
soon	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
neceſsity	O
,	O
as	O
upon	O
examination	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
complaints	O
too	O
well	O
founded	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
conduct	O
in	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
his	O
pay	O
,	O
&	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
well	O
provided	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
&	O
without	O
debt	O
,	O
he	O
now	O
leaves	O
the	O
Army	O
without	O
reputation	O
&	O
much	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
credit	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
I	O
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Debts	O
,	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
upon	O
honor	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
whole	O
amount	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
truth	O
&	O
honor	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
daily	O
making	O
discoveries	O
of	O
engagements	O
he	O
has	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
for	O
very	O
large	O
Sums	O
for	O
things	O
unnecessary	O
&	O
which	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
discharge	O
for	O
instance	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
discovery	O
yesterday	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bespoke	O
a	O
watch	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
£70.0.0	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
I	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
promiſsory	O
Drafts	O
payable	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
for	O
one	O
hundred	O
&	O
five	O
Guineas	O
for	O
a	O
Phaeton	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
proposed	O
making	O
his	O
appearance	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
;	O
the	O
Horses	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
other	O
great	O
expence	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
addreſs	O
to	O
persuade	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Phaeton	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
£	O
25	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
Drafts	O
which	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
Judge	O
of	O
the	O
painfu	O
l	O
state	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
in	O
the	O
recollection	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
Son	O
so	O
totally	O
devoid	O
of	O
truth	O
honesty	O
&	O
common	O
sense	O
,	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
subject	O
?	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
desirous	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
permit	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Germany	B-place
after	O
his	O
visit	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
confidence	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
having	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
such	O
principles	O
,	O
what	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
expected	O
but	O
continual	O
discord	O
?	O
Palombi	B-pers
has	O
communicated	O
to	O
me	O
his	O
expected	O
happineſs	O
;	O
if	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
resembles	O
her	O
Br	O
.	O
in	O
any	O
respect	O
O	O
Derbyshire	B-place
!	O
supply	O
the	O
rest	O
yourself	O
Remember	O
me	O
most	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
Affect	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
July	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1791	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
Orchard	O
St	O
.	O
Portman	O
Sqr	O
.	O
Since	O
my	O
writing	O
the	O
within	O
complaints	O
of	O
Rt	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
countermanded	O
the	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
his	O
final	O
disclosure	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
amount	O
of	O
his	O
debts	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
that	O
single	O
Article	O
only	O
there	O
is	O
room	O
for	O
some	O
little	O
extenuation	O
.	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
particulars	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
only	O
lead	O
him	O
to	O
falsify	O
I	O
must	O
insist	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
if	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
find	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
troublesome	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
hint	O
&	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
withdrawn	O
immediately	O
&	O
the	O
secret	O
kept	O
.	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
with	O
either	O
Servant	O
or	O
horse	O
P.S	O
.	O
Pray	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Robert	B-pers
s	O
Succeſsor	O
lodges	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
Cornetcy	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
discharge	O
my	O
Debt	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Interest	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
due	O
in	O
October	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
but	O
just	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
avail	O
'd	O
myself	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
kindneſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
