TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
June	O
1802	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Three	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
it	O
to	O
Leighton	O
House	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
You	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
find	O
you	O
out	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
your	O
Letter	O
from	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
arrived	O
here	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
your	O
Miſs	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
believe	O
any	O
reports	O
of	O
her	O
illneſses	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
convinced	O
,	O
by	O
ocular	O
demonstration	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Absurdity	O
of	O
imagining	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
so	O
robust	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
from	O
Nervous	O
complaints	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
dont	O
let	O
your	O
Old	O
Women	O
Doctors	O
terrify	O
You	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Geese	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
time	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Event	O
must	O
be	O
looked	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D.	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
in	O
his	O
health	O
from	O
his	O
attention	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
All	O
here	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
Love	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
(	O
although	O
chiefly	O
unknown	O
)	O
to	O
You	O
and	O
all	O
your	O
Concern	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
First	O
June	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
HAWICK	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
