TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
Tuesday	O
July	O
30	O
th	O
:	O
1771	O
How	O
shall	O
I	O
expreſs	O
my	O
gratitude	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
Friendship	O
you	O
have	O
honour	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
Civilities	O
your	O
good	O
Papa	O
&	O
Mama	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
Boy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
perpetually	O
talking	O
of	O
?	O
we	O
think	O
him	O
much	O
grown	O
,	O
&	O
improved	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
is	O
good	O
;	O
his	O
dispositions	O
seem	O
at	O
present	O
such	O
as	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
;	O
I	O
pray	O
God	O
to	O
continue	O
them	O
so	O
!	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
increase	O
in	O
Virtue	O
&	O
Religion	O
rather	O
than	O
Fortune	O
.	O
Your	O
dispositions	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
have	O
taken	O
a	O
happy	O
turn	O
;	O
you	O
lay	O
out	O
your	O
whole	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
improvement	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
no	O
leisure	O
for	O
those	O
Childish	O
diſsipations	O
so	O
natural	O
to	O
your	O
Sex	O
&	O
Age	O
;	O
Go	O
on	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
the	O
delight	O
of	O
your	O
fond	O
parents	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
all	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
Humility	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
preserve	O
you	O
from	O
pedantry	O
,	O
a	O
character	O
which	O
in	O
our	O
Sex	O
is	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
the	O
cause	O
why	O
a	O
Wise	O
Woman	O
is	O
in	O
general	O
disliked	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
no	O
Rivals	O
in	O
knowledge	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
angry	O
at	O
every	O
Woman	O
who	O
shall	O
attempt	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
is	O
,	O
our	O
Sex	O
are	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
proud	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
true	O
cause	O
,	O
why	O
we	O
are	O
despised	O
,	O
a	O
fund	O
of	O
useful	O
knowledge	O
in	O
either	O
Sex	O
is	O
highly	O
commendable	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
keep	O
in	O
View	O
the	O
Ultimate	O
End	O
of	O
all	O
Learning	O
;	O
the	O
Glory	O
of	O
God	O
;	O
&	O
knowledge	O
of	O
ones	O
self	O
.	O
this	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
by	O
your	O
Conversation	O
&	O
Letters	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
pursuit	O
;	O
&	O
whilst	O
you	O
keep	O
this	O
point	O
in	O
view	O
,	O
your	O
Studys	O
will	O
always	O
give	O
you	O
sattisfaction	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
look	O
back	O
with	O
pleasure	O
on	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
spent	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
heartfelt	O
Joy	O
of	O
self	O
approbation	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
support	O
you	O
through	O
all	O
the	O
Calamities	O
&	O
vexations	O
of	O
this	O
foolish	O
Life	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
every	O
situation	O
is	O
liable	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
am	O
preaching	O
a	O
Sermon	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
writing	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
an	O
odd	O
Correspondent	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
remember	O
't	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
fault	O
,	O
you	O
woud	O
have	O
me	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Jack	B-pers
tells	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
working	O
Chairs	O
,	O
I	O
admire	O
your	O
taste	O
,	O
in	O
having	O
one	O
single	O
figure	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
much	O
more	O
Elegant	O
,	O
than	O
being	O
crouded	O
full	O
of	O
different	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
generally	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
entertaining	O
work	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
reckon	O
'd	O
bad	O
for	O
the	O
shape	O
.	O
I	O
Shall	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
finish	O
'd	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
kind	O
in	O
wishing	O
to	O
see	O
yo	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
Northn	B-place
:	I-place
was	O
not	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shoud	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
taking	O
a	O
trip	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
present	O
must	O
content	O
myself	O
with	O
hearing	O
from	O
my	O
good	O
Friends	O
there	O
;	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
sincere	O
regard	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
will	O
accept	O
my	O
most	O
sin	O
cere	O
respects	O
;	O
&	O
acknowledgments	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
th	O
eir	O
favours	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Mrs.	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
joyn	O
;	O
&	O
beli	O
eve	O
me	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
(	O
with	O
a	O
thousand	O
kind	O
wishes	O
for	O
your	O
Health	O
&	O
happineſs	O
)	O
your	O
sincere	O
Friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
most	O
Affcet	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
violent	O
favorite	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Sally	B-pers
Northampton	B-place
