TOKEN	NE
1765	O
To	O
Charles	B-pers
&	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
Yours	O
of	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Jany	O
.	O
came	O
safe	O
to	O
hand	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
&	O
found	O
me	O
at	O
Florence	B-place
where	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
great	O
benefit	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
health	O
by	O
the	O
mild	O
air	O
of	O
Pisa	B-place
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
advantage	O
,	O
society	O
entertainment	O
or	O
even	O
tolerable	O
accommodation	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
poor	O
deserted	O
&	O
miserable	O
country	O
.	O
However	O
as	O
my	O
principal	O
end	O
of	O
going	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
answerd	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
regret	O
the	O
may	O
solitary	O
days	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
.	O
there	O
As	O
my	O
health	O
is	O
now	O
almost	O
reestablish	O
'd	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
inducement	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
prolonging	O
my	O
stay	O
abroad	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
things	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
quite	O
differently	O
from	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
eight	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
most	O
thoroughly	O
convinced	O
that	O
an	O
English	O
woman	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
being	O
transplanted	O
into	O
France	B-place
or	O
Italy	B-place
unleſs	O
she	O
is	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
accommodate	O
herself	O
to	O
their	O
respective	O
customs	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
case	O
she	O
must	O
first	O
divest	O
herself	O
of	O
decency	O
&	O
of	O
every	O
idea	O
of	O
right	O
&	O
propriety	O
;	O
in	O
short	O
unleſs	O
it	O
is	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
health	O
a	O
woman	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
proper	O
inducement	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
;	O
&	O
a	O
man	O
en	O
Famille	O
must	O
frequently	O
find	O
himself	O
in	O
ridiculous	O
situations	O
,	O
these	O
reflexions	O
were	O
not	O
new	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
abroad	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
them	O
of	O
consequence	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
lay	O
aside	O
a	O
plan	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
health	O
and	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
absolutely	O
requir	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
now	O
extremely	O
happy	O
as	O
the	O
material	O
point	O
is	O
answerd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
considerd	O
this	O
matter	O
in	O
its	O
proper	O
light	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
fixed	O
my	O
departure	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
next	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
by	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
I	O
know	O
immediately	O
occur	O
to	O
you	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
plan	O
?	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
have	O
any	O
reserve	O
with	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
difficulty	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
a	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
acquainting	O
you	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
views	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
shou	O
'd	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
improper	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
affection	O
for	O
me	O
will	O
not	O
permit	O
you	O
to	O
conceal	O
your	O
sentiments	O
.	O
Not	O
having	O
any	O
desire	O
or	O
even	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
further	O
Preferment	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
I	O
have	O
many	O
strong	O
objections	O
against	O
fixing	O
my	O
residence	O
in	O
that	O
Country	O
it	O
must	O
then	O
be	O
somewhere	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
some	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
totally	O
unknown	O
&	O
where	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
perpetually	O
reminded	O
of	O
former	O
disagreeable	O
situations	O
or	O
stumbled	O
upon	O
by	O
Friends	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
is	O
what	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
to	O
be	O
desir	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
Norwich	B-place
will	O
answer	O
my	O
purpose	O
in	O
most	O
of	O
these	O
particulars	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
formerly	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Town	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
good	O
society	O
the	O
whole	O
year	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
you	O
know	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Country	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
immense	O
trade	O
I	O
conclude	O
the	O
markets	O
must	O
be	O
good	O
&	O
reasonable	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
particularly	O
so	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
further	O
induced	O
by	O
your	O
opinion	O
upon	O
this	O
matter	O
to	O
make	O
trial	O
of	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
to	O
some	O
Person	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
getting	O
lodgings	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
without	O
having	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
known	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
auckward	O
situation	O
.	O
Do	O
me	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
acquainting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pasham	I-pers
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
take	O
her	O
Daughter	O
under	O
her	O
own	O
tuition	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
July	O
next	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
expreſs	O
our	O
obligations	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
your	O
kind	O
attention	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
,	O
my	O
Affection	O
for	O
her	O
increases	O
daily	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
that	O
my	O
happineſs	O
cou	O
'd	O
depend	O
so	O
much	O
upon	O
so	O
young	O
a	O
personage	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
particularly	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
She	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
for	O
near	O
this	O
fortnight	O
past	O
with	O
the	O
scarlet	O
Fever	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
disorder	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
the	O
Fever	O
&	O
the	O
irruption	O
h	O
a	O
v	O
r	O
e	O
now	O
over	O
but	O
the	O
Physiscian	O
will	O
insist	O
upon	O
her	O
keeping	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
to	O
come	O
as	O
relapses	O
sometimes	O
happen	O
&	O
are	O
commonly	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Banker	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
&	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
observe	O
my	O
instructions	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
runaway	O
Tenant	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
now	O
be	O
unneceſsary	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
Fetherston	B-pers
any	O
instructions	O
about	O
our	O
affair	O
.	O
A	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
wrote	O
ten	O
days	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
in	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
.	O
Brother	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Florence	B-place
Feby	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1765	O
.	O
A	O
Monsr	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
c	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
chez	O
Carlo	B-pers
Hadfield	I-pers
a	O
Florence	B-place
Italie	B-place
P.S	O
.	O
Our	O
Child	O
here	O
is	O
extremely	O
well	O
&	O
has	O
already	O
had	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
favourable	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
London	B-place
by	O
sea	O
from	O
Leghorn	B-place
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
.	O
