TOKEN	NE
Harleyford	B-place
.	O
March	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
Yesterday	O
to	O
add	O
a	O
Line	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
pretty	O
affectionate	O
Letter	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Manuscript	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
which	O
entertain	O
'd	O
me	O
&	O
all	O
here	O
vastly	O
.	O
Nobody	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
sensible	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
expreſs	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
sincerely	O
return	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
my	O
present	O
State	O
makes	O
me	O
incapable	O
of	O
expreſsing	O
or	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
will	O
pardon	O
my	O
Defficiencies	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
rejoice	O
however	O
about	O
the	O
happineſs	O
caused	O
by	O
P.	B-pers
William	I-pers
s	O
return	O
,	O
thō	O
I	O
feel	O
vastly	O
being	O
debarr	O
'd	O
my	O
Share	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
least	O
Amendment	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
was	O
my	O
dread	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
disorder	O
,	O
for	O
without	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
I	O
look	O
forward	O
with	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
These	O
Thoughts	O
every	O
body	O
tells	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
banish	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
will	O
intrude	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Situation	O
as	O
mine	O
,	O
where	O
inability	O
must	O
destroy	O
all	O
my	O
powers	O
of	O
being	O
useful	O
,	O
&	O
consequently	O
of	O
being	O
happy	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
good	O
hearts	O
of	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
have	O
experienced	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
thousand	O
Instances	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
wear	O
your	O
Spirits	O
with	O
my	O
Distreſs	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
feel	O
the	O
more	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
relieve	O
it	O
.	O
Adieu	O
ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
I	O
have	O
by	O
mistake	O
begun	O
on	O
a	O
half	O
Sheet	O
so	O
can	O
not	O
seal	O
it	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
awkward	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
St	O
James	O
's	O
