TOKEN	NE
Horton	B-place
3	O
d	O
June	O
1783	O
Tuesday	O
Eveg	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
Here	O
I	O
am	O
comfortably	O
enjoying	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
Your	O
Father	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
Sister	O
,	O
whilst	O
You	O
are	O
dreading	O
the	O
fatigue	O
of	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Folio	O
sheet	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
intend	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
influence	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
fill	O
'd	O
for	O
Your	O
amusement	O
--	O
how	O
it	O
will	O
answer	O
that	O
intention	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
--	O
yet	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
(	O
Notwithstanding	O
the	O
Rain	O
)	O
wonderfully	O
bright	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
particularly	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
been	O
tiring	O
herself	O
to	O
Death	O
here	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
Place	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
no	O
Fire	O
and	O
thought	O
herself	O
quite	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
three	O
comfortleſs	O
Rooms	O
especially	O
as	O
the	O
Weather	O
towards	O
3	O
o'clock	O
changed	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
worse	O
.	O
During	O
Dinner	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
perished	O
with	O
the	O
Cold	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
eat	O
a	O
morcel	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
at	O
last	O
prevailed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
eating-Room	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
Sr	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
who	O
through	O
a	O
very	O
usual	O
Absence	O
of	O
Mind	O
called	O
her	O
Miſs	O
Flora	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
ashamed	O
at	O
the	O
reception	O
our	O
Guest	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
It	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
rain	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
it	O
ceased	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
shewing	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
Stables	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
was	O
dragged	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
ancles	O
in	O
the	O
Wet	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
Supper	O
and	O
sitting	O
very	O
comfortably	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
--	O
--	O
only	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
you	O
last	O
Night	O
that	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
)	O
--	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.——	I-pers
thinks	O
the	O
Suite	O
of	O
Rooms	O
horrible	O
,	O
old	O
fashioned	O
&	O
a	O
hundred	O
horrible	O
&	O
ceteras	O
.	O
I	O
deny	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
foregoing	O
subject	O
;	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
has	O
spent	O
a	O
delightfull	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
drive	O
from	O
C——	O
Hall	O
--	O
is	O
quite	O
enchanted	O
with	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
thinks	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
most	O
beautifull	O
spot	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
--	O
the	O
house	O
magnificent	O
,	O
commodious	O
,	O
&	O
surtout	O
comfortable	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
particularly	O
charmed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
dear	O
little	O
round	O
tables	O
--	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
conversation	O
has	O
been	O
lively	O
,	O
&	O
brilliant	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
been	O
wonderfully	O
entertained	O
by	O
my	O
st	O
d	O
rumming	O
upon	O
the	O
harpsichord	O
--	O
by	O
our	O
continual	O
eloges	O
of	O
Flora	O
--	O
&	O
by	O
Papa	O
s	O
wit	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
she	O
it	O
will	O
quite	O
break	O
her	O
heart	O
,	O
to	O
tear	O
herself	O
from	O
our	O
delightfull	O
society	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
only	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
soon	O
returning	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
wit	O
--	O
[	O
Is	O
how	O
much	O
in	O
Town	B-place
?	O
I	O
will	O
trouble	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
--	O
How	O
snug	O
we	O
are	O
--	O
My	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
Worthies	O
--	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
lately	O
in	O
the	O
Hotel	O
de	O
Ponthomme	O
or	O
conveyed	O
any	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
Pink	O
What	O
Nonsense	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
writing	O
--	O
My	O
--	O
only	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
--	O
]	O
we	O
underwritten	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
present	O
our	O
congratulations	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
tomorrow	O
--	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
G.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Rob	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
This	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
prelude	O
to	O
B-	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
comfortable	O
Letter	O
--	O
M.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Yo	O
.	O
all	O
the	O
Warts	O
upon	O
his	O
fingers	O
are	O
gone	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
more	O
comfortable	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
flatter	O
my	O
good	O
friends	O
by	O
praising	O
their	O
Wit	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
fail	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
presumption	O
to	O
suppose	O
I	O
should	O
succeed	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
You	O
then	O
in	O
plain	O
terms	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
day	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
reception	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
pleasant	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
resolve	O
to	O
ac̄ept	O
the	O
friendly	O
invitation	O
of	O
spending	O
some	O
time	O
here	O
after	O
my	O
Return	O
from	O
Derbyshire	B-place
.	O
I	O
hope	O
then	O
to	O
enjoy	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
paſsing	O
some	O
happy	O
hours	O
with	O
You	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
in	O
the	O
Yellow	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Your	O
Sister	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
feel	O
quite	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
provided	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
table	O
--	O
pen	O
&	O
Ink	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
B.G——	B-pers
yesterday	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
You	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
tooth	O
that	O
pains	O
You	O
drawn	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proper	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
use	O
laudanum	O
&	O
that	O
if	O
You	O
lost	O
rest	O
by	O
suffering	O
pain	O
it	O
might	O
bring	O
on	O
Your	O
old	O
complaints	O
--	O
think	O
of	O
this	O
&	O
be	O
advised	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
&	O
Mother	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
C	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
leave	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
return	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Sunday	O
Next	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
will	O
be	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Children	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
goes	O
into	O
Eſsex	B-place
--	O
they	O
will	O
stay	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
You	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
the	O
plan	O
of	O
our	O
intended	O
excursions	O
--	O
into	O
Yorkshire	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
You	O
before	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Ball	O
why	O
did	O
You	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
amuse	O
my	O
Charge	O
?	O
--	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
neglect	O
saying	O
something	O
for	O
me	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Curious	O
letter	O
of	O
scraps	O
Wednesday	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
prayers	O
are	O
just	O
over	O
&	O
I	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
opportunity	O
whilst	O
Hero	B-pers
is	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
to	O
add	O
another	O
line	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
sleepy	O
last	O
night	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
half	O
I	O
intended	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
a	O
full	O
account	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
Birth	O
day	O
&	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
were	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
heavenly	O
day	O
--	O
it	O
looks	O
gloomy	O
&	O
the	O
Skies	O
promise	O
rain	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
all	O
appear	O
in	O
spirits	O
&	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
health	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
tres	O
Chere	O
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
;	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
recd	O
.	O
Your	O
little	O
letter	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
