TOKEN	NE
9	O
OClock	O
Saturday	O
Evg	O
11	O
Feby	O
.	O
AD	O
1786	O
--	O
At	O
5	O
I	O
sent	O
of	O
a	O
frank	O
to	O
my	O
affectionate	O
Wife	O
inclosing	O
9	O
pages	O
of	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
diary	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
joint	O
L——	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s.	O
--	O
not	O
having	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
Account	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
&	O
finding	O
my	O
self	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
6	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
findg	O
her	O
extremely	O
chearful	O
,	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
giddineſs	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
bled	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
--	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
set	O
a	O
part	O
one	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
receive	O
their	O
Visits	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
16	O
people	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
Miſ	B-pers
-	I-pers
She	O
very	O
lively	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
you	O
could	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
we	O
talked	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
ye-	O
Royl	O
.	O
family	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
something	O
of	O
my	O
better	O
half	O
and	O
She	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
Vivacity	O
,	O
said	O
“	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
allow	O
that	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
good	O
hearts	O
perfectly	O
united	O
”	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
frequently	O
makes	O
enquiries	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
wants	O
to	O
know	O
“	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
happy	O
--	O
for	O
you	O
“	O
deserve	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
”	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
you	O
loved	O
Anecdotes	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
day	O
as	O
that	O
little	O
princeſs	O
Amelia	B-pers
was	O
dining	O
with	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
She	O
fixed	O
her	O
Eyes	O
upon	O
some	O
fish	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
's	O
Spirit	O
was	O
hurt	O
at	O
this	O
Refusal	O
--	O
&	O
turning	O
her	O
head	O
to	O
the	O
Attendants	O
--	O
“	O
here	O
(	O
said	O
she	O
)	O
take	O
this	O
fish	O
away	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
good	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
”	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
says	O
her	O
house	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
is	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Lodges	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
devotes	O
every	O
afternoon	O
to	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Commands	O
a	O
nd	O
desired	O
me	O
particularly	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
--	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
made	O
agreeable	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
their	O
majesties	O
laid	O
aside	O
all	O
restraint	O
&	O
form	O
--	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
shewn	O
great	O
civilities	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
--	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
--	O
who	O
seeing	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
at	O
their	O
exercise	O
,	O
run	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Kings	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
one	O
day	O
aſsisted	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
in	O
putting	O
on	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
was	O
light	O
&	O
warm	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
Q	O
.	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
&	O
presented	O
a	O
Cloak	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
I	O
almost	O
love	O
her	O
for	O
these	O
Attentions	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
so	O
dear	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
came	O
in	O
which	O
interupted	O
our	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
recollect	O
every	O
thing	O
yr-	O
dear	O
friend	O
says	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
made	O
many	O
Enquiries	O
abt-	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
if	O
I	O
shd	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
paſsing	O
thrō	O
Lincoln	B-place
Inn	I-place
fields	I-place
in	O
a	O
heavy	O
shower	O
of	O
rain	O
,	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
find	O
a	O
welcome	O
shelter	O
under	O
his	O
Roof	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
bow	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
run	O
over	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
and	O
had	O
the	O
happineſs	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
interrupted	O
my	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
Sunday	O
--	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
this	O
morning	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
s	O
--	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
prosaick	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
delicate	O
Situation	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
introduced	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
he	O
soon	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
busineſs	O
--	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
warm	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
appeased	O
his	O
wrath	O
by	O
telling	O
him	O
yt	O
.	O
no	O
person	O
had	O
any	O
demand	O
against	O
him	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
£	O
5	O
.	O
&	O
she	O
prevented	O
Kinder	B-pers
from	O
reading	O
ye-	O
body	O
of	O
her	O
second	O
Letter	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
K——	I-pers
said	O
the	O
whole	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
artfully	O
contrived	O
&	O
he	O
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Letter	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
Andrew	B-pers
Freece	I-pers
--	O
wh	O
en	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
write	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
hesitate	O
&	O
said	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wis	O
hed	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
really	O
wd	O
.	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
ha	O
d	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Objection	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Butler	O
was	O
a	O
confidential	O
one	O
&	O
therefore	O
every	O
neceſsary	O
information	O
