TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
July	O
26	O
1773	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
very	O
obligeing	O
Letter	O
found	O
me	O
at	O
Schaw	O
Park	O
as	O
did	O
yours	O
to	O
yr	O
Guardian	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
has	O
prevented	O
me	O
&	O
still	O
does	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
durst	O
travel	O
came	O
down	O
here	O
&	O
got	O
to	O
Schaw	O
Park	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Ilneſs	O
arrived	O
to	O
Us	O
there	O
--	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
ever	O
since	O
been	O
greatly	O
an	O
Invallid	O
--	O
for	O
some	O
hours	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
danger	O
&	O
we	O
,	O
obliged	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
another	O
Physician	O
to	O
aſsist	O
the	O
one	O
we	O
comonly	O
employ	O
thank	O
God	O
their	O
Endevours	O
succeeded	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
not	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
b	O
ut	O
getting	O
gradually	O
well	O
--	O
only	O
not	O
yet	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
L	O
etters	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
Visitts	O
.	O
as	O
we	O
knew	O
yr	O
.	O
goodness	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
would	O
lead	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
Anxious	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
t	O
his	O
Intelligence	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
prefferance	O
to	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
great	O
title	O
to	O
expect	O
it	O
.	O
Buxton	B-place
raised	O
the	O
Gouty	O
Matter	O
&	O
sett	O
it	O
affloat	O
:	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
powerful	O
enough	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Extreamity	O
's	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
tormented	O
him	O
in	O
different	O
shapes	O
.	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
or	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
all	O
yr	O
kind	O
attentions	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
for	O
the	O
fire	O
Screen	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
I	O
prize	O
it	O
greatly	O
as	O
it	O
deserves	O
for	O
its	O
beauty	O
but	O
Infinatly	O
more	O
so	O
for	O
being	O
yr	O
Work	O
&	O
heartily	O
wish	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Oportunity	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
you	O
here	O
--	O
.	O
Our	O
Races	O
are	O
just	O
over	O
&	O
have	O
I	O
bellieve	O
been	O
very	O
Briliant	O
but	O
as	O
my	O
Ld	O
was	O
confined	O
till	O
the	O
very	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
till	O
that	O
day	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Air	O
that	O
lenth	O
wt	O
me	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
from	O
Schaw	O
Park	O
were	O
here	O
with	O
My	O
Br	O
:	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
Amusements	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
&	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
aprovenapproven	O
of	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
&	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
remembred	O
with	O
Affection	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
whenever	O
I	O
write	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
&	O
yr	O
Young	O
friends	O
here	O
join	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
request	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
very	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
much	O
Obliged	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
My	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
Ld	O
will	O
write	O
whenever	O
he	O
is	O
able	O
--	O
mean	O
time	O
be	O
as	O
easy	O
about	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Physicians	O
now	O
are	O
.	O
