TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Tho	O
'	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
in	O
Her	O
great	O
Indulgence	O
&	O
Condescension	O
has	O
forbid	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
duty	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
easy	O
without	O
making	O
this	O
Inquiry	O
after	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Humble	O
duty	O
&	O
acknowledgements	O
for	O
the	O
Honour	O
they	O
did	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
attempted	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
expreſs	O
her	O
gratefull	O
acknowledgements	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
magnificent	O
present	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
did	O
her	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
bestow	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
is	O
miserable	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Eyes	O
fail	O
her	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
gratifye	O
her	O
sensibility	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
think	O
nothing	O
nothing	O
can	O
exceed	O
her	O
gratitude	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
delighted	O
!	O
with	O
the	O
Elegance	O
&	O
taste	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
&	O
it	O
's	O
contents	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
her	O
Eyes	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
overcome	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
such	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
high	O
Honour	O
&	O
great	O
Condescension	O
of	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
;	O
which	O
she	O
shall	O
ever	O
esteem	O
as	O
a	O
Treasure	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
very	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
place	O
&	O
her	O
kind	O
love	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
Obliged	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
MC	B-pers
:	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Bullstrode	O
Decber	O
16	O
th	O
1781	O
I	O
am	O
ashamed	O
of	O
the	O
Blunder	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
Birthday	O
is	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
of	O
May	O
