TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
the	O
most	O
bitter	O
regret	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
impending	O
calamity	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
where	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
hand	O
to	O
have	O
administerd	O
in	O
person	O
every	O
poſsible	O
consolation	O
to	O
the	O
supreme	O
object	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
my	O
parting	O
embrace	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
afflicting	O
situation	O
,	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
coud	O
answer	O
every	O
neceſsary	O
object	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
shock	O
'd	O
to	O
perceive	O
that	O
her	O
medical	O
assistants	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
received	O
regular	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
their	O
attendance	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
supposed	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
sufficient	O
fund	O
in	O
my	O
dear	O
Daughter	O
's	O
hands	O
under	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
who	O
it	O
seems	O
was	O
her	O
Cash	O
keeper	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
referrd	O
you	O
to	O
answer	O
every	O
exigence	O
that	O
might	O
occur	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
fresh	O
supply	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
has	O
hitherto	O
largely	O
anticipated	O
her	O
wants	O
;	O
where	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
confusion	O
her	O
Physicians	O
have	O
been	O
left	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
conclusions	O
from	O
whence	O
their	O
remuneration	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
therefore	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
inform	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
respects	O
that	O
due	O
attention	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
that	O
object	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
Daughter	O
has	O
been	O
suddenly	O
struck	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Providence	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
prevented	O
from	O
communicating	O
her	O
neceſsities	O
to	O
me	O
shoud	O
any	O
have	O
really	O
existed	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
felt	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
anticipating	O
her	O
wants	O
.	O
Mann	B-pers
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
communicated	O
to	O
you	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hands	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
had	O
she	O
done	O
this	O
a	O
supply	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
answer	O
'd	O
every	O
purpose	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
particular	O
desire	O
that	O
every	O
medical	O
expence	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
forthwith	O
accounted	O
for	O
according	O
to	O
each	O
Person	O
's	O
attendance	O
.	O
It	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
inconvenience	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
perceive	O
the	O
money	O
can	O
be	O
remitted	O
at	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
notice	O
.	O
So	O
sudden	O
a	O
demand	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
foreseen	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
can	O
not	O
reproach	O
myself	O
with	O
having	O
neglected	O
my	O
dear	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
render	O
'd	O
doubly	O
so	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
misfortunes	O
she	O
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
favor	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
call	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
from	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
before	O
you	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
s	O
cash	O
Acct	O
.	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
to	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Balance	O
into	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
high	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
integrity	O
,	O
yet	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
confidence	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
knew	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recommend	O
;	O
her	O
argument	O
was	O
the	O
trifling	O
advantage	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
interest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
negotiated	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
circumstance	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
,	O
my	O
poor	O
Daughter	O
was	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
accurate	O
in	O
keeping	O
an	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
&	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
on	O
my	O
remonstrating	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
her	O
fault	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
perfect	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Your	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
heart	O
has	O
drawn	O
upon	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
more	O
trouble	O
than	O
you	O
were	O
aware	O
of	O
;	O
proceed	O
I	O
intreat	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Tragedy	O
,	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
owe	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
my	O
obligations	O
to	O
no	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
volunteer	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
ever	O
since	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
the	O
pleasing	O
reflexion	O
that	O
I	O
acquitted	O
myself	O
with	O
propriety	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
you	O
can	O
never	O
fail	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
guided	O
by	O
that	O
heavenly	O
maxim	O
do	O
as	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
woud	O
hardly	O
give	O
credit	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
horrid	O
treatment	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
guarded	O
against	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
capable	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
bad	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
showing	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
by	O
laying	O
claim	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
s	O
property	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
no	O
longer	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
may	O
lay	O
a	O
legal	O
claim	O
to	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
oppose	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
will	O
make	O
but	O
a	O
feeble	O
opposition	O
to	O
his	O
violence	O
&	O
shoud	O
avoid	O
all	O
intercourse	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
obliged	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
May	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
surprised	O
by	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
as	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
my	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
had	O
plenty	O
of	O
money	O
--	O
Somebody	O
must	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
J.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
May	O
30	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
