TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Febry-	O
1803	O
Most	O
unreasonable	O
Sister	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
really	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
old	O
Frumps	O
?	O
Your	O
Ld=	B-pers
N	I-pers
's	O
,	O
&	O
your	O
Harpur	B-pers
's	O
,	O
are	O
alive	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
know	O
neither	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
second	O
question	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
Garrick	B-pers
injustice	O
,	O
for	O
really	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
either	O
about	O
You	O
,	O
or	O
Yours	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
perfectly	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Princeſses	O
often	O
talk	O
of	O
You	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
(	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
right	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
probable	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
think	O
of	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
about	O
replying	O
to	O
her	O
acknowledgment	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Your	O
Counteſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
is	O
hobbling	O
about	O
like	O
an	O
old	O
Gander	O
.	O
He	O
affected	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
exactly	O
where	O
You	O
lived	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
visited	O
You	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
conversation	O
concluded	O
with	O
his	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Leighton	O
House	O
.	O
Uncle	B-pers
Sir	I-pers
William	I-pers
(	O
Kenwood	B-place
)	O
is	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
produce	O
an	O
Heir	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Drummond	I-pers
looks	O
as	O
like	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
is	O
grown	O
very	O
fat	O
.	O
Your	O
Sentiments	O
and	O
mine	O
,	O
about	O
Town	O
Residences	O
,	O
exactly	O
agree	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
remained	O
with	O
My	O
Mamma	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
mutual	O
torments	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
Board	O
,	O
Coals	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
gratified	O
her	O
Servants	O
,	O
I	O
suspect	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
much	O
œconomy	O
in	O
the	O
Plan	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
my	O
own	O
whims	O
--	O
in	O
Somerset	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
given	O
way	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
Hers	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
Forty	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
my	O
Age	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
Lent	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
proper	O
will	O
the	O
opportunity	O
be	O
of	O
bewailing	O
my	O
Iniquities	O
;	O
and	O
resolving	O
to	O
amend	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
are	O
Ten	O
years	O
older	O
than	O
Me	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
high	O
time	O
that	O
You	O
should	O
set	O
about	O
your	O
Reformation	O
too	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
delay	O
it	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
&	O
Robert	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
Boots	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
,	O
have	O
hardly	O
been	O
dry	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Ground	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
soft	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
favourite	O
amusement	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
him	O
good	O
Sport	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
's	O
very	O
Affectionately	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
has	O
had	O
some	O
good	O
Apples	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
Comiſsion	O
about	O
Napier	B-pers
's	O
Ware	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
i	O
it	O
?	O
Rib	O
&	O
Brats	O
at	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
Letters	O
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Third	O
Febry-	O
1803	O
Wedgewood	B-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
