TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Decr-	O
1791	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Was	O
you	O
born	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
?	O
Did	O
You	O
ever	O
dip	O
in	O
the	O
Shannon	O
?	O
Resolve	O
me	O
these	O
questions	O
speedily	O
,	O
for	O
till	O
You	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
remain	O
lost	O
in	O
wonderment	O
&	O
astoundation	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
that	O
humble	O
,	O
penitential	O
acknowledgement	O
of	O
your	O
Negligence	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
my	O
uncommon	O
condescension	O
in	O
writing	O
a	O
Second	O
Letter	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Page	O
of	O
your	O
Folio	O
Epistle	O
contains	O
a	O
downright	O
attack	O
on	O
Me	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
expectation	O
of	O
my	O
falling	O
on	O
my	O
Marrow	O
Bones	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
we	O
may	O
chance	O
to	O
meet	O
.	O
Luckily	O
,	O
a	O
Snow	O
Storm	O
&	O
an	O
Empty	O
Purse	O
,	O
are	O
two	O
strong	O
Motives	O
for	O
remaining	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
otherwise	O
have	O
been	O
tempted	O
,	O
instantly	O
to	O
have	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
You	O
in	O
Person	O
.	O
Be	O
aſsured	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
want	O
of	O
inclination	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
above	O
mentioned	O
Causes	O
&	O
my	O
well	O
known	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Moderation	O
,	O
that	O
prevent	O
my	O
taking	O
my	O
Revenge	O
,	O
by	O
transporting	O
myself	O
&	O
Family	O
to	O
eat	O
You	O
out	O
of	O
House	O
&	O
Home	O
this	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Think	O
of	O
the	O
punishment	O
You	O
have	O
escaped	O
,	O
&	O
let	O
the	O
terrifying	O
Nature	O
of	O
it	O
sink	O
so	O
deep	O
into	O
your	O
Memory	O
as	O
to	O
work	O
a	O
complete	O
Reformation	O
&	O
Amendment	O
in	O
your	O
manners	O
.	O
And	O
beware	O
of	O
forcing	O
Me	O
,	O
to	O
vent	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Gall	O
&	O
Spleen	O
on	O
You	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
divers	O
croſs	O
&	O
diabolical	O
machinations	O
of	O
my	O
Enemies	O
,	O
have	O
caused	O
to	O
arise	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
discompose	O
the	O
amiable	O
gentleneſs	O
of	O
my	O
disposition	O
.	O
Having	O
said	O
so	O
much	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
caution	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
a	O
stop	O
in	O
my	O
Exhortations	O
,	O
to	O
allow	O
You	O
proper	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
reflect	O
seriously	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
enormity	O
of	O
your	O
Effrontery	O
&	O
Presumption	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
pleased	O
to	O
refer	O
Me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Why	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
But	O
be	O
it	O
known	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
entertain	O
too	O
high	O
an	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Dignity	O
&	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
&	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Family	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
so	O
groſs	O
an	O
Affront	O
on	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
suppose	O
him	O
bound	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
a	O
Wife	O
's	O
Lazineſs	O
or	O
Inattention	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
positively	O
command	O
You	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
own	O
proper	O
submiſsion	O
&	O
Apology	O
under	O
your	O
own	O
proper	O
signature	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
You	O
was	O
so	O
conscious	O
of	O
the	O
Arrogance	O
of	O
your	O
last	O
Letter	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
sent	O
it	O
away	O
without	O
date	O
or	O
name	O
affixed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
page	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
has	O
,	O
“	O
Taxal	B-place
Novr	O
1791	O
”	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
Page	O
appears	O
“	O
Decr	O
.	O
4	O
--	O
1791	O
”	O
--	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
these	O
can	O
be	O
esteemed	O
legal	O
dates	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
entirely	O
drive	O
You	O
to	O
Despair	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
condescend	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
whenever	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
either	O
bring	O
or	O
send	O
You	O
here	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
be	O
received	O
with	O
decent	O
affection	O
&	O
treated	O
with	O
a	O
tolerable	O
share	O
of	O
kindneſs	O
.	O
The	O
sooner	O
you	O
make	O
your	O
appearance	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
convinced	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
of	O
your	O
Contrition	O
,	O
and	O
really	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
bring	O
You	O
here	O
without	O
loſs	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
suspect	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
sharp	O
Rebuke	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
We	O
wont	O
starve	O
You	O
,	O
for	O
be	O
it	O
known	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
now	O
kill	O
all	O
our	O
own	O
Meat	O
.	O
Excellent	O
Mutton	O
,	O
Admirable	O
Highland	O
Beef	O
,	O
Delicate	O
Chinese	O
Pork	O
,	O
&	O
delicious	O
Poultry	O
of	O
all	O
kinds	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
pity	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Chevalier	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
did	O
not	O
stray	O
as	O
far	O
North	O
as	O
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
fancy	O
for	O
my	O
Sister	O
Harriot	B-pers
,	O
&	O
so	O
removed	O
the	O
probability	O
,	O
which	O
now	O
attends	O
her	O
,	O
of	O
leading	O
Apes	O
,	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
fortunate	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
the	O
vexation	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
inclination	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
given	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
of	O
your	O
Engaging	O
,	O
Charming	O
Emma	B-pers
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
,	O
except	O
having	O
heard	O
,	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
married	O
a	O
Young	O
,	O
beautiful	O
woman	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
musical	O
disposition	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
the	O
illnatured	O
world	O
suspected	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
a	O
footing	O
of	O
intimacy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
their	O
Nuptials	O
.	O
Not	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Noble	O
K	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
as	O
accountable	O
to	O
Me	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
actions	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
enquired	O
further	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
receive	O
any	O
communication	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
subject	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
profound	O
Attention	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
flatter	O
yourself	O
with	O
my	O
good	O
wishes	O
&	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
Rib	O
.	O
Love	O
&	O
affection	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Brat	O
.	O
My	O
Brats	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
,	O
denominated	O
Sophia	B-pers
.	O
All	O
this	O
from	O
Your	O
Affece	O
.	O
Brother	O
,	O
till	O
Death	O
,	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Hawick	B-place
Thirteenth	O
Decr=	O
1791	O
.	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
HAWICK	B-place
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
by	O
Derby	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
