TOKEN	NE
Ipswich	B-place
July	O
ye	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
Yours	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
inst	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
inclosed	O
for	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
came	O
safe	O
to	O
hand	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
usual	O
punctually	O
in	O
money	O
matters	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
Hint	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
when	O
he	O
was	O
last	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
this	O
purpose	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
it	O
much	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
and	O
cou	O
'd	O
I	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
visit	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
make	O
any	O
where	O
that	O
woud	O
make	O
me	O
half	O
so	O
happy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
defer	O
that	O
satisfaction	O
untill	O
another	O
opportunity	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
concerned	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
your	O
old	O
Complaint	O
is	O
still	O
troublesome	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
flattered	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
the	O
good	O
airs	O
of	O
Northampton	B-place
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
prevented	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
the	O
frequent	O
returns	O
of	O
that	O
disagreeable	O
disorder	O
.	O
I	O
conclude	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Contrary	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Neice	O
are	O
well	O
;	O
you	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
most	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
for	O
your	O
Healths	O
and	O
happineſs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
me	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
Sister	O
and	O
much	O
obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
R.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Betty	B-pers
who	O
often	O
talks	O
of	O
her	O
good	O
uncle	O
,	O
aunt	O
and	O
Cousin	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Love	O
.	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Northampton	B-place
By	O
London	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Hon	B-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
fm	O
Ipswich	O
July	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1768	O
