TOKEN	NE
Last	O
Wenneſs-day	O
William	B-pers
returned	O
home	O
from	O
Portsmouth	B-place
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
better	O
&	O
will	O
continue	O
so	O
.	O
Augusta	B-pers
and	I-pers
me	I-pers
have	O
got	O
a	O
deliteful	O
house	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
lower	O
Loge	O
the	O
room	O
's	O
are	O
delitteful	O
and	O
very	O
pleasant	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
them	O
soon	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
thunder	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
hear	O
.	O
Mama	O
has	O
read	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
fine	O
sermon	O
.	O
&	O
two	O
very	O
Pretty	O
Spectators	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
yours	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
.	O
