TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
--	I-place
Wells	I-place
.	O
May	O
21	O
--	O
1789	O
--	O
Dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
You	O
your	O
Seven	O
obliging	O
Packets	O
which	O
I	O
recieved	O
here	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
acknowleged	O
more	O
immediately	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
waiting	O
for	O
some	O
information	O
from	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
about	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
You	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
your	O
particular	O
enquiries	O
.	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
I——	I-pers
writes	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
constantly	O
,	O
yet	O
She	O
neglects	O
answering	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
point	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
therefore	O
hope	O
She	O
may	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
You	O
herself	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
now	O
confide	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Sources	O
of	O
Facts	O
&	O
Ideas	O
,	O
scarce	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
wait	O
longer	O
&	O
appear	O
ungrateful	O
.	O
Pray	O
view	O
my	O
Paper	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
on	O
several	O
accounts	O
remarkable	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
size	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
a	O
Folio	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
credit	O
for	O
undertaking	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
enclose	O
You	O
a	O
Letter	O
I	O
recieved	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
ago	O
from	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
Mr-	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Wherwell	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
his	O
Sonnets	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
take	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
You	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Copies	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
his	O
“	O
Riddle	O
of	O
a	O
serious	O
cast	O
,	O
a	O
counterpart	O
to	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Sigh	O
”	O
is	O
amongst	O
those	O
You	O
sent	O
me	O
?	O
otherwise	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
You	O
will	O
indulge	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
Solution	O
of	O
the	O
french	O
Riddles	O
I	O
return	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
ventured	O
to	O
copy	O
out	O
those	O
on	O
the	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
that	O
contane	O
so	O
many	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
clearly	O
know	O
whether	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
end	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Page	O
&	O
are	O
seperate	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
suspect	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Page	O
is	O
distinct	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
means	O
to	O
describe	O
Silence	O
.	O
If	O
You	O
will	O
correct	O
me	O
in	O
these	O
particulars	O
,	O
&	O
lend	O
me	O
them	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
thank	O
You	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
like	O
to	O
add	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Collection	O
.	O
the	O
other	O
few	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
all	O
that	O
remain	O
from	O
any	O
hoards	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
trouble	O
Yourself	O
ever	O
to	O
return	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
shall	O
make	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Packets	O
of	O
Today	O
;	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
Your	O
's	O
I	O
shall	O
beg	O
to	O
delay	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
.	O
The	O
Cenotaph	O
Inscription	O
which	O
I	O
enclose	O
You	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
strikingly	O
pretty	O
in	O
it	O
's	O
Mind	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
time	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
my	O
Letter	O
from	O
these	O
Wells	O
,	O
which	O
perhaps	O
has	O
surprised	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
friend	O
Louisa	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
state	O
of	O
Health	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
anxiety	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
ordered	O
by	O
Sr-	B-pers
G——	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
to	O
try	O
this	O
air	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
You	O
know	O
her	O
admirable	O
&	O
tender	O
attachment	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
cruel	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
seperation	O
under	O
the	O
circumstances	O
too	O
of	O
weak	O
Health	O
&	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
neceſsarily	O
detaned	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
Town	B-place
,	O
on	O
Family	O
Busineſs	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
disagreable	O
Nature	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
wonder	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Sister	O
You	O
enquire	O
after	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
become	O
the	O
companion	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
habits	O
of	O
intimacy	O
between	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
me	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
far	O
more	O
those	O
of	O
Sisters	O
&	O
Friends	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
office	O
I	O
therefore	O
naturally	O
felt	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
recover	O
very	O
eſsentially	O
,	O
of	O
paſsing	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
exactly	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
I	O
like	O
best	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
beautiful	O
country	O
which	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
suits	O
both	O
our	O
Tastes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
visited	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Yearsley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
not	O
yet	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Chatterton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
former	O
told	O
me	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
lately	O
writing	O
4	O
Tragedies	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
one	O
,	O
entitled	O
Goodwin	O
would	O
very	O
soon	O
come	O
forth	O
on	O
the	O
Bristol	B-place
Stage	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Diffidence	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
expressions	O
at	O
my	O
first	O
conversing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tho't	O
I	O
soon	O
percieved	O
great	O
want	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
She	O
condemned	O
all	O
our	O
Poets	O
,	O
without	O
discrimination	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
done	O
justice	O
to	O
the	O
female	O
Character	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
She	O
could	O
have	O
represented	O
Elfrida	O
in	O
better	O
colors	O
than	O
Mason	B-pers
did	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
friends	O
&	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
had	O
interfered	O
between	O
them	O
improperly	O
&	O
did	O
mischief	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
now	O
be	O
rectified	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
still	O
spoke	O
handsomely	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
yet	O
she	O
seemed	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Self-satisfied	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
feel	O
the	O
coolneſs	O
,	O
or	O
betray	O
those	O
marks	O
of	O
zeal	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
understood	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
better	O
impreſsion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
Lord	B-pers
De	I-pers
Clifford	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Blaize	O
Castle	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
expedition	O
we	O
have	O
made	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
,	O
since	O
my	O
friend	O
's	O
amendment	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
able	O
to	O
enjoy	O
;	O
&	O
We	O
are	O
quite	O
Enthusiasts	O
for	O
Prospects	O
such	O
as	O
we	O
beheld	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Latter	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
smaller	O
style	O
of	O
Elegance	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
partial	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
is	O
most	O
apt	O
to	O
excite	O
my	O
Envy	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
inclined	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
situated	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
beautiful	O
Scenery	O
,	O
contributes	O
a	O
full	O
half	O
towards	O
the	O
Happineſs	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
effect	O
it	O
has	O
on	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
of	O
enlarging	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
even	O
give	O
ideas	O
;	O
&	O
of	O
tranquilising	O
the	O
Spirits	O
.	O
I	O
enjoy	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
us	O
here	O
,	O
these	O
sublime	O
Rocks	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
fine	O
rich	O
contrast	O
in	O
Somersetshire	B-place
,	O
around	O
the	O
pretty	O
Village	O
of	O
ashton	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
walked	O
one	O
Morning	O
while	O
Louisa	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
rode	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
double	O
Horse	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
will	O
dismiſs	O
You	O
from	O
a	O
Country	O
I	O
believe	O
You	O
are	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
;	O
&	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
may	O
serve	O
to	O
convince	O
You	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
incapable	O
of	O
entering	O
with	O
You	O
into	O
all	O
the	O
Delights	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
abound	O
around	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
if	O
I	O
recollect	O
arightly	O
what	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
where	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
on	O
any	O
account	O
interrupt	O
Mr.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
aſsiduous	O
Pursuits	O
in	O
Grove	O
or	O
Kitchen-garden	O
,	O
directed	O
I	O
suppose	O
in	O
turn	O
to	O
Pleasure	O
&	O
Utility	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
wherwell	B-place
I	O
could	O
discern	O
some	O
traits	O
of	O
his	O
Activity	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
his	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
heart	O
,	O
whenever	O
the	O
Gran	O
pa	O
of	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
or	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
were	O
in	O
question	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
You	O
will	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
record	O
this	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
You	O
will	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
return	O
for	O
his	O
french	O
Songs	O
&	O
his	O
Love	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
time	O
at	O
this	O
season	O
for	O
singing	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
the	O
leſs	O
scruple	O
keeping	O
the	O
Songs	O
till	O
I	O
return	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
hence	O
to	O
Wherwell	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Musick	O
Book	O
,	O
into	O
which	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
introduce	O
them	O
.	O
Neither	O
my	O
friend	O
or	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
we	O
covet	O
it	O
;	O
It	O
is	O
reckoned	O
full	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
list	O
hardly	O
that	O
we	O
know	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
3	O
genteel	O
looking	O
Girls	O
here	O
,	O
Miſs	O
Suttons	O
the	O
Daughters	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Manners	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
pleasing	O
looking	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
marry	O
the	O
eldest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Meynell	I-pers
is	O
marrid	O
,	O
&	O
gone	O
with	O
Mari	O
&	O
Mother	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
of	O
Dashwoods	O
into	O
Switzerland	B-place
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Lord	B-pers
Lesley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
near	O
10	O
years	O
Younger	O
than	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
does	O
not	O
much	O
approve	O
,	O
but	O
means	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
is	O
lively	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
kept	O
very	O
much	O
constraned	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
I	O
suspect	O
now	O
dash	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
The	O
youngest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Mr-	B-pers
Desbrough	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
;	O
&	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Villiers	I-pers
's	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Tichfield	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
W.	I-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
.	O
--	O
My	O
little	O
new	O
Reading	O
came	O
out	O
during	O
the	O
Winter	O
.	O
You	O
probably	O
know	O
that	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
Sonnets	O
are	O
come	O
forth	O
with	O
their	O
additions	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
yet	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
edition	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Wherwell	B-place
,	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Library	O
here	O
of	O
so	O
very	O
Trumpery	O
a	O
sort	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
subscribe	O
to	O
Bulls	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
instead	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
our	O
Books	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Have	O
You	O
met	O
with	O
“	O
Voyages	O
d'Anacharsis	O
en	O
Gréce	O
?	O
”	O
lately	O
come	O
out	O
?	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
I——	I-pers
mentions	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
letters	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
reading	O
with	O
great	O
delight	O
the	O
Botanical	O
Garden	O
or	O
Loves	O
of	O
the	O
Plants	O
.	O
Dearest	O
Mrs-	B-pers
I——	I-pers
(	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
love	O
&	O
respect	O
her	O
)	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
this	O
Winter	O
in	O
quite	O
the	O
comfortable	O
health	O
her	O
best	O
friends	O
must	O
wish	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
appeared	O
extremely	O
relaxed	O
,	O
&	O
complaned	O
much	O
of	O
feeling	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
given	O
herself	O
more	O
up	O
to	O
Indolence	O
,	O
than	O
with	O
her	O
Constitution	O
I	O
fear	O
is	O
advisable	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
blooded	O
too	O
for	O
Giddineſs	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
better	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
such	O
a	O
Character	O
is	O
subject	O
to	O
such	O
disorders	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
one	O
particularly	O
solicitous	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Father	O
also	O
had	O
very	O
severe	O
attacks	O
of	O
Cold	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
start	O
from	O
Town	B-place
so	O
soon	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
some	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Shades	O
of	O
Harewood	O
.	O
Little	B-pers
Catha	I-pers
'	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
tolerably	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Walnut	O
Season	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
so	O
ingeniously	O
practised	O
a	O
little	O
fineſse	O
to	O
taste	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
effects	O
soon	O
shew	O
'd	O
themselves	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
attributing	O
all	O
the	O
pale	O
looks	O
which	O
gave	O
You	O
alarm	O
;	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
entre	O
Nous	O
,	O
Vous	O
&	O
Moi	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
let	O
You	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
truly	O
interested	O
You	O
was	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
coughs	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
that	O
have	O
lasted	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
longer	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
lively	O
&	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
grows	O
tall	O
&	O
thin	O
.	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
wish	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
your	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
breadth	O
;	O
pray	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
“	O
petit	O
Baiser	O
”	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
And	O
thus	O
far	O
have	O
I	O
gained	O
upon	O
my	O
paper	O
without	O
one	O
Word	O
of	O
the	O
Royals	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
may	O
surprise	O
You	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
scarcely	O
wonder	O
at	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
By	O
this	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
insinuate	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
interested	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
what	O
You	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
agree	O
is	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
shocking	O
Reports	O
&	O
Nonsense	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
Party	O
;	O
the	O
warmth	O
&	O
Contradictions	O
of	O
each	O
,	O
in	O
every	O
Company	O
one	O
went	O
into	O
was	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
,	O
&	O
really	O
fatiguing	O
.	O
I	O
liked	O
the	O
Illuminations	O
exceſsively	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
driving	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
letters	O
even	O
from	O
impartial	O
People	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
that	O
the	B-pers
K——	I-pers
is	O
debilitated	O
really	O
almost	O
to	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
Idiotism	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
live	O
long	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
tell	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
observations	O
I	O
can	O
make	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
inference	O
I	O
can	O
draw	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
hear	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
fate	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
when	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
quarrel	O
between	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Lennox	I-pers
,	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
intended	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
quit	O
the	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
As	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
diſsipated	O
life	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
I	O
led	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
one	O
amongst	O
particular	O
friends	O
it	O
may	O
apologise	O
for	O
the	O
little	O
News	O
I	O
send	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
often	O
.	O
Your	O
's	O
sincerely	O
E.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
--	O
