TOKEN	NE
Albemarle	O
Street	O
March	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Ten	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
comfortable	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
inform	O
'd	O
us	O
that	O
your	O
excellent	O
husband	O
was	O
arrived	O
safe	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
suffer	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
from	O
the	O
strain	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
both	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
good	O
Brother	O
s	O
kind	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
regard	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
tell	O
him	O
his	O
joy	O
at	O
seeing	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
has	O
made	O
him	O
very	O
absent	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
directs	O
his	O
letter	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
the	O
fifth	O
;	O
Be	O
not	O
uneasy	O
my	O
kind	O
friend	O
about	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
sometimes	O
complaining	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
this	O
cold	O
weather	O
agrees	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
when	O
settled	O
weather	O
comes	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
recover	O
my	O
health	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
elegant	O
&	O
polite	O
party	O
,	O
The	B-pers
Duchess	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
&	O
two	O
neices	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
Sr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
seventy	O
people	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
were	O
the	O
only	O
singers	O
,	O
the	O
Former	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
taste	O
&	O
elegance	O
,	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
pretty	O
She	O
sung	O
divinely	O
,	O
she	O
this	O
year	O
far	O
exceeds	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
their	O
were	O
five	O
instrumental	O
performers	O
,	O
One	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
his	O
name	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
pleasing	O
agreeable	O
&	O
rather	O
a	O
handsome	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
Story	O
of	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
must	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
,	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
(	O
perhaps	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
)	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Holland	B-place
to	O
follow	O
his	O
pro	O
ff	O
f	O
eſsion	O
as	O
a	O
Musician	O
when	O
there	O
a	O
Lady	O
of	O
family	O
&	O
great	O
fortune	O
fell	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
made	O
proposals	O
of	O
marriage	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
up	O
his	O
prof	O
f	O
eſsion	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
when	O
she	O
fell	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
&	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
during	O
her	O
illneſs	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
will	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
leaves	O
him	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
considerable	O
indeed	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
buried	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
all	O
her	O
relations	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
who	O
though	O
people	O
of	O
fash	O
i	O
on	O
in	O
Holland	B-place
were	O
very	O
poor	O
)	O
he	O
read	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
he	O
divided	O
every	O
thing	O
equa	O
lly	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
keeping	O
for	O
himself	O
£200	O
a	O
year	O
a	O
diamond	O
and	O
another	O
ring	O
&	O
her	O
picture	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
England	B-place
to	O
follow	O
his	O
profeſsion	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
careſs	O
'd	O
&	O
noticed	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
great	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
true	O
&	O
real	O
generosity	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
read	O
or	O
heard	O
off	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
my	O
Brother	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
card	O
player	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
party	O
at	O
cards	O
for	O
Sunday	O
sevennight	O
The	O
answer	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
wait	O
on	O
the	O
Lady	O
on	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
..	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
cards	O
on	O
a	O
sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
highly	O
improper	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
person	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
my	O
answer	O
was	O
proper	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
which	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
surprised	O
at	O
,	O
a	O
thought	O
came	O
acroſs	O
me	O
yesterday	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
communicate	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
ask	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cartar	I-pers
s	O
op	O
p	O
inion	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
remarkably	O
clever	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
trust	O
to	O
her	O
Judgement	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
's	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
always	O
consult	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
take	O
any	O
new	O
steps	O
,	O
therefore	O
after	O
you	O
have	O
thought	O
seriou	O
s	O
ly	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
write	O
me	O
word	O
what	O
yr	O
op	O
p	O
inion	O
is	O
.	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
here	O
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
looks	O
rather	O
thin	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
Sally	B-pers
has	O
call	O
'd	O
here	O
,	O
She	O
wishes	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
place	O
now	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
long	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
Indeed	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
had	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
&	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
answer	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
will	O
wait	O
for	O
Your	O
answer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Grimwoods	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
&	O
english	O
Gorze	O
or	O
furze	O
Seed	O
is	O
two	O
&	O
nine	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
but	O
if	O
any	O
quantity	O
is	O
wanted	O
two	O
&	O
six	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
spoke	O
as	O
every	O
body	O
else	O
does	O
well	O
of	O
your	O
good	O
man	O
.	O
Tell	O
him	O
we	O
miſs	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
.	O
To	O
morrow	O
seven-night	O
I	O
am	O
engaged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Fitzherbert	I-pers
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
I	O
remain	O
yours	O
unalterably	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
inclose	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
silk	O
,	O
pray	O
present	O
our	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
My	O
pen	O
paper	O
&	O
ink	O
must	O
be	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
this	O
scrawl	O
