TOKEN	NE
Liverpool	B-place
16	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1794	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
here	O
the	O
first	O
Week	O
in	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
remain	O
a	O
fixture	O
here	O
till	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
important	O
reasons	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
my	B-pers
Son	I-pers
to	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Kittens	O
while	O
the	O
Old	O
Cat	O
is	O
adding	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
in	O
yesterday	O
with	O
a	O
Company	O
from	O
Manchester	B-place
,	O
with	O
whom	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
.	O
Furious	O
Republicans	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
not	O
enrolled	O
in	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
your	O
friends	O
.	O
A	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Elis	I-pers
.	I-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
best	O
affections	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
very	O
faithfully	O
and	O
Sincerely	O
Napier	B-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
1794	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchester	B-place
