TOKEN	NE
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
your	O
little	O
note	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Accapulco	B-place
.	O
--	O
ju	O
g	O
d	O
ge	O
judge	O
how	O
miserable	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
seeing	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
Eldest	O
Pſs	O
's	O
.	O
,	O
ye	O
:	O
others	O
come	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
after	O
with	O
Elise	B-pers
.	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Note	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
kept	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
&	O
entirely	O
forgot	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
--	O
My	O
God	O
wt	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
give	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
nurse	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
You	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
Adieu	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
Your	O
Miranda	B-pers
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
your	O
head	O
does	O
&	O
Your	O
Cough	O
3	O
d	O
June	O
1781	O
Osyris	B-pers
&	O
Rhea	B-pers
ask	O
'd	O
after	O
you	O
last	O
Night	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
ym	O
.	O
of	O
Yor	O
distreſs	O
's	O
Rhea	B-pers
said	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
send	O
to	O
yo	O
.	O
about	O
yor	O
.	O
not	O
coming	O
ye	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
manner	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
June	O
17	O
81	O
