TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
November	O
2	O
d	O
If	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
grown	O
the	O
very	O
worst	O
of	O
Correspondants	O
from	O
being	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
alarmed	O
at	O
your	O
frequent	O
and	O
long	O
Silences	O
--	O
but	O
by	O
experience	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
imply	O
ill	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
leſs	O
oubli	O
or	O
indifference	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
you	O
have	O
long	O
loved	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
loves	O
you	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
sincerely	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
therefore	O
determined	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
neither	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
nor	O
angry	O
--	O
the	O
latter	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
nor	O
can	O
be	O
with	O
those	O
Friends	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
--	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
al	O
l	O
ways	O
has	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
unatural	O
&	O
unworthy	O
mark	O
of	O
Friendships	O
,	O
to	O
expreſs	O
doubts	O
,	O
suspicion	O
,	O
mistrust	O
&	O
anger	O
!	O
yet	O
some	O
People	O
hold	O
these	O
affections	O
to	O
be	O
inseparable	O
from	O
true	O
regard	O
!	O
I	O
shall	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
and	O
do	O
write	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sincerely	O
happy	O
and	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
received	O
no	O
doubt	O
my	O
letter	O
from	O
Farmborough	B-place
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
on	O
a	O
folio	O
sheet	O
,	O
was	O
filled	O
&	O
promised	O
you	O
another	O
soon	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
written	O
around	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
&	O
properly	O
directed	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
for	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
where	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
spent	O
my	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
mos	O
t	O
agreeable	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
the	O
Place	O
I	O
doat	O
upon	O
--	O
the	O
Inhabi	O
t	O
ants	O
I	O
love	O
--	O
the	O
Visitors	O
are	O
pleasant	O
--	O
I	O
but	O
the	O
Charm	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
considered	O
as	O
a	O
tame	O
Cat	O
&	O
allowed	O
,	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
walk	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
please	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
never	O
questioned	O
or	O
inquired	O
for	O
,	O
whatever	O
I	O
do	O
or	O
wherever	O
I	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
allowed	O
to	O
rove	O
for	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
Forest	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
indulge	O
my	O
own	O
thoughts	O
without	O
molestation	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
for	O
the	O
Drawingr	O
oom	O
with	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
--	O
she	O
received	O
that	O
Day	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
's	O
Death	O
--	O
this	O
Event	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
&	O
constantly	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
's	O
sufferings	O
,	O
was	O
become	O
so	O
desirable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
relief	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
shock	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
after	O
the	O
Drawingroom	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
mortification	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
state	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
nearly	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
last	O
Autumns	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
entirely	O
lost	O
her	O
appetite	O
--	O
literally	O
so	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
or	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
Broth	O
with	O
out	O
great	O
pain	O
--	O
yet	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
says	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
doing	O
in	O
her	O
case	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
not	O
even	O
ordered	O
her	O
any	O
Medicine	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
exercise	O
,	O
warm	O
cloathing	O
and	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
--	O
my	O
anxiety	O
,	O
which	O
notwithstanding	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
s	O
aſsurances	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
writi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
or	O
attending	O
to	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
during	O
my	O
Stay	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
of	O
October	O
--	O
stayed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
delightful	O
weather	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
profited	O
most	O
comple	O
tely	O
my	O
Sister	O
rode	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Miles	O
every	O
day	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
,	O
a	O
bleſsing	O
I	O
can	O
boast	O
of	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
thankfu	O
l	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Park	O
last	O
Thursday	O
for	O
Farmborough	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
to	O
celebrate	O
Mr	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
s	O
Wedding	O
Day	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
dance	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Lothian	I-pers
's	O
--	O
to	O
see	O
the	B-pers
Ly	I-pers
Kerrs	I-pers
who	O
are	O
charming	O
Girls	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
delight	O
of	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
&	O
of	O
enjoying	O
her	O
singing	O
in	O
so	O
comfortable	O
a	O
way	O
from	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
constraint	O
of	O
a	O
London	B-place
Concert	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
fixed	O
on	O
one	O
chair	O
for	O
4	O
hours	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
hot	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
Monday	O
,	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
some	O
little	O
busine	O
ſs	O
here	O
before	O
the	O
Drawingroom	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
room	O
ever	O
since	O
without	O
moving	O
even	O
to	O
Din	O
ner	O
and	O
have	O
found	O
occupation	O
enough	O
,	O
from	O
8	O
to	O
11	O
without	O
any	O
society	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
ir	O
re	O
are	O
People	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
enquired	O
,	O
&	O
should	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
interrupted	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
has	O
left	O
Lord	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
and	O
Besborough	B-pers
Executors	O
--	O
4000	O
£	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Ly	B-pers
Waldegraves	I-pers
--	O
other	O
Legacies	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Bulk	O
of	O
her	O
fortune	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Heſse	I-pers
--	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
morrow	O
to	O
Richmond	B-place
,	O
&	O
next	O
week	O
to	O
St	B-place
Leond	I-place
with	O
BEIG	B-pers
--	O
she	O
&	O
my	O
Father	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
Car	O
a	O
mi	O
a	O
write	O
soon	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Octer	O
.	O
1786	O
