TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
ſtaid	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
laſt	O
night	O
,	O
expecting	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
resumed	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
humour	O
you	O
then	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
's	O
good	O
opinion	O
I	O
value	O
much	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
's	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
muſt	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
loſt	O
That	O
,	O
provoked	O
me	O
againſt	O
the	O
Tattlers	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
supposed	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
blind	O
to	O
my	O
Affection	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
imagined	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
ſensible	O
Woman	O
you	O
wink	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
paſt	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
alſo	O
natural	O
to	O
imagine	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Objection	O
than	O
my	O
want	O
of	O
fortune	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
hereafter	O
be	O
accidentally	O
removed	O
.	O
A	O
remarka	O
ble	O
Change	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
in	O
you	O
r	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
behaviour	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
put	O
me	O
on	O
gueſsing	O
at	O
the	O
Cause	O
;	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
had	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
wrong	O
to	O
truſt	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Company	O
.	O
--	O
This	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
id	O
le	O
Stories	O
of	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
may	O
have	O
occaſion	O
'd	O
a	O
prejudice	O
aga	O
inſt	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
attempt	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
Affection	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
there	O
was	O
probabi	O
lity	O
of	O
my	O
making	O
her	O
happier	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
ſhould	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
behav	O
ed	O
ung	O
ratefully	O
or	O
injuriously	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
marry	O
ing	O
yo	O
ur	O
conſent	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
the	O
do	O
ctrine	O
taught	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
father	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
ſtill	O
profeſs	O
;	O
that	O
Children	O
are	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
God	O
&	O
Nature	O
,	O
entitled	O
to	O
the	O
Dispoſal	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Perſons	O
,	O
when	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
Years	O
of	O
Discretion	O
,	O
altho	O
their	O
Parents	O
ought	O
ever	O
to	O
offer	O
them	O
their	O
beſt	O
Aſsiſtance	O
&	O
Advice	O
.	O
--	O
Should	O
this	O
declaration	O
of	O
my	O
ſentiments	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
Concern	O
,	O
I	O
ſh	O
(	O
which	O
,	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
's	O
behaviour	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
never	O
ought	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
ſhall	O
not	O
take	O
amiſs	O
your	O
giving	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
invitations	O
to	O
your	O
Houſe	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
promise	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
entirely	O
ea	O
sy	O
,	O
)	O
that	O
before	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
Return	O
from	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
ſhall	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
ſome	O
Other	O
Retreat	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
with	O
conſtant	O
regard	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
Your	O
much	O
obliged	O
&	O
affecte	O
:	O
hum	O
:	O
Servt	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Sunday	O
,	O
13	O
Decemr	O
:	O
