TOKEN	NE
at	O
3	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
had	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
&	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
answers	O
to	O
notes	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsed	O
scribbled	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
was	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
5	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Charriot	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
only	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
(	O
Mr	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
tutor	O
&	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
3	O
boys	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
desert	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
soon	O
--	O
Lady	O
S	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
½	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
my	O
poor	O
Woman	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
family	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
10	O
Minutes	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
told	O
us	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
was	O
better	O
(	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
again	O
&	O
if	O
he	O
goes	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
ha	O
d	O
s	O
done	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
he	O
will	O
fall	O
a	O
Victim	O
to	O
his	O
irregularities	O
.	O
--	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
9	O
left	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
St	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
had	O
his	O
Chariot	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
--	O
a	O
large	O
party	O
&	O
few	O
People	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
ex	O
Conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
Young	B-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
M	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
others	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
his	O
daughter	O
--	O
.	O
sat	O
up	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wrote	O
Notes	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
would	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Sunday	O
--	O
21	O
st	O
..	O
March	O
1784	O
Fanny	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
read	O
together	O
the	O
letter	O
in	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Eloise	O
on	O
Duelling	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
till	O
thursday	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
friend	O
Jean	B-pers
Jacques	I-pers
Rousseau	I-pers
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
t	O
h	O
e	O
felt	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
for	O
the	O
friendly	O
advice	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
endeavourd	O
to	O
correct	O
his	O
errors	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
our	O
conversation	O
she	O
was	O
good	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Stratford	O
Place	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
--	O
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
but	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
(	O
Lady	O
Cecilia	O
)	O
.	O
Rice	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
)	O
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
Lady	B-pers
Denniver	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
Hymn	O
&	O
Songung	O
a	O
Song	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
composing	O
wch	O
..	O
was	O
not	O
without	O
merit	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Beauties	O
of	O
Matlock	B-place
&	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
Derbyshire	B-place
that	O
I	O
feel	O
more	O
impatient	O
than	O
ever	O
to	O
see	O
these	O
Romantick	O
Views	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
describe	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
company	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
8	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
&	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
on	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
alone	O
only	O
her	O
Great	O
Neice	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
was	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
I	O
read	O
one	O
aloud	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
correspond	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
lively	O
stile	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Compliments	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
were	O
just	O
&	O
expresſ	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
peculiar	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
in	O
an	O
elegant	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Servt	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
as	O
she	O
sends	O
daily	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
friend	O
.	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Grace	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
getting	O
a	O
ticket	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Ancient	O
Musick	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
Eveg	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
nine	O
Swift	B-pers
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
calld	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
at	O
one	O
of	O
ye-	O
Clubs	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
gether	O
his	O
house	O
--	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
setting	O
together	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
Cambridge	B-place
--	O
we	O
had	O
supper	O
&	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Diſsolution	O
of	O
Parliament	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
topics	O
of	O
conversation	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minut	O
es	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
&	O
her	O
little	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Monday	O
22	O
d	O
March	O
1784	O
--	O
Notes	O
from	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
wrote	O
to	O
Fanny	B-pers
to	O
inform	O
her	O
she	O
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
might	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Vase	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
say	O
Lady	B-pers
Baſset	I-pers
&	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
any	O
Morning	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
were	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
ticket	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Papers	O
&	O
chatted	O
..	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
dreſser	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
came	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
little	O
Girls	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
Ladies	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
this	O
Morning	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
ye	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
left	O
me	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
As	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nevin	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
dinner	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Ticket	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
)	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Concert	O
--	O
sent	O
immediately	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
ran	O
up	O
&	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
better	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
was	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Coach	O
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
.	O
went	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
W	I-pers
Wynn	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
e	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
Dear	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Concert	O
--	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
People	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
&	O
c	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
Musick	O
--	O
some	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
s	O
Chorus	O
's	O
were	O
finely	O
perform	O
'd	O
--	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
&	O
I	O
quitted	O
ye	O
.	O
C—	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
over	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Gilford	I-pers
Handel	B-pers
&	O
c	O
were	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
waiting	O
Room	O
conversd	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
&	O
came	O
away	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
home	O
.	O
M	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Greenwich	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Coventry	I-pers
came	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dressing	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
then	O
my	O
old	O
Maid	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Marry	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
advice	O
wth	O
.	O
respect	O
to	O
her	O
affairs	O
&	O
future	O
plans	O
for	O
settling	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
ask	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
respecting	O
the	O
man	O
she	O
talkd	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
partnership	O
wth	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Goodyar	B-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
they	O
sat	O
sometime	O
--	O
my	O
Aunt	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Son	O
Miſs	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
was	O
better	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
Dowr	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
went	O
to	O
Col.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
three	O
walk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
(	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
)	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
she	O
was	O
unhappy	O
about	O
her	O
Nephew	O
Lord	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
who	O
was	O
worse	O
.	O
--	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
some	O
very	O
pretty	O
Verses	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
to	O
Copy	O
--	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
charge	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
Give	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
--	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
her	O
Brother	O
had	O
desired	O
ye	O
.	O
Copys	O
not	O
be	O
multiplied	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
attended	O
me	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
s	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Chaperon	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Bed	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
Ague	O
fit	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
however	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
spirits	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s.	O
where	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
&	O
health	O
--	O
though	O
his	O
eyes	O
were	O
bad	O
.	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
after	O
dinner	O
&	O
brought	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
this	O
I	O
cld	O
not	O
comply	O
with	O
.	O
he	O
returnd	O
again	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
After	O
he	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
read	O
aloud	O
till	O
supper	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
s	O
Hist	O
:	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
reign	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
trial	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Earl	O
of	O
Stratford	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Clarendon	I-pers
after	O
supper	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ministers	O
&	O
great	O
Speakers	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
in	O
that	O
Reign	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
coach	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
ye	I-pers
:	I-pers
2d	I-pers
.	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
read	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
was	O
undreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
a	O
Dialogue	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
much	O
comfort	O
Wednesday	O
24	O
th	O
:	O
March	O
1784	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
went	O
&	O
set	O
wth	O
.	O
Plato	B-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Papers	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
my	B-pers
friend	I-pers
came	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
his	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
upstairs	O
to	O
my	O
breakfast	O
room	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
complied	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
busineſs	O
&	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Morning	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
marriage	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
but	O
was	O
equally	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
accepted	O
--	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
good	O
Character	O
--	O
is	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
&	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
judge	O
from	O
her	O
manners	O
&	O
countenance	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
fortune	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
proper	O
rank	O
in	O
life	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
marry	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
affair	O
over	O
--	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
told	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
only	O
went	O
in	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
went	O
on	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
&	O
waited	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
whilst	O
I	O
paid	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
but	O
better	O
&	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
--	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
their	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
&	O
gave	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
News	O
of	O
the	O
Great	O
Seal	O
being	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
s	O
house	O
.	O
heard	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
was	O
so	O
far	O
Recoverd	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
on	O
horseback	O
yesterday	O
&	O
was	O
going	O
today	O
to	O
ye	O
House	O
of	O
Lord	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Apothecary	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Bark	O
wd	O
.	O
soon	O
Remove	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
fever	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
paper	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Yesterday	O
containing	O
the	O
melancholy	O
narrative	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
distreſs	O
's	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
from	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
towards	O
a	O
subscription	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Children	O
s	O
relief	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Seton	I-pers
told	O
me	O
her	O
father	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
She	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
went	O
back	O
for	O
her	O
father	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
during	O
my	O
absence	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
work	O
'd	O
.	O
till	O
4	O
oClock	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
our	O
opposite	O
Neighbours	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
only	O
themselves	O
--	O
we	O
continued	O
in	O
ye	O
dining	O
room	O
till	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
melancholy	O
Story	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
promised	O
me	O
to	O
subscribe	O
--	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Seton	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
secretly	O
a	O
Guinea	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
notice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
before	O
tea	O
I	O
run	O
home	O
stay	O
'd	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
:	O
to	O
answer	O
some	O
notes	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
left	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
going	O
this	O
Eveg	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
in	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Trip	I-pers
s	O
&	O
enclosed	O
some	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
come	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
at	O
8	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
&	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
his	O
conversation	O
uninter̄upted	O
.	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
works	O
,	O
his	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
Gram̄ont	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
published	O
a	O
new	O
Edition	O
of	O
Gram̄ont	O
wth	O
.	O
Notes	O
.	O
The	O
conversation	O
was	O
well	O
kept	O
up	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
agreeable	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
supper	O
--	O
read	O
Hamilton	B-pers
s	O
Poem	O
on	O
Hope	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
they	O
were	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
&	O
gave	O
it	O
ye	O
:	O
praises	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
merits	O
.	O
After	O
supper	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
their	O
Villa	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
(	O
Lucan	B-place
)	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
warm	O
imagination	O
&	O
her	O
descriptions	O
are	O
lively	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
very	O
pictoresque	O
.	O
Lucan	O
is	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Place	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
has	O
built	O
a	O
fine	O
house	O
there	O
not	O
many	O
years	O
since	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
&	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Thursday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
Notable	O
Work	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
3	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
no	O
body	O
should	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
sometime	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
&	O
kept	O
me	O
near	O
2	O
hours	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
smart	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
great	O
admirer	O
of	O
this	O
author	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
am	O
reading	O
it	O
.	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
reap	O
profit	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
pleasure	O
by	O
studying	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
read	O
whilst	O
my	O
hair	O
is	O
dreſsing	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
means	O
that	O
time	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
idle	O
spent	O
.	O
at	O
5	O
oClock	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Betty	B-pers
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Plato	B-pers
&	O
Aunt	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
&	O
Daughter	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
6	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
--	O
The	O
conversation	O
was	O
chiefly	O
family	O
subjects	O
--	O
Relations	O
--	O
connexions	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
bore	O
little	O
part	O
for	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
portion	O
of	O
family	O
pride	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
Musick	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
topic	O
--	O
&	O
other	O
general	O
Subjects	O
.	O
William	B-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
'	O
9	O
--	O
My	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
his	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
before	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
6	O
Weeks	O
as	O
he	O
goes	O
on	O
Monday	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
to	O
settle	O
some	O
affairs	O
.	O
At	O
10	O
oClock	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
--	O
my	O
Aunt	O
s	O
Warwicks	O
second	O
Husband	O
.	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
offer	O
me	O
his	O
Coach	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
my	O
Aunt	O
s	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Carriage	O
&	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
her	O
Horses	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
Crowds	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
two	O
Aſsemblies	O
--	O
a	O
¼	O
past	O
ten	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
U	B-pers
:	I-pers
F	I-pers
--	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
's	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
house	O
&	O
handsomely	O
fitted	O
up	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Company	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
many	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
ton	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
few	O
people	O
&	O
then	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
his	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
s	O
(	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
Lad	O
y	O
)	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
more	O
elegant	O
Aſsembly	O
This	O
House	O
too	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
but	O
not	O
on	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
Scale	O
as	O
Chandos	O
House	O
--	O
one	O
room	O
is	O
very	O
elegantly	O
fitted	O
up	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
form	O
a	O
long	O
Oval	O
.	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
are	O
hung	O
with	O
some	O
fine	O
Pictures	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
wth	O
..	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Chandos	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
there	O
were	O
few	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Aſsemblies	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
busy	O
in	O
Politicks	O
&	O
preparing	O
for	O
a	O
New	O
Election	O
.	O
the	O
Young	O
Ladies	O
we	O
most	O
them	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
en	O
habi	O
t	O
de	O
Bal	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Almack	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
soberly	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
12	O
&	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
Lord	B-pers
Clarendon	I-pers
March	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
got	O
up	O
pretty	O
early	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
answer	O
'd	O
Notes	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
&	O
telling	O
me	O
she	O
hoped	O
it	O
wd	O
..	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
meet	O
.	O
--	O
sorted	O
my	O
Papers	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
our	O
little	O
family	O
of	O
Birds	O
--	O
had	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marquis	I-pers
de	I-pers
Bouillé	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
the	O
day	O
so	O
snowin	O
bad	O
--	O
Snow	O
&	O
rain	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Fanny	B-pers
as	O
I	O
intended	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
oClock	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Eſsex	B-place
--	O
after	O
Dinner	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
desert	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
looks	O
&	O
is	O
vastly	O
better	O
.	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
soon	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
below	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
his	B-pers
Son	I-pers
s	O
verses	O
wth	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
delighted	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
told	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
satisfaction	O
it	O
gave	O
her	O
yt	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
not	O
offer	O
himself	O
a	O
Candidate	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
New	O
Parliament	O
as	O
his	O
health	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
room	O
at	O
6	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
were	O
there	O
&	O
remain	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
we	O
chat	O
ted	O
on	O
com	O
topicks	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W——	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
readings	O
--	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
prevail	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
but	O
I	O
resisted	O
their	O
entreaties	O
&	O
my	O
own	O
inclinations	O
--	O
&	O
made	O
ym	O
.	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
out	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
&	O
Texier	B-pers
at	O
Backgammon	O
.	O
they	O
soon	O
left	O
off	O
&	O
he	O
&	O
I	O
conversed	O
together	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
the	O
aid	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
--	O
the	O
American	O
War	O
.	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
whom	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
esteems	O
very	O
highly	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Washington	I-pers
--	O
to	O
the	O
merit	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
these	O
--	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Glover	O
did	O
ample	O
justice	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fayette	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
from	O
the	O
Oratorio	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
immediately	O
in	O
their	O
Coach	O
.	O
Marquis	B-pers
de	I-pers
Boulle	I-pers
was	O
out	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
before	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
.	O
had	O
Miſsrs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
before	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
to	O
talk	O
over	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
intention	O
,	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
here	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
answer	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
left	O
word	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
or	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
call	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Goodyar	B-pers
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Saturday	O
27	O
th	O
:	O
March	O
1784	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
.	O
The	O
snow	O
lay	O
as	O
deep	O
as	O
it	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
time	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
Winter	O
--	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Sun	O
was	O
out	O
&	O
the	O
day	O
look	O
'd	O
chearful	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
a	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Large	O
fortune	O
advanced	O
in	O
Years	O
simple	O
of	O
plain	O
in	O
his	O
manners	O
but	O
well	O
bred	O
&	O
sensible	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
age	O
--	O
well	O
bred	O
unaffected	O
&	O
very	O
sensible	O
--	O
they	O
both	O
poſseſs	O
great	O
taste	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
Arts	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
been	O
improved	O
by	O
travel	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
an	O
only	O
Child	O
who	O
is	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
Rich	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
of	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
.	O
Their	O
House	O
is	O
near	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
it	O
is	O
large	O
&	O
spacious	O
--	O
all	O
the	O
principal	O
rooms	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
are	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Ground	O
floor	O
.	O
every	O
room	O
has	O
an	O
Air	O
of	O
Comfort	O
.	O
&	O
is	O
furnished	O
wth	O
.	O
fine	O
Pictures	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
best	O
Masters	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
s	O
collection	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
claſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Aufere	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
past	O
9	O
&	O
he	O
had	O
walkd	O
from	O
Town	B-place
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pelham	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
for	O
our	O
time	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
all	O
wth	O
.	O
that	O
attention	O
they	O
merit	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
has	O
just	O
made	O
an	O
addition	O
to	O
his	O
Collection	O
of	O
thr	O
4	O
Pictures	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
france	B-place
.	O
2	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Landscapes	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
one	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Meredith	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
cupids	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
Landscape	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
these	O
are	O
very	O
Capital	O
Pictures	O
--	O
particularly	O
ye	O
.	O
Gasper	B-pers
Pousin	I-pers
s	O
wch	O
..	O
are	O
in	O
his	O
very	O
best	O
manner	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
our	O
time	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
was	O
interesting	O
&	O
agreeable	O
--	O
at	O
12	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
visiting	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
before	O
his	O
Return	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
he	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Parlour	O
made	O
Albano	B-pers
a	O
visit	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
B	O
.	O
room	O
scribbled	O
in	O
my	O
diary	O
.	O
Salvator	B-pers
Rosa	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
Gasper	B-pers
Pousin	I-pers
was	O
better	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Ticket	O
allows	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
whole	O
Box	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
Drury	O
lane	O
Theatre	O
for	O
one	O
night	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
for	O
next	O
thursday	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
is	O
to	O
act	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
to	O
join	O
my	O
party	O
&	O
invited	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
gladly	O
accept	O
it	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
inform	O
me	O
if	O
his	O
Daughter	O
could	O
come	O
go	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
sometime	O
--	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
he	O
goes	O
on	O
Monday	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
happy	O
glad	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
invite	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
as	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
have	O
Ladies	O
enough	O
to	O
fill	O
ye	O
.	O
front	O
Row	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
home	O
before	O
dinner	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
friend	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
with	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
aſsembly	O
--	O
or	O
rather	O
Bas	O
bleu	O
.	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Headach	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
writing	O
&	O
conversation	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
our	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
went	O
to	O
their	O
rooms	O
at	O
11	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
them	O
finishing	O
an	O
extract	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Manuscript	O
letters	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C—s	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
--	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
&	O
I	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
can	O
hear	O
each	O
other	O
so	O
easily	O
that	O
we	O
generally	O
have	O
some	O
talk	O
after	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Sunday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
.	O
Intended	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
as	O
Betty	O
was	O
to	O
dreſs	O
us	O
both	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
--	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Service	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
wht	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
for	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
--	O
yt	O
.	O
her	O
sister	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
ye	O
House	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
came	O
.	O
Col.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
to	O
take	O
a	O
jumble	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Portman	O
square	O
--	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
drive	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
return	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
who	O
goes	O
next	O
tuesday	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
some	O
Months	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
s	O
--	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
down	O
--	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
s	O
--	O
enquired	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
left	O
word	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
on	O
tuesday	O
Eveg	O
..	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
3	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Notes	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
answerd	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Humes	I-pers
cd	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
could	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
4	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Is	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
daughter	O
(	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
Md	O
.	O
of	O
Honor	O
)	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
fine	O
Colord	O
Drawing	O
's	O
&	O
Prints	O
--	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ornaments	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Vatican	O
after	O
tea	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
came	O
she	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
were	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
H.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Concert	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
both	O
these	O
young	O
women	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
well	O
bred	O
&	O
fashionable	O
without	O
Airs	O
.	O
before	O
8	O
--	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
--	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
Square	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
Coach	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Adelphi	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Sr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
Wynne	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kaye	I-pers
who	O
is	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
--	O
we	O
all	O
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vanburgh	I-pers
s	O
a	O
tolerably	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
--	O
Miſs	O
C	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Noseley	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
talk	O
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Monday	O
29	O
th	O
..	O
March	O
1784	O
A	O
Cold	O
Snowny	O
Day	O
.	O
&	O
high	O
Wind	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
came	O
at	O
12	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
poorly	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
--	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
town	B-place
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
even	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
wrote	O
abundance	O
of	O
Notes	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
extracts	O
out	O
of	O
Fanny	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
did	O
Miſs	B-pers
Purdecy	I-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
2	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
as	O
did	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
.	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
did	O
saw	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Carriage	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
set	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
the	O
Election	O
--	O
nobody	O
but	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
desire	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
on	O
thursday	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
youngest	O
boys	O
came	O
down	O
Lord	B-pers
Stor	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
in	O
disgrace	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
till	O
8.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Master	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
ye	O
.	O
to	O
remain	O
there	O
all	O
next	O
Winter	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Tu	O
esday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
she	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
R	O
Family	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
8	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Carriage	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
s	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
s	O
Aſsembly	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
early	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
were	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
saw	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
4	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
invited	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
London	B-place
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
would	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
came	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
&	O
some	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Minchins	O
Bathursts	O
.	O
Tollemaches	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Conversation	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Scawen	I-pers
.	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sensible	O
pleasing	O
Young	O
Woman	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
only	O
her	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Tri	I-pers
:	I-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
House	O
affairs	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
place	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
(	O
Airshire	B-place
&	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
built	O
there	O
for	O
him	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
had	O
known	O
him	O
intimately	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
Lady	O
Wake	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
little	O
Burlington	O
House	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Caſsels	I-pers
s	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
we	O
renew	O
'd	O
our	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
wch	O
.	O
from	O
some	O
accident	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
came	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Asgill	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
visit	O
as	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
always	O
had	O
an	O
affection	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
beautiful	O
--	O
elegant	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
very	O
amiable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
--	O
Saw	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
.	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
dinner	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
whilst	O
she	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
4	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
7.	O
had	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s.	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
youngest	O
Daughter	O
at	O
home	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
chatted	O
talkd	O
of	O
eoconomy	O
.	O
Scotch	O
Relations	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartreys	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
s	O
former	O
tutor	O
there	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
Our	O
Man	O
was	O
ill	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
not	O
without	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
Wednesday	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
March	O
1784	O
Read	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
our	O
Man	O
Servt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
very	O
ill	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
Ague	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
walkd	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Servt	O
.	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
but	O
poorly	O
.	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
now	O
generally	O
known	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
desire	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
acquaint	O
ye	O
.	O
Stormonts	O
&	O
his	O
other	O
Relations	O
as	O
they	O
wd	O
.	O
take	O
it	O
ill	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
first	O
from	O
others	O
.	O
went	O
wt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Servt	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
.	O
sat	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
there	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
&	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
s.	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
&	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Dreſsing	O
room	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaws	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Moyston	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
sisters	O
--	O
their	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
6	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
brought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
to	O
the	O
ir	O
house	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
my	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
a	O
large	O
&	O
fine	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
many	O
foreigners	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
introduced	O
her	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Daughter	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
French	I-pers
Ambaſsador	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
,	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
a	O
great	O
aſsembly	O
generally	O
is	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
he	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
saw	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
s	O
ye	O
.	O
new	O
invented	O
Lamp	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
more	O
hereafter	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Triphena	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
enquired	O
how	O
our	O
poor	O
Servt	O
.	O
did	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
poorly	O
--	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Thursday	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Hartcourt	I-pers
came	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
Grey	I-pers
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
next	O
Wedy	O
.	O
afternoon	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
her	O
--	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
in	O
reading	O
writing	O
&	O
working	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
's	O
Sister	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
AMaria	B-pers
&	O
Betty	B-pers
came	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
before	O
6	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
went	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
&	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
we	O
got	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
before	O
it	O
began	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
very	O
great	O
in	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Lady	O
Randolph	O
in	O
Douglaſs	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
actors	O
were	O
all	O
bad	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
was	O
come	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Is	I-pers
:	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
play	O
was	O
over	O
before	O
9	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
s	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
People	O
I	O
met	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
his	O
manners	O
are	O
not	O
elegant	O
nor	O
does	O
he	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
fashion	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Is	I-pers
:	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
French	I-pers
Ambaſsador	I-pers
--	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
french	I-pers
Ambaſsador	I-pers
where	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Aſsembly	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
their	O
coach	O
--	O
undreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
&	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Is	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
staid	O
ye	O
.	O
entertainmt	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
till	O
12	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Bathursts	I-pers
&	O
the	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Adams	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
morng	O
Friday	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
at	O
12	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Visits	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
were	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
their	O
Coach	O
&	O
a	O
Servt	O
.	O
as	O
ours	O
was	O
still	O
too	O
ill	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
wish	O
'd	O
her	O
joy	O
of	O
son	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
intended	O
marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Servt	O
as	O
mine	O
was	O
ill.	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
both	O
her	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servt	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
,	O
only	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
poorly	O
.	O
enquired	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowans	I-pers
door	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
heard	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
Lord	B-pers
Falmouth	I-pers
.	O
*	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Crewe	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
rather	O
better	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Julia	I-pers
Conyers	I-pers
came	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
beau	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
alone	O
.	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
after	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
run	O
over	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
extremely	O
Ill	O
--	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
int	O
o	O
her	O
bed	O
room	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
good	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
much	O
alter	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
illneſs	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
there	O
met	O
her	O
two	O
Daughters	O
--	O
viz	O
the	O
young	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
,	O
her	O
sis	O
te	O
r	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
--	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
(	O
Mother	O
in	O
law	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Levenson	I-pers
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
her	O
husband	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
(	O
by	O
h	O
er	O
first	O
husband	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Gore	I-pers
s	O
)	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Levenson	I-pers
.	O
&	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
there	O
was	O
one	O
Card	O
Table	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
was	O
also	O
there	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pleasing	O
Woman	O
--	O
Elections	O
&	O
Politicks	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
principal	O
topicks	O
of	O
Conversation	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
making	O
what	O
use	O
I	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
distreſs	O
for	O
a	O
Carriage	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Leslie	I-pers
aſsembly	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
long	O
been	O
married	O
--	O
was	O
a	O
Miſs	O
Egerton	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
early	O
for	O
many	O
people	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
Churchills	O
ye	O
Humes	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
some	O
Men	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
Geneva	B-place
was	O
there	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
introduced	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
him	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
me	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
having	O
seen	O
me	O
when	O
very	O
young	O
at	O
my	O
Great	O
Aunts	O
Lady	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
then	O
came	O
away	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
found	O
Madame	B-pers
Saladin	I-pers
de	I-pers
Crans	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
room	O
--	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
we	O
chatted	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Saturday	O
3	O
d	O
:	O
April	O
1784	O
.	O
At	O
11	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Colley	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
--	O
went	O
there	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
--	O
she	O
,	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	B-place
.	I-place
City	I-place
--	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Glover	O
was	O
better	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
was	O
paſsing	O
by	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
door	O
--	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
his	O
Grandmothers	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
s	O
'	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
took	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
to	O
excuse	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Coffee	O
was	O
ready	O
.	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
putting	O
off	O
going	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
a	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
Sisters	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
off	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
till	O
12	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
not	O
up	O
&	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
Visit	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
room	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Graham	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
introduce	O
her	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
as	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Pictures	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
'	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
--	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
's	O
who	O
recd	O
.	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
civility	O
&	O
took	O
ye	O
.	O
trouble	O
of	O
shewing	O
us	O
her	O
fine	O
Collection	O
of	O
Pictures	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
is	O
Widow	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bristol	O
s	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
judge	O
&	O
lover	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Art	O
&	O
had	O
indulged	O
himself	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
collection	O
of	O
ye	O
works	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Masters	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
exceed	O
the	O
limits	O
of	O
my	O
diary	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
those	O
Pictures	O
wch	O
.	O
pleased	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
--	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
equal	O
to	O
descriptions	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
not	O
to	O
such	O
as	O
wd	O
.	O
well	O
expreſs	O
or	O
convey	O
any	O
true	O
idea	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
some	O
other	O
Company	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
--	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
my	O
Journal	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
their	O
mornings	O
excursions	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
5	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
Carriage	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
there	O
--	O
met	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
mutual	O
in	O
our	O
congratulations	O
on	O
his	O
approaching	O
Marriage	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
many	O
kind	O
&	O
proper	O
things	O
&	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
present	O
Lady	O
Napier	O
at	O
Court	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
ye	O
Grahams	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Autumn	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
were	O
still	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
excuses	O
for	O
not	O
dining	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
were	O
accepted	O
.	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
her	O
Nephew	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Abbé	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
--	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
represent	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
--	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
were	O
coming	O
in	O
we	O
hurried	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
Dr	B-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pepys	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
his	O
wife	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Younge	I-pers
(	O
Shipley	O
)	O
&	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Eveg	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
Hoare	I-pers
went	O
away	O
early	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Neice	O
's	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
&	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
St	I-pers
Astraph	I-pers
.	O
oldest	B-pers
Daughter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
first	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
rooms	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
12	O
--	O
Sunday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
May	O
fair	O
Chapel	O
--	O
the	O
Clergyman	O
's	O
Text	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Isaiah	O
Isaiah	O
--	O
“	O
For	O
Israel	O
will	O
not	O
“	O
hear	O
,	O
my	O
People	O
will	O
not	O
Consider	O
.	O
”	O
Isaih	O
1.3	O
,	O
KJV	O
he	O
censured	O
ye	O
.	O
diſsipations	O
of	O
the	O
fashionable	O
world	O
--	O
the	O
evils	O
of	O
arising	O
from	O
bad	O
example	O
to	O
inferiors	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
his	O
language	O
was	O
poor	O
--	O
his	O
delivery	O
bad	O
--	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
it	O
was	O
sad	O
common	O
place	O
stuff	O
.	O
After	O
Chapel	O
we	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
who	O
lives	O
near	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
parted	O
from	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
&	O
paid	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
after	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
soon	O
follow	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
away	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
future	O
plans	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
hoped	O
out	O
friendship	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
leſsen	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Marriage	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
woud	O
esteem	O
his	O
Wife	O
as	O
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
parted	O
wth	O
.	O
mutual	O
aſsurances	O
of	O
Affection	O
&	O
friendship	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
sometime	O
together	O
before	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
we	O
were	O
well	O
amused	O
in	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Pictures	O
.	O
soon	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
came	O
join	O
'd	O
f	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
in	O
who	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Westminster	B-place
Election	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
left	O
us	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
is	O
a	O
little	O
lively	O
old	O
Woman	O
Wife	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
--	O
The	O
late	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hood	I-pers
was	O
her	O
Brother	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hood	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
much	O
admired	O
by	O
the	O
Men	O
&	O
had	O
many	O
offers	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
refused	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
inclination	O
to	O
Marry	O
--	O
her	O
attra	O
c	O
tions	O
were	O
,	O
her	O
sense	O
,	O
good	O
humor	O
&	O
vivacity	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
handsome	O
&	O
had	O
not	O
even	O
a	O
good	O
Person	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hood	I-pers
was	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
her	O
almost	O
many	O
Years	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
gain	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
dint	O
of	O
perseverance	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
50	O
Years	O
old	O
when	O
she	O
married	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
near	O
80	O
&	O
20	O
Years	O
younger	O
Older	O
than	O
her	O
Husband	O
--	O
his	O
attachment	O
to	O
her	O
is	O
as	O
lively	O
as	O
ever	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
happy	O
couple	O
.	O
Admiral	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
&	O
Gilbert	B-pers
West	I-pers
entertain	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
wth	O
.	O
descriptions	O
of	O
the	O
dreſses	O
of	O
former	O
times	O
--	O
the	O
Farthingales	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
ladies	O
riding	O
on	O
Horseback	O
wth	O
.	O
immense	O
Hoops	O
&	O
long	O
lappets	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
show	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
her	O
pictures	O
wch-	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Bishop	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
stile	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
French	O
call	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
raisonné	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Admiral	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
was	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
there	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
the	B-pers
Glovers	I-pers
came	O
before	O
Supper	O
Politicks	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
principal	O
topick	O
of	O
discou	O
r	O
se	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Monday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
2	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
&	O
stay	O
'd	O
sometime	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
Birthday	O
--	O
he	O
enters	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
me	O
long	O
before	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
she	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
understood	O
from	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
that	O
a	O
friendship	O
had	O
long	O
subsisted	O
between	O
us	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
approved	O
his	O
choice	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
share	O
in	O
our	O
friendship	O
in	O
future	O
.	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
felt	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
merited	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
suit	O
each	O
other	O
&	O
be	O
as	O
happy	O
as	O
the	O
general	O
l	O
ity	O
of	O
Mankind	O
are	O
who	O
are	O
good	O
humor	O
'd	O
,	O
sensible	O
&	O
prudent	O
.	O
The	O
Dartrey	O
's	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
ready	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
ym	O
.	O
&	O
they	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
back	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
through	O
Piccadilly	O
saw	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
on	O
Horseback	O
going	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Court	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
House	O
he	O
kiſs	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
ill	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
were	O
the	O
Company	O
--	O
we	O
congratulated	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
return	O
of	O
this	O
--	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
presents	O
he	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
were	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
chearfully	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Wakes	I-pers
left	O
us	O
after	O
Coffee	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
to	O
tea	O
we	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Commerce	O
to	O
amuse	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
People	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
before	O
supper	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
ye	O
.	O
moment	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
staid	O
&	O
chatted	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
conversation	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
6	O
th	O
..	O
April	O
1784	O
Recd	O
.	O
many	O
notes	O
&	O
invitations	O
,	O
sent	O
answers	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
both	O
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Gunnings	O
came	O
they	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
was	O
got	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
Yesterday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
..	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
out	O
since	O
her	O
illneſs	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Ball	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
went	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
some	O
uncomfortable	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
alone	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
near	O
8	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sit	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
:	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
various	O
distreſs	O
's	O
--	O
respecting	O
her	O
uncertainties	O
in	O
or	O
rather	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
pretty	O
&	O
affected	O
us	O
much	O
by	O
telling	O
us	O
the	O
story	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
s	O
imprisonment	O
&	O
danger	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
life	O
in	O
America	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
anxiety	O
&	O
misery	O
of	O
herself	O
&	O
Parents	O
--	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
well	O
the	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
had	O
acted	O
--	O
how	O
feelingly	O
she	O
recd	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
her	O
Brother	O
&	O
herself	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
this	O
last	O
summer	O
to	O
return	O
thanks	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
recollect	O
&	O
write	O
down	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
Queen	B-pers
of	I-pers
France	I-pers
came	O
home	O
&	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
Lady	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
distreſs	O
abt	O
.	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
prepared	O
to	O
quit	O
it	O
so	O
soon	O
--	O
sent	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
offered	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
aſsistance	O
in	O
our	O
power	O
--	O
She	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Wedn-	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
early	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
how	O
affairs	O
went	O
on	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
both	O
saw	O
him	O
--	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
Mr	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
staid	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
again	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
other	O
Lodgings	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Uncle	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
wife	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
meſsages	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
F	B-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
--	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
it	O
was	O
5	O
oClock	O
he	O
brought	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeve	O
Buttons	O
--	O
&	O
made	O
him	O
give	O
me	O
his	O
old	O
ones	O
.	O
was	O
introduced	O
to	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
she	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
friendly	O
&	O
good	O
natured	O
Woman	O
--	O
without	O
pretensions	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
Mother	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
her	O
late	O
Husband	O
s	O
Children	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
has	O
ever	O
treated	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
&	O
justly	O
much	O
attached	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
introduced	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
is	O
sister	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
--	O
&	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
equally	O
as	O
sensible	O
&	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
--	O
before	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Peachel	I-pers
presented	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
ring	O
with	O
hers	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
hair	O
enclosed	O
&	O
repeated	O
her	O
wishes	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
equal	O
share	O
in	O
my	O
friendship	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts-	O
were	O
withdrawn	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
several	O
neceſsary	O
aranjements	O
respecting	O
ye	O
.	O
marriage	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
&	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
they	O
rejoin	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
soon	O
after	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
great	O
neice	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Spirits	O
for	O
her	O
Old	O
friend	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
oſDowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
is	O
dangerously	O
Ill	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
siezed	O
last	O
Sunday	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Paralectic	O
Stroke	O
--	O
her	O
friends	O
must	O
wish	O
for	O
her	O
release	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
I	O
beleive	O
81	O
&	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
swallow	O
any	O
sustenance	O
or	O
speak	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
staid	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
time	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
came	O
&	O
stay	O
'd	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
asking	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
if	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
my	O
friend	O
s	O
grandfather	O
She	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
both	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
well	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
circumstances	O
relative	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Grandaughter	O
made	O
many	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
had	O
often	O
spoke	O
of	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
tenderest	O
Affection	O
--	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
as	O
I	O
felt	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Grace	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Assembly	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
foriegners	O
of	O
Distinction	O
&	O
fine	O
folks	O
--	O
had	O
ye	O
usual	O
aſsembly	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
&	O
came	O
away	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
Card	O
tables	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
-	O
Room	O
Musick	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Sandys	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
very	O
finely	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
sat	O
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
for	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Thursday	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Dr.	B-pers
S—	I-pers
came	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
--	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
had	O
Miſs	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
Abt	O
.	O
1	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
coming	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
ye	O
..	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
said	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
was	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
was	O
there	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
grandaughters	O
(	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
child	O
.	O
)	O
--	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
but	O
I	O
declined	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
Visits	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
found	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
down	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
W——	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Milbanke	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
--	O
we	O
returned	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
together	O
we	O
were	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
a	O
West	O
Indian	O
--	O
where	O
Miſs	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
is	O
on	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
we	O
saw	O
only	O
Dgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
a	O
mon	O
gre	O
nor	O
ever	O
was	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
proud	O
,	O
--	O
mean	O
,	O
under-bred	O
conceited	O
Miſs	O
.	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burke	I-pers
of	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
paſs	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
&	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
wht-	O
news	O
there	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Elections	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
only	O
left	O
a	O
meſsage	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
--	O
she	O
then	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
&	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
going	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
visit	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
our	O
conversation	O
was	O
wholly	O
relative	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
we	O
lamented	O
the	O
alteration	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
heard	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
was	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
of	O
a	O
large	O
fortune	O
--	O
After	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartry	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
sometime	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
.	O
before	O
6	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
B	O
room	O
--	O
wrote	O
some	O
advice	O
i	O
o	O
n	O
general	O
subjects	O
in	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
had	O
left	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
6	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
c	O
o	O
me	O
to	O
Town	B-place
from	O
Nor'tonshire	O
&	O
other	O
Places	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dined	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
A	B-pers
M——	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
mortification	O
ye	O
.	O
Spencers	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
People	O
of	O
Northampton	O
having	O
rejected	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
for	O
their	O
Member	O
--	O
&	O
having	O
chose	O
one	O
in	O
opposition	O
to	O
the	O
interest	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
family	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
left	O
us	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
paid	O
Miſs	O
Cs	O
a	O
visit	O
below	O
--	O
the	O
comfortable	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
Lord	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
&	O
I	O
,	O
had	O
hoped	O
to	O
have	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
was	O
cruelly	O
disturbed	O
by	O
an	O
unforeseen	O
event	O
--	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
11	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
home	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
conceal	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
agitating	O
her	O
Spirits	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Friday	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
was	O
so	O
very	O
indifferent	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
that	O
we	O
put	O
off	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
were	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
we	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
together	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pain	O
her	O
heart	O
by	O
a	O
communication	O
of	O
wthht-	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
la	O
st	O
night	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
his	O
mother	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
airing	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
&	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J——	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
took	O
little	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
pd	O
.	O
their	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
I	O
got	O
set	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
we	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
he	O
croſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
through	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
to	O
Kensington	B-place
there	O
was	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Carriages	O
&	O
Riders	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
lively	O
.	O
we	O
left	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
at	O
a	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
friend	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
she	O
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
sometime	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
for	O
a	O
½	O
a	O
Mile	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Wakes	I-pers
read	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
discourse	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Chester	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartry	I-pers
.	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughters	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth-	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
to	O
ok	O
leave	O
of	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Porteous	B-pers
till	O
she	O
was	O
summond	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
them	O
whilst	O
they	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
5	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Carriage	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
the	O
Tutor	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
ye	O
Children	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
till	O
near	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
till	O
near	O
11.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Marriage	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
means	O
to	O
present	O
Lady	O
Napier	O
if	O
poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
is	O
soon	O
released	O
--	O
she	O
still	O
continues	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
state	O
.	O
we	O
talkd	O
over	O
our	O
Childish	O
days	O
&	O
our	O
old	O
acquaintances	O
--	O
our	O
Parents	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
before	O
11.	O
had	O
her	O
Carriage	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
alone	O
we	O
conversed	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
--	O
her	O
Cold	O
was	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
Saturday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
me	O
or	O
rather	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
was	O
amused	O
in	O
reading	O
it	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
leſs	O
than	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
myself	O
this	O
he	O
had	O
written	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
stile	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
partial	O
friend	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
AMaria	B-pers
was	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Visit	O
.	O
--	O
After	O
they	O
went	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
--	O
he	O
Shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Watch	O
&	O
Bracelets	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
friendly	O
offers	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
present	O
to	O
present	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
spoke	O
however	O
very	O
sensibly	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
subject	O
&	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
behave	O
always	O
towards	O
him	O
wth	O
.	O
propriety	O
--	O
&	O
acquiescd	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
merits	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
easy	O
to	O
turn	O
aside	O
ye	O
.	O
pr	O
e	O
judices	O
of	O
Young	O
Men	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
--	O
a	O
¼	O
after	O
4	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
yt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
past	O
4	O
his	B-pers
Tutor	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
recd	O
ye	O
.	O
long	O
expected	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
from	O
Mansfield	B-place
--	O
it	O
depreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
spirits	O
for	O
it	O
contain	O
'd	O
an	O
uncomfortable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
her	O
Sister	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
home	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Coa	O
c	O
h	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
's	O
.	O
where	O
I	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
--	O
Lady	O
Shelborne	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
diverting	O
anecdote	O
of	O
A	O
Mans	O
going	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
ye	O
.	O
Porter	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
&	O
brought	O
the	O
Seals	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
lately	O
stol'n	O
&	O
put	O
a	O
Basket	O
carefully	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
--	O
The	O
Porter	O
flew	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
who	O
eagerly	O
order	O
'd	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
in	O
opening	O
ye	O
.	O
Basket	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
to	O
instead	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Seals	O
a	O
pretty	O
new	O
born	O
Infant	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
--	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
for	O
his	O
reward	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Shelborne	I-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
Dartrey	B-pers
s	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
upon	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Chancellor	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
son	O
to	O
B	B-pers
--	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
grown	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
room	O
--	O
the	O
Wakes	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Master	B-pers
George	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Sunday	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Cold	O
being	O
very	O
indifferent	O
I	O
proposed	O
our	O
reading	O
Prayers	O
together	O
at	O
home	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
soon	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
some	O
time	O
together	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
at	O
2	O
&	O
staid	O
sometime	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
thank	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
little	O
present	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
hoped	O
our	O
acquaintance	O
wd	O
improve	O
&	O
other	O
very	O
civil	O
things	O
paſsd	O
Lady	B-pers
invited	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
next	O
friday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
the	O
day	O
ye	O
.	O
new	O
married	O
pair	O
are	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
tomorrow	O
After	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
came	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
dine	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
many	O
promises	O
of	O
future	O
good	O
conduct	O
--	O
&	O
many	O
profeſsions	O
of	O
affection	O
gratitude	O
&	O
so	O
forth	O
.	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
the	O
Miſs	O
C	O
's	O
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
6	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
read	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Scripture	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
7	O
oClock	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
heart	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
struggles	O
of	O
her	O
Mind	O
wth	O
.	O
respect	O
to	O
her	O
attachment	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
--	O
how	O
far	O
that	O
interfered	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
God	O
&	O
duty	O
towards	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
opinion	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
we	O
need	O
retire	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
to	O
fulfill	O
our	O
duties	O
--	O
for	O
if	O
we	O
are	O
placed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
midst	O
of	O
temptations	O
our	O
resisting	O
them	O
is	O
an	O
example	O
to	O
our	O
weaker	O
brethern	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
certainly	O
a	O
greater	O
power	O
of	O
doing	O
good	O
&	O
may	O
often	O
influence	O
by	O
our	O
others	O
to	O
admire	O
&	O
follow	O
Virtue	O
--	O
She	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
whom	O
she	O
saw	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
abt	O
.	O
7	O
years	O
ago	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
admired	O
him	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
talkd	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
her	O
opinions	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Monday	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
I	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
died	O
this	O
Morng	O
Monday	O
12	O
April	O
1784	O
Rouſseau	B-pers
&	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Matrimonial	O
arrangements	O
--	O
seem	O
'd	O
happy	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
us	O
as	O
she	O
goes	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
(	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
going	O
to	O
Upshire	O
farm	O
in	O
Eſsex	B-place
wch	O
.	O
is	O
but	O
14	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	B-place
)	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
ye-	O
Week	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
left	O
us	O
together	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
told	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
(	O
&	O
alas	O
!	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
has	O
reason	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
went	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
just	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
us	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
we	O
dind	O
together	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
till	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
When	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
s	O
--	O
a	O
Bas	O
Blue	O
party	O
.	O
there	O
were	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
.	O
Sr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pepy	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Second	O
Brother	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
--	O
the	O
Chief	O
thing	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
a	O
difference	O
of	O
opinion	O
respecting	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Monboddo	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
extolld	O
him	O
above	O
all	O
our	O
Poets	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Dryden	B-pers
had	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
lately	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
escorted	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Dr.	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
s	O
Mistreſs	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
&	O
that	O
her	O
Uncle	O
was	O
painting	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
picture	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
intelligence	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
entertainment	O
in	O
plaguing	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
came	O
away	O
also	O
&	O
Chs	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
set	O
us	O
both	O
down	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
at	O
home	O
&	O
me	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
s	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
at	O
home	O
I	O
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
ym	O
.	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
immediately	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
before	O
11	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
sometime	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
advice	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
stand	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
&	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
it	O
gratefully	O
--	O
&	O
his	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
was	O
so	O
full	O
that	O
he	O
wept	O
like	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
parting	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
improbable	O
we	O
may	O
meet	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
as	O
his	O
father	O
talks	O
of	O
coming	O
again	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
If	O
this	O
Youth	O
is	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
to	O
withstand	O
the	O
snares	O
and	O
temptations	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
comfort	O
of	O
his	O
Parents	O
&	O
the	O
delight	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
&	O
a	O
valuable	O
Member	O
of	O
Society	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
his	O
Ship	O
not	O
sailing	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
was	O
expected	O
he	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
friends	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
sometime	O
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
some	O
Manuscript	O
Poems	O
--	O
particularly	O
a	O
Song	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
written	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
a	O
character	O
sometime	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
will	O
attempt	O
to	O
describe	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
Old	O
Maid	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
succeeded	O
his	O
Lordship	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
last	O
week	O
to	O
a	O
Lord	B-pers
Monboddo	I-pers
--	O
was	O
now	O
settled	O
in	O
busineſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
use	O
my	O
endeavours	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
&	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
&	O
a	O
Breakfast	O
Cloth	O
towards	O
her	O
house	O
linnen	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
neither	O
could	O
I	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
Lord	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
till	O
6	O
oClock	O
in	O
Goodyar	B-pers
s	O
odes	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
remind	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
promise	O
to	O
serve	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
at	O
7	O
the	O
Gray	B-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Wm-	B-pers
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
's	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
came	O
--	O
both	O
she	O
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
were	O
very	O
low	O
ye	O
.	O
death	O
of	O
their	O
old	O
friend	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
had	O
much	O
afflicted	O
them	O
.	O
orders	O
were	O
given	O
that	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
esteem	O
'd	O
it	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
their	O
affection	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Company	O
in	O
preference	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
--	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
amuse	O
them	O
&	O
succeeded	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
conversation	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
whether	O
they	O
thought	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
a	O
real	O
convert	O
to	O
Christianity	O
&	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Observer	O
of	O
Religious	O
duties	O
--	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
both	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
--	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
's	O
Coach	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
our	O
Vis	O
a	O
Vis	O
Neighbour	O
Lady	B-pers
Andover	I-pers
did	O
--	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
were	O
sitting	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
good	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
Jennings	I-pers
appear	O
'd	O
much	O
recover	O
'd	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
she	O
said	O
s	O
her	O
Cold	O
was	O
better	O
&	O
had	O
she	O
known	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
home	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
so	O
early	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
finish	O
&	O
sent	O
my	O
letter	O
&	O
Diary	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
at	O
M.——	B-place
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Wedn	O
.	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
all	O
my	O
leisure	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
looking	O
over	O
&	O
reading	O
letters	O
some	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
recall	O
'd	O
very	O
painfull	O
Ideas	O
of	O
past	O
events	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
my	O
Uncle	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
that	O
my	O
Uncle	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Villa	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
England	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
--	O
except	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
tea	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
.	O
we	O
chatted	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
.	O
till	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
home	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
visited	O
me	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
for	O
ye	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
time	O
this	O
Compt	O
.	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
having	O
married	O
her	O
Neice	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
notes	O
from	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
Johnston	I-pers
came	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
sat	O
up	O
writing	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Thursday	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
The	O
whole	O
day	O
Mo	O
rning	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
writing	O
extracts	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
excuses	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
s	O
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
&	O
co	O
had	O
tea	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
continued	O
writing	O
ye	O
.	O
extracts	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
made	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
flying	O
Visits	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Course	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
an	O
invitation	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
next	O
Sunday	O
Friday	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1784	O
Had	O
my	O
Hair	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
--	O
read	O
in	O
a	O
Novel	O
call	O
'd	O
Henrietta	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
strokes	O
of	O
nature	O
wch	O
.	O
affected	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
my	O
time	O
till	O
dinner	O
in	O
writing	O
extracts	O
from	O
Dear	O
Master	B-pers
Maſsey	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
congratulations	O
to	O
greet	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Johnston	I-pers
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
wht	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Lennox	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
me	O
.	O
rec	O
'd	O
.	O
an	O
affectionate	O
answer	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
short	O
visit	O
--	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
room	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
continued	O
writing	O
the	O
Extracts	O
till	O
near	O
7	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
best	O
bib	O
&	O
Tucker	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Bride	O
&	O
Bridegroom	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Lord	B-pers
s	O
Carriage	O
&	O
Servts	O
:	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
invited	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
.	O
notwithstanding	O
a	O
Heavy	O
shower	O
of	O
rain	O
&	O
contrary	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
custom	O
in	O
