TOKEN	NE
Uppm-	B-place
Decr	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
1805	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
found	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
on	O
My	O
return	O
from	O
Newark	B-place
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
weeks	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
Staid	O
there	O
much	O
longer	O
but	O
was	O
against	O
my	O
inclination	O
Obliged	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Upping	B-place
Ham	I-place
to	O
Sign	O
Some	O
Deeds	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
Estate	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
is	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
paid	O
for	O
&	O
the	O
money	O
placed	O
in	O
the	O
funds	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
trouble	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
offering	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
Situation	O
for	O
us	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
Till	O
Mr-	B-pers
J	I-pers
's	O
return	O
from	O
London	B-place
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
say	O
what	O
our	O
annual	O
income	O
will	O
be	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
may	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
£50	O
a	O
year	O
each	O
for	O
board	O
and	O
lodging	O
--	O
&	O
certainly	O
expect	O
two	O
rooms	O
entirely	O
to	O
our-Selves	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
wish	O
three	O
but	O
two	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
without	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
wish	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
about	O
Feby-	O
&	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
Mary	B-pers
will	O
join	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
returned	O
from	O
Newark	B-place
quite	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
and	O
Since	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
staying	O
till	O
till	O
this	O
eveg	O
at	O
the	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Grantham	B-place
--	O
&	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
other	O
visits	O
to	O
make	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
employ	O
my	O
time	O
till	O
feby-	O
perhaps	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
possible	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bargain	O
with	O
whom	O
we	O
may	O
board	O
with	O
to	O
deduct	O
something	O
whenever	O
we	O
are	O
absent	O
longer	O
than	O
a	O
certain	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
about	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tren	I-pers
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
&	O
Mary	B-pers
will	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
be	O
not	O
leſs	O
frequently	O
from	O
home	O
--	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
deduction	O
is	O
only	O
sufficient	O
to	O
defray	O
our	O
travelling	O
expences	O
(	O
tho	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
considerably	O
more	O
)	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
worth	O
speaking	O
for	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
so	O
well	O
the	O
kind	O
of	O
family	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
Suit	O
us	O
that	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
--	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
I	O
met	O
with	O
great	O
encouragement	O
to	O
Settle	O
there	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shod-	O
certainly	O
have	O
attempted	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Situation	O
)	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
agreably	O
Surprised	O
at	O
My	O
return	O
to	O
Uppm-	B-place
to	O
find	O
that	O
You	O
remembered	O
Your	O
kind	O
Promise	O
of	O
introducing	O
us	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
Your	O
friends	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
&	O
also	O
endeavoring	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
Situation	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
Newark	B-place
--	O
for	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
decided	O
preference	O
for	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
fixed	O
at	O
the	O
former	O
place	O
merely	O
from	O
Neceſsity	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
this	O
Sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
I	O
will	O
Conclude	O
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
Yr-	O
Obliged	O
&	O
affte	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
My	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
have	O
really	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
can	O
at	O
all	O
entertain	O
you	O
but	O
as	O
your	O
favor	O
came	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
resist	O
acknoledging	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
from	O
home	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
copying	O
any	O
patterns	O
for	O
you	O
Yet	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
May	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
buy	O
some	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
folio	O
Sheet	O
with	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
desire	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
particularly	O
what	O
you	O
want	O
them	O
for	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
a	O
variety	O
for	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
uses	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
taken	O
with	O
Dr-	B-pers
Ingles	I-pers
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
excuse	O
My	O
sending	O
him	O
any	O
particular	O
kind	O
Meſsage	O
--	O
and	O
only	O
hope	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
by	O
my	O
absence	O
from	O
Leighton	B-place
,	O
experience	O
a	O
double	O
portion	O
of	O
his	O
polite	O
attentions	O
--	O
Pray	O
tell	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
as	O
I	O
th	O
in	O
k	O
you	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
enq	O
uiry	O
after	O
the	O
lady	O
of	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Poppy	O
--	O
or	O
whether	O
was	O
entirely	O
forgotten	O
--	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Public	O
aſsembly	O
and	O
one	O
private	O
ball	O
--	O
at	O
both	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
beautiful	O
but	O
far	O
more	O
apparently	O
far	O
more	O
pleasing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jon	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
's	O
Daughter	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
this	O
because	O
I	O
think	O
yr-	O
Mama	O
knows	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
Saw	O
a	O
woman	O
more	O
admired	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
an	O
uncommon	O
pretty	O
dame	O
--	O
She	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roger	I-pers
Pocklington	I-pers
--	O
her	O
husband	O
s	O
Sister	O
--	O
the	O
private	O
ball	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
,	O
the	O
aſsembly	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
lately	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
great	O
luck	O
for	O
dancing	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
aſsembly	O
here	O
only	O
two	O
evegs-	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newark	B-place
&	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
on	O
friday	O
in	O
honor	O
of	O
the	O
victory	O
--	O
a	O
victory	O
at	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
shoud	O
rather	O
lament	O
than	O
rejoice	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
go	O
if	O
any	O
family	O
is	O
going	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
accompany	O
--	O
during	O
the	O
t	O
he	O
ime	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
I	O
had	O
another	O
invitation	O
to	O
a	O
ball	O
at	O
Blatherwick	O
hall	O
--	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
O'brien	I-pers
's	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
of	O
course	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
attend	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
Oakham	B-place
as	O
I	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
today	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
little	O
New	O
Cousin	O
George	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
boy	O
--	O
Mary	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
and	O
interesting	O
little	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
youngest	O
child	O
,	O
grown	O
plain	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
is	O
in	O
town	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Torkey	I-pers
still	O
here	O
but	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
returns	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
agreable	O
Sister	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
only	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
say	O
takes	O
her	O
place	O
--	O
he	O
intends	O
while	O
she	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
clergimans	O
widow	O
or	O
well	O
educated	O
woman	O
to	O
Superintend	O
his	O
children	O
and	O
family	O
--	O
the	O
best	O
plan	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
can	O
pursue	O
as	O
the	O
children	O
are	O
too	O
young	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
School	O
--	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
good	O
Scool	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
as	O
Mr-	B-pers
W	I-pers
seems	O
very	O
anxious	O
if	O
we	O
fix	O
there	O
to	O
place	O
his	O
children	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
old	O
enought	O
there	O
--	O
believe	O
me	O
dr	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
Ys	O
affly	O
F	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
I	O
was	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
who	O
passed	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
s	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
K	I-pers
had	O
been	O
confined	O
near	O
three	O
weeks	O
at	O
Wooburn	B-place
by	O
a	O
dangerous	O
illness	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
--	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
My	O
hand	O
is	O
quite	O
cramped	O
with	O
writing	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
hand	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dr-	O
Louisa	B-pers
you	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
it	O
--	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
success	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
application	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
love	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Grants	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Bedfordshire	B-place
