TOKEN	NE
Burlington	O
Street	O
18	O
th	O
June	O
1789	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
should	O
they	O
do	O
otherwise	O
most	O
likely	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
remain	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
your	O
Company	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
months	O
trouble	O
with	O
the	O
Petition	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
ended	O
with	O
our	O
obtaining	O
the	O
Right	O
of	O
Voting	O
only	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Committee	O
seem	O
tired	O
of	O
us	O
--	O
His	O
Grace	O
&	O
myself	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
adhered	O
to	O
the	O
plan	O
of	O
detaching	O
myself	O
from	O
a	O
dinner	O
party	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hurtful	O
to	O
my	O
busineſs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
North	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
You	O
mention	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
Nanny	B-pers
lately	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
still	O
continues	O
so	O
absurdly	O
a	O
Slave	O
to	O
Madneſs	O
&	O
Folly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
up	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
dependance	O
.	O
The	O
Children	O
broke	O
up	O
yesterday	O
for	O
the	O
Holidays	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
where	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
Nanny	B-pers
wishes	O
to	O
be	O
sometime	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
those	O
two	O
Devil	O
Sister	O
's	O
worry	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
reply	O
that	O
whenever	O
it	O
is	O
agreeable	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
after	O
her	O
conduct	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
make	O
any	O
engagement	O
the	O
durance	O
whereof	O
,	O
shall	O
depend	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
great	O
advocate	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
Tontine	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
Louisa	B-pers
will	O
live	O
till	O
80	O
she	O
may	O
benefit	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
approve	O
thereof	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
you	O
a	O
Hundred	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
put	O
more	O
on	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
or	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
they	O
will	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
hardly	O
conceive	O
that	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
any	O
diſsolution	O
of	O
Parliament	O
this	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
some	O
quiet	O
--	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
by	O
all	O
accounts	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
better	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
than	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Produce	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
opinion	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Duel	O
between	O
Col.	B-pers
Lenox	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Highneſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
leſson	O
for	O
Princes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
now	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
to	O
understand	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
insult	O
,	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
with	O
impunity	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
,	O
and	O
Fanny	B-pers
s	O
neck	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
has	O
every	O
prospect	O
of	O
doing	O
well	O
without	O
a	O
scar	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
Katherine	B-pers
write	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
very	O
soon	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
very	O
obed	O
Servt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
London	B-place
1789	O
