TOKEN	NE
Letters	O
written	O
to	O
+	O
+	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Dſs	B-pers
Athol	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Walkinskaw	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Goldsworthy	B-pers
Monla	B-pers
Md	B-pers
la	I-pers
Fête	I-pers
Planta	B-pers
Bewley	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
DartreyCremorne	I-pers
Wake	B-pers
Stormont	B-pers
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mſs	B-pers
Do	I-pers
Master	B-pers
Do	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
——	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
——	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
Burney	B-pers
Palmer	B-pers
Clarke	B-pers
Asgill	B-pers
Ldy-	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Herries	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Rogers	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Thunby	I-pers
Gunning	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
Walpole	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
c	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Stan	O
.	O
St	O
Augt	O
:	O
18	O
th	O
:	O
1785	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
Time	O
to	O
say	O
thank	O
you	O
from	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
for	O
allowing	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
delightful	O
Letter	O
,	O
you	O
wrote	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
indeed	O
it	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
unspeakable	O
Pleasure	O
.	O
Sincerely	O
do	O
I	O
rejoice	O
in	O
yr	O
:	O
happineſs	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
ye	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
June	O
--	O
)	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
happy	O
as	O
he	O
makes	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Comfort	O
of	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
is	O
recovering	O
fast	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
left	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
she	O
was	O
surprisingly	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
yr	O
:	O
good	O
Fd	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
sends	O
you	O
particulars	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
go	O
on	O
Sat	O
.	O
next	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
where	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dawson	I-pers
are	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Yrs	O
:	O
Affly	O
PCremorne	B-pers
We	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
than	O
when	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
your	O
best	O
Friend	O
