TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
has	O
just	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Enclosed	O
that	O
She	O
has	O
recd	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
send	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
shew	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
not	O
sending	O
him	O
on	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
done	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
tomorrow	O
Night	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
will	O
write	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
P.	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
by	O
the	O
Stage	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Duty	O
&	O
Complimts	O
.	O
as	O
due	O
.	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Monday	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
