TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
Sepr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
,	O
No	O
Packet	O
being	O
yet	O
arrived	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
since	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
an	O
Enumeration	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
I	O
had	O
wrote	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
enclosed	O
for	O
their	B-pers
Rl	I-pers
Highneſses	I-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
here	O
repeat	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
long	O
since	O
been	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
thō	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
proceed	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
leaving	O
the	O
Caldas	B-place
,	O
where	O
Ld	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
has	O
so	O
much	O
benefited	O
,	O
that	O
excepting	O
an	O
Increase	O
of	O
Strength	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
wish	O
'd	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
&	O
in	O
this	O
particular	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
mended	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
accompany	O
Me	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
Northward	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
still	O
the	O
universal	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
paſs	O
his	O
Winter	O
in	O
a	O
Southern	O
Climate	O
.	O
This	O
Idea	O
which	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
by	O
returning	O
by	O
Land	O
,	O
has	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
determine	O
against	O
the	O
Sea	O
Voyage	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
dreaded	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
it	O
disagreed	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
finding	O
a	O
proper	O
Neutral	O
Veſsel	O
ready	O
to	O
Sail	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
reach	O
England	O
before	O
November	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
uncertain	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
Apprehensions	O
of	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Portuguese	O
,	O
whose	O
Skill	O
at	O
Sea	O
is	O
not	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
English	O
.	O
By	O
Land	O
no	O
doubt	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
tedious	O
,	O
Expensive	O
,	O
and	O
Inconvenient	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
Sure	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
can	O
never	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Paſsage	O
by	O
Sea	O
.	O
Our	O
Route	O
will	O
be	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
to	O
Madrid	B-place
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Bayonne	B-place
,	O
&	O
so	O
to	O
Ostend	B-place
.	O
As	O
we	O
shall	O
only	O
stop	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Places	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
rest	O
ourselves	O
&	O
refit	O
for	O
our	O
Journey	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
time	O
much	O
exceed	O
what	O
the	O
going	O
by	O
Sea	O
,	O
&	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
proper	O
Veſsel	O
to	O
Sail	O
might	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
therefore	O
we	O
think	O
we	O
shall	O
certainly	O
adopt	O
that	O
plan	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
&	O
honour	O
of	O
paying	O
my	O
Grateful	O
Thanks	O
&	O
Duty	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
for	O
their	O
Gracious	O
Indulgence	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
kiſsing	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
dear	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
I	O
am	O
quite	O
overcome	O
with	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
this	O
Thought	O
gives	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
feel	O
how	O
Grateful	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
to	O
Providence	O
that	O
has	O
given	O
so	O
unexpected	O
&	O
happy	O
a	O
Conclusin	O
to	O
my	O
(	O
at	O
first	O
)	O
dismal	O
Undertaking	O
.	O
The	O
Preparations	O
for	O
this	O
long	O
Journey	O
,	O
will	O
take	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
Paſsports	O
must	O
be	O
got	O
,	O
Carriages	O
bought	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
Thouſd	O
.	O
things	O
that	O
occur	O
upon	O
such	O
Occasions	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
detain	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
however	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
stopt	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
paying	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portugal	I-pers
,	O
for	O
whose	O
Gracious	O
Attentions	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
bound	O
to	O
shew	O
every	O
mar	O
k	O
of	O
respectful	O
Gratitude	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
Court	O
Days	O
here	O
so	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
always	O
applied	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
name	O
a	O
day	O
for	O
receving	O
those	O
that	O
ask	O
an	O
Audience	O
&	O
I	O
understand	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
refuse	O
to	O
Lisbon	B-place
till	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
dreſs	O
also	O
to	O
make	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
brought	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Octr	O
.	O
before	O
you	O
can	O
receive	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
an	O
immediate	O
Answer	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Madrid	B-place
Poste	O
restante	O
(	O
Via	O
Ostende	B-place
)	O
as	O
I	O
calculate	O
it	O
must	O
meet	O
me	O
there	O
where	O
we	O
are	O
also	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
finding	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
still	O
at	O
Porto	B-place
,	O
&	O
intend	O
wintering	O
in	O
the	B-place
South	I-place
of	I-place
France	I-place
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
may	O
every	O
thing	O
go	O
on	O
prosperously	O
&	O
happily	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
&	O
may	O
I	O
ere	O
long	O
be	O
the	O
happy	O
Witneſs	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Duty	O
Affections	O
Complimts	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
you	O
will	O
dispose	O
of	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
wish	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
most	O
faithfully	O
&	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
C.Finch	B-pers
I	O
suppose	O
my	O
next	O
Letter	O
you	O
will	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Spanish	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
begs	O
her	O
kindest	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
London	B-place
(	O
Via	O
Ostende	B-place
)	O
Inglaterra	B-place
