TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
As	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
hope	O
to	O
ſee	O
you	O
now	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
refrain	O
from	O
expreſsing	O
to	O
you	O
upon	O
Paper	O
,	O
how	O
truly	O
&	O
tenderly	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
do	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
every	O
Argument	O
of	O
Comfort	O
that	O
your	O
Situation	O
allows	O
of	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
Providence	O
will	O
aſsist	O
your	O
Endeavours	O
of	O
resigning	O
yourself	O
to	O
his	O
Will	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
much	O
&	O
kindly	O
you	O
are	O
mention	O
'd	O
by	O
every	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
,	O
&	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
have	O
both	O
been	O
particular	O
in	O
their	O
Enquiries	O
about	O
you	O
;	O
&	O
expreſsing	O
their	O
Concern	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
hoped	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
all	O
poſsible	O
Care	O
of	O
yourself	O
,	O
&	O
let	O
no	O
Thought	O
of	O
yr	O
Attendance	O
here	O
be	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
own	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
most	O
contribute	O
to	O
your	O
Ease	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
on	O
so	O
trying	O
an	O
Occasion	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
you	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
calm	O
&	O
composed	O
,	O
&	O
willing	O
thankfully	O
to	O
enjoy	O
that	O
portion	O
of	O
happineſs	O
&	O
Comfort	O
that	O
a	O
kind	O
Providence	O
allots	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
that	O
hurt	O
in	O
his	O
Goodneſs	O
,	O
who	O
alone	O
knows	O
what	O
is	O
best	O
&	O
fittest	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
tender	O
&	O
Sensible	O
a	O
Friend	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
with	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
last	O
Letter	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
kind	O
&	O
feeling	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
,	O
my	O
Daurs	O
.	O
sincerely	O
join	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
approve	O
myself	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
most	O
Affcte	O
.	O
Friend	O
&	O
faithful	O
Sert	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
St	O
James	O
's	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
..	O
1778	O
recd	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
My	O
beloved	O
Mother	O
.	O
Typed	O
On	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Death	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
