TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
receiving	O
the	O
Balance	O
of	O
your	O
Account	O
entire	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
town	O
yesterday	O
to	O
settle	O
that	O
busineſs	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Huband	I-pers
;	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
unneceſsary	O
delay	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Tenants	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
distreſs	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
received	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
my	O
May	O
Rents	O
of	O
my	O
Lands	O
in	O
the	O
Counties	O
of	O
Kildare	B-place
&	O
Meath	B-place
&	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
ejecting	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Tenants	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
highly	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
confidence	O
you	O
have	O
reposed	O
in	O
me	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
improper	O
use	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
freedom	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
use	O
in	O
disclosing	O
your	O
sentiments	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
any	O
subject	O
.	O
It	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
and	O
tiresome	O
detail	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
minutely	O
of	O
my	O
expectations	O
&	O
disappointments	O
from	O
a	O
certain	O
quarter	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
insist	O
upon	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
man	O
living	O
who	O
had	O
better	O
founded	O
pretensions	O
,	O
resting	O
upon	O
the	O
basis	O
of	O
royal	O
Promises	O
frequently	O
repeated	O
;	O
how	O
it	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
derived	O
so	O
little	O
good	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
;	O
no	O
impatience	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
was	O
ever	O
improperly	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
late	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
many	O
years	O
ago	O
had	O
an	O
audience	O
of	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
my	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
expreſs	O
his	O
rembrance	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
terms	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
resigning	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
Chaplain	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
having	O
held	O
it	O
a	O
certain	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
residence	O
In	O
Ireland	B-place
made	O
it	O
extremely	O
expensive	O
&	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Ireland	O
annually	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
dismiſsing	O
myself	O
&	O
giving	O
up	O
all	O
further	O
expectations	O
,	O
my	O
Br	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
W.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
my	O
particular	O
desire	O
made	O
my	O
resignation	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
explain	O
'd	O
my	O
motives	O
to	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
fifteen	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
to	O
resume	O
solicitations	O
so	O
long	O
suspended	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Br	O
.	O
aſsured	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
his	B-pers
M——y	I-pers
when	O
he	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
hopeleſs	O
undertaking	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
my	O
ardor	O
for	O
worldly	O
Things	O
is	O
now	O
much	O
abated	O
,	O
having	O
nearly	O
attain	O
'd	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
51	O
years	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
policy	O
of	O
Ministers	O
to	O
fill	O
almost	O
every	O
department	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
with	O
very	O
low	O
men	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
by	O
chance	O
been	O
a	O
Schoolmaster	O
or	O
a	O
Tutor	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
I	O
might	O
probably	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Bishop	O
,	O
for	O
of	O
such	O
materials	O
is	O
that	O
order	O
here	O
principally	O
composed	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
descended	O
from	O
noble	O
ancestors	O
inheriting	O
from	O
them	O
sentiments	O
of	O
honour	O
&	O
integrity	O
with	O
a	O
respectable	O
landed	O
property	O
if	O
urged	O
as	O
pretensions	O
to	O
favors	O
wou	O
'd	O
produce	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
an	O
answer	O
of	O
contempt	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
Parliamentary	O
interest	O
what	O
can	O
he	O
do	O
for	O
or	O
against	O
us	O
?	O
are	O
the	O
questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
that	O
Persons	O
of	O
low	O
&	O
mean	O
origin	O
who	O
have	O
risen	O
to	O
high	O
Stations	O
through	O
worldly	O
craft	O
&	O
servility	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
adequate	O
ideas	O
of	O
honour	O
&	O
dignity	O
of	O
sentiment	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
for	O
the	O
interests	O
of	O
a	O
State	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
frequent	O
thoughts	O
of	O
making	O
my	O
appearance	O
in	O
London	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
busineſs	O
of	O
renewing	O
my	O
solicitations	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
always	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
deceive	O
myself	O
as	O
to	O
entertain	O
hopes	O
of	O
suceſs	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
forgotten	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
pretensions	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
advised	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
proceed	O
in	O
form	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Memorial	O
,	O
which	O
unleſs	O
presented	O
&	O
back	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
consequence	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
as	O
little	O
weight	O
as	O
the	O
Petition	O
of	O
a	O
mad	O
Apothecary	O
that	O
I	O
rember	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Antichamber	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
it	O
is	O
full	O
time	O
to	O
quit	O
this	O
unpleasing	O
subject	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
fail	O
'd	O
of	O
advancement	O
in	O
my	O
Profeſsion	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
thankful	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
comforts	O
I	O
enjoy	O
,	O
excellent	O
health	O
,	O
admirable	O
spirits	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
competency	O
;	O
if	O
added	O
to	O
these	O
bleſsings	O
,	O
I	O
enjoy	O
the	O
esteem	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
an	O
aſsertion	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
properly	O
from	O
myself	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
me	O
an	O
unhappy	O
being	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
much	O
affronted	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
the	O
letters	O
you	O
enclosed	O
--	O
As	O
your	O
royal	O
eléves	O
are	O
not	O
slow	O
in	O
attaining	O
the	O
stature	O
of	O
women	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
hopes	O
,	O
unleſs	O
you	O
are	O
honor	O
'd	O
with	O
an	O
additional	O
supply	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
when	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
honor	O
'd	O
with	O
some	O
substantial	O
mark	O
of	O
approbation	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Latour	O
October	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1779	O
.	O
