TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
In	O
obedience	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
commands	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
conveying	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
thro	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
enclos	O
'd	O
Comments	O
on	O
the	O
ten	O
Commandments	O
.	O
My	O
partiality	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
has	O
perhaps	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
mention	O
this	O
little	O
Publication	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fear	O
may	O
be	O
deemd	O
unworthy	O
of	O
royal	O
Notice	O
.	O
The	O
Author	O
is	O
a	O
truly	O
pious	O
,	O
parochial	O
Clergyman	O
:	O
He	O
dedicates	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
to	O
the	O
Instruction	O
of	O
The	O
lower	O
Orders	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
considers	O
principally	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
his	O
aſsistance	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Parish	O
he	O
has	O
instituted	O
a	O
School	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
presides	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
which	O
all	O
the	O
infant	O
Poor	O
are	O
admitted	O
.	O
The	O
present	O
Work	O
is	O
intended	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
these	O
little	O
Ones	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
perfect	O
of	O
its	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
Gilpin	B-pers
has	O
given	O
no	O
Comments	O
specifically	O
on	O
the	O
Commandments	O
,	O
and	O
Secker	B-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
thousand	O
reasons	O
,	O
is	O
ill-calculated	O
for	O
an	O
infant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
I	O
presum	O
'd	O
to	O
mention	O
the	O
present	O
Performance	O
:	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
myself	O
happy	O
if	O
it	O
answers	O
the	O
expectation	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
may	O
have	O
formd	O
from	O
my	O
description	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
be	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
yr	O
sincere	O
Friend	O
and	O
obt	O
servt	O
John	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
17	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1782	O
Kew	B-place
