TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Single	O
Mama	O
desires	O
her	O
kindest	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
which	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
unite	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
does	O
not	O
forget	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
the	O
Aſses	O
who	O
all	O
wish	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
&	O
love	O
her	O
dearly	O
--	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
our	O
Northampton	B-place
Ladies	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
?	O
one	O
is	O
Extract	O
from	O
Darwin	B-pers
's	O
Poem	O
The	O
Loves	O
of	O
the	O
Plants	O
“	O
--	O
So	O
now	O
Delany	B-pers
forms	O
her	O
mimic	O
Bowers	O
,	O
Her	O
Paper	O
Foliage	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
silken	O
Flowers	O
;	O
Her	O
Virgin	O
Train	O
the	O
tender	O
Sciſsars	O
ply	O
,	O
Vein	O
the	O
green	O
leaf	O
,	O
the	O
purple	O
Petal	O
dye	O
:	O
Bound	O
wiry	O
Stems	O
the	O
flaxen	O
tendril	O
bends	O
,	O
Moſs	O
creeps	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
waxen	O
Fruit	O
impends	O
.	O
Cold	O
Winter	O
views	O
amid	O
his	O
realms	O
of	O
Snow	O
Delany	B-pers
's	O
vegetable	O
Statues	O
blow	O
;	O
Smooth	O
's	O
his	O
stern	O
brow	O
,	O
delays	O
his	O
hoary	O
wing	O
,	O
And	O
Eyes	O
with	O
wonder	O
all	O
the	O
Blooms	O
of	O
Spring	O
Erasmus	O
Darwin	O
(	O
1789	O
)	O
The	O
Loves	O
of	O
the	O
Plants	O
,	O
ll.155-64	O
.	O
Mama	O
desires	O
I	O
will	O
add	O
in	O
Case	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
this	O
Poem	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
curious	O
Production	O
of	O
Genius	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Poetr	O
y	O
fine	O
.	O
