TOKEN	NE
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
my	O
Dear	O
that	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
really	O
finds	O
you	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
exceedingly	O
so	O
that	O
your	O
pains	O
have	O
erased	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
you	O
was	O
alarmed	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
a	O
Sore	O
Throat	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
coming	O
here	O
till	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
certain	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
reason	O
that	O
prevents	O
yr	O
coming	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
never	O
feel	O
the	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
relieve	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
follow	O
my	O
Motherly	O
Advice	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
coming	O
Thursday	O
I	O
forbid	O
you	O
.	O
Dr	O
little	O
Prſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
she	O
with	O
me	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
Love	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
deliver	O
yours	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
with	O
Denoyer	B-pers
but	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
Dr	O
most	O
Afy	O
Yr	O
MCG	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
