TOKEN	NE
From	O
J	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
Bell	O
Derby	B-place
17	O
Feby	O
1789	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
Here	O
am	O
I	O
arrived	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
tolerably	O
dry	O
from	O
the	O
Knees	O
upwards	O
--	O
but	O
below	O
that	O
point	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
plight	O
indeed	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
something	O
that	O
will	O
call	O
forth	O
feelings	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
Nature	O
--	O
That	O
poor	O
wretch	O
Sir	B-pers
Hry	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
is	O
dead	O
'	O
--	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
--	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
that	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
Ly	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
will	O
be	O
in	O
great	O
distreſs	O
Yet	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
rejoicing	O
that	O
an	O
End	O
is	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
uncomfortable	O
State	O
in	O
which	O
She	O
lived	O
--	O
Kiſs	O
our	O
dear	O
Child	O
an	O
hundred	O
times	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Sweet	O
little	O
Creature	O
how	O
affectionate	O
She	O
is	O
--	O
I	O
still	O
see	O
her	O
sitting	O
in	O
State	O
with	O
the	O
pillow	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
enjoying	O
herself	O
--	O
If	O
it	O
shall	O
please	O
God	O
to	O
bleſs	O
her	O
&	O
me	O
by	O
sparing	O
your	O
precious	O
Life	O
--	O
She	O
may	O
grow	O
up	O
an	O
Ornament	O
to	O
Society	O
&	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
Excellence	O
to	O
her	O
Sex	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
the	O
happiest	O
of	O
Husbands	O
I	O
am	O
Yours	O
entirely	O
And	O
Most	O
Affly	O
JD	B-pers
Say	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
proper	O
to	O
the	O
Tredrille	O
party	O
--	O
