TOKEN	NE
Impromptu	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
Octer	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1779	O
Ye	O
lovely	O
stars	O
of	O
Sunning	B-place
dale	I-place
Which	O
you	O
with	O
brightneſs	O
fill	O
,	O
Leonidas	O
muſt	O
now	O
bewail	O
Your	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
hill	O
.	O
There	O
damps	O
and	O
rain	O
di	O
s	O
ſ	O
solve	O
your	O
charm	O
;	O
Sore	O
cramps	O
his	O
speed	O
have	O
barr	O
'd	O
;	O
Poor	O
wife	O
sighs	O
oer	O
a	O
scalded	O
arm	O
,	O
And	O
can	O
not	O
hold	O
a	O
card	O
.	O
