TOKEN	NE
1	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
7	O
th	O
March	O
1773	O
Your	O
very	O
kind	O
Letter	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
will	O
occasion	O
you	O
more	O
trouble	O
than	O
you	O
were	O
aware	O
on	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
propoſe	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
your	O
complaints	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
fatigue	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
apt	O
to	O
pay	O
too	O
little	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
Complaints	O
of	O
young	O
people	O
as	O
being	O
but	O
temporary	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ſincerely	O
wiſh	O
your	O
's	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
ſhortest	O
duration	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
mended	O
my	O
Pen	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
;	O
which	O
ſerves	O
like	O
a	O
Hem	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Cough	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
blowing	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
pause	O
,	O
in	O
Converſation	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
gives	O
one	O
time	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
&	O
put	O
one	O
's	O
Words	O
in	O
order	O
.	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
intended	O
by	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
vindication	O
of	O
my	O
Conduct	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
begin	O
;	O
--	O
that	O
looks	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
plead	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Cause	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
confeſs	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
vindicate	O
myſelf	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Story	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
muſt	O
begin	O
with	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
my	O
marriage	O
;	O
--	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
commencement	O
of	O
my	O
happineſs	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
afterwards	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
origin	O
of	O
my	O
misfortunes	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
busineſs	O
,	O
&	O
could	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
very	O
comfortably	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
confided	O
in	O
Poſseſsion	O
alone	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
2	O
trusted	O
to	O
Hopes	O
&	O
Expectations	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
's	O
father	O
had	O
often	O
declared	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
preference	O
before	O
marriage	O
,	O
that	O
ſhe	O
ſhould	O
have	O
a	O
fortune	O
of	O
£5	O
.	O
or	O
6000.	O
and	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
hearty	O
Reconci	O
l	O
liation	O
.	O
An	O
old	O
Aunt	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
Coheireſs	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
)	O
had	O
often	O
aſsured	O
her	O
ſhe	O
would	O
leave	O
her	O
£10,000	O
.	O
--	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
reaſon	O
to	O
expect	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
Articles	O
he	O
himself	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
partnerſhip	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
Trade	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
Twenty	O
,	O
)	O
that	O
my	O
Patrimony	O
would	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
term	O
of	O
years	O
,	O
be	O
doubled	O
.	O
--	O
With	O
all	O
theſe	O
proſpects	O
in	O
View	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
numerous	O
acquaintance	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
natural	O
for	O
young	O
people	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
ſtile	O
of	O
Life	O
far	O
beyond	O
their	O
Income	O
.	O
mean	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Aunt	O
died	O
without	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
Will	O
;	O
--	O
The	O
expected	O
Reconciliation	O
never	O
took	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
dear	O
Companion	O
could	O
wait	O
for	O
it	O
no	O
longer	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
'll	O
ſend	O
you	O
with	O
This	O
two	O
the	O
Copies	O
of	O
two	O
Letters	O
ſhe	O
wrote	O
her	O
Parents	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
,	O
which	O
ſhe	O
certainly	O
kept	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
juſtification	O
;	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
preſerve	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
leſt	O
they	O
may	O
hereafter	O
be	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
mother	O
's	O
Death	O
was	O
occaſion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
conſtitutional	O
3	O
Disorder	O
;	O
whereas	O
,	O
theſe	O
Letters	O
ſhew	O
that	O
the	O
Cause	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
conſtant	O
operation	O
of	O
real	O
Sorrow	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
when	O
ſhe	O
wrote	O
these	O
Copies	O
contrary	O
to	O
her	O
custom	O
ſhe	O
muſt	O
certainly	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
End	O
in	O
meditation	O
.	O
--	O
Since	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
paſs	O
this	O
melancholy	O
Subject	O
unnoticed	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
my	O
Papers	O
concerning	O
It	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
ſend	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
Collection	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
mentioning	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
only	O
adds	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
my	O
ſerious	O
Reflection	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
painful	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
consider	O
that	O
the	O
peruſal	O
of	O
m	O
th	O
e	O
affecting	O
narration	O
may	O
afford	O
Inſtruction	O
to	O
an	O
a	O
young	O
&	O
unexperienced	O
Friend	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
'll	O
find	O
,	O
among	O
theſe	O
Papers	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
's	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
and	O
her	O
laſt	O
one	O
from	O
Brockhall	B-place
in	O
this	O
County	O
,	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
--	O
both	O
preſerv	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Copies	O
of	O
her	O
Letters	O
to	O
her	O
Parents	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
handwriting	O
;	O
--	O
you	O
'll	O
next	O
find	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
written	O
to	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
in	O
Holland	B-place
,	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
deſired	O
he	O
might	O
return	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
to	O
contribute	O
towards	O
the	O
future	O
ſatisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
Children	O
;	O
--	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
alſo	O
read	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
our	O
moſt	O
intimate	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bayne	I-pers
,	O
4	O
(	O
a	O
moſt	O
worthy	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
E	B-place
:	I-place
Indies	I-place
,	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ſo	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
to	O
reconcile	O
me	O
to	O
myself	O
after	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
--	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
conſidering	O
myself	O
as	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Causer	O
Author	O
--	O
Peace	O
to	O
her	O
good	O
Soul	O
!	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
forgot	O
it	O
yet	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
often	O
I	O
have	O
attempted	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
Beauty	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
often	O
wiſh	O
'd	O
my	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
Mind	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
--	O
And	O
thence	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
ſprung	O
another	O
cause	O
of	O
my	O
Misfortunes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Winter	O
after	O
my	O
Loſs	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
my	O
Return	O
to	O
London	B-place
,	O
my	O
Companions	O
,	O
perceiving	O
my	O
melancholy	O
but	O
little	O
diminiſh	O
'd	O
,	O
imagined	O
,	O
the	O
Amusements	O
&	O
Diſsipation	O
of	O
the	B-place
Town	I-place
,	O
would	O
be	O
moſt	O
conducive	O
to	O
banish	O
my	O
Sorrow	O
.	O
--	O
They	O
accordingly	O
plunged	O
me	O
headlong	O
into	O
them	O
;	O
&	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
wrote	O
the	O
inclosed	O
Letter	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
firſt	O
to	O
ſhew	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
wish	O
'd	O
-for	O
Relief	O
.	O
What	O
my	O
ſmall	O
ſhare	O
of	O
Religion	O
&	O
Philosophy	O
could	O
not	O
effect	O
,	O
was	O
operated	O
by	O
Diſsipation	O
;	O
&	O
a	O
conſtant	O
repetition	O
of	O
ſuch	O
a	O
palatable	O
&	O
palliative	O
Medicine	O
,	O
by	O
degrees	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
;	O
--	O
ſo	O
far	O
at	O
leaſt	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
Mind	O
from	O
dwelling	O
5	O
dwelling	O
on	O
the	O
Recoll	O
e	O
ction	O
of	O
happier	O
Days	O
;	O
--	O
for	O
ſtill	O
they	O
will	O
occur	O
to	O
my	O
Memory	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
left	O
without	O
attachment	O
to	O
ſome	O
female	O
friend	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
conſider	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
understanding	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
read	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
though	O
ſhe	O
has	O
ſ	O
yet	O
ſeen	O
little	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
thus	O
hazard	O
her	O
good	O
opinion	O
by	O
a	O
confeſsion	O
of	O
my	O
Sins	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
too	O
,	O
muſt	O
be	O
indulgent	O
to	O
my	O
weakneſs	O
,	O
&	O
consider	O
me	O
leſs	O
as	O
an	O
impoſtor	O
than	O
a	O
fool	O
;	O
--	O
and	O
indeed	O
my	O
whole	O
Life	O
has	O
been	O
folly	O
&	O
extravagance	O
;	O
&	O
,	O
on	O
reflecting	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
narration	O
ought	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
term	O
'd	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cauſes	O
of	O
my	O
failing	O
in	O
Life	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
Justification	O
of	O
my	O
Conduct	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Relations	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
have	O
aſsiſted	O
in	O
handing	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
few	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
'till	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
reach	O
'd	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
--	O
But	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
I	O
ſhall	O
ſleep	O
on	O
to-night	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
'll	O
only	O
add	O
a	O
ſhort	O
application	O
to	O
the	O
above	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Tale	O
:	O
--	O
It	O
teaches	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
ſolid	O
Conſolation	O
under	O
the	O
Afflictions	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
virtuous	O
Life	O
Conduct	O
&	O
a	O
constant	O
resignation	O
to	O
the	O
divine	O
Will	O
.	O
--	O
6	O
.	O
Monday	O
morng	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
ſpared	O
myself	O
the	O
Moral	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
laſt	O
Page	O
,	O
for	O
on	O
reading	O
over	O
again	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
have	O
ſtolen	O
the	O
Reflection	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
confounded	O
my	O
head	O
ſo	O
much	O
with	O
reading	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
wonder	O
my	O
invention	O
,	O
Evening	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
bright	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
--	O
To	O
proceed	O
with	O
my	O
Story	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Relations	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
let	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Linlithgow	I-place
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
got	O
me	O
elected	O
to	O
repreſent	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Petition	O
preſented	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
againſt	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
my	O
Election	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
That	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Carriage	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Winters	O
,	O
to	O
drive	O
about	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
viſit	O
the	O
great	O
people	O
&	O
to	O
ſolicit	O
Votes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
thruſt	O
myself	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
into	O
company	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
ſ	O
l	O
give	O
Entertainments	O
;	O
--	O
for	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Relations	O
by	O
but	O
£200	O
.	O
pr	O
:	O
Ann	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
thus	O
led	O
into	O
expenſive	O
Connexions	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afterwards	O
ſo	O
ſpeedily	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
been	O
allow	O
'd	O
a	O
proper	O
any	O
other	O
compensation	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
than	O
as	O
above	O
named	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
have	O
deserted	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
my	O
Vote	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
agreeable	O
with	O
their	O
ſelfish	O
Views	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
really	O
the	O
Case	O
;	O
for	O
motives	O
of	O
public	O
benefit	O
,	O
they	O
can	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
deserting	O
me	O
;	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
(	O
written	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
preſent	O
minister	O
was	O
not	O
expected	O
to	O
ſtand	O
,	O
)	O
expreſsing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
warmeſt	O
manner	O
,	O
his	O
approbation	O
of	O
my	O
voting	O
according	O
to	O
Conſcience	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
ſat	O
in	O
Parliament	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
but	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
--	O
Here	O
you	O
ſee	O
my	O
private	O
Reaſon	O
for	O
publiſhing	O
the	O
political	O
Letters	O
I	O
ſhew	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
When	O
a	O
man	O
talks	O
much	O
about	O
himself	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
either	O
from	O
Vanity	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
consciousness	O
that	O
his	O
Conduct	O
ſtands	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
Justification	O
:	O
--	O
I	O
foreſaw	O
my	O
Affairs	O
would	O
one	O
day	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
Criſis	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
to	O
bespeak	O
the	O
pity	O
of	O
the	O
Public	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
their	O
forgiveneſs	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
my	O
Follies	O
.	O
--	O
But	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
comment	O
on	O
my	O
Letters	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
needleſsly	O
to	O
expoſe	O
my	O
Relations	O
;	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
acted	O
vindictively	O
&	O
offenſively	O
,	O
inſtead	O
8	O
of	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Defenſive	O
,	O
I	O
ſhould	O
have	O
added	O
Lord	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
to	O
my	O
Publication	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
without	O
ſerving	O
myself	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
injured	O
perhaps	O
have	O
materially	O
injured	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
His	O
aim	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
British	O
Peerage	O
;	O
&	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
That	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
&	O
Him	O
muſt	O
prove	O
the	O
ir	O
ſincerity	O
of	O
their	O
Attachment	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
abandoning	O
me	O
&	O
ſhewing	O
a	O
lasting	O
&	O
public	O
Resentment	O
&	O
public	O
Disapprobation	O
of	O
my	O
political	O
Conduct	O
.	O
I	O
ſhall	O
I	O
am	O
thus	O
become	O
a	O
Victim	O
to	O
Ambition	O
.	O
--	O
But	O
they	O
will	O
never	O
gain	O
their	O
Ends	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
too	O
well	O
in	O
what	O
Light	O
our	O
Family	O
is	O
looked	O
upon	O
at	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
expect	O
they	O
'll	O
be	O
ſhewn	O
any	O
favour	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
them	O
ſo	O
,	O
formerly	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
thought	O
me	O
a	O
young	O
Politician	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
younger	O
ſtill	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
gain	O
more	O
credit	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Vote	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
belonging	O
to	O
your	O
family	O
;	O
--	O
Suppoſe	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
purport	O
;	O
--	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
ſome	O
effect	O
in	O
my	O
favour	O
,	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
ill	O
taken	O
;	O
--	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Circumſtance	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
open	O
their	O
Eyes	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Intereſt	O
9	O
Intereſt	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
ſuppoſe	O
,	O
to	O
they	O
have	O
with	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
favourite	O
;	O
--	O
if	O
in	O
This	O
I	O
ask	O
any	O
thing	O
improper	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
to	O
grant	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
judge	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
the	O
Liberty	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
;	O
ſince	O
I	O
was	O
deſired	O
to	O
point	O
out	O
in	O
what	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
--	O
Now	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
proposed	O
Letter	O
:	O
--	O
“	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
--	O
My	O
mother	O
&	O
I	O
having	O
“	O
ſent	O
to	O
your	O
Couſin	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
“	O
confined	O
here	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
in	O
what	O
“	O
we	O
could	O
ſerve	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
“	O
Anſwer	O
,	O
his	O
Requeſt	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
write	O
“	O
your	O
Lordship	O
the	O
following	O
Anecdote	O
,	O
which	O
“	O
he	O
thought	O
might	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
in	O
removing	O
“	O
one	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
displeaſure	O
of	O
his	O
Relations	O
,	O
“	O
arising	O
to	O
from	O
the	O
part	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
parliament	O
“	O
contrary	O
in	O
oppoſition	O
to	O
their	O
political	O
“	O
friends	O
.	O
--	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
“	I-pers
Weir	I-pers
's	O
laſt	O
Election	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
“	O
Linlithgow	B-place
,	O
Several	O
People	O
in	O
ye	O
Court	O
interest	O
came	O
“	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
expreſs	O
requeſt	O
,	O
from	O
“	O
Lord	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
vote	O
“	O
for	O
Sir	B-pers
Willm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Cuningham	I-pers
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
1	O
0	O
“	O
neuter	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
his	O
Vote	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
--	O
“	O
Forgive	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Liberty	O
I	O
have	O
“	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
ſole	O
view	O
of	O
ſerving	O
a	O
friend	O
“	O
in	O
need	O
,	O
”	O
&	O
c	O
a	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
a	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
the	O
matter	O
only	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
expreſs	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
Words	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
laſt	O
,	O
a	O
poetical	O
Description	O
of	O
my	O
Confinement	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
far	O
from	O
Distreſs	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
lodged	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
fine	O
pleaſant	O
Bowling	O
Green	O
,	O
to	O
walk	O
on	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
pleaſe	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Bowling	O
Green	O
Houſe	O
,	O
oppoſite	O
the	O
old	O
Castle	O
Walls	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
ſend	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wye	I-pers
's	O
,	O
your	O
own	O
choice	O
of	O
a	O
French	O
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
Italian	O
Book	O
;	O
&	O
he	O
will	O
forward	O
them	O
hence	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Lines	O
,	O
I	O
ſent	O
you	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dicey	I-pers
inſiſted	O
on	O
printing	O
;	O
&	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
deſtributed	O
among	O
Acquaintances	O
to-	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
all	O
the	O
Papers	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
ſend	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Portefeuille	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
left	O
them	O
looſe	O
in	O
my	O
Bureau	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wye	I-pers
's	O
;	O
--	O
you	O
ſhall	O
have	O
them	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
(	O
thoſe	O
that	O
are	O
wanting	O
;	O
--	O
)	O
mean	O
while	O
I	O
11	O
I	O
have	O
ſupplied	O
their	O
Place	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
give	O
equal	O
Illucidation	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
circumſtances	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
ſocial	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
.	O
--	O
Indeed	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
ever	O
ventures	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
for	O
Life	O
,	O
muſt	O
resemble	O
her	O
in	O
character	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
ſhall	O
ne'er	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
--	O
Forgive	O
me	O
touching	O
on	O
that	O
String	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
ſometim	O
es	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
--	O
)	O
it	O
made	O
every	O
Nerve	O
of	O
me	O
thrill	O
again	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
this	O
Letter	O
before	O
Dinner	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Pauſe	O
,	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
ſolitary	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Bowling	O
Green	O
,	O
to	O
drive	O
away	O
the	O
Reflections	O
occaſion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
opening	O
these	O
Papers	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dicey	I-pers
found	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
prevented	O
me	O
proceeding	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
--	O
After	O
Dinner	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
it	O
was	O
Aſsembly	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
reſolved	O
not	O
to	O
ſadden	O
the	O
Mirth	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
next	O
ſtruck	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
melancholy	O
Tale	O
might	O
haunt	O
your	O
Dreams	O
&	O
disturb	O
your	O
Reſt	O
;	O
which	O
prevents	O
me	O
from	O
sending	O
it	O
'till	O
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
--	O
As	O
it	O
my	O
Will	O
is	O
,	O
These	O
ſheets	O
ſhould	O
be	O
preſerved	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
date	O
,	O
ſign	O
,	O
&	O
direct	O
it	O
them	O
in	O
due	O
form	O
.	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Your	O
obliged	O
&	O
affecte	O
:	O
friend	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
--	O
Monday	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1773	O
Docr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bleneve	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
this	O
Evening	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
gain	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
more	O
acquainted	O
.	O
--	O
This	O
Paper	O
to	O
be	O
preserved	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
if	O
demanded	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
