TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
left	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
&	O
had	O
in	O
charge	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
together	O
with	O
your	O
marriage	O
Settlement	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
since	O
understood	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
further	O
use	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
subsequent	O
arrangement	O
;	O
my	O
motive	O
in	O
returning	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
was	O
perfectly	O
innocent	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
has	O
either	O
not	O
been	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
this	O
transaction	O
differently	O
from	O
what	O
was	O
my	O
meaning	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
exhibited	O
such	O
uncommon	O
instances	O
of	O
friendship	O
and	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
afflicting	O
occasion	O
,	O
I	O
shoud	O
abhor	O
myself	O
,	O
cou	O
'd	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
soon	O
been	O
capable	O
of	O
forgetting	O
my	O
obligations	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
therefore	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
relieved	O
from	O
my	O
anxiety	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
;	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
my	O
present	O
distreſs	O
I	O
can	O
ill	O
bear	O
the	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
acted	O
improperly	O
towards	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
claim	O
to	O
my	O
esteem	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
August	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
49	O
.	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
single	O
Mr	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Aug	O
.	O
19	O
1810	O
