TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1800	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
post	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
condescend	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
comfortably	O
seated	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Arm	O
Chair	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
well	O
jumbled	O
croſsing	O
Carter	O
Fell	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
at	O
Newcastle	B-place
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Covey	O
is	O
now	O
collected	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Addition	O
,	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Patrick	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
is	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Maria	B-pers
entirely	O
free	O
from	O
a	O
Cough	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
troublesome	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Months	O
Weeks	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
pulled	O
her	O
down	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
My	O
sovereign	O
remedy	O
,	O
Aſses	O
Milk	O
,	O
removed	O
the	O
Cough	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
the	O
warm	O
weather	O
will	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
like	O
herself	O
again	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
have	O
commissioned	O
me	O
to	O
return	O
you	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Your	O
Books	O
are	O
deposited	O
in	O
their	O
collections	O
,	O
and	O
form	O
a	O
very	O
smart	O
addition	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
has	O
transferred	O
the	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
daughter	O
.	O
Our	O
Cousins	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
friendly	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
I	O
dined	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
Greville	O
Mansfields	O
,	O
had	O
She	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
see	O
much	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
admitted	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
a	O
forenoon	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
looking	O
delicate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
were	O
not	O
living	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
He	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Regiment	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
,	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
thriving	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
burden	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
fortunate	O
,	O
and	O
produce	O
a	O
Son	O
.	O
Our	O
friend	O
Archibald	B-pers
was	O
made	O
a	O
Churchman	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
wish	O
.	O
Had	O
his	O
father	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
probably	O
might	O
have	O
procured	O
some	O
decent	O
provision	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Military	O
spirit	O
he	O
exhibits	O
might	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
necessity	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
Parish	O
Priests	O
,	O
besworded	O
,	O
and	O
be-Helmeted	O
.	O
Poor	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
acting	O
laudably	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
entered	O
on	O
the	O
drilling	O
of	O
a	O
Troop	O
.	O
The	O
opinion	O
of	O
Bishops	O
,	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
different	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Hay	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
busy	O
.	O
Present	O
my	O
Love	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
and	O
those	O
of	O
my	O
Household	O
,	O
to	O
your	O
Guid	O
Man	O
,	O
your	O
Brat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Tenth	O
July	O
1800	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
HAWICK	B-place
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
