TOKEN	NE
March	O
1797	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
their	O
portraits	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
elder	O
orme	B-pers
also	O
their	O
Daughter	O
1797	O
(	O
22	O
d	O
Febry-	O
)	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Arrived	O
in	O
London	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
our	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
Lower	O
Brook	O
Str	O
.	O
Nr	O
:	O
58	O
--	O
found	O
Morrison	B-pers
there	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
dinner	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
left	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Profile	O
--	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dining	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Br	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
dined	O
out	O
these	O
7	O
Years	O
--	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
Leave	O
Londn	B-place
.	I-place
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Sons	O
Sr.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
at	O
Caulk	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
he	O
also	O
went	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
Dearest	O
of	O
friends	O
well	O
--	O
her	O
two	O
daughters	O
at	O
home	O
Marianne	B-pers
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
Charlotte	B-pers
quite	O
gay	O
.	O
Sup	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
--	O
Wrote	O
letter	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
at	O
Bath	B-place
23	O
d	O
/	O
A	O
Footman	O
came	O
recommended	O
by	O
Mr-	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
--	O
we	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
one	O
Guinea	O
pr	O
.	O
week	O
--	O
his	O
name	O
Martyn	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
a	O
married	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
steady	O
appearance	O
seemingly	O
between	O
40	O
&	O
50	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
&	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
sattin	O
Housewife	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
L	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
--	O
10	O
--	O
saw	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
amiable	O
woman	O
lookg	O
well	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
14	O
--	O
Saw	O
there	O
also	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Weldren	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Governeſs	O
who	O
seems	O
in	O
a	O
decline	O
--	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
wth-	O
her	O
before	O
Ly	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
Call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
King	I-pers
she	O
is	O
better	O
still	O
in	O
ye	O
Country	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
found	O
her	O
vastly	O
well	O
--	O
my	O
Lord	O
better	O
but	O
still	O
indifferent	O
--	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
(	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
)	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
s	O
he	O
is	O
still	O
confined	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
&	O
declining	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
me	O
din	O
'd	O
Lady	B-pers
Wa	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Left	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
there	O
went	O
at	O
7	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
--	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
Much	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
tolerably	O
--	O
saw	O
Ly	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
who	O
is	O
grown	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Girl	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Dogr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s	O
--	O
saw	O
the	O
General	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
her	O
husband	O
--	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
there	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
found	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
Went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Ducie	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
,	O
Baron	B-pers
Nagell	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Husband	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
Whist	O
party	O
--	O
Baron	B-pers
Nagell	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
went	O
away	O
we	O
staid	O
supper	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
early	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
agreeable	O
Eveg	O
at	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
amusement	O
in	O
relating	O
wonderful	O
Stories	O
of	O
Ghosts	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Sent	O
Letters	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
Friday	O
--	O
Schram	B-pers
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
L	B-pers
&	O
I.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
ye	O
Daughters	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
at	O
Blackheath	B-place
where	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
small	O
house	O
for	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
melancholy	O
State	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
at	O
Bath	B-place
for	O
her	O
health	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
s	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
left	O
notes	O
--	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Homes	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
7	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
her	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Montgommerys	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
11	O
ye	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
of	O
next	O
Mont	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
)	O
the	O
youngest	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Susan	I-pers
14	O
Months	O
younger	O
--	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
was	O
much	O
affected	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
so	O
deplorable	O
a	O
state	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
at	O
home	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
De	I-pers
S——	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
s	O
aſsembly	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Peckhamwell	I-pers
there	O
Nephew	O
--	O
an	O
agreeable	O
sensible	O
modest	O
young	O
Man	O
of	O
20	O
Studies	O
ye	O
.	O
law	O
--	O
Came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
Wrote	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Finch-Hatton	I-pers
(	I-pers
née	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
)	I-pers
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Ladies	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Saturday	O
--	O
25	O
Febry-	O
/	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Hair	O
Dreſser	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
&	O
Me	O
--	O
To	O
begin	O
to	O
dreſs	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
at	O
10-6	O
Pr	O
.	O
Week	O
--	O
much	O
amused	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
volubility	O
--	O
of	O
tongue	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Dixon	B-pers
accompanied	O
by	O
Louisa	B-pers
at	O
12	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
converse	O
abt	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
My	O
dear	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
Mem	O
}	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
never	O
invited	O
in	O
private	O
since	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sophia	I-pers
s	O
affair	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kennicot	I-pers
he	O
seemed	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
(	O
Md	O
.	O
of	O
Honor	O
)	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
there	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
saw	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leveson	I-pers
--	O
the	O
landg	O
of	O
French	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
1400	O
taken	O
prisoners	O
--	O
--	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Lord	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Miſs	O
Mordaunts	O
Ly	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
calld	O
at	O
some	O
other	O
Miſs	O
Mordaunts	O
there	O
--	O
places	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
s	O
before	O
8	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
staid	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
confidential	O
conversation	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
till	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
looks	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
has	O
outgrown	O
his	O
strength	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
from	O
Westr	O
.	O
School	O
there	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
12	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
agre̅able	O
pretty	O
boy	O
--	O
he	O
cuts	O
out	O
admirably	O
--	O
Dogs	O
Horses	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
c	O
u	O
t	O
ab	O
o	O
ut	O
two	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
George	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
curious	O
complete	O
suit	O
of	O
armour	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
in	O
Tin	O
--	O
the	O
Shield	O
was	O
engraved	O
two	O
Warriors	O
resting	O
from	O
combat	O
--	O
all	O
done	O
wth-	O
an	O
old	O
pr	O
.	O
of	O
Siſsars	O
--	O
Henry	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
play	O
'd	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
wth	O
Mr.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
sent	O
her	O
home	O
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
her	O
Drawg-	O
Book	O
Sunday	O
26	O
read	O
Prayers	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
visits	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Selsey	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Home	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
Benn	B-pers
bad	O
cold	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Johnstone	B-pers
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
1	O
h	O
:	O
&	O
½	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
went	O
out	O
for	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D—	I-pers
saw	O
her	O
Morrison	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sally	B-pers
More	I-pers
Teston	B-place
Kent	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Bouvries	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
birth	O
day	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Marianne	B-pers
s	O
daughter	O
there	O
--	O
an	O
agreeable	O
young	O
Woman	O
26	O
years	O
old	O
--	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
set	O
Miſs	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Miller	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
went	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Nephew	O
of	O
hers	O
wth-	O
her	O
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
day	O
on	O
busineſs	O
--	O
Monday	O
27	O
th	O
Made	O
visits	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mat	I-pers
Montague	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
Ly-	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Fitzgerrald	I-pers
s	O
--	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
s	O
--	O
still	O
very	O
ill	O
--	O
some	O
other	O
visits	O
--	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Genl-	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
to	O
a	O
Ld	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
s	O
After	O
7	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
--	O
left	O
Mr	B-pers
Noverre	I-pers
there	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
Sub-	O
Concert	O
--	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
Berkely	O
Square	O
3	O
Good	O
rooms	O
--	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
&	O
very	O
handsome	O
taste	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
abt-	O
the	O
Iremongers	O
--	O
saw	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
old	O
acquaintances	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
only	O
one	O
Instrument	O
ye	O
.	O
Large	O
piano	O
Forté	O
--	O
the	O
3	O
Miſs	O
Abrams	O
--	O
Genl-	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
&	O
c	O
sung	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
Went	O
at	O
11	O
to	O
Stephens	B-pers
saw	O
her	O
--	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Harrison	B-pers
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
has	O
3	O
Girls	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
eldest	O
3	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bigge	I-pers
s	O
Jeweller	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
trunk	O
of	O
Plate	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B—	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
low	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rundell	I-pers
s	O
who	O
died	O
this	O
Morng	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
86	O
--	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
ago	O
--	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
he	O
&	O
Doct	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Selsey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
there	O
who	O
reminded	O
me	O
of	O
civilities	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
her	O
Mother	O
&	O
Sisters	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
--	O
went	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
rather	O
fatigued	O
wth	O
her	O
Journey	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
every	O
day	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
called	O
--	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
Wedn	O
.	O
March	O
1	O
Made	O
Visits	O
--	O
Saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Schram	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Home	I-pers
with	O
her	O
--	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
displeased	O
that	O
7	O
Gentlemen	O
not	O
Peers	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Peers	O
seat	O
at	O
ye	O
Chapel	O
Royal	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſsrs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
who	O
was	O
very	O
friendly	O
&	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
who	O
surprised	O
me	O
by	O
looking	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
the	O
Dear	O
Woman	O
was	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Met	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
--	O
calld	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Found	O
M	O
saw	O
3	O
Miſs	O
Jacksons	O
&	O
their	O
Father	O
.	O
Sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
whos	O
cold	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
came	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
seem	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Spirits	O
.	O
--	O
Call	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
left	O
card	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Sent	O
name	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Orford	I-pers
Call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
took	O
her	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
s	O
where	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
only	O
Ly	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
day	O
--	O
took	O
Mrs	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
home	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
fine	O
shop	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
--	O
bought	O
an	O
Ink	O
stand	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Char	I-pers
:	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
wth-	O
Wedgewood	B-pers
since	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
several	O
People	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Sat	O
up	O
till	O
one	O
to	O
string	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Bracelet	O
.	O
Wrote	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Thursday	O
2	O
d	O
-	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
at	O
1	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
partly	O
well	O
except	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
back	O
--	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
--	O
Queens	O
House	O
--	O
Schram	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
&	O
c	O
:	O
all	O
well	O
--	O
left	O
name	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
King	B-pers
tomorrow	O
--	O
was	O
engaged	O
.	O
Queen	B-pers
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Went	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
down	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Haymarket	O
Theatre	O
--	O
a	O
Concert	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
New	O
musical	O
Fund	O
for	O
decayed	O
Musicians	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
found	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
very	O
indifferent	O
with	O
colds	O
sat	O
near	O
two	O
hours	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
Great	O
George	O
Str	O
.	O
Westr-	B-place
Herself	O
&	O
2	O
Sons	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Peckwell	I-pers
--	O
found	O
this	O
worthy	O
woman	O
much	O
alterd	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
he	O
has	O
already	O
3	O
children	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Home	I-pers
at	O
Ly-	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
s	O
--	O
saw	O
3	O
Miſs	O
Jackson	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Langton	I-pers
their	O
Governeſs	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
there	O
--	O
brought	O
Morrison	B-pers
home	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Noverre	B-pers
returned	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Concert	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
died	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
at	O
5	O
oClock	O
--	O
turned	O
80	O
--	O
Friday	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
their	B-pers
father	I-pers
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
abt	O
.	O
4	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
came	O
grown	O
a	O
fine	O
Girl	O
--	O
Poor	O
Lord	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
much	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Shram	B-pers
--	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
Good	O
news	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
taking	O
Spanish	O
Ships	O
by	O
Louisa	B-pers
every	O
body	O
in	O
great	O
spirits	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
tomorrow	O
look	O
'd	O
much	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
last	O
--	O
Took	O
Morrison	B-pers
wth-	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
visits	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lloyds	I-pers
(	O
Manchester	O
Street	O
Manchester	O
Square	O
)	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
but	O
low	O
but	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
Goes	O
to	O
her	O
Nephew	O
Admiral	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
s	O
Farnbourough	O
Place	O
.	O
for	O
6	O
weeks	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
Made	O
visits	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
(	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
--	O
Saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
--	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Conyers	O
&	O
a	O
frd	O
.	O
who	O
is	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
tolerably	O
well	O
&	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
recommended	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
as	O
a	O
drawing	O
Master	O
--	O
His	O
general	O
terms	O
are	O
4	O
leſsons	O
--	O
1-	O
L	O
1-	O
s	O
if	O
a	O
scholar	O
has	O
learnt	O
before	O
no	O
entrance	O
--	O
if	O
not	O
1	O
.	O
L	O
1	O
s	O
Teaches	O
etching	O
engraving	O
--	O
Chalks	O
Crayons	O
Water	O
&	O
Body	O
Colors	O
.	O
Miniature	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
¼	O
of	O
an	O
found	O
him	O
vastly	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Good	O
News	O
--	O
he	O
read	O
me	O
an	O
extract	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
L—	I-pers
&	O
Orme	B-pers
's	O
letters	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Continent	O
--	O
Printed	O
only	O
for	O
their	O
friends	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
affecting	O
Picture	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
ruined	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Revolution	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
us	O
--	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
perhaps	O
her	O
frd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
wth	O
us	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
Sr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
s	O
Box	O
at	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
Theatre	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
to	O
Charlotte	B-pers
at	O
4	O
--	O
am	O
extremely	O
pleased	O
with	O
his	O
Manner	O
of	O
teaching	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
s	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
Schram	B-pers
Louisa	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Nothing	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
news	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Spanish	O
½	O
Dollar	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
day	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
intelligence	O
--	O
Was	O
sorry	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
agreeable	O
party	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
who	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
tolerable	O
health	O
.	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Calder	I-pers
&	O
Admiral	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
was	O
much	O
amused	O
with	O
anecdotes	O
by	O
him	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
The	O
Minister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
to	O
make	O
mem	O
:	O
of	O
some	O
--	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Letter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Saturday	O
4	O
th	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
&	O
Ord	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
to	O
Dk	B-pers
.	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
--	O
Sent	O
Lord	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
some	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
dr	O
awings	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
--	O
Schram	B-pers
Orme	B-pers
s	O
Uncle	O
call	O
'd	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
--	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Lloy'ds	O
--	O
wth	O
.	O
offers	O
of	O
aſsistance	O
in	O
their	O
present	O
difficulties	O
from	O
Orme	B-pers
Went	O
to	O
Lady	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
&	O
Morrison	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Morrison	B-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
there	O
--	O
heard	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
had	O
written	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
recovered	O
--	O
Sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth-	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
saw	O
--	O
her	O
3	O
boys	O
&	O
girls	O
--	O
Eldest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
10	O
last	O
Novbr	O
youngest	O
boy	O
1	O
Year	O
¾	O
--	O
Sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Hatton	I-pers
She	O
talked	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
the	O
Genls-	O
Niece	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Hatton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Cecilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
&	O
c	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Lela	O
&	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
She	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
Goes	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
told	O
me	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Ly	B-pers
Julianna	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Selsey	I-pers
s	O
Eldest	O
Daughter	O
was	O
Married	O
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leveson	I-pers
(	I-pers
Gore	I-pers
)	I-pers
a	O
Scotchman	O
--	O
Who	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
in	O
India	B-place
--	O
he	O
is	O
ten	O
Years	O
older	O
than	O
ye	O
.	O
Duke	O
--	O
mem	O
:	O
entirely	O
her	O
own	O
choice	O
she	O
is	O
abt	O
.	O
20	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
her	O
very	O
fine	O
Diamonds	O
--	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
after	O
ye-	O
ceremony	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kings	I-pers
still	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
much	O
better	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
Dear	O
Dk	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
came	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
sleep	O
at	O
Sr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Mendes	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
be	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
time	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
Play	O
House	O
--	O
Admiral	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mr-	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
me	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
took	O
up	O
Miſs	B-pers
Anna	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Seige	O
of	O
Belgrade	O
very	O
thin	O
House	O
--	O
set	O
Louisa	B-pers
at	O
home	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
s	O
Bloomsbury	O
Sq	O
r	O
-	O
&	O
AM	B-pers
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
called	O
Sunday	O
5	O
March	O
--	O
Caught	O
so	O
severe	O
a	O
cold	O
&	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
could	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
AM	I-pers
came	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Foundling	O
--	O
Charlotte	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
Sister	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
dine	O
--	O
--	O
Recd	O
visits	O
&	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
A	B-pers
M—	I-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
3	O
Miſs	O
Jacksons	O
&	O
their	O
Governeſs	O
Morrison	B-pers
--	O
Morrison	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
--	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
long	O
Visits	O
Mr	B-pers
from	O
10	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
paid	O
long	O
visits	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Cicilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sr	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
she	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
dining	O
room	O
to	O
accomodate	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
--	O
sent	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
recd	O
.	O
Note	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Monday	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
to	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Roſs	I-pers
at	O
10	O
lent	O
her	O
my	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Porteous	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holyord	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
P	O
.	O
long	O
visit	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
Mr	B-pers
Scahm	I-pers
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
conversed	O
abt	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
A	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
for	O
¼	O
hour	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Piáno	O
Forté	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth-	O
us	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
came	O
early	O
in	O
ye-	O
afternoon	O
staid	O
supper	O
--	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
s	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
very	O
indifferent	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Morng	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
March	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Still	O
in	O
great	O
pain	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Came	O
after	O
breakfast	O
lent	O
her	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
She	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Bromley	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
Morrison	B-pers
came	O
while	O
Noverre	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
w	O
h	O
ere	O
here	O
--	O
heard	O
A	B-pers
M—	I-pers
play	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
visits	O
this	O
Morng	O
&	O
saw	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
--	O
Schram	B-pers
&	O
Orme	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Cicilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
.	O
her	O
Daughter	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leveson	I-pers
Gore	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Campbell	I-pers
at	O
5	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Susan	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
&	O
Schram	B-pers
came	O
early	O
to	O
tea	O
Louisa	B-pers
sat	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
little	O
Party	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
left	O
us	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
who	O
arrived	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
day	O
Ly	B-pers
sang	O
&	O
Play	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B—	I-pers
died	O
rather	O
suddenly	O
this	O
afternoon	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
sons	O
left	O
me	O
copy	O
of	O
original	O
letter	O
from	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
Wedy	O
.	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1797	O
Fast	O
day	O
--	O
still	O
indifferent	O
but	O
rather	O
better	O
not	O
yet	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
convers	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schewlenbergen	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
Pope	B-pers
--	O
&	O
dear	O
Ly	B-pers
Cicilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
--	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
&	O
seem	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
cd-	O
have	O
flattered	O
myself	O
after	O
all	O
her	O
ill	O
health	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
This	O
dr	O
.	O
friend	O
came	O
abt	O
.	O
8	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
staid	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
she	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
comfortable	O
little	O
Supper	O
--	O
it	O
put	O
us	O
in	O
Mind	O
of	O
past	O
times	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
not	O
quite	O
well	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
her	O
Cold	O
heavy	O
again	O
--	O
Gave	O
her	O
James	O
Powder	O
&	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
Thursday	O
8	O
th	O
9	O
th	O
March	O
1797	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
who	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
seems	O
very	O
well	O
this	O
Morng	O
--	O
except	O
a	O
cold	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
--	O
many	O
enquiries	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Old	O
Porter	O
who	O
once	O
lived	O
wth	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
had	O
him	O
upstairs	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lord	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
her	O
Neice	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye-	O
death	O
of	O
poor	O
Govenor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
--	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
england	B-place
this	O
Spring	O
--	O
has	O
left	O
his	O
young	O
Widow	O
wth-	O
a	O
Child	O
--	O
had	O
much	O
converse	O
abt	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
of	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Congratulated	O
her	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Marriage	O
of	O
her	O
eldest	O
Niece	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
is	O
soon	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
--	O
Henry	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
her	O
Father	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
s	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
8	O
more	O
Spanish	O
Ships	O
--	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
only	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
&	O
brought	O
ye	O
Papers	O
to	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
they	O
had	O
mislaid	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
immediately	O
to	O
Bromley	B-place
--	O
told	O
me	O
dr	O
:	O
Admiral	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
had	O
caught	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
--	O
sent	O
her	O
some	O
A—	O
Pills	O
--	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
had	O
a	O
kind	O
note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
W	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
s	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
also	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
De	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
delighted	O
to	O
find	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
eyes	O
better	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
we	O
gueſs	O
by	O
what	O
fell	O
in	O
conversation	O
63	O
years	O
old	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
England	B-place
in	O
1747	O
when	O
16	O
She	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
s	O
in	O
Yorkshire	B-place
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Housekeeper	O
of	O
ye	O
Queens	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
least	O
30	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
&	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
wth	O
.	O
Red	O
&	O
White	O
&	O
false	O
eye	O
brows	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
strong	O
nervous	O
affection	O
s	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
&	O
wear	O
Feathers	O
when	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
took	O
her	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Burlington	I-pers
s	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
s	O
during	O
her	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
met	O
at	O
Schram	B-pers
s	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
was	O
alone	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
--	O
wrote	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
--	O
Friday	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Noverre	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Nephew	O
came	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
many	O
particulars	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
s	O
death	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ord	I-pers
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
his	O
Brothers	O
have	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
very	O
large	O
as	O
represented	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Brothers	O
was	O
in	O
England	B-place
some	O
years	O
ago	O
&	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
audacity	O
to	O
present	O
a	O
Mistreſs	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Court	O
under	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
a	O
Lady	O
of	O
Quality	O
travell	O
'd	O
to	O
England	B-place
--	O
&	O
c	O
Monr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schwelenberg	I-pers
his	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
to	O
Germany	B-place
&	O
c	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
went	O
out	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wirtenberg	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
hour	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
beg	O
if	O
I	O
cld	O
.	O
I	O
wld	O
.	O
come	O
to	O
night	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Kenicott	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Chair	O
lest	O
I	O
shd	O
take	O
cold	O
in	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
carriage	O
--	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
L—y	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ventured	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kenicott	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
know	O
I	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
this	O
Eveg-	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
sent	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
in	O
to	O
her	O
Call	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
Md	O
of	O
Honor	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
coach	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
was	O
removed	O
5	O
oClock	O
next	O
Morng	O
&	O
c	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
opened	O
conjectured	O
to	O
be	O
67	O
--	O
Neither	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
n	O
or	O
herself	O
knew	O
her	O
age	O
.	O
--	O
Came	O
home	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schwbergen	I-pers
called	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
was	O
very	O
chilly	O
&	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Queen	B-pers
's	O
colds	O
heavy	O
upon	O
them	O
a	O
terribly	O
cold	O
bleak	O
Wind	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
Queen	B-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
partly	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
wth-	O
us	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
curious	O
collection	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
Louisa	B-pers
Morrison	B-pers
envited	O
us	O
much	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	B-place
--	O
was	O
uncom̅ly	O
pleasant	O
we	O
talked	O
confidentially	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
his	O
Son	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
Mr	B-pers
Havesides	I-pers
went	O
--	O
made	O
Mrs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
ho	O
h	O
n	O
ey	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Sent	O
Mr	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
a	O
double	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
by	O
Ly	B-pers
Webbe	I-pers
frank	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
to	O
day	O
sick	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Cold	O
--	O
Saturday	O
11	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Lousisa	B-pers
's	O
cold	O
so	O
indifferent	O
could	O
not	O
profit	O
much	O
by	O
her	O
leſson	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
thought	O
an	O
Airing	O
wd	O
do	O
me	O
good	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Shram	B-pers
s	O
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Orme	I-pers
Berkley	O
Sqr	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Scrham	I-pers
s	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hervey	I-pers
--	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs	B-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Arian̅a	I-pers
Egerton	I-pers
she	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye-	O
Coach	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
had	O
been	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
under	O
an	O
op	O
p	O
eration	O
for	O
his	O
Teeth	O
&	O
c	O
Doct	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warton	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Mason	O
Poems	O
Book	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
to	O
invite	O
us	O
to	O
dinner	O
tomorrow	O
&	O
c	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
afternoon	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
T—	I-pers
for	O
¼	O
hour	O
Ly	B-pers
C—	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
D—	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Sunday	O
12	O
March	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
read	O
Papers	O
to	O
us	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
scarce	O
--	O
Gold	O
was	O
become	O
--	O
a	O
Guinea	O
wd-	O
fetch	O
2	O
L	O
2	O
,	O
s	O
6	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
who	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
Recd-	O
Rundells	B-pers
frm	O
.	O
Dery	O
.	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
had	O
been	O
ordaind	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lloy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
inquire	O
Had	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
looks	O
ill	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
several	O
Visits	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
Mr	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
her	O
Yorkshire	B-place
Steward	O
dined	O
wth	O
us	O
--	O
a	O
Shrew	O
'd	O
sensible	O
quiet	O
Man	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
pd	O
.	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hervey	I-pers
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Bownes	I-pers
--	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
s	O
at	O
10	O
he	O
sat	O
half	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
s	O
cold	O
better	O
--	O
Meſsages	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Monday	O
13	O
th	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
cold	O
better	O
Mine	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepy	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng-	O
Recd	O
some	O
Visits	O
--	O
Went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriage	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
L.	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
ill	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
had	O
been	O
&	O
still	O
was	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
that	O
Louisa	B-pers
lived	O
at	O
Richmond	O
Lodge	O
--	O
has	O
two	O
Children	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
my	O
former	O
friend	O
--	O
his	O
Son	O
Noverre	B-pers
has	O
3	O
Children	O
--	O
(	O
Miſsrs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
dead	O
)	O
took	O
Sr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roſs	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
&	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
Sloane	O
Street	O
.	O
Calld	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
she	O
but	O
indifferent	O
Left	O
my	O
name	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
--	O
her	O
Mother	O
died	O
that	O
Morng	O
or	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
before	O
she	O
sent	O
some	O
relation	O
a	O
Widow	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Ly-	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chevely	I-pers
Home	O
.	O
calld	O
Lady	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
Gammon	I-pers
door	O
--	O
Several	O
visits	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
calld	O
&	O
left	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hindley	I-pers
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
&	O
very	O
pretty	O
viade	O
poche	O
&	O
some	O
books	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
took	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
at	O
6	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
to	O
the	O
Ball	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
but	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
took	O
Ly-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
Tavistock	O
Street	O
--	O
saw	O
Louisa	B-pers
who	O
promised	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
how	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
affairs	O
went	O
on	O
--	O
calld	O
Went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
found	O
these	O
worthy	O
people	O
at	O
Tea	O
--	O
wth-	O
3	O
of	O
their	O
Sons	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
them	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
came	O
--	O
home	O
--	O
Papa	O
&	O
Morrison	B-pers
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
12	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
quite	O
gay	O
&	O
happy	O
&	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
worse	O
for	O
dancing	O
There	O
were	O
at	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
&	O
Ly-	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
&	O
daughters	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
daughters	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Auckland	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Young	O
Mr	B-pers
too	O
much	O
indisposed	O
to	O
attend	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Home	I-pers
twice	O
Sent	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
to	O
thank	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Ball	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
14	O
th	O
:	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
again	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
this	O
afternoon	O
Recd	O
.	O
meſsages	O
&	O
Visits	O
--	O
Saw	O
Counte	O
the	O
two	O
Langtons	O
came	O
&	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Shram	B-pers
--	O
Went	O
out	O
at	O
one	O
tho	O
my	O
Cold	O
was	O
bad	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
--	O
Got	O
out	O
at	O
Dr	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
her	O
tolerably	O
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
caught	O
me	O
there	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
--	O
saw	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Poor	O
Mr-	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
can	O
not	O
last	O
long	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
her	O
Cold	O
bad	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
s	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
at	O
Mrs-	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
she	O
came	O
in	O
ye-	O
Coach	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
dined	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
after	O
Wch	O
.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
came	O
for	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng-	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
7	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
--	O
Saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Homes	I-pers
--	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
Leslie	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
much	O
better	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
at	O
Vienna	B-place
--	O
good	O
accts-	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
shew	O
'd	O
ye	O
Childn	O
.	O
some	O
drawgs	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Henry	B-pers
Ly	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
&	O
c	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
M—	I-pers
--	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
Orme	B-pers
married	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
to	O
day	O
Wednesday	O
16	O
15	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1797	O
Campel	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
A	I-pers
Gammon	I-pers
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Porteus	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Holyor'yd	I-pers
&	O
c	O
:	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
Much	O
in	O
praise	O
of	O
Lt.	B-pers
Col.	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
--	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
company	O
my	O
cold	O
so	O
bad	O
--	O
Shram	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Mordaunts	O
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
Orme	B-pers
L—	B-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
s	O
--	O
only	O
their	O
Son	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Farhill	I-pers
--	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Army	O
abt	O
.	O
17	O
--	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
time	O
previous	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
ye	B-place
.	I-place
Cape	I-place
of	I-place
Good	I-place
Hope	I-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Sister	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
came	O
in	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Cudg	O
l	O
e	O
l	O
playing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
5	O
daughter	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
15	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
6	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
ye	O
Youngest	O
at	O
Warwick	O
Castle	O
aged	O
6	O
months	O
delighted	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
who	O
is	O
3	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
3	O
Sons	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
in	O
Scotland	B-place
18	O
--	O
Corporal	B-pers
Kyle	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
--	O
the	O
latter	O
intended	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
at	O
Eaton	B-place
at	O
present	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Came	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
danced	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Cousins	O
--	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Tambour	O
de	O
basque	O
--	O
triangles	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Piano	O
Forté	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
brought	O
Lord	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
home	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
s	O
--	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
tea	O
--	O
Robert	B-pers
readg	O
ye	O
newspaper	O
to	O
the	O
once	O
much	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
who	O
is	O
now	O
quite	O
blind	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
however	O
very	O
stout	O
&	O
well	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
C—	I-pers
's	O
Cold	O
very	O
bad	O
--	O
She	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
present	O
of	O
2	O
birds	O
on	O
Vellum	O
wth	O
.	O
their	O
Natural	O
Feathers	O
we	O
--	O
came	O
abt	O
10	O
oClock	O
Thursday	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1797	O
/	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Col	B-pers
Barré	I-pers
&	O
she	O
went	O
this	O
Eveg	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lay	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
as	O
Louisa	B-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
James	O
Powder	O
--	O
Had	O
Shram	B-pers
in	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
friendly	O
to	O
me	O
Orme	B-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
5	O
daughters	O
--	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Noverre	B-pers
--	O
Saw	O
&	O
had	O
visits	O
frm	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Louisa	B-pers
told	O
me	O
much	O
abt	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
Monr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Guiffadierre	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
not	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
--	O
&	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Chart	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
wth-	O
her	O
--	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
G	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
She	O
&	O
P	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
s	O
little	O
Thursday	O
concert	O
--	O
he	O
again	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
he	O
brought	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	O
play	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
had	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
A	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
:	I-pers
for	O
ye	O
1	O
st	O
-	O
time	O
to	O
teach	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
exercise	O
of	O
ye	O
broad	O
Sword	O
--	O
L	O
1	O
:	O
s	O
1	O
entrance	O
3-	O
6	O
pr	O
Leſson	O
--	O
from	O
7	O
till	O
8	O
--	O
he	O
teaches	O
Louisa	B-pers
Morrison	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
wth	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
Sent	O
Letter	O
to	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
this	O
morng	O
--	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
ill	O
&	O
had	O
this	O
bad	O
Cold	O
Friday	O
17	O
th	O
..	O
March	O
1797	O
Corporal	B-pers
Lyle	I-pers
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
s	O
--	O
&	O
Winchelsea	B-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
all	O
Morng-	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
my	O
Cold	O
Miſs	B-pers
AMClarke	I-pers
came	O
to	O
invite	O
us	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
the	O
Dr	O
.	O
still	O
very	O
indifferent	O
wth-	O
ye	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
Sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
Noverre	B-pers
tomorrow	O
--	O
was	O
engaged	O
--	O
At	O
5	O
Schram	B-pers
&	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
--	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
Old	O
Woman	O
Not	O
so	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Sandel	O
wood	O
fan	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Porteous	I-pers
--	O
met	O
at	O
Ly-	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
A	O
very	O
pleasant	O
sensible	O
party	O
--	O
Like	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
extremely	O
--	O
a	O
Scotch-man	O
has	O
travell	O
'd	O
wth	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
talk	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
his	O
Lady	O
--	O
n.b	O
:	O
1	O
st	O
Year	O
2	O
200	O
Mitt	O
&	O
Mantua	O
Maker	O
--	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
Opera	O
Box	O
Servts-	O
every	O
thing	O
next	O
year	O
1700	O
--	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
allowance	O
of	O
600	O
Pin	O
Money	O
--	O
he	O
paid	O
60000	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
&	O
c	O
Much	O
talk	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Mr	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
--	O
her	O
swearing	O
&	O
c	O
Douglaſs	O
Cause	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Levinstone	I-pers
&	O
c	O
A	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
there	O
Neice	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Eglingtoun	I-pers
took	O
Dſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
home	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
Kyle	O
ye	O
Corporal	O
--	O
Major	B-pers
Sempil	I-pers
went	O
away	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foote	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
,	O
ye	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Madonalds	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
Shew	O
'd	O
ye-	O
Beautiful	O
Coral	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
--	O
spent	O
a	O
pleasant	O
½	O
hour	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
home	O
wth-	O
me	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
eat	O
oysters	O
&	O
c	O
Ly-	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Coll-	B-pers
s	O
ye	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
had	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
Satry-	O
18	O
March	O
1797	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Invitations	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Heavyside	I-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Miranda	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
&	O
Orme	B-pers
came	O
&	O
chatted	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
Berkely	O
Square	O
&	O
a	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
for	O
½	O
hour	O
--	O
Wake	B-pers
told	O
me	O
Langton	B-pers
had	O
3	O
boys	O
--	O
Algernon	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
is	O
now	O
Consul	O
at	O
Algiers	B-place
--	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
describe	O
as	O
a	O
red	O
dull	O
place	O
--	O
Climate	O
good	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
in	O
London	O
has	O
4	O
Children	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Some	O
other	O
visits	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
At	O
5	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Col	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
met	O
at	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Saledin	I-pers
de	I-pers
Cran	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
Charles	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Sisters	O
to	O
the	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
speaker	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
--	O
very	O
agreeable	O
sensible	O
Women	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
A	O
very	O
Pleasant	O
party	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Bragge	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Goodenough	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
George	I-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Rbt	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Louise	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
another	O
Sister	O
of	O
ye-	O
Speaker	O
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Abott	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Mathew	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Portuguese	O
Ambaſsador	O
--	O
the	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Gisburne	I-pers
--	O
&	O
many	O
others	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Batt	I-pers
went	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Corporal	O
--	O
Bishop	B-pers
Barington	I-pers
carriage	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
--	O
promised	O
if	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
Eveg-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
home	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
paragoric	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
immediately	O
being	O
sadly	O
oppreſsed	O
with	O
my	O
Cold	O
--	O
19	O
--	O
Had	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
night	O
of	O
coughing	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
People	O
to	O
bleed	O
me	O
.	O
his	O
Partner	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
came	O
a	O
pretty	O
Modest	O
young	O
man	O
--	O
Sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
Recd	O
visits	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
course	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
(	O
NB	O
he	O
staid	O
near	O
2	O
hours	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
Manuscripts	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
Devaynes	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Higinston	I-pers
--	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
took	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
--	O
he	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Montagus	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
Monday	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
came	O
staid	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
came	O
by	O
appointment	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
saw	O
dr	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hingiston	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Hatton	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
M	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
(	O
Son	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
Childers	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
George	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
--	O
very	O
pleasant	O
--	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
went	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Corporal	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leslie	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Circle	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Levan	I-pers
.	O
the	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Allens	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Ly-	B-pers
Ch—	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Cousin	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Md	O
.	O
of	O
Honor	O
--	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Dowgr	B-pers
Mrs	I-pers
:	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Lloy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
s	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
there	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Lelands	I-pers
Ly-	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
found	O
Ly-	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
playing	O
Duetts	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
sup	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
22	O
d	O
-	O
Ly	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Lloy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
--	O
took	O
Mr-	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Papa	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Paid	O
Visits	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Cunynghame	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
3	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
pretty	O
Work-basket	O
of	O
Noverre	B-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Call	O
'd	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
Privy	O
Gardens	O
--	O
his	O
Sister	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
gone	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
wth-	O
her	O
Niece	O
lately	O
married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
they	O
are	O
to	O
return	O
on	O
Saturday	O
next	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Do	O
.	O
Pſs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Sophia	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
--	O
Sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
--	O
Lt.	B-pers
Col.	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
there	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
daughter	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
s	O
½	O
Sister	O
a	O
beautiful	O
young	O
Woman	O
--	O
seems	O
Modest	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
--	O
Sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
--	O
talk	O
of	O
young	O
Ly	B-pers
Cicilia	I-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
youngest	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Coke	I-pers
that	O
was	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
16	O
times	O
wth	O
.	O
Child	O
in	O
abt	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
has	O
living	O
--	O
lost	O
her	O
Eldest	O
Girl	O
--	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
idiot	O
at	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
has	O
one	O
Girl	O
born	O
wth	O
.	O
one	O
eye	O
--	O
another	O
Child	O
a	O
cripple	O
--	O
another	O
a	O
Martyr	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Rheumatism	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Miſs	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
has	O
2	O
boys	O
2	O
Girls	O
--	O
eldest	O
(	O
Girl	O
)	O
abt-	O
10	O
--	O
/	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ld	I-pers
.	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
as	O
usual	O
to	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Saladin	I-pers
du	I-pers
Crans	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
abt	O
8	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
--	O
she	O
better	O
my	O
Lord	O
poorly	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
--	O
Made	B-pers
.	I-pers
Saladin	I-pers
,	O
Schram	B-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
a	O
mistake	O
abt	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
going	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
his	O
Corporal	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
died	O
yesterday	O
--	O
His	O
eldest	O
Son	O
only	O
L	O
200	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
all	O
being	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
power	O
&	O
c	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
--	O
Thursday	O
23	O
d	O
March	O
1797	O
Paid	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
A	O
Month	O
in	O
London	B-place
Yesterday	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D—	I-pers
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
2	O
young	O
Langtons	O
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
ym-	O
or	O
other	O
visitors	O
--	O
at	O
2	O
Lord	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
S—	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
City	O
to	O
change	O
some	O
Plate	O
at	O
Orme	B-pers
s	O
saw	O
some	O
fine	O
Jewels	O
--	O
&	O
some	O
belonging	O
to	O
Schram	B-pers
Watch	O
very	O
fine	O
650	O
L	O
-	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
got	O
praised	O
for	O
her	O
drawing	O
--	O
At	O
7	O
I	O
took	O
Mr-	B-pers
Randell	I-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
s	O
Academy	O
--	O
the	B-pers
elder	I-pers
Orme	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
her	O
Eldest	O
daughter	O
--	O
a	O
pretty	O
clever	O
Girl	O
16	O
Short	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
but	O
in	O
proportion	O
--	O
ye-	O
2	O
d	O
Daughter	O
very	O
like	O
her	O
father	O
Noverre	B-pers
3	O
Miſs	O
B	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
sang	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
Duetts	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
he	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Failure	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Home	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
a	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Susan	B-pers
Montgom̅ery	I-pers
at	O
¼	O
past	O
ten	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Chs	I-pers
Blagdon	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
this	O
Morng	O
Alderman	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Friday	O
24	O
th	O
.-	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Dr	B-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
L—	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
franks	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Schram	I-pers
--	O
Sent	O
excuse	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
dine	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Worsley	I-pers
--	O
Went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
to	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
for	O
Money	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
his	B-pers
Father	I-pers
s	O
to	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
been	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
At	O
our	O
return	O
home	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
L'loyd	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
Morrison	B-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
from	O
Duckenfield	B-place
Lady	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
At	O
5	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
&	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
took	O
her	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
Recd	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
of	O
Bath	B-place
+++	O
Recd	O
Mr	B-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
dined	O
there	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg-	O
a	O
numerous	O
&	O
pleasant	O
Party	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Sr-	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Swiſs	O
--	O
knighted	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
wrote	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Revolution	O
in	O
Switzerland	B-place
&	O
the	O
agreeable	O
Randelph	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Foote	I-pers
Dr	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
D'Evernois	I-pers
2	O
daughters	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Blagden	I-pers
&	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
16	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
L	I-pers
:	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
many	O
more	O
others	O
--	O
Saturday	O
25	O
th	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mat	I-pers
:	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Langton	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
Schram	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Orme	B-pers
to	O
sit	O
for	O
our	O
Portraits	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
better	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
took	O
her	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
--	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Went	O
for	O
¼	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
--	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Elder	I-pers
Orme	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
/	O
--	O
found	O
poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Dr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
there	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
Hour	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Blackman	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Prince	O
gives	O
a	O
dinner	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
c	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
very	O
agreeable	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Dk	B-pers
.	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
Miniature	O
paintings	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lansdowne	I-pers
!	O
reprobated	O
his	O
conduct	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
Sunday	O
26	O
th	O
--	O
Fox	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
my	O
advice	O
relative	O
to	O
wt	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
imprudently	O
said	O
at	O
Md	O
of	O
Honors	O
Table	O
respecting	O
the	O
stop	O
at	O
ye	O
House	O
of	O
Masters	O
&	O
Co	O
:	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Church	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
F	I-pers
--	O
at	O
2	O
P	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
(	O
they	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
)	O
made	O
her	O
mind	O
easy	O
&	O
gave	O
her	O
copy	O
of	O
wht-	O
she	O
shd-	O
write	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
Transparent	O
drawings	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
there	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
Mem	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Master	O
L	O
2,0000	O
--	O
spends	O
L	O
100	O
pr-	O
An	O
--	O
never	O
married	O
no	O
children	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Th	O
3	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Transparent	O
Drawings	O
very	O
beautiful	O
--	O
other	O
drawgs	O
--	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Picture	O
Virgin	O
&	O
Child	O
--	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
--	O
the	O
expreſsion	O
drawing	O
&	O
c	O
exquisite	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H—	I-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
very	O
galant	O
&	O
very	O
agreeable	O
.	O
Took	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
home	O
--	O
we	O
calld	O
for	O
¼	O
hour	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dees	I-pers
--	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
B—d—	I-pers
there	O
&	O
another	O
Lady	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Salsa	B-pers
ferato	I-pers
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	B-pers
B—	I-pers
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
went	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
there	O
--	O
heard	O
good	O
accts	O
.	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Ly-	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
Blagden	I-pers
--	O
spent	O
an	O
2	O
hours	O
very	O
agreeably	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
Genl-	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
truth	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Geography	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bible	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
The	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
(	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
then	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Welsh	O
Judge	O
--	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
great	O
humour	O
--	O
learned	O
Scholar	O
&	O
c	O
very	O
pleasant	O
--	O
Major	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
or	I-pers
Reynells	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Ar	I-pers
:	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
--	O
Cambridge	B-pers
--	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Macdonalds	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
many	O
others	O
--	O
We	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
home	O
--	O
su	O
p	O
p	O
'd	O
at	O
Sr	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
s	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
cheerful	O
only	O
Ly	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
Leslie	I-pers
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
her	O
Cold	O
Bad	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
comes	O
frm-	O
Courteenhall	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Monday	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1797	O
lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
breakfasted	O
wth	O
us	O
--	O
declared	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Flockbourough	B-place
&	O
c	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
good	O
news	O
we	O
had	O
just	O
heard	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
St.	B-place
Trinidad	I-place
in	O
ye	O
.	O
West	B-place
Indies	I-place
burnt	O
taken	O
3	O
Ships	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Spanish	O
line	O
&	O
a	O
burnt	O
Frigate	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
had	O
just	O
heard	O
it	O
from	O
Charlotte	B-pers
who	O
was	O
going	O
wth-	O
ye-	O
intelligence	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
Frank	O
'd	O
Letters	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
&	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
--	O
recd	O
lettr	O
.	O
Dixon	B-pers
Mr	B-pers
Houghnam	I-pers
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
were	O
to	O
return	O
from	O
Liverpool	B-place
to	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
to	O
leave	O
Buxton	B-place
to	O
meet	O
them	O
--	O
Took	O
Miſs	B-pers
AClarke	I-pers
&	O
Papa	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
made	O
my	O
ex	O
our	O
excuses	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
there	O
this	O
Eveg-	O
to	O
meet	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Conyers	O
--	O
Took	O
Louisa	B-pers
an	O
airing	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
intended	O
her	O
future	O
schemes	O
for	O
residence	O
&	O
c	O
Noverre	B-pers
had	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
who	O
accompanied	O
her	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Violin	O
her	O
Papa	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Baſs	O
--	O
she	O
did	O
playd	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Tickets	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Sub	O
.	O
Concert	O
of	O
Cathe	O
Catches	O
&	O
Glees	O
&	O
c	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s	O
Portman	O
Square	O
--	O
Met	O
there	O
the	O
Pepys	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Schram	B-pers
Bloſset	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
in	O
a	O
very	O
polite	O
manner	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Eveg-	O
We	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
Wednesday	O
Tuesday	O
28	O
th	O
March	O
1797	O
--	O
Paid	O
Lady	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
12	O
leſsons	O
1-11-6	O
Sr	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
he	O
looks	O
thin	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
Selsey	I-pers
so	O
grown	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wedell	I-pers
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Scham	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
her	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
&	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
who	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
yesterday	O
--	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
had	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
accident	O
by	O
breaking	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Glaſs	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
head	O
cut	O
his	O
forehead	O
--	O
sat	O
¼	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roſs	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Inchiquin	I-pers
--	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
paid	O
Miſs	O
L'loyds	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Went	O
&	O
bought	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
a	O
toy	O
--	O
dined	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
after	O
dinner	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
toy	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Guiffadiere	I-pers
wd-	O
pay	O
for	O
4-6	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
without	O
her	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
Morrison	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
the	O
Lelands	O
they	O
were	O
alone	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
saw	O
Morrison	B-pers
who	O
sd	O
.	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
occupied	O
for	O
ye	O
public	O
Service	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Elder	I-pers
Orme	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Dr	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
there	O
--	O
Politics	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
took	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
home	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
Thursday	O
Wednesday	O
29	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1797	O
+	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
breakfasted	O
wth-	O
us	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
enter	O
holy	O
orders	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D'Oily	I-pers
took	O
him	O
&	O
Ld	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
sat	O
for	O
her	O
Picture	O
--	O
her	O
Papa	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
exercise	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
met	O
Sr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Blagden	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
Miſs	O
Langtons	O
calld	O
&	O
c	O
took	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
Orme	B-pers
.	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
late	O
Queen	O
of	O
France	O
&	O
c	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
in	O
frm	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Levee	O
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchelsea	I-pers
that	O
was	O
)	O
Took	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Dowg	I-pers
Rothes	I-pers
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
her	O
Papa	O
came	O
left	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
,	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Call	O
'd	O
Lord	B-pers
Lavington	I-pers
she	O
was	O
better	O
Sr	B-pers
R	I-pers
Payne	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
late	O
&	O
present	O
lady	O
&	O
c	O
took	O
Noverre	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
up	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Counteſs	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
playd	O
well	O
Sent	O
Letter	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
For	O
ye	O
.	O
Eve	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
--	O
Papa	B-pers
came	O
saw	O
her	O
--	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg-	O
went	O
Schram	B-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
met	O
there	O
L	B-pers
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
AMClarke	I-pers
s	O
:	O
Wife	O
)	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
+	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
(	O
Sister	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Miss	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
(	I-pers
née	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
)	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
--	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
+	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
Miss	B-pers
(	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
)	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
Thursday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1797	O
Lord	B-pers
FitzwilliamMarquis	I-pers
Rockingham	I-pers
)	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Wedell	I-pers
to	O
Ly	B-pers
--	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
c	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng-	O
Ly	B-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Townsend	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Orme	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Holles	O
Street	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
Hour	O
on	O
Mr	B-pers
Scrahhram	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
had	O
a	O
very	O
crowded	O
Aſsembly	O
Noverre	B-pers
there	O
--	O
noticed	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
the	O
room	O
so	O
crowded	O
no	O
dancing	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
L—	B-pers
s	O
--	O
M	B-pers
--	O
Orme	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
Dſs-	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
--	O
My	O
Ld=	O
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
in	O
charming	O
Spirits	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Whist	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
at	O
8	O
--	O
the	O
room	O
full	O
a	O
formal	O
circle	O
&	O
2	O
Card	O
tables	O
--	O
a	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Genl-	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
whether	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
had	O
left	O
500	O
pr	O
Annum	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
life	O
--	O
if	O
she	O
married	O
/	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
cease	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
12000	O
independant	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
went	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
met	O
there	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leland	I-pers
2	O
Miſs	O
More	O
:	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
Burdett	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
L—	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
sang	O
wth	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
fetched	O
Col	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
from	O
Mr	B-pers
s	O
--	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
s	O
great	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
next	O
thursday	O
ye	O
last	O
--	O
the	O
company	O
mostly	O
gone	O
--	O
saw	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Home	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
afft	O
.	O
letter	O
from	O
L	B-pers
:	I-pers
Note	O
Morrison	B-pers
--	O
heard	O
Noverre	B-pers
was	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wedell	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Friday	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
March	O
1797	O
Sent	O
Note	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Coke	I-pers
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
&	O
she	O
&	O
Papa	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Levenson	I-pers
s	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
Sent	O
letter	O
Ly-	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Broderick	I-pers
s	O
saw	O
Mr	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
Bride	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
s	O
wife	O
--	O
sat	O
¼	O
hour	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Smelt	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
tomorrow	O
--	O
Schram	B-pers
remains	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
found	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Noverre	B-pers
&	O
c	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
5	O
--	O
the	O
Girl	O
3	O
in	O
May	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
educate	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
Lord	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
related	O
to	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
sad	O
accident	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
had	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroy	I-pers
'd	I-pers
.	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Roſs	I-pers
s	O
Portrait	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
done	O
in	O
1	O
hour	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
a	O
very	O
strong	O
likeneſs	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
Eveg-	O
Miſs	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Streatfield	I-pers
s	O
staid	O
¼	O
hour	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
S—	I-pers
--	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Mother	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Porteous	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D—	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
M	O
rs	O
-	O
Orme	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
sat	O
chatting	O
pleasantly	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
her	O
she	O
left	O
us	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
wth-	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
Mr.	B-pers
Heaviside	I-pers
&	O
c	O
:	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
--	O
Saturday	O
1	O
st	O
..	O
April	O
1797	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
--	O
she	O
sent	O
letter	O
to	O
Grandpapa	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
frank	O
'd	O
cover	O
--	O
--	O
Went	O
to	O
ye	O
Honble	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
found	O
her	O
languid	O
&	O
weak	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt-	O
her	O
Mother	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Left	O
my	O
name	O
Miſs	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Portman	O
Square	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
26	O
Devonshire	O
Street	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
young	O
Orme	B-pers
&	O
c	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Schram	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
--	O
only	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Broderick	I-pers
and	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
dinner	O
--	O
conversation	O
Animated	O
&	O
sensible	O
--	O
We	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
oClock	O
Went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
--	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
Langton	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
eldest	O
Brother	O
s	O
Wife	O
&	O
daughter	O
ye	O
Mother	O
beautiful	O
--	O
a	O
resemblance	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
a	O
pleasant	O
lively	O
young	O
Woman	O
h	O
was	O
a	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
L.	I-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
son	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
H—	I-pers
&	O
several	O
others	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Came	O
home	O
abt.-	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ewart	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
s	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Falls	I-pers
--	O
Sunday	O
2	O
d	O
April	O
1797	O
--	O
Mr	O
:	O
D	O
:	O
went	O
before	O
breakfast	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farquhar	I-pers
he	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
night	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
F—	I-pers
came	O
his	O
Wife	O
indifferent	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Blagden	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Levinstone	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Canyon	O
Street	O
Chapel	O
May	B-place
fair	I-place
Revd	B-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
Sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Dr	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
(	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
Son	O
)	O
in	O
her	O
Seat	O
Ld-	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
sat	O
next	O
Pew	O
wth	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
a	O
very	O
energetic	O
good	O
Sermon	O
well	O
delivered	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
American	O
--	O
The	O
Text	O
was	O
Psalm	O
77	O
th	O
.	O
Verse	O
3	O
d	O
-	O
“	O
When	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
heavineſs	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
think	O
upon	O
God	O
:	O
when	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
vexed	O
I	O
will	O
complain	O
.	O
”	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
us	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
They	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
next	O
Saturday	O
.	O
After	O
Chapel	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
L	B-pers
s	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
--	O
both	O
out	O
--	O
Capt	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
went	O
for	O
½	O
hour	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
.	O
Took	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Ducie	I-pers
--	O
Queens	O
House	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Coomb	I-pers
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
melancholy	O
History	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
:	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Mem	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
told	O
me	O
She	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
s	O
people	O
were	O
7	O
quarters	O
in	O
arrear	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
Influenza	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
worthy	O
man	O
so	O
little	O
altered	O
well	O
little	O
altered	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Mr-	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Gom	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
s	O
dined	O
there	O
only	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S—	I-pers
Miſs	O
Wake	O
s	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
we	O
set	O
K—	B-pers
down	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
s	O
--	O
My	O
frd	O
spoke	O
with	O
some	O
warmth	O
respecting	O
ye	O
:	O
unreasonable	O
expectations	O
of	O
Children	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
brought	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
home	O
changed	O
my	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
went	O
for	O
Mr-	B-pers
D—	I-pers
--	O
they	O
pai	O
d	O
a	O
Visit	O
at	O
the	O
Bloſsets	O
then	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
L—	B-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
company	O
on	O
acct	O
of	O
a	O
Head	O
ache	O
--	O
their	O
Daughter	O
Mr-	B-pers
did	O
the	O
honors	O
wth	O
.	O
propriety	O
&	O
modesty	O
met	O
there	O
Ly-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
ye	O
Historian	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
Leſslie	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Mat	I-pers
.	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Coxe	B-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Price	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowen	I-pers
--	O
2	O
Sons	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leveson	I-pers
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
c	O
Mrs-	B-pers
told	O
us	O
his	O
Brother	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
was	O
married	O
--	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
created	O
a	O
Doctor	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wraxal	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Oxford	O
was	O
recovering	O
from	O
ye	O
:	O
effect	O
of	O
ye	O
Goulard	O
he	O
is	O
76	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Lambton	I-pers
correspondence	O
wth-	O
a	O
french	O
Lady	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
preservation	O
of	O
her	O
beauty	O
--	O
East	O
Wind	O
destructive	O
to	O
ye	O
Skin	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
We	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Monday	O
3	O
d	O
-	O
April	O
1797	O
--	O
Snow	O
--	O
Counteſs	B-pers
Dowg	I-pers
Rothes	I-pers
came	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
Bonnet	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Oxford	O
Xtian	O
patience	O
&	O
c	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Coxe	B-pers
Edward	B-pers
Better	O
--	O
took	O
Inglis	B-pers
to	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
s	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Ly	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
--	O
she	O
sat	O
¼	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth-	O
me	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
that	O
was	O
)	O
--	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
ye	O
Coach	O
in	O
her	O
shift	O
--	O
Sheridan	B-pers
weakly	O
given	O
up	O
his	O
party	O
--	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
proxy	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
influences	O
Lord	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
--	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
frd-	O
.	O
of	O
hers	O
a	O
Clergymans	O
daughter	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
--	O
a	O
miserable	O
rainy	O
day	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
full	O
folio	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
recd	O
letters	O
from	O
her	O
&	O
Noverre	B-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sheridan	I-pers
--	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Ogle	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
Dk	I-pers
.	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Sent	O
excuses	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S—	I-pers
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
--	O
Met	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
s	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Schram	B-pers
wife	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
(	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
)	O
who	O
wrote	O
travels	O
into	O
Spain	B-place
&	O
c	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
Man	O
--	O
2	O
of	O
his	O
daughters	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
wife	O
fine	O
Girls	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
--	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Berens	O
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
converzatione	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
home	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
name	O
M	O
Paid	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
L	O
4-	O
s	O
4-	O
Paid	O
Mr.	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
for	O
12	O
leſsons	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
L	O
1-	O
s	O
11	O
,	O
d	O
6	O
28	O
March	O
1797	O
Tue	O
Wednesday	O
pd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Traycy	I-pers
to	O
begin	O
again	O
Thursday	O
--	O
