TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
This	O
Fog	O
makes	O
me	O
so	O
generous	O
/as	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
grieve	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
increase	O
it	O
by	O
coming	O
out	O
to	O
me/	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
Princeſs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Dasckaw	I-pers
&	O
c	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
this	O
Eveng.-	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
this	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
tomorrow	O
also	O
/for	O
She	O
comes	O
tomorrow	O
Eveng	O
:	O
/	O
but	O
as	O
ye	O
:	O
weather	O
is	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
be	O
ungenerous	O
&	O
cd	O
:	O
not	O
ansr	O
:	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Conscience	O
--	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
acted	O
so	O
greatly	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
if	O
the	O
Fog	O
should	O
disperse	O
&	O
you	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
this	O
Eveng	O
:	O
tho	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
--	O
&	O
tomorrow	O
because	O
she	O
does	O
--	O
perhaps	O
you	O
wd	O
:	O
dine	O
here	O
also	O
&	O
meet	O
Capt	B-pers
:	I-pers
Salvyn	I-pers
who	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
has	O
asked	O
;	O
pray	O
do	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
:	O
cold	O
is	O
better	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
one	O
too	O
--	O
our	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
Mrs.-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
fear	O
this	O
Fog	O
affects	O
her	O
Breath	O
--	O
it	O
does	O
mine	O
in	O
a	O
slight	O
degree	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Je	O
suis	O
tout	O
à	O
vous	O
PD	B-pers
Friday	O
Morng	O
:	O
To	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
James	O
Street	O
Westminster	B-place
