TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
Decr	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
1774	O
Yours	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
I	O
recieved	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
&	O
had	O
imagined	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
quite	O
given	O
me	O
up	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
you	O
ſince	O
I	O
left	O
Shaw	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
to	O
write	O
myself	O
having	O
ever	O
ſince	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
been	O
confined	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
&	O
room	O
but	O
always	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
complication	O
of	O
distempers	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
opinion	O
the	O
least	O
favorable	O
Symtom	O
till	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
all	O
this	O
wt	O
ye	O
most	O
violent	O
lowneſs	O
of	O
Spirits	O
imaginable	O
has	O
really	O
reduced	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
animal	O
&	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
last	O
however	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
this	O
bout	O
&	O
that	O
my	O
health	O
will	O
mend	O
by	O
the	O
spring	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
once	O
more	O
enjoy	O
that	O
health	O
I	O
formerly	O
had	O
wh-	O
out	O
which	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
be	O
pleasing	O
&	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
ſeen	O
little	O
or	O
not	O
none	O
these	O
Six	O
or	O
Seven	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
two	O
marriages	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
off	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
ſoon	O
but	O
its	O
Miss	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
to	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
&	O
Miss	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
to	O
my	O
first	O
Couſin	O
Mr	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
of	I-pers
Balgowan	I-pers
but	O
unleſs	O
they	O
write	O
you	O
before	O
their	O
marriage	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
'll	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Duchess	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
deſires	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
spoke	O
off	O
till	O
o	O
ver	O
what	O
her	O
whim	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
but	O
its	O
eaſily	O
indulging	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
triffle	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
will	O
gain	O
his	O
Seat	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
keen	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
as	O
my	O
friends	O
are	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
Parliament	O
at	O
present	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
command	O
a	O
single	O
frank	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
is	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
Jack	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
there	O
never	O
was	O
nor	O
never	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
least	O
chance	O
of	O
his	O
sitting	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
now	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
has	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Army	O
in	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
Regt	O
of	O
Foot	O
but	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
carrying	O
on	O
his	O
education	O
as	O
the	O
Regt	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
quartered	O
here	O
for	O
ſome	O
Years	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
great	O
inducement	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
into	O
that	O
Regiment	O
Adieu	O
My	O
deare	O
st	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
am	O
able	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
this	O
being	O
my	O
second	O
letter	O
in	O
many	O
months	O
,	O
remember	O
me	O
&	O
mine	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
they	O
deſire	O
their	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
most	O
affctly	O
Yours	O
Napier	B-pers
This	O
Letter	O
written	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Death	O
Bed	O
of	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Friend	O
--	O
he	O
died	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
&	O
in	O
answer	O
'd	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
heart-breaking	O
intelligen	O
c	O
e	O
from	O
his	O
Son	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
that	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
ever	O
lost	O
my	O
beloved	O
my	O
valuable	O
Friend	O
--	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
about	O
5	O
months	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
Death	O
--	O
May	O
the	O
God	O
of	O
infinite	O
Mercy	O
receive	O
their	O
Souls	O
&	O
may	O
we	O
meet	O
in	O
Heaven	O
--	O
never	O
to	O
part	O
again	O
.	O
