TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
How	O
fare	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
think	O
it	O
an	O
age	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
,	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
long	O
since	O
last	O
Thursday	O
&	O
then	O
you	O
only	O
staid	O
a	O
minute	O
come	O
&	O
breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Chapel	O
&	O
walk	O
till	O
9	O
&	O
then	O
breakfast	O
you	O
had	O
bette	O
r	O
do	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
early	O
come	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
engaged	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
come	O
Friday	O
&	O
spend	O
the	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
comfort	O
&	O
have	O
never	O
don	O
e	O
it	O
but	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
occupied	O
&	O
anxious	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
recovered	O
Ld	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
's	O
vararies	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
whi	O
ch	O
I	O
feel	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
anything	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
infinitly	O
beyond	O
praise	O
&	O
encomiun	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
returns	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Harrowgate	B-place
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
ever	O
your	O
affce	O
:	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Wednesday	O
antient	O
M	O
.	O
Music	O
to	O
night	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1788	O
London	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
