TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
presents	O
his	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
encloses	O
to	O
her	O
another	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Milkwoman	O
s	O
verses	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
forgot	O
to	O
return	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
this	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knows	O
full	O
well	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
the	O
weekly	O
trips	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
break	O
in	O
upon	O
time	O
:	O
he	O
will	O
however	O
certainly	O
find	O
leisure	O
when	O
he	O
returns	O
to	O
London	B-place
next	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
Friday	O
Morn	O
:	O
Jan	O
:	O
28	O
1785	O
