TOKEN	NE
indeed	O
that	O
my	O
pleasing	O
her	O
will	O
depend	O
,	O
totally	O
on	O
my	O
Health	O
&	O
spirits	O
.	O
which	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
command	O
nor	O
can	O
at	O
present	O
bragg	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
suite	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Chapter	O
of	O
Accidents	O
‘	O
the	O
chapter	O
of	O
knowledge	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
chapter	O
of	O
accidents	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
one.	O
’	O
Lord	O
Chesterfield	O
to	O
Solomon	O
Dayrolles	O
,	O
16	O
February	O
1753	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliffe	O
,	O
S	O
.	O
(	O
Ed	O
.	O
)	O
Oxford	O
Essential	O
Quotations	O
(	O
Oxford	O
:	O
Oxford	O
University	O
Press	O
)	O
.Accessed	O
03-09-2020	O
.	O
,	O
nor	O
lay	O
out	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
is	O
indeed	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
woman	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
her	O
Character	O
which	O
however	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
Lady	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
Youth	O
.	O
She	O
seems	O
much	O
diſsappointed	O
at	O
not	O
meeting	O
you	O
here	O
.	O
Coll-	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
(	O
but	O
dont	O
tell	O
Him	O
)	O
I	O
love	O
&	O
whenever	O
I	O
have	O
spirits	O
flirt	O
with	O
.	O
Yours	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
the	O
greatest	O
Pleasure	O
in	O
one	O
respect	O
(	O
that	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
had	O
setled	O
evry	O
thing	O
to	O
yr	O
mind	O
:	O
)	O
but	O
regreate	O
infinatly	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
reason	O
for	O
not	O
comeing	O
here	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
wont	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
as	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
by	O
the	O
shortest	O
road	O
to	O
Edr	B-place
:	I-place
whenever	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
able	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
he	O
will	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
in	O
paſsing	O
heartily	O
do	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
come	O
here	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
lived	O
so	O
near	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
you	O
a	O
Visitt	O
be	O
asured	O
nothing	O
could	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
greater	O
Pleasure	O
.	O
Yours	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
Edr	B-place
:	I-place
where	O
yr	O
young	O
friends	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
would	O
have	O
wrote	O
you	O
a	O
poscript	O
instead	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
testiffie	O
our	O
Regreate	O
at	O
yr	O
not	O
comeing	O
here	O
but	O
his	O
fingers	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
crampt	O
by	O
drinking	O
the	O
Watters	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Pen	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
boast	O
much	O
yet	O
.	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
recovery	O
e	O
ith	O
er	O
of	O
Health	O
or	O
Spiritts	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Dr	O
has	O
just	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
new	O
System	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
'll	O
still	O
return	O
to	O
yr	O
Wish	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
seems	O
to	O
get	O
better	O
daily	O
we	O
heartily	O
join	O
in	O
best	O
compts	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
excuse	O
this	O
Scrawle	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Cards	O
tables	O
talking	O
by	O
me	O
so	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
writing	O
Spadile	O
Manille	O
&	O
Basto	O
I	O
shall	O
conclude	O
by	O
asureing	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
most	O
Affect	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
