TOKEN	NE
Uppingham	B-place
June	O
3	O
d	O
1802	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
that	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
carelessness	O
in	O
directing	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
recieve	O
the	O
news	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
confinement	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hoped	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
done	O
but	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
every	O
poſsible	O
amends	O
by	O
answering	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
immediately	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
late	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
post	O
leaves	O
Uppingham	B-place
early	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
&	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
herself	O
&	O
Child	O
are	O
getting	O
quite	O
stout	O
She	O
sat	O
up	O
Yesterday	O
from	O
two	O
till	O
eight	O
wch	O
.	O
considering	O
the	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
a	O
fort'night	O
Confined	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
She	O
is	O
happy	O
in	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
nurse	O
herself	O
The	O
baby	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Mary	O
Anna	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
T	B-pers
Carill	I-pers
Worsley	I-pers
s	O
Esq	O
Platt	O
House	O
near	O
Manchester	B-place
