TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
regrate	O
extremly	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
befor	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
intended	O
it	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
exceedingly	O
hott	O
I	O
realy	O
durst	O
not	O
venture	O
upon	O
any	O
expidition	O
,	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
I	O
leave	O
town	O
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
goe	O
first	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Archer	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
stay	O
some	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
when	O
the	O
blue	O
knoting	O
will	O
be	O
wanted	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
as	O
much	O
time	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
spared	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
doe	O
the	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
realy	O
done	O
nothing	O
els	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
and	O
notwithstanding	O
there	O
is	O
still	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
doe	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
neſsesery	O
to	O
send	O
what	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
Care	O
it	O
is	O
sent	O
safe	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
keep	O
your	O
health	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
such	O
Charmine	O
weather	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
walk	O
and	O
take	O
exercise	O
,	O
nothing	O
so	O
good	O
for	O
nervous	O
Complaints	O
,	O
provided	O
you	O
dont	O
over	O
doe	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
allways	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
happy	O
the	O
last	O
it	O
is	O
imposible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
doubt	O
your	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
charmine	O
Situation	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
therefor	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
and	O
injoy	O
it	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
writ	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
very	O
great	O
regard	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
affectionat	O
friend	O
and	O
faithful	O
servant	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Maddox	O
Street	O
Jully	O
17	O
th	O
1779	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
direct	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
Hale	B-place
Downton	I-place
Wilts	B-place
