TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
26	O
April	O
1779	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
last	O
an	O
immense	O
packet	O
arrived	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Eldest	O
Sister	O
having	O
taken	O
unto	O
herself	O
a	O
helpmate	O
&	O
gone	O
to	O
Dumfries	B-place
,	O
&	O
Harriot	B-pers
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
presumption	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Seals	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
great	O
was	O
my	O
surprise	O
when	O
out	O
dropt	O
a	O
Lockit	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
a	O
large	O
paper	O
directed	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
&	O
the	O
Servants	O
aſsured	O
me	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
packet	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
paper	O
directed	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
which	O
inclosed	O
a	O
most	O
beautiful	O
purse	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
came	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
credit	O
for	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
work	O
universally	O
admired	O
&	O
wait	O
with	O
impatience	O
till	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
in	O
course	O
of	O
Post	O
writes	O
me	O
something	O
Tendant	O
ou	O
dénouëment	O
.	O
The	O
Writing	O
upon	O
the	O
different	O
covers	O
,	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
imagine	O
you	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
so	O
cavaleirly	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
consider	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
third	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
without	O
obtaining	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
purse	O
is	O
of	O
your	O
fabricating	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
you	O
a	O
million	O
of	O
thanks	O
for	O
it	O
&	O
shall	O
preserve	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
small	O
collection	O
of	O
my	O
Valuables	O
.	O
The	O
book	O
I	O
presume	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
&	O
shall	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
;	O
the	O
Lockit	O
I	O
have	O
retained	O
'till	O
she	O
informs	O
me	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
over	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
before	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
disappointment	O
,	O
&	O
people	O
above	O
are	O
now	O
almost	O
as	O
little	O
remembered	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
military	O
Ideas	O
have	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
been	O
at	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
happy	O
in	O
being	O
well	O
received	O
by	O
some	O
few	O
friends	O
whom	O
who	O
I	O
esteem	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
profeſs	O
a	O
regard	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
week	O
brings	O
about	O
a	O
Marriage	O
between	O
two	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
entertain	O
the	O
most	O
sincere	O
freindship	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Cousin	O
German	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
s	O
tho	O
'	O
younger	O
than	O
myself	O
)	O
has	O
consented	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
hand	O
&	O
heart	O
next	O
friday	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Binning	I-pers
,	O
oldest	O
Son	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hadinton	I-pers
&	O
a	O
near	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
most	O
amiable	O
pair	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
&	O
even	O
the	O
busy	O
public	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
their	O
future	O
felicity	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
have	O
leisure	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
the	O
good	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
?	O
Miſs	B-pers
K.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
?	O
The	O
little	O
Baronet	O
?	O
&	O
our	O
Cousin	O
of	O
Stormont	O
?	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
remain	O
sincerely	O
Your	O
Affect	O
.	O
Friend	O
N——	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
London	B-place
