TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
Street	O
6	O
Decr	O
1766	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
trouble	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
want	O
of	O
knowing	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
;	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
Slight	O
Colds	O
excepted	O
,	O
&	O
Enjoy	O
this	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
very	O
uneasy	O
winter	O
we	O
had	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
;	O
findg	O
our	O
selves	O
now	O
peaceably	O
&	O
quietly	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
so	O
much	O
toſsing	O
about	O
on	O
the	O
Subjt	O
:	O
of	O
health	O
&	O
--	O
pursuing	O
it	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
appears	O
of	O
double	O
value	O
from	O
the	O
Comparison	O
of	O
the	O
past	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
give	O
my	O
Lord	O
&	O
me	O
very	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
your	O
Situation	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
is	O
perfectly	O
to	O
your	O
mind	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
whose	O
health	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
yours	O
,	O
we	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
good	O
Act	O
:	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
your	O
Daughter	O
turns	O
out	O
to	O
your	O
wiſh	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
expectation	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
appeard	O
to	O
us	O
extremely	O
promising	O
.	O
I	O
supose	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
good	O
part	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
told	O
her	O
Daughter	O
is	O
,	O
as	O
tall	O
as	O
herself	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Complimt	O
:	O
I	O
meet	O
with	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
tho	O
mine	O
wants	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
thirteen	O
:	O
Charles	B-pers
is	O
so	O
Stout	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
four	O
horses	O
,	O
on	O
horseback	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
Turnham	B-place
green	I-place
&	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
out	O
the	O
least	O
fatigue	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Docr	O
.	O
thinks	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Br	O
.	O
at	O
Eton	B-place
after	O
Easter	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Archd	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
shew	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
him	O
&	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
grown	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
dreſs	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
before	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
just	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
speakg	O
every	O
thing	O
intelligeably	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
&	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
yrs	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
met	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
may	O
cause	O
some	O
alteration	O
as	O
to	O
looks	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
article	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
is	O
the	O
Same	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
s	O
affecte	O
good	O
wishes	O
&	O
kind	O
Compts	O
:	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
your	O
Most	O
Affectionate	O
Sister	O
&	O
c	O
J.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
