TOKEN	NE
Deal	O
Castle	O
.	O
May	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
This	O
Letter	O
was	O
intended	O
for	O
Yesterdays	O
Post	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
&	O
therefore	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
deferr	O
it	O
till	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
continuing	O
the	O
good	O
Accounts	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
hitherto	O
to	O
send	O
constantly	O
of	O
our	O
little	O
Prince	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
bathing	O
agreeing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Nights	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
mended	O
&	O
his	O
Appetite	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
gain	O
Ground	O
,	O
&	O
thō	O
his	O
Face	O
is	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
clear	O
of	O
the	O
Irruption	O
that	O
disfigured	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
rather	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
than	O
any	O
fresh	O
breaking	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Eye-lid	O
that	O
seem	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
is	O
also	O
getting	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
effect	O
of	O
weak'ning	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
afraid	O
of	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
happineſs	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
of	O
Seeing	O
my	O
Son	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
Landing	O
,	O
he	O
hurried	O
away	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
be	O
in	O
time	O
for	O
his	O
presentings	O
preperatory	O
to	O
appearing	O
at	O
the	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
now	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
preparing	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
open	O
our	O
Windows	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
firing	O
of	O
the	O
Guns	O
,	O
which	O
shakes	O
the	O
Castle	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
that	O
Precaution	O
they	O
would	O
all	O
be	O
broke	O
&	O
the	O
Sound	O
is	O
very	O
tremendous	O
,	O
P.	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
however	O
is	O
very	O
courageous	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
&	O
seems	O
rather	O
to	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
that	O
Ceremony	O
twice	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
honor	O
of	O
his	O
Arrival	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
last	O
on	O
the	O
Restoration	O
Day	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
I	O
have	O
often	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Seeing	O
,	O
&	O
except	O
her	O
usual	O
Head-achs	O
,	O
think	O
She	O
appears	O
vastly	O
well	O
&	O
cheerful	O
.	O
My	O
little	O
Girls	O
are	O
quite	O
delightful	O
'Companions	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
the	O
Weather	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
windy	O
&	O
cold	O
I	O
believe	O
would	O
prevail	O
on	O
me	O
sometimes	O
to	O
walk	O
upon	O
the	O
Sands	O
with	O
them	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
attempt	O
,	O
but	O
paſs	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
by	O
a	O
Fireside	O
(	O
wch	O
you	O
will	O
hardly	O
credit	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
pretty	O
little	O
room	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
delightful	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
begun	O
reading	O
Antonis	O
de	O
Solis	O
in	O
Spanish	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
having	O
furnish	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
(	O
without	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
attempt	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
am	O
continuing	O
Made	B-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
Adele	O
&	O
Theodore	O
;	O
these	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
Children	O
s	O
Studies	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
own	O
Letter	O
writing	O
,	O
fill	O
my	O
day	O
very	O
completely	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
generally	O
retire	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
enables	O
me	O
to	O
rise	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
Madl	B-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
is	O
mending	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
aſsure	O
her	O
how	O
concern	O
'd	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
hearing	O
of	O
her	O
Illneſs	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Influenza	O
which	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
general	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
belonging	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
make	O
all	O
my	O
Duties	O
&	O
Comps	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
should	O
wish	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
will	O
do	O
the	O
kindest	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
by	O
You	O
in	O
concluding	O
this	O
,	O
from	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
faithful	O
&	O
affcte	O
.	O
Servant	O
C	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Letter	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
's	O
't	O
is	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
.	O
