TOKEN	NE
Harleyford	B-place
.	O
April	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
return	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
&	O
entertaining	O
Letter	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
happiness	O
you	O
wish	O
'd	O
of	O
shewing	O
dear	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
quite	O
recover	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
thō	O
my	O
progreſs	O
is	O
slow	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
certainly	O
mend	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
now	O
had	O
2	O
good	O
Nights	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
refresh	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
wears	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
want	O
of	O
Rest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
delighted	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
Acquisition	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
for	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
,	O
nobody	O
having	O
a	O
higher	O
value	O
for	O
them	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
The	O
Chaisè	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
our	O
Airing	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
My	B-pers
Hamn	I-pers
.	I-pers
Ever	O
Affcte	O
.	O
&	O
Obliged	O
C.	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsy	I-pers
.	I-pers
