TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
30	O
th	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1779	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
wrote	O
last	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
temper	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
incapable	O
of	O
answering	O
some	O
questions	O
in	O
your	O
letter	O
so	O
calmly	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Never	O
was	O
poor	O
Devil	O
so	O
tormented	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
&	O
still	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
from	O
an	O
exceſs	O
of	O
prudence	O
&	O
delicacy	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
happen	O
to	O
loſs	O
lose	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
my	O
wishes	O
.	O
Under	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
Silence	O
'till	O
an	O
answer	O
is	O
received	O
from	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
America	B-place
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
addreſs	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
small	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
a	O
rising	O
attachment	O
in	O
her	O
breast	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
a	O
Young	O
Earl	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
attachment	O
strengthened	O
by	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
her	O
Cousin	O
and	O
Confidant	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
appears	O
to	O
gain	O
ground	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
my	O
resolution	O
is	O
fixed	O
of	O
finishing	O
the	O
matter	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
promotion	O
Treaty	O
in	O
great	O
forwardneſs	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
in	O
about	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
suspect	O
me	O
of	O
being	O
jealous	O
.	O
My	O
information	O
comes	O
from	O
too	O
good	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
no	O
leſs	O
a	O
personage	O
than	O
Ly-	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
who	O
is	O
her	O
Aunt	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
m	O
y	O
i	O
ne	O
&	O
who	O
wishes	O
me	O
well	O
--	O
You	O
see	O
the	O
scrape	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
require	O
great	O
addreſs	O
&	O
ingenuity	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
more	O
I	O
fear	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
Master	O
of	O
--	O
however	O
Fortune	O
favors	O
the	O
brave	O
&	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
cast	O
down	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
my	O
Estate	O
--	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
appearance	O
there	O
.	O
No	O
house	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Castles	O
without	O
side	O
Walls	O
,	O
Roofs	O
,	O
Windows	O
,	O
Doors	O
or	O
floors	O
.	O
Next	O
Summer	O
my	O
intention	O
is	O
to	O
build	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
palace	O
but	O
a	O
Cottage	O
--	O
Lofty	O
green	O
hills	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
planted	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
in	O
River	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
,	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
rising	O
into	O
Mountains	O
likewise	O
to	O
be	O
planted	O
&	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
an	O
Old	O
Castle	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
principle	O
object	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
some	O
day	O
or	O
other	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Yours	O
Affecty-	O
N——	B-pers
.	O
