TOKEN	NE
My	O
good	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Impatient	O
of	O
Confinement	O
I	O
ventured	O
out	O
last	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
sufficiently	O
recovered	O
my	O
Strength	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
suffered	O
from	O
my	O
Rashneſs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
slight	O
return	O
of	O
my	O
Fever	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
my	O
Cough	O
increased	O
;	O
I	O
therefore	O
think	O
it	O
prudent	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
longer	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
person	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
any	O
pecuniary	O
relief	O
would	O
be	O
but	O
temporary	O
,	O
&	O
no	O
eſsential	O
&	O
lasting	O
service	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
enclose	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
well	O
see	O
that	O
a	O
present	O
pecuniary	O
relief	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
real	O
service	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
the	O
fitting	O
out	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
levy	O
contributions	O
on	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
Guineas	O
or	O
half	O
Guineas	O
therefore	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
be	O
very	O
thankful	O
for	O
.	O
Another	O
matter	O
which	O
I	O
hinted	O
to	O
you	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
&	O
wished	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
upon	O
is	O
this	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
when	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blomberg	I-pers
's	O
busineſs	O
,	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
his	O
conduct	O
at	O
Cambridge	B-place
,	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
Tutor	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
consult	O
him	O
what	O
plan	O
was	O
best	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
pursue	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
into	O
orders	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
the	O
Tutor	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
yesterday	O
a	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
--	O
Now	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
I	O
should	O
inform	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
that	O
I	O
have	O
executed	O
her	O
orders	O
.	O
Would	O
there	O
be	O
any	O
impropriety	O
in	O
your	O
mentioning	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
?	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
by	O
what	O
other	O
channel	O
to	O
apply	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
for	O
many	O
reasons	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
John	B-pers
B——	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Permit	O
me	O
to	O
subscribe	O
myself	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
JFisher	B-pers
Friday	O
Morn	O
:	O
Will	O
you	O
be	O
good	O
enough	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
B	O
letters	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
her	O
addreſs	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
