TOKEN	NE
Cork	B-place
,	O
8	O
Dec	O
Janry-	O
1786	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
no	O
longer	O
a	O
Miſs	O
about	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
risen	O
into	O
the	O
far	O
more	O
respectable	O
situation	O
of	O
a	O
Country	O
Housewife	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
employed	O
superintending	O
&	O
aſsisting	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
housekeeper	O
in	O
the	O
fabrication	O
of	O
Mince	O
Pyes	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
expect	O
that	O
my	O
letter	O
should	O
begin	O
by	O
Wishing	O
you	O
the	O
Compliments	O
of	O
the	O
Season	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
serious	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
resigned	O
to	O
her	O
situation	O
.	O
Her	O
loſs	O
is	O
(	O
I	O
beleive	O
)	O
irreparable	O
)	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
s	O
bad	O
health	O
must	O
have	O
long	O
given	O
her	O
reason	O
to	O
fear	O
what	O
you	O
write	O
me	O
word	O
has	O
happened	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
,	O
her	O
family	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
not	O
large	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
you	O
talk	O
of	O
any	O
child	O
but	O
the	O
present	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
death	O
I	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
.	O
Whatever	O
Airs	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
given	O
myself	O
relative	O
to	O
his	O
writings	O
,	O
be	O
aſsured	O
I	O
ever	O
respected	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
knowing	O
his	O
disinterested	O
Attachment	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
myself	O
have	O
lately	O
experienced	O
Alarms	O
,	O
which	O
thank	O
God	O
are	O
now	O
all	O
over	O
.	O
My	O
vexatious	O
Legacy	O
had	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dublin	B-place
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
little	O
Mary	B-pers
in	O
the	O
small	O
Pox	O
from	O
which	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
leaving	O
Cork	B-place
,	O
a	O
spotted	O
Fever	O
was	O
very	O
prevalent	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
many	O
days	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
when	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Maria	B-pers
telling	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Fever	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
beleive	O
I	O
immediately	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
from	O
that	O
disorder	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
complaint	O
in	O
her	O
bowells	O
attended	O
with	O
very	O
alarming	O
circumstances	O
,	O
which	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
made	O
me	O
apprehend	O
the	O
most	O
fatal	O
consequences	O
--	O
But	O
that	O
Providence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
Maria	B-pers
was	O
equally	O
beneficent	O
in	O
preserving	O
her	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
remain	O
thankfull	O
for	O
the	O
Gift	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
swindling	O
business	O
no	O
longer	O
exists	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
conceive	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
single	O
You	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
playing	O
their	O
Pranks	O
on	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
neighbours	O
in	O
that	O
Square	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
much	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Scrape	O
!	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
attention	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
wished	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
unfortunately	O
inherited	O
the	O
Gout	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
lately	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
attack	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Stomack	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
its	O
visiting	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
Life	O
that	O
disorder	O
must	O
be	O
alarming	O
&	O
in	O
her	O
situation	O
her	O
family	O
have	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
fear	O
.	O
My	O
Letter	O
absolutely	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
the	O
Bills	O
of	O
Mortality	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
Yo	O
u	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
feel	O
--	O
The	O
newspaper	O
accounts	O
were	O
not	O
perfectly	O
exact	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
The	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Rutland	I-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
an	O
airing	O
&	O
dined	O
with	O
her	O
Grace	O
in	O
private	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
recovered	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
exhibit	O
herself	O
in	O
public	O
.	O
The	O
Dutcheſs	O
had	O
no	O
companion	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
consequently	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
feeling	O
herself	O
obliged	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
for	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
silly	O
Woman	O
,	O
not	O
comfortable	O
in	O
her	O
matrimonial	O
connection	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
more	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
Pity	O
,	O
than	O
Envy	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
naturally	O
good	O
humoured	O
,	O
but	O
fond	O
of	O
universal	O
Admiration	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
attached	O
to	O
his	O
Bottle	O
makes	O
her	O
Grace	O
a	O
secondary	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
esteem	O
.	O
Such	O
a	O
System	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
unites	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
kind	O
and	O
affectionate	O
wish	O
to	O
Yourself	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
we	O
hope	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
personally	O
that	O
we	O
esteem	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
lives	O
of	O
Soldiers	O
are	O
uncertain	O
.	O
We	O
(	O
like	O
true	O
philosophers	O
)	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
whatever	O
situation	O
my	O
Duty	O
throws	O
Us	O
into	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithfull	O
friend	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
,	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
IRELAND	B-place
CORK	B-place
by	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
