TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
May	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
I	O
write	O
two	O
lines	O
to	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
just	O
to	O
ſay	O
I	O
got	O
hers	O
from	O
Canterbury	B-place
&	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
sending	O
you	O
a	O
Dog	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
morrow	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
like	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Cloe	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
she	O
dances	O
&	O
plays	O
many	O
tricks	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
that	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Puppy	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Dog	O
for	O
you	O
but	O
a	O
horse	O
broke	O
its	O
Leg	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
drown	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lady	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
one	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
write	O
soon	O
derect	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Panmure	I-pers
Chesterfield	O
Street	O
May	B-place
fair	I-place
London	B-place
as	O
His	O
Lordship	O
will	O
always	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
ſend	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
family	O
leave	O
this	O
to	O
morrow	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
Adieu	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
most	O
Affctly-	O
N——r	B-pers
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
