TOKEN	NE
Octr	O
.	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
oppartunity	O
,	O
of	O
answering	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Father	O
still	O
has	O
the	O
gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
which	O
hinders	O
us	O
from	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
this	O
week	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mamma	O
desires	O
her	O
kind	O
love	O
,	O
&	O
thinks	O
for	O
prudence	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
good	O
quality	O
's	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
pattern	O
to	O
your	O
sex	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Matthias	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
money	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
we	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Chealsea	B-place
yesterday	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
inquir	O
'd	O
after	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yours	O
ever	O
to	O
command	O
M	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
