TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
May	O
ye	O
11	O
.	O
1765	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ye	O
Pleaſure	O
to	O
forward	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
your	O
Br	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
good	O
Accts	O
..	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
only	O
to	O
receive	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
four	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
likewiſe	O
aſhamed	O
to	O
own	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
mislaid	O
a	O
Letter	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
William	B-pers
for	O
you	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
I	O
perused	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
containtnd	O
no	O
news	O
but	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
thoſe	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
Affection	O
&	O
Regard	O
which	O
ſhe	O
sincerely	O
feels	O
for	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Flock	O
are	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witneſs	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
underſtand	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
will	O
paſs	O
the	O
Regency	O
Bill	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Seſsion	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
a	O
Period	O
the	O
Week	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
however	O
be	O
long	O
enough	O
here	O
to	O
receive	O
any	O
Commands	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
and	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
and	O
my	O
Niece	O
s	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remembered	O
and	O
am	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
moſt	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brother	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
continue	O
well	O
:	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
part	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
paſt	O
than	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
.	O
