TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
The	O
reason	O
of	O
your	O
leaving	O
Town	O
so	O
suddenly	O
makes	O
all	O
apologies	O
unneceſsary	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
recovery	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
at	O
the	O
plan	O
you	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
separated	O
from	O
your	O
Friends	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
summer	O
.	O
I	O
conclude	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
has	O
informed	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
with	O
an	O
inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
lungs	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
her	O
existence	O
last	O
Monday	O
after	O
an	O
illneſs	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fatal	O
event	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
her	O
better	O
that	O
day	O
than	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
&	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
great	O
sensibility	O
for	O
my	O
attention	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
visited	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
during	O
her	O
illneſs	O
at	O
her	O
desire	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
with	O
great	O
fortitude	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
perfectly	O
sensible	O
of	O
her	O
approaching	O
diſsolution	O
,	O
she	O
conversed	O
with	O
ease	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
her	O
faultering	O
voice	O
woud	O
permit	O
,	O
&	O
frequently	O
joked	O
;	O
she	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
grave	O
faces	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
expreſsion	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
anxiety	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
reason	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
's	O
company	O
was	O
leſs	O
agreeable	O
to	O
her	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
Persons	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
Room	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Gen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
succeeded	O
me	O
with	O
Pope	O
's	O
Homer	O
which	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
read	O
&	O
&	O
she	O
listned	O
to	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
earnestneſs	O
;	O
trivial	O
conversations	O
she	O
said	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
up	O
her	O
attention	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
highly	O
interested	O
in	O
the	O
heroic	O
exploits	O
of	O
Achilles	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
a	O
very	O
singular	O
Will	O
,	O
very	O
spirited	O
&	O
quite	O
in	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
mention	O
but	O
one	O
particular	O
at	O
present	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
legacy	O
of	O
£500	O
.	O
&	O
all	O
her	O
cloaths	O
&	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
maid	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
near	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
interr	O
'd	O
at	O
Warwick	B-place
to	O
which	O
place	O
her	O
corpse	O
was	O
sent	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
arrived	O
from	O
Geneva	B-place
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
improved	O
in	O
stature	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
no	O
other	O
respect	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
concluded	O
every	O
thing	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
for	O
his	O
taking	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
care	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
further	O
consideration	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
advisable	O
to	O
lay	O
aside	O
that	O
plan	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
answer	O
'd	O
well	O
for	O
either	O
party	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
yet	O
undecided	O
how	O
I	O
shall	O
dispose	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
my	O
Apologies	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
reasons	O
for	O
my	O
change	O
of	O
sentiment	O
;	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
where	O
the	O
judgement	O
must	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
room	O
for	O
Compts	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
inceſsant	O
rain	O
&	O
I	O
perceive	O
the	O
wind	O
is	O
now	O
completely	O
settled	O
in	O
the	O
west	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
soon	O
expect	O
warm	O
weather	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
's	O
death	O
is	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
circumstance	O
of	O
consolation	O
to	O
poor	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
for	O
he	O
gains	O
£500	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
demands	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
are	O
now	O
completely	O
cancell	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
saving	O
of	O
£100	O
,	O
five	O
months	O
ago	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Patoun	I-pers
You	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
punctuality	O
.	O
Our	O
account	O
stands	O
thus	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
£600	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
Bond	O
the	O
Sums	O
in	O
the	O
order	O
following	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
forgot	O
any	O
other	O
sum	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
rectified	O
£190	O
.	O
--	O
.	O
--	O
350	O
.	O
--	O
.	O
--	O
Interest	O
due	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Bill	O
on	O
Meſsrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Gosling	I-pers
15.12	O
£580.12	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
Jane	B-pers
says	O
she	O
will	O
speak	O
for	O
herself	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
very	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
May	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
May	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
