TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Agent	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
acquainting	O
me	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
nor	O
had	O
even	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
positive	O
answer	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
paid	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
certainly	O
very	O
properly	O
at	O
liberty	O
not	O
to	O
consider	O
him	O
any	O
further	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
immediately	O
execute	O
a	O
proper	O
Bond	O
for	O
your	O
security	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
authorize	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
on	O
your	O
behalf	O
;	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
dated	O
as	O
I	O
formerly	O
mention	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
day	O
your	O
Bill	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
Manchester	B-place
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Scotch	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
busineſs	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
now	O
require	O
a	O
new	O
arrangement	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
safely	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
consider	O
your	O
interest	O
with	O
every	O
possible	O
attention	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
ready	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
pleasure	O
,	O
to	O
return	O
your	O
money	O
into	O
your	O
hands	O
,	O
wherever	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
signify	O
your	O
inclination	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Theatre	O
in	O
the	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
greater	O
doings	O
in	O
music	O
than	O
ever	O
the	O
ensuing	O
Winter	O
&	O
Spring	O
.	O
Marchesi	B-pers
certainly	O
returns	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
yesterday	O
;	O
Pacchierotti	B-pers
is	O
already	O
here	O
with	O
some	O
new	O
great	O
Instrumental	O
Performers	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
offer	O
the	O
Compts	O
.	O
of	O
my	O
Family	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
obliged	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
249	O
.	O
November	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
de	I-place
la	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
