TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
House	O
Tues	O
day	O
Morg	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Humble	O
Duty	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
acquaint	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
Dear	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
tolerable	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
Prince	B-pers
Octavius	I-pers
are	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
desire	O
their	O
Duty	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Love	O
to	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Hammy	B-pers
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
--	O
Sent	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
Tuesday	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1782	O
