TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
.	I-place
Nov	O
:	O
10	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
quite	O
forgotten	O
you	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
last	O
kind	O
letter	O
(	O
franked	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
)	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
so	O
ill	O
that	O
it	O
required	O
great	O
medical	O
skill	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
's	O
tender	O
care	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
To	O
let	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
this	O
attack	O
was	O
entirely	O
brought	O
on	O
by	O
agitation	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
unpleasant	O
state	O
of	O
suspense	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
been	O
in	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
terminated	O
by	O
the	O
discovery	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
does	O
not	O
wish	O
,	O
nor	O
,	O
in	O
fact	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
consent	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
renewed	O
his	O
engagement	O
.	O
He	O
adduces	O
various	O
reasons	O
so	O
little	O
credible	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
strongest	O
ground	O
to	O
fear	O
that	O
the	O
true	O
one	O
must	O
be	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
attachment	O
.	O
Rumours	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
reached	O
me	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
credit	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
chief	O
motives	O
he	O
alledged	O
being	O
a	O
plan	O
of	O
œconomy	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
addition	O
to	O
our	O
income	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
enabling	O
us	O
to	O
live	O
comfortably	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
proposition	O
being	O
unsuccessful	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
confirms	O
my	O
suspicions	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
easily	O
judge	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
suffered	O
,	O
particularly	O
as	O
the	O
suspense	O
was	O
so	O
protracted	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
,	O
bear	O
with	O
what	O
patience	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
a	O
misfortune	O
not	O
brought	O
on	O
by	O
any	O
fault	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	B-place
a	O
short	O
time	O
since	O
;	O
having	O
resolved	O
upon	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
little	O
moderate	O
establishment	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
here	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
air	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
never	O
agreed	O
well	O
with	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dislike	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
residence	O
on	O
various	O
other	O
accounts	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
likes	O
it	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
without	O
all	O
hope	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
Should	O
he	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
not	O
remove	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
visit	O
him	O
every	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
vexed	O
to	O
hear	O
this	O
ill	O
news	O
.	O
I	O
deferred	O
writing	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
hope	O
that	O
things	O
might	O
take	O
a	O
favourable	O
turn	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
hope	O
is	O
now	O
extinct	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
quit	O
the	O
subject	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
painful	O
a	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dwell	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
account	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
heart	O
made	O
her	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
great	O
regard	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
afflicted	O
by	O
a	O
similar	O
visitation	O
--	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
about	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Halsey	I-pers
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
not	O
very	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
I	O
regret	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
money	O
so	O
oddly	O
:	O
besides	O
his	O
Sisters	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
something	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
so	O
trifling	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
her	O
provisions	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
token	O
of	O
remembrance	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
have	O
been	O
well	O
since	O
I	O
last	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
in	O
tolerably	O
good	O
health	O
,	O
but	O
spirits	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
mended	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
Bath	B-place
suits	O
him	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
moving	O
is	O
such	O
an	O
operation	O
at	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
certainty	O
of	O
his	O
resolving	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
write	O
,	O
direct	O
No	O
:	O
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
Street	O
,	O
as	O
,	O
wherever	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
.	O
Has	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
:	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
been	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
does	O
she	O
do	O
?	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
unpleasant	O
state	O
;	O
which	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
already	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
unfolded	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
your	O
obliged	O
&	O
affecte	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
