TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
obey	O
your	O
directions	O
,	O
by	O
sending	O
in	O
your	O
name	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
because	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
expected	O
that	O
such	O
Meſsages	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
whatever	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
her	O
Carriage	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
hear	O
anything	O
about	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
burial	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
inform	O
You	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
except	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
pick	O
up	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
information	O
among	O
the	O
Atholls	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
since	O
the	O
Week	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
yet	O
dined	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Party	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
.	O
This	O
season	O
of	O
Devotion	O
comes	O
very	O
opportunely	O
for	O
composing	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
preparing	O
me	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
final	O
Decisions	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
my	O
Adversaries	O
throw	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
claims	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Naper	I-pers
's	O
property	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
Costs	O
on	O
a	O
17	O
Years	O
Suit	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
will	O
amount	O
to	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
,	O
this	O
Statement	O
is	O
correct	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
chearfully	O
give	O
four	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
Discharge	O
in	O
full	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
Road	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
,	O
the	O
Sedleys	O
at	O
Stapleford	O
Hall	O
,	O
&	O
their	O
Father	O
at	O
Nuttal	O
Temple	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
paſsed	O
by	O
,	O
without	O
calling	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
occasion	O
more	O
delay	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
my	O
mind	O
to	O
bear	O
,	O
being	O
most	O
anxious	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
&	O
Children	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
can	O
escape	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
This	O
busineſs	O
coming	O
on	O
Me	O
,	O
when	O
absent	O
from	O
Maria	B-pers
,	O
has	O
been	O
doubly	O
distreſsing	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
supported	O
by	O
a	O
Gracious	O
Providence	O
,	O
and	O
enabled	O
to	O
meet	O
every	O
difficulty	O
,	O
this	O
Life	O
subjects	O
us	O
too	O
with	O
calmneſs	O
&	O
resignation	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Louisa	B-pers
is	O
better	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Nothing	O
is	O
known	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
about	O
Peace	O
&	O
War	O
.	O
Parliament	O
adjourned	O
yesterday	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
19	O
th	O
-	O
Inst-	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Eighth	O
April	O
1803	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
