TOKEN	NE
William	O
Cel	O
L'amitié	O
nous	O
uniè	O
Les	O
bagatelles	O
montrent	O
respect	O
Written	O
&	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
March	O
1781	O
