TOKEN	NE
Horton	B-place
August	O
11	O
th	O
1787	O
--	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
long	O
expected	O
and	O
wished	O
for	O
letter	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
mine	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
grateful	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
recollect	O
that	O
you	O
still	O
owe	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
now	O
owe	O
me	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
increased	O
your	O
debt	O
to	O
me	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
lazy	O
and	O
idle	O
as	O
heat	O
can	O
make	O
me	O
.	O
your	O
letter	O
indeed	O
short	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
relief	O
to	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
grown	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
ignorance	O
of	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
myself	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
all	O
your	O
anxieties	O
are	O
over	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
mine	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
quite	O
recovered	O
,	O
&	O
your	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
got	O
over	O
inoculation	O
,	O
which	O
indeed	O
there	O
was	O
little	O
doubt	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
comfortable	O
thing	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
runs	O
no	O
longer	O
any	O
risk	O
of	O
infection	O
.	O
Pray	O
my	O
dear	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
your	O
plans	O
for	O
the	O
Autumn	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
probabilities	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
you	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
is	O
leſs	O
chance	O
than	O
ever	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
your	O
family	O
is	O
increased	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
tells	O
me	O
that	O
that	O
she	O
reckons	O
upon	O
your	O
coming	O
to	O
spend	O
sometime	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
when	O
will	O
that	O
sometime	O
be	O
?	O
can	O
it	O
not	O
be	O
managed	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
succeed	O
a	O
little	O
sometime	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
change	O
my	O
fortnights	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
poſsibly	O
catch	O
you	O
here	O
--	O
pray	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
turn	O
over	O
all	O
this	O
in	O
your	O
mind	O
and	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
indeed	O
notwistanding	O
what	O
I	O
suffer	O
from	O
the	O
heat	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
has	O
been	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
these	O
two	O
Days	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
fever	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
howeve	O
r	O
thank	O
God	O
not	O
attended	O
with	O
any	O
alarming	O
symtoms	O
she	O
is	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
--	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
begs	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
my	O
Brother	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
going	O
into	O
Herefordshire	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
some	O
very	O
pleasant	O
days	O
last	O
week	O
at	O
Wakefield	B-place
with	O
Ld	B-pers
and	O
Ly	B-pers
Euston	I-pers
who	O
are	O
both	O
charming	O
People	O
so	O
happy	O
,	O
so	O
fond	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
so	O
contented	O
to	O
live	O
alw	O
ays	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
fortune	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
somewhat	O
increased	O
by	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
live	O
entirely	O
at	O
Wakefield	B-place
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
delighted	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
so	O
near	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
hardly	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
discover	O
any	O
traces	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
beauty	O
,	O
so	O
exceſsivly	O
is	O
she	O
altered	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
altered	O
likewise	O
and	O
improved	O
in	O
her	O
manner	O
&	O
disposition	O
,	O
&	O
grown	O
vastly	O
pleasing	O
&	O
interesting	O
.	O
we	O
dined	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
last	O
Saturday	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
well	O
but	O
has	O
since	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
cold	O
which	O
prevent	O
ed	O
her	O
coming	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
improved	O
in	O
her	O
manner	O
&	O
looks	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
tho	O
'	O
&	O
eats	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
addit	O
t	O
ion	O
to	O
our	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
one	O
to	O
our	O
occupations	O
&	O
amuseme	O
nts	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
's	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
all	O
wished	O
to	O
remove	O
from	O
an	O
infected	O
air	O
&	O
a	O
scene	O
of	O
misery	O
&	O
confusion	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
attended	O
to	O
&	O
whe	O
re	O
her	O
Health	O
was	O
sufferi	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
child	O
as	O
to	O
disposition	O
and	O
very	O
quick	O
--	O
poor	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
is	O
dyi	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
m	O
os	O
t	O
cruel	O
manner	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
her	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
to	O
deposit	O
his	O
little	O
Charge	O
here	O
I	O
pray	O
every	O
day	O
for	O
her	O
release	O
,	O
nobody	O
was	O
every	O
better	O
prepared	O
in	O
every	O
sense	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
world	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
much	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
will	O
suffer	O
eſsentia	O
lly	O
from	O
his	O
wonderful	O
attentions	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
he	O
scarce	O
quits	O
Ly	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
24	O
nor	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
for	O
Months	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
yet	O
have	O
sunk	O
under	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
such	O
continued	O
anxiety	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
daily	O
subject	O
of	O
astonishment	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
consideri	O
n	O
g	O
too	O
the	O
infected	O
air	O
he	O
is	O
confined	O
to	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
accust	O
om	O
ed	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
violent	O
exercise	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
by	O
the	O
obligati	O
on	O
of	O
dreſsing	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
neighbou	O
rs	O
who	O
dined	O
here	O
--	O
the	O
Mansels	B-pers
amongst	O
others	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
my	O
aversion	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
it	O
is	O
over	O
this	O
is	O
Sunday	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
concludi	O
n	O
g	O
my	O
letter	O
before	O
Church	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
is	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
--	O
the	O
fever	O
is	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
headache	O
and	O
languor	O
remain	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
disagreeable	O
symptoms	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
go	O
off	O
--	O
Have	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Lounger	O
a	O
new	O
Scotch	O
periodical	O
work	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
abused	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
charmi	O
n	O
g	O
papers	O
in	O
it	O
particularly	O
all	O
those	O
signed	O
Z.	O
read	O
it	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
,	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
&	O
write	O
soon	O
--	O
adieu	O
ever	O
affce	O
:	O
&	O
c	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
11	O
August	O
1787	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
