TOKEN	NE
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
preſents	O
his	O
respectful	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
they	O
are	O
ſafe	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Northton	B-place
.	O
He	O
intends	O
paying	O
his	O
respects	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
perſon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
prevent	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
begs	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
Companion	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
the	O
laſt	O
Drawing	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
--	O
It	O
will	O
ſhew	O
he	O
has	O
amused	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Abſence	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
than	O
Concerts	O
,	O
Scandal	O
,	O
Excurſions	O
&	O
Verſes	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
has	O
little	O
merit	O
than	O
being	O
the	O
only	O
Drawing	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
eleven	O
years	O
paſt	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Goodwill	O
with	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
given	O
,	O
muſt	O
plead	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
all	O
it	O
's	O
Imperfections	O
.	O
--	O
