TOKEN	NE
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
30	O
th	O
-	O
June	O
1780	O
Did	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
know	O
how	O
my	O
fully	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
employ	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
“	O
so	O
unreasonable	O
”	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
ten	O
letters	O
unanswer	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
table	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
however	O
very	O
sorry	O
the	O
post	O
should	O
go	O
away	O
yesterday	O
without	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
Rhea	B-pers
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
&	O
friendly	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
highly	O
improper	O
for	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
answer	O
'd	O
i	O
t	O
immediately	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
indisposed	O
--	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
&	O
violent	O
Cold	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
--	O
this	O
has	O
prevented	O
my	O
Bathing	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
doing	O
before	O
now	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
--	O
my	O
cold	O
is	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
Perfecta	B-pers
is	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
your	O
remembrance	O
&	O
both	O
she	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
their	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
fine	O
things	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
fine	O
things	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
daily	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wont	O
tire	O
you	O
with	O
repeti	O
tions	O
How	O
comes	O
it	O
,	O
yt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ancaster	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Tunbridge	B-place
?	O
--	O
poor	O
Woman	O
!	O
my	O
Heart	O
bleeds	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
--	O
pray	O
continue	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
intelligence	O
you	O
can	O
about	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Daughters	O
.	O
--	O
is	O
Lord	B-pers
Althorpe	I-pers
better	O
?	O
The	O
more	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
wth	O
our	O
society	O
ye	O
.	O
more	O
I	O
approve	O
,	O
&	O
like	O
them	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
is	O
about	O
27	O
--	O
handsome	O
,	O
modest	O
,	O
amiable	O
&	O
well	O
bred	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
upon	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
appointed	O
preceptor	O
to	O
P.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
pursuing	O
ye	O
.	O
Study	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
law	O
--	O
he	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
profited	O
by	O
a	O
liberal	O
education	O
;	O
reads	O
,	O
&	O
recites	O
remarkably	O
well	O
--	O
writes	O
poetry	O
in	O
an	O
easy	O
,	O
elegant	O
manner	O
,	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
from	O
a	O
translation	O
of	O
a	O
latin	O
Epitaph	O
he	O
gave	O
Perfecta	B-pers
the	O
other	O
morng	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
is	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
some	O
years	O
older	O
than	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
about	O
35	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
advantage	O
of	O
person	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
disagreeable	O
--	O
his	O
countenance	O
is	O
an	O
index	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
is	O
perfectly	O
amiable	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
talents	O
,	O
taste	O
,	O
&	O
genius	O
--	O
he	O
draws	O
finely	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
continually	O
taking	O
advantage	O
of	O
this	O
delightful	O
accomplishment	O
by	O
taking	O
views	O
of	O
every	O
prospect	O
worthy	O
his	O
pencil	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
travell	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
&	O
nothing	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
escap	O
'd	O
his	O
observation	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
useful	O
or	O
elegant	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
,	O
reads	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
English	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
in	O
French	O
--	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
is	O
giving	O
me	O
&	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
instructions	O
in	O
drawing	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
task	O
for	O
Lands	O
capes	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
turns	O
to	O
explore	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
are	O
our	O
guides	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
picturesque	O
paints	O
of	O
view	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Pevensey	B-place
--	O
the	O
Noble	O
Ruin	O
of	O
a	O
Castle	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
is	O
worthy	O
observation	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
me	O
clambering	O
up	O
the	O
ruins	O
&	O
seated	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Parson	O
's	O
chair	O
--	O
perch	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Magpie	O
--	O
King	O
William	O
ye	O
.	O
Conqueror	O
landed	O
here	O
--	O
&	O
Oliver	O
Cromwell	O
destroy	O
'd	O
this	O
vast	O
&	O
Noble	O
Building	O
--	O
I	O
want	O
much	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
further	O
intelligence	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
d	O
es	O
criptions	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Antiquities	O
of	O
England	B-place
one	O
may	O
meet	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
ask	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
yet	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
advantage	O
we	O
experience	O
by	O
the	O
vicinity	O
of	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
Place	O
Lady	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
Compton	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
it	O
belongs	O
,	O
has	O
politely	O
given	O
their	O
R	O
H	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
priviledge	O
of	O
going	O
thither	O
whenever	O
they	O
chuse	O
--	O
we	O
daily	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
&	O
Grounds	O
--	O
the	O
Children	O
can	O
there	O
enjoy	O
ye	O
.	O
benifit	O
of	O
shade	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
whenever	O
we	O
please	O
--	O
we	O
often	O
spend	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
library	O
--	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
not	O
Modern	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
pretty	O
large	O
,	O
convenient	O
,	O
&	O
well	O
calculated	O
for	O
comfort	O
&	O
society	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
repair	O
--	O
&	O
has	O
the	O
elegance	O
of	O
neatneſs	O
beyond	O
what	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
.	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
Bell	B-pers
is	O
unwell	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
return	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
complaint	O
that	O
alarm	O
'd	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
tell	O
how	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
yt-	O
she	O
has	O
m	O
y	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
speedy	O
recovery	O
--	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
begin	O
a	O
correspondence	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
J——	I-pers
had	O
I	O
once	O
done	O
so	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
impolite	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
a	O
letter	O
--	O
My	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
new	O
correspondent	O
--	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
write	O
