TOKEN	NE
H3	O
.	O
To	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
King	B-pers
George	I-pers
s	O
advice	O
as	O
to	O
Eton	O
Windsor	B-place
17	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1782	O
My	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
The	O
Illneſs	O
of	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
has	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
so	O
entirely	O
unsettled	O
us	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
leisure	O
for	O
the	O
pleasant	O
occupation	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
apprehensive	O
you	O
may	O
impute	O
my	O
silence	O
to	O
a	O
wrong	O
cause	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
defer	O
writing	O
because	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
send	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
written	O
in	O
haste	O
.	O
this	O
poor	O
Child	O
has	O
been	O
return	O
'd	O
fm	O
.	O
Deal	B-place
near	O
3	O
weeks	O
he	O
had	O
fever	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Doctor	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
more	O
immediately	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
&	O
intended	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
removed	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea-air	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
now	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
apprehend	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
recover	O
and	O
even	O
his	O
Parents	O
are	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
--	O
You	O
who	O
are	O
a	O
fond	O
&	O
tender	O
Mother	O
can	O
judge	O
what	O
these	O
Affectionate	O
Parents	O
must	O
suffer	O
--	O
You	O
ask	O
if	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
's	O
accident	O
was	O
as	O
represented	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
misfortune	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
shoulder	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
sometime	O
before	O
he	O
can	O
recover	O
ye	O
.	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
part	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
dislocation	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
guest	O
for	O
three	O
day	O
's	O
&	O
invited	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
Birth	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
last	O
tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
better	O
health	O
or	O
spirits	O
--	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
envy	O
'd	O
for	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
roof	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
except	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
looking	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
situated	O
in	O
this	O
family	O
,	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
enjoy	O
ye	O
society	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
disappointed	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
not	O
already	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Jebb	I-pers
to	O
day	O
&	O
certainly	O
will	O
tell	O
him	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wms	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
in	O
n	O
attention	O
to	O
his	O
advice	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
particularly	O
sorry	O
you	O
delay	O
'd	O
going	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
for	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Jebb	I-pers
has	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
health	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
but	O
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
therefore	O
have	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
advantage	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
consult	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
in	O
good	O
order	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
best	O
proof	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
of	O
his	O
affection	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
triffle	O
with	O
his	O
health	O
;	O
surely	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
forgot	O
his	O
sufferings	O
of	O
last	O
Winter	O
?	O
&	O
will	O
he	O
not	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
guard	O
against	O
paſsing	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
manner	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
delighted	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cotten	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rowston	I-pers
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Godson	O
--	O
what	O
are	O
your	O
intentions	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
yet	O
found	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
intend	O
keeping	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
If	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
to	O
advise	O
--	O
he	O
wld	O
.	O
say	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Eaton	O
--	O
his	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
partial	O
to	O
this	O
school	O
&	O
thinks	O
,	O
Boys	O
ought	O
to	O
go	O
even	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
early	O
age	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
old	O
&	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse	O
School	O
as	O
he	O
terms	O
them	O
,	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
..	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
from	O
Tunbridge	B-place
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
mentions	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
--	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
amuse	O
an	O
idle	O
moment	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
going	O
forward	O
thither	O
--	O
dont	O
shew	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
&	O
return	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
I	O
get	O
any	O
letters	O
yt	O
.	O
have	O
matter	O
or	O
entertainment	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
sometimes	O
inclose	O
ym	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
depend	O
upon	O
Your	O
prudence	O
&	O
discretion	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
sometimes	O
treat	O
indulge	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
friend	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
M	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
pray	O
write	O
soon	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
real	O
pleasure	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
hearing	O
from	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
