TOKEN	NE
Oakford	B-place
Monday	O
morning	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
13	O
Sepr	O
.	O
13	O
Not	O
having	O
an	O
Oppy	O
of	O
writing	O
when	O
I	O
wish	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
after	O
8	O
this	O
morng	O
before	O
Thursday	O
I	O
got	O
at	O
6	O
to	O
scribble	O
on	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
got	O
after	O
turnings	O
&	O
windings	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Exmouth	B-place
we	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Sands	O
&	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
Shells	O
the	O
refuse	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
but	O
threw	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
away	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Row	O
of	O
houses	O
called	O
the	O
Beacon	O
that	O
are	O
built	O
on	O
the	O
Rock	O
above	O
the	O
Sea	O
that	O
have	O
a	O
commanding	O
prospect	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
is	O
built	O
hickledy	O
piggledy	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Aſsembly	O
room	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
houses	O
let	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
15	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Week	O
--	O
We	O
met	O
some	O
promenaders	O
bowing	O
&	O
scraping	O
,	O
ducking	O
&	O
even	O
curtseying	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
some	O
on	O
Donkeys	O
&	O
c	O
a	O
true	O
picture	O
of	O
a	O
Watering	O
place	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Embankment	O
here	O
done	O
by	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
by	O
wch	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
snug	O
Corner	O
from	O
the	O
Sea	O
at	O
present	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
wear	O
the	O
Appearance	O
of	O
profit	O
--	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
croſsed	O
this	O
water	O
to	O
Dawlish	B-place
wch	O
.	O
is	O
two	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
only	O
¼	O
Mile	O
by	O
water	O
but	O
finding	O
James	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
averse	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
up	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
objections	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
a	O
boat	O
&	O
jumped	O
overboard	O
&	O
very	O
nearly	O
took	O
him	O
too	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
up	O
&	O
we	O
took	O
another	O
road	O
by	O
the	O
Œstuary	O
for	O
2	O
miles	O
which	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
view	O
of	O
Powderham	B-place
Castle	I-place
--	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
avoid	O
Topsham	B-place
,	O
again	O
we	O
miſsed	O
our	O
way	O
--	O
&	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
got	O
our	O
Noses	O
set	O
straight	O
forward	O
--	O
We	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Barracks	O
,	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Exeter	B-place
which	O
are	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Scale	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
2	O
on	O
comparing	O
Notes	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
our	O
hearty	O
Luncheon	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
Dinner	O
--	O
My	O
Companion	O
had	O
dawdled	O
away	O
so	O
much	O
time	O
in	O
changing	O
his	O
dreſs	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Equestrian	O
performances	O
at	O
7	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
hardly	O
time	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
--	O
for	O
the	O
Waiter	O
told	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
by	O
7	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
get	O
seats	O
so	O
we	O
drank	O
our	O
Tea	O
a	O
la	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
nearly	O
scolded	O
our	O
throats	O
&	O
then	O
posted	O
to	O
the	O
elegant	O
Theatre	O
--	O
constructed	O
of	O
boards	O
&	O
an	O
Awning	O
--	O
it	O
looked	O
comical	O
&	O
answered	O
the	O
purpose	O
--	O
We	O
were	O
in	O
good	O
time	O
to	O
choose	O
Seats	O
&	O
paid	O
3/	O
for	O
Admittance	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
military	O
band	O
I	O
believe	O
5	O
th	O
Regiment	O
who	O
played	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
the	O
performances	O
were	O
equal	O
to	O
any	O
Thing	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
the	O
Master	O
Mr.	B-pers
West	I-pers
is	O
the	O
handsomest	O
Man	O
in	O
face	O
&	O
person	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
&	O
an	O
excellent	O
Rider	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
feats	O
--	O
hoisting	O
one	O
another	O
on	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
stories	O
high	O
in	O
various	O
ways	O
,	O
tumbling	O
,	O
riding	O
,	O
jumping	O
&	O
tumbling	O
over	O
4	O
horses	O
at	O
once	O
--	O
a	O
dextrous	O
poney	O
&	O
pretty	O
Woman	O
doing	O
such	O
feats	O
on	O
the	O
Slack	O
wire	O
as	O
astonished	O
me	O
--	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
table	O
placed	O
an	O
the	O
Wire	O
--	O
on	O
it	O
were	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
wh-	O
Candles	O
--	O
a	O
Tea	O
pot	O
&	O
2	O
Cups	O
&	O
Saucers	O
--	O
then	O
swinging	O
with	O
great	O
force	O
,	O
She	O
pretend	O
ed	O
to	O
pour	O
out	O
Tea	O
into	O
the	O
Cups	O
--	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
Cup	O
Saucer	O
in	O
each	O
hand	O
&	O
moved	O
the	O
Cups	O
about	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
the	O
Indian	O
moved	O
the	O
Rings	O
round	O
his	O
Toes	O
&	O
did	O
various	O
other	O
feats	O
that	O
were	O
very	O
extra	O
ordinary	O
--	O
Afterwards	O
a	O
Man	O
amused	O
us	O
with	O
his	O
dexterity	O
on	O
the	O
Slack	O
Rope	O
where	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
perfectly	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seldom	O
been	O
more	O
amused	O
for	O
2	O
hours	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
J.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
spend	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
his	O
friend	O
who	O
we	O
met	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
Theatre	O
so	O
I	O
wished	O
a	O
good	O
Night	O
&	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
write	O
my	O
letter	O
fm	O
.	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
before	O
12	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
slack	O
Wire	O
had	O
unstrung	O
my	O
Nerves	O
--	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
Nothing	O
occurred	O
before	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
except	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee	O
Room	O
where	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
the	O
Hero	O
of	O
Maida	B-place
came	O
in	O
&	O
asked	O
an	O
Admiral	O
who	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
me	O
what	O
News	O
?	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
surprised	O
if	O
Bonaparte	B-pers
gained	O
some	O
advantages	O
at	O
first	O
&	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
despond	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Tilsit	B-place
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
succeed	O
eventually	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
great	O
Authority	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
Theatre	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
Man	O
--	O
Who	O
the	O
Admiral	O
was	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Oppy	O
of	O
making	O
an	O
Enquiry	O
--	O
The	O
Bishop	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
ask	O
us	O
to	O
dinner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
out	O
himself	O
but	O
hoped	O
we	O
shd	O
.	O
stay	O
over	O
Monday	O
--	O
This	O
we	O
excused	O
ourselves	O
--	O
he	O
consulted	O
me	O
about	O
putting	O
a	O
Curtain	O
behind	O
the	O
Singers	O
&	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
suggest	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Organ	O
Loft	O
&	O
introduced	O
the	O
Organist	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Opinion	O
so	O
&	O
so	O
--	O
The	O
Organist	O
said	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
certainly	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
effect	O
but	O
they	O
expected	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
people	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
at	O
a	O
lower	O
price	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
diſsatisfied	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
unanswerable	O
so	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
our	O
Seats	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
convinced	O
by	O
a	O
Chorus	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
powers	O
sufft	O
.	O
to	O
fill	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
&	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Bp	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
my	O
Opinion	O
&	O
thought	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
best	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
the	O
Chorus	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
too	O
loud	O
to	O
be	O
agreeable	O
--	O
This	O
Youth	O
who	O
sings	O
so	O
finely	O
&	O
who	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Marsh	O
has	O
a	O
Hair	O
Lip	O
--	O
his	O
Voice	O
is	O
perfectly	O
clear	O
&	O
harmonious	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
equal	O
to	O
Braham	B-pers
--	O
He	O
has	O
imitated	O
Catalani	B-pers
&	O
unfortunately	O
mimicked	O
her	O
f	O
all	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
her	O
quivering	O
Chin	O
--	O
When	O
the	O
Bp	O
.	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
P	B-pers
.	I-pers
observed	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sing	O
in	O
Te	O
deum	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
B	O
.	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
sour	O
look	O
afterwards	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
present	O
the	O
Book	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
speak	O
earnestly	O
&	O
good	O
humourdly	O
to	O
Marsh	B-pers
&	O
I	O
gueſsed	O
what	O
was	O
paſsing	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
sing	O
delightfully	O
the	O
whole	O
Anthem	O
was	O
a	O
Solo	O
except	O
the	O
concluding	O
Chorus	O
--	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
regular	O
Conveyance	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
there	O
to	O
day	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
None	O
but	O
post	O
Chaises	O
&	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
suit	O
my	O
Calculations	O
This	O
little	O
excursion	O
cost	O
me	O
enough	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
James	B-pers
pay	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
managed	O
as	O
delicately	O
as	O
poſsible	O
&	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Boy	O
1£	O
Note	O
thinking	O
it	O
would	O
please	O
the	O
Mother	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
little	O
urchin	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
Brother	O
--	O
Before	O
we	O
left	O
Exeter	B-place
we	O
saw	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Sidwells	O
Church	O
wch	O
is	O
nearly	O
finished	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prettiest	O
Church	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
built	O
after	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
a	O
Cathedral	O
--	O
The	O
pillars	O
are	O
light	O
&	O
the	O
Ornaments	O
beautifully	O
executed	O
after	O
the	O
ancient	O
Models	O
--	O
the	O
profit	O
of	O
the	O
music	O
to	O
day	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
towards	O
a	O
steeple	O
.	O
The	O
Body	O
has	O
cost	O
8000	O
L	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
painted	O
Glass	O
Window	O
at	O
the	O
East	O
End	O
--	O
representing	O
our	O
Saviour	O
rising	O
in	O
the	O
Clouds	O
--	O
The	O
Head	O
is	O
fine	O
&	O
some	O
parts	O
besides	O
&	O
some	O
shocking	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Graingers	O
Garden	O
wch	O
.	O
adjoins	O
the	O
Castle	O
as	O
is	O
truly	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lions	O
at	O
Exeter	B-place
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
poplar	O
(	O
Lombardy	O
)	O
&	O
a	O
Platanus	O
that	O
exceed	O
any	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
seen	O
in	O
size	O
&	O
heigtht	O
--	O
The	O
Garden	O
is	O
unique	O
Depending	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
Exeter	B-place
till	O
3	O
OClock	O
--	O
we	O
rested	O
our	O
Horses	O
½	O
hour	O
at	O
Tiverton	B-place
&	O
then	O
found	O
the	O
private	O
road	O
dark	O
as	O
in	O
many	O
places	O
it	O
is	O
overshadowed	O
wh-	O
trees	O
--	O
The	O
Moon	O
was	O
obscured	O
&	O
sometimes	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
see	O
the	O
road	O
--	O
P	B-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Tooth	O
ache	O
,	O
his	O
horse	O
not	O
well	O
&	O
tired	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
led	O
the	O
Way	O
--	O
Mumchance	O
--	O
We	O
walked	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horrible	O
hills	O
near	O
this	O
place	O
&	O
hard	O
work	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
covered	O
with	O
loose	O
Stones	O
--	O
We	O
got	O
home	O
safe	O
--	O
eat	O
a	O
good	O
Supper	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Please	O
to	O
inform	O
Madam	B-pers
La	I-pers
Comteſse	I-pers
......	O
that	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
(	O
he	O
lives	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
Exeter	O
St	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
)	O
has	O
cured	O
3	O
persons	O
afflicted	O
wh-	O
the	O
Tic	O
doloreux	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
8	O
Years	O
continuance	O
--	O
The	O
Drs	O
.	O
affect	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
,	O
but	O
Rev	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Jerome	I-pers
De	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
aſsured	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fact	O
--	O
Monday	O
I	O
am	O
either	O
to	O
fish	O
or	O
shoot	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Tomorrow	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
shoot	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
's	O
&	O
return	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
On	O
Thursday	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
again	O
&	O
then	O
fix	O
a	O
day	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
peregrinations	O
--	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
Amen	O
Single	O
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
