TOKEN	NE
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
leave	O
London	B-place
without	O
sending	O
You	O
a	O
line	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
moment	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
sleeping	O
3	O
nights	O
in	O
different	O
Beds	O
&	O
upon	O
hard	O
mattraſs	O
's	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
,	O
has	O
quite	O
destroy	O
'd	O
my	O
rest	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
extremely	O
Nervous	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
hold	O
my	O
pen	O
steady	O
.	O
if	O
You	O
see	O
Dr.	B-pers
T——	I-pers
Turton	B-pers
tell	O
him	O
I	O
sent	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
for	O
4	O
D	O
raughts	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
opening	O
dose	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
--	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
