TOKEN	NE
with	O
what	O
pleasure	O
do	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
charming	O
,	O
kind	O
and	O
comforting	O
letter	O
now	O
lying	O
before	O
me	O
!	O
few	O
things	O
could	O
have	O
afforded	O
me	O
more	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
experienced	O
from	O
the	O
receit	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
The	O
interest	O
you	O
expreſs	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
and	O
the	O
anxiety	O
,	O
about	O
that	O
dejection	O
of	O
spirits	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
too	O
apparent	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
here	O
,	O
are	O
truly	O
gratify	O
ing	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
relieve	O
your	O
mind	O
from	O
any	O
uneasineſs	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
by	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
traces	O
left	O
of	O
the	O
bad	O
spirits	O
I	O
had	O
during	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
light	O
as	O
air	O
,	O
chearful	O
,	O
nay	O
gay	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
unite	O
me	O
to	O
all	O
I	O
love	O
most	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
followed	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
progreſs	O
of	O
my	O
depreſsion	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
known	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
nay	O
perhaps	O
better	O
than	O
myself	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
the	O
causes	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
those	O
that	O
related	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
well	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
--	O
various	O
,	O
trifling	O
perhaps	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
a	O
heart	O
&	O
mind	O
very	O
well	O
disposed	O
to	O
receive	O
&	O
nourish	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
united	O
&	O
grew	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
ensemble	O
that	O
affected	O
my	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
disposition	O
--	O
many	O
disap	O
pointing	O
circumstances	O
happened	O
to	O
my	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
uneasineſs	O
on	O
their	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
exactly	O
how	O
to	O
conduct	O
,	O
myself	O
&	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
easy	O
to	O
extricate	O
,	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
felt	O
certainly	O
desolate	O
&	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
my	O
Family	O
particularly	O
my	O
Sister	O
--	O
All	O
these	O
circumstan	O
ces	O
united	O
and	O
contributed	O
to	O
that	O
dejection	O
which	O
you	O
complain	O
of	O
--	O
and	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
separately	O
could	O
constitute	O
a	O
source	O
of	O
misery	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
could	O
have	O
satisfied	O
you	O
,	O
enumerated	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
it	O
have	O
admitted	O
of	O
an	O
explanation	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
justified	O
me	O
--	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
I	O
wished	O
for	O
you	O
!	O
--	O
How	O
many	O
comfortable	O
,	O
hours	O
might	O
we	O
have	O
spent	O
together	O
!	O
--	O
But	O
fate	O
has	O
deemed	O
it	O
otherwise	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
separated	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
long	O
separations	O
check	O
&	O
stop	O
that	O
mutual	O
confidence	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
ones	O
Friend	O
,	O
seeks	O
another	O
Chanel	O
--	O
The	O
want	O
of	O
this	O
Friend	O
always	O
at	O
hand	O
&	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
could	O
always	O
open	O
myself	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
primary	O
cause	O
of	O
my	O
dejection	O
--	O
for	O
as	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
commit	O
to	O
paper	O
,	O
to	O
chance	O
,	O
&	O
perhaps	O
to	O
other	O
Eyes	O
a	O
million	O
of	O
trifles	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
even	O
bear	O
one	O
self	O
to	O
immortalize	O
(	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
degree	O
by	O
writing	O
them	O
)	O
&	O
which	O
are	O
yet	O
of	O
consequence	O
at	O
the	O
minute	O
they	O
occur	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
and	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
I	O
fear	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
soon	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
in	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
enjoying	O
that	O
free	O
air	O
&	O
directi	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
disposition	O
of	O
my	O
Flower	O
Garden	O
--	O
chatti	O
n	O
g	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
Bell	B-pers
--	O
&	O
telli	O
n	O
g	O
her	O
all	O
that	O
has	O
paſsed	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
--	O
are	O
there	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
from	O
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
&	O
c	O
or	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
Town	O
?	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
I	O
hope	O
enters	O
into	O
your	O
consideration	O
of	O
future	O
Plans	O
--	O
London	B-place
is	O
just	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
gaiety	O
--	O
Balls	O
without	O
end	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
two	O
this	O
week	O
--	O
ones	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Melbourne	I-pers
s	O
to	O
night	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tollemashe	I-pers
s	O
--	O
The	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
is	O
to	O
give	O
three	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
two	O
--	O
the	O
Prince	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Faulconberg	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
very	O
well	O
but	O
il	O
y	O
a	O
trop	O
et	O
trop	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
tired	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
long	O
for	O
June	O
and	O
Horton	B-place
--	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
longest	O
Winter	O
I	O
ever	O
remember	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
(	O
excepting	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
my	O
Family	O
)	O
not	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
much	O
in	O
public	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
admire	O
,	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
&	O
love	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
everyday	O
--	O
Indeed	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
particularly	O
fortuna	O
te	O
in	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
known	O
to	O
value	O
her	O
uncomm	O
on	O
worth	O
--	O
their	O
are	O
very	O
few	O
such	O
in	O
this	O
monde	O
--	O
such	O
feminine	O
softneſs	O
of	O
manner	O
,	O
a	O
temper	O
so	O
pleacid	O
with	O
so	O
masculine	O
an	O
understanding	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
fortitude	O
&	O
command	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
united	O
to	O
such	O
&	O
such	O
good	O
principles	O
,	O
forms	O
a	O
character	O
one	O
seldom	O
m	O
eets	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
vastly	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
which	O
will	O
delight	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
c	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
or	O
22	O
d	O
--	O
what	O
pleasure	O
!	O
what	O
happineſs	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
reading	O
German	O
à	O
force	O
&	O
have	O
some	O
delightful	O
Books	O
Mm-	B-pers
de	I-pers
Reventlau	I-pers
has	O
lent	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
danish	O
Ministers	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
play	O
fellow	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
&	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
amiable	O
&	O
accomplished	O
Woman	O
--	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
General	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
a	O
Man	O
of	O
honor	O
,	O
good	O
sense	O
&	O
truth	O
,	O
about	O
Madm	B-pers
Busche	I-pers
&	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
believes	O
all	O
the	O
reports	O
concerni	O
n	O
g	O
he	O
r	O
&	O
P.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
related	O
to	O
her	O
bad	O
conduct	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
certainly	O
the	O
Prince	O
admired	O
&	O
followed	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
thinks	O
her	O
a	O
truly	O
good	O
&	O
amiable	O
woman	O
--	O
&	O
whose	O
character	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
injured	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
well	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
--	O
may	O
you	O
long	O
long	O
,	O
ever	O
,	O
preserve	O
the	O
Bleſsing	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
other	O
you	O
enjoy	O
and	O
deserve	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
!	O
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
and	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
his	O
best	O
compts	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
send	O
me	O
your	O
next	O
directions	O
May	O
9	O
th	O
1786	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
9	O
May	O
1786	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Courteen	B-place
hall	I-place
Northamton	B-place
