TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
Decr	O
.	O
Twenty	O
first	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchester	B-place
JMurray	B-pers
