TOKEN	NE
1	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1782	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
last	O
week	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
mortified	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
are	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
in	O
this	O
Family	O
people	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
consider	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
fix	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
happens	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
despair	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
myself	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
's	O
absence	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
fe	O
l	O
e	O
l	O
very	O
sensibly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
last	O
week	O
,	O
who	O
desird	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Camp	O
on	O
Thursday	O
with	O
her	O
whole	O
Family	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
if	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
shou	O
'd	O
go	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
I	O
shoud	O
very	O
soon	O
get	O
better	O
if	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
take	O
the	O
Bark	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
prevented	O
by	O
a	O
constant	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
affects	O
me	O
dreadfully	O
,	O
altho	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
stronger	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
shoud	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
on	O
the	O
Terrace	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
some	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
a	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
as	O
an	O
improper	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
if	O
you	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
veto	O
I	O
must	O
content	O
myself	O
with	O
Richmond	O
Gardens	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
respectfully	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
Princeſses	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
&	O
to	O
Prince	B-pers
Octavius	I-pers
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
Adieu	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
most	O
sincerely	O
yrs	O
John	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
