TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
May	O
19	O
th	O
:	O
1782	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
must	O
not	O
say	O
Hamilton	B-pers
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
formal	O
--	O
how	O
little	O
you	O
yet	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
use	O
formality	O
with	O
those	O
I	O
love	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
paſs	O
over	O
this	O
Day	O
,	O
witho	O
ut	O
wishing	O
you	O
Joy	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
no	O
one	O
can	O
more	O
sincerely	O
join	O
with	O
me	O
than	O
yourself	O
,	O
in	O
wishing	O
many	O
&	O
many	O
happy	O
returns	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
your	O
kind	O
and	O
gracious	O
Mistreſs	O
.	O
--	O
how	O
very	O
much	O
one	O
's	O
mind	O
is	O
affected	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
mine	O
is	O
,	O
)	O
by	O
different	O
Situations	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
fix	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
arrange	O
my	O
House	O
against	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
return	O
--	O
&	O
to	O
go	O
quickly	O
to	O
Church	O
on	O
this	O
Sunday	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
puts	O
my	O
thoughts	O
into	O
a	O
different	O
train	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
still	O
in	O
theLondon	B-place
--	O
at	O
an	O
earlier	O
hour	O
I	O
rose	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
quiet	O
time	O
before	O
breakfast	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
gratitude	O
with	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
burst	O
of	O
Spring	O
--	O
(	O
wh	O
:	O
tho	O
backward	O
)	O
is	O
now	O
surrounding	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
that	O
my	O
Prayers	O
were	O
offered	O
up	O
for	O
One	O
--	O
who	O
tho	O
'	O
seated	O
on	O
a	O
costly	O
Throne	O
,	O
has	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
made	O
her	O
Supplications	O
this	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Throne	O
of	O
Heaven	O
--	O
may	O
She	O
be	O
aſsisted	O
to	O
keep	O
steadily	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
of	O
every	O
Virtue	O
&	O
at	O
length	O
service	O
&	O
an	O
unfading	O
Crown	O
which	O
will	O
last	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
--	O
&	O
may	O
we	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
profit	O
by	O
her	O
Example	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
go	O
through	O
our	O
Pilgrimage	O
on	O
Earth	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
by	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
our	O
pardoning	O
God	O
--	O
be	O
everlastingly	O
blest	O
hereafter	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
is	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
uneasy	O
at	O
not	O
having	O
heard	O
from	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
he	O
will	O
come	O
either	O
tonight	O
or	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
ready	O
.	O
the	O
poor	O
Fringe	O
not	O
yet	O
finished	O
--	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
was	O
safely	O
at	O
home	O
again	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Yrs	O
:	O
sincerely	O
PD	B-pers
My	O
cold	O
is	O
better	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
my	O
Children	O
are	O
--	O
wh	O
:	O
is	O
much	O
more	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
write	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
pray	O
wish	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
Joy	O
for	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Day	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
wish	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
all	O
my	O
my	O
heart	O
dictates	O
.	O
what	O
delightful	O
great	O
news	O
from	O
the	O
W.West	B-place
I.Indies	I-place
I	O
am	O
so	O
sorry	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
is	O
not	O
here	O
to	O
fire	O
off	O
our	O
little	O
Cannon	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
:	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
