TOKEN	NE
Wandsworth	O
hill	O
Sepr	O
.	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
yet	O
received	O
no	O
answer	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
take	O
for	O
granted	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Letters	O
has	O
been	O
lost	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
--	O
in	O
case	O
mine	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
arrived	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
I	O
think	O
it	O
right	O
to	O
repeat	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
my	O
last	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Papa	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
they	O
wish	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
's	O
Christening	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
either	O
to	O
morrow	O
or	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
day	O
till	O
they	O
know	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
convenient	O
&	O
agreeable	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
their	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
desire	O
he	O
will	O
keep	O
himself	O
unengaged	O
for	O
that	O
occasion	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
contrive	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
us	O
all	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
and	O
none	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
yr	O
.	O
very	O
affecte-	O
Elizath	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
c	O
are	O
all	O
perfectly	O
well	O
--	O
Be	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
line	O
by	O
the	O
bearer	O
