TOKEN	NE
Savil	O
e	O
Row	O
Jany	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
89	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
I	O
found	O
yr	O
letter	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
Town	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
answered	O
it	O
sooner	O
,	O
&	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
kind	O
concern	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
waited	O
&	O
hoped	O
for	O
an	O
amendment	O
in	O
his	O
health	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
this	O
severe	O
weather	O
lasts	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
little	O
chance	O
of	O
his	O
losing	O
his	O
Cough	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
;	O
her	O
progreſs	O
dans	O
l'art	O
de	O
plaire	O
will	O
now	O
be	O
dayly	O
visible	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
she	O
will	O
ever	O
contribute	O
to	O
your	O
amusement	O
,	O
comfort	O
&	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
--	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
)	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
certain	O
ly	O
give	O
yr	O
meſsage	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
This	O
day	O
's	O
account	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
is	O
very	O
favorable	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
God	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
eſsentially	O
better	O
,	O
notwithstand	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
Dr	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
's	O
declerations	O
--	O
My	O
S	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
hopes	O
soon	O
to	O
receive	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
letter	O
she	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
desires	O
to	O
be	O
remembered	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
sends	O
10000	O
kiſses	O
to	O
the	O
dear	O
Bambino	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
it	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
rely	O
yrs	O
I.B.G——	B-pers
This	O
is	O
from	O
Miss	B-pers
C.M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
's	O
sister	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
