TOKEN	NE
Stan	O
.	O
St	O
:	O
Octr	O
:	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Fd	O
:	O
One	O
Line	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
Beloved	O
Child	O
is	O
released	O
from	O
all	O
his	O
Sufferings	O
,	O
&	O
Bleſsed	O
be	O
God	O
his	O
poor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Father	O
&	O
I	O
are	O
not	O
sunk	O
under	O
the	O
Afflicting	O
Blow	O
.	O
My	O
Eyes	O
are	O
weak	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
otherwise	O
most	O
wonderfully	O
well	O
--	O
Adieu	O
God	O
Bless	O
you	O
&	O
yrs	O
PC	B-pers
next	O
Monday	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
I	O
'll	O
write	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Oct	O
br	O
-	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
