TOKEN	NE
No	O
.	O
13	O
--	O
True	O
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Bloſsett	I-pers
Saturday	O
Night	O
This	O
being	O
sufficient	O
employment	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
shall	O
be	O
deferred	O
till	O
another	O
Opportunity	O
The	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
my	O
grattitude	O
the	O
Sigil	O
of	O
the	O
Elegant	O
Epistle	O
further	O
I	O
've	O
not	O
it	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
it	O
I	O
write	O
so	O
ting	O
well	O
For	O
the	O
last	O
four	O
Nights	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
has	O
read	O
aloud	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Voice	O
that	O
you	O
probably	O
heard	O
at	O
Birch	B-place
,	O
tho	O
'	O
extremely	O
well	O
--	O
but	O
pronouncing	O
the	O
Letter	O
R.	O
which	O
occur	O
'd	O
pretty	O
frequently	O
in	O
the	O
Eastern	O
Names	O
so	O
emphatically	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
required	O
pretty	O
strong	O
nerves	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
peaceably	O
--	O
The	O
Subject	O
was	O
“	O
Reflections	O
on	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
Indostan	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Short	O
Sketch	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Bengal	O
from	O
1738	O
to	O
1756	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Affairs	O
to	O
1758	O
--	O
by	O
Luke	O
Scrafton	O
Esq	O
r	O
-	O
”	O
--	O
London	O
--	O
printed	O
1763	O
--	O
reprinted	O
by	O
W.	O
Strahan	O
Jnr	O
.	O
--	O
for	O
George	O
Kearsley	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
T.	O
Cadell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
1780	O
.	O
”	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
wishes	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Names	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
Picked	O
out	O
the	O
Title	O
given	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
,	O
as	O
quite	O
sufficient	O
to	O
break	O
as	O
many	O
Teeth	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
to	O
spare	O
“	O
Zubdut	O
Ulmulk	O
Nuſseera	O
Dowla	O
Sahbut	O
Jung	O
Bahader	O
”	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
remonstrated	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
fidgetty	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
lately	O
been	O
unwell	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
manner	O
of	O
taking	O
leave	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
likely	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Nervous	O
--	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
(	O
and	O
pray	O
do	O
me	O
credit	O
for	O
keeping	O
my	O
Countenance	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
earnestly	O
recommended	O
a	O
blister	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
--	O
on	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Head	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
herself	O
had	O
received	O
great	O
benefit	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Friend	O
's	O
Nerves	O
might	O
probably	O
want	O
rousing	O
likwise	O
.	O
--	O
Notwithstanding	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
delightfully	O
pleasant	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mind	O
being	O
so	O
cultivated	O
makes	O
her	O
Conversation	O
at	O
all	O
Times	O
interesting	O
.	O
--	O
Her	O
Spirits	O
are	O
surprizingly	O
good	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
to	O
day	O
to	O
request	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
little	O
pen-wiper	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Inkstand	O
which	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
left	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evening	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
Lover	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
neatest	O
little	O
Articles	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
high	O
feather	O
and	O
his	O
Eyes	O
glitter	O
'd	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
one	O
's	O
heart	O
good	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
look	O
so	O
happy	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
coming	O
again	O
in	O
April	O
or	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
advising	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
hatches	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
significant	O
smile	O
and	O
nod	O
,	O
“	O
O	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
now	O
”	O
--	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
leave	O
Leighton	B-place
next	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
tea	O
here	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
dared	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
fault	O
of	O
his	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
laughing	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
at	O
poor	O
dear	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
pompous	O
&	O
correct	O
pronounciation	O
of	O
hard	O
Eastern	O
Names	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
Such	O
pains	O
to	O
teach	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
poor	O
eyes	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
trace	O
wha-	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Bandinel	B-pers
has	O
kindly	O
written	O
down	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
per	O
above	O
)	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
amazin̄ly	O
good	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
night	O
lighted	O
her	O
wax	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
glaſs	O
Lanthorn	O
--	O
nodded	O
very	O
significantly	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
stole	O
away	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
her	O
usual	O
Kiss	O
,	O
or	O
taking	O
any	O
other	O
particular	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
except	O
looking	O
twice	O
into	O
the	O
Coal-	O
sckuttle	O
,	O
as	O
Bandinel	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
telling	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
secret	O
convention	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
explained	O
it	O
.	O
Though	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
laughed	O
at	O
the	O
writing	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s	O
Note	O
,	O
or	O
looking	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
since	O
James	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
gives	O
pain	O
to	O
my	O
feelings	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
evident	O
either	O
her	O
hand	O
or	O
eyes	O
are	O
failing	O
rapidly	O
--	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
is	O
an	O
exact	O
counterpart	O
of	O
the	O
specimen	O
I	O
got	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
to	O
copy	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
rack	O
my	O
imagination	O
&	O
inventive	O
powers	O
before	O
Monday	O
Morg-	O
when	O
her	O
meſsenger	O
is	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
an	O
answer	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
for	O
an	O
explanation	O
of	O
its	O
contents	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
all	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
morng	O
to	O
Wing	B-place
,	O
about	O
Whitelock	O
,	O
&	O
had	O
fortunately	O
finished	O
it	O
before	O
Mrs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
messenger	O
arrived	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Wing	B-place
.	O
I	O
do	O
strongly	O
opine	O
that	O
that	O
couple	O
are	O
most	O
than	O
dull	O
just	O
now	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
might	O
perceive	O
from	O
her	O
last	O
note	O
--	O
My	O
time	O
is	O
arrived	O
,	O
so	O
good	O
night	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
A'propos	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
joke	O
,	O
(	O
an	O
elegant	O
word	O
,	O
almost	O
as	O
much	O
so	O
as	O
fun	O
&	O
fun̄y	O
)	O
--	O
to	O
make	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bandinel	I-pers
inform	O
Louisa	B-pers
that	O
she	O
blushed	O
at	O
the	O
high	O
colouring	O
of	O
Govenour	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Mesurier	I-pers
s	O
Manne	O
r	O
amiabilities	O
,	O
sense	O
,	O
accomplishments	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
meant	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
poor	O
A.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
gueſsed	O
our	O
good	O
friend	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
Louisa	B-pers
a	O
Million	O
of	O
pardon	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
