TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
glad	O
I	O
have	O
proposed	O
to	O
have	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
's	O
body	O
open	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
mankind	O
whereas	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
most	O
peremptorily	O
forbid	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
apprehensions	O
of	O
the	O
dangerous	O
consequences	O
from	O
the	O
putrid	O
effluvia	O
to	O
the	O
innocent	O
proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
&	O
who	O
have	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
young	O
children	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
read	O
my	O
letter	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
your	O
aſsertion	O
.	O
I	O
therefore	O
repeat	O
my	O
prohibition	O
that	O
no	O
such	O
operation	O
shall	O
take	O
place	O
at	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
50	O
in	O
Mortimer	O
St	O
.	O
It	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
cruel	O
to	O
hazard	O
the	O
safety	O
of	O
Persons	O
to	O
whom	O
my	O
dear	O
daughter	O
has	O
thought	O
herself	O
obliged	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
either	O
not	O
received	O
my	O
letter	O
or	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
.	O
Sure	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
written	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
With	O
your	O
letter	O
of	O
yesterday	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
absurd	O
one	O
of	O
three	O
lines	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
communicating	O
the	O
afflicting	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
now	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
his	O
dear	O
Jane	B-pers
.	O
I	O
feel	O
the	O
greatest	O
poſsible	O
regard	O
&	O
affection	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Halliday	I-pers
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
so	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
this	O
with	O
great	O
perturbation	O
&	O
remain	O
most	O
faithfully	O
Yours	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bath	B-place
June	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
