TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
returning	O
you	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
letter	O
from	O
Taxal	B-place
of	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
only	O
received	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
offer	O
of	O
leaving	O
your	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
upon	O
the	O
security	O
proposed	O
&	O
at	O
5	O
pr.Ct	O
.	O
for	O
leſs	O
interest	O
I	O
never	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
offering	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
your	O
Debtor	O
than	O
almost	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
off	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
which	O
my	O
Agent	O
gave	O
me	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
towards	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
will	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
to	O
my	O
Agent	O
signifying	O
my	O
inclination	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
abhorrence	O
from	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
unhandsome	O
by	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
may	O
be	O
engaged	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
furnish	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
desir	O
'd	O
an	O
immediate	O
answer	O
for	O
your	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
shou	O
'd	O
fortunately	O
turn	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
keep	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
course	O
commenc	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
Manchester	B-place
,	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
shall	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
your	O
name	O
&	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
I	O
will	O
also	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
collateral	O
Bond	O
of	O
Security	O
upon	O
my	O
personal	O
Property	O
.	O
The	O
Interest	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
punctually	O
every	O
six	O
months	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
without	O
the	O
necessity	O
of	O
applying	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
favor	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
repay	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
your	O
Father	O
has	O
acted	O
so	O
generously	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
this	O
certainly	O
implies	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
conscious	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
deserving	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
accept	O
the	O
best	O
Compts	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
be	O
aſsured	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
The	O
Cornet	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
join	O
his	O
Regiment	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
relieve	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
of	O
light	O
Dragoons	O
now	O
in	O
attendance	O
upon	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
May	O
next	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
review	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
labouring	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
drill	O
both	O
on	O
foot	O
&	O
on	O
horseback	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
recruit	O
to	O
the	O
Regiment	O
,	O
his	O
form	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
being	O
upwards	O
of	O
5	O
feet	O
9	O
Inches	O
with	O
the	O
countenance	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
already	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Riding	O
Master	O
expects	O
will	O
turn	O
out	O
well	O
if	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
the	O
sole	O
credit	O
of	O
him	O
will	O
be	O
mine	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obliged	O
Hum	O
ble	O
Serv	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
.	O
249	O
November	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
de	I-place
la	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
