TOKEN	NE
Vitoria	B-place
23	O
d	O
June	O
1813	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
upon	O
Francis	B-pers
f	O
or	O
not	O
writing	O
sooner	O
after	O
promisig	O
do	O
it	O
but	O
although	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
forget	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Nothing	O
perticuler	O
has	O
happened	O
scince	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
myself	O
or	O
my	O
Regt	O
till	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
which	O
day	O
was	O
a	O
dreadfull	O
day	O
for	O
the	O
71	O
st	O
which	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
certainely	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
glorious	O
day	O
for	O
the	O
British	O
nation	O
but	O
purchased	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
dear	O
rate	O
our	O
poor	O
Regt	O
lost	O
388	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
16	O
officers	O
Col	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
sold	O
himself	O
by	O
too	O
much	O
rashneſs	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
commencment	O
of	O
the	O
action	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
the	O
first	O
R	O
B	O
ritish	O
Regiment	O
engaged	O
and	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
they	O
did	O
their	O
duty	O
and	O
showed	O
an	O
example	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
army	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
belong	O
we	O
left	O
48	O
lying	O
on	O
one	O
spot	O
we	O
lost	O
52	O
out	O
of	O
91	O
which	O
we	O
began	O
with	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
left	O
in	O
t	O
his	O
place	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
collecting	O
the	O
wounded	O
and	O
prisoners	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
surprised	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
Egland	B-place
with	O
them	O
This	O
busineſs	O
will	O
most	O
probably	O
finish	O
the	O
Spanish	O
war	O
Joseph	B-pers
has	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
plunder	O
their	O
is	O
a	O
report	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
night	O
the	O
people	O
are	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
look	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
mention	O
of	O
another	O
action	O
which	O
I	O
partly	O
beleave	O
Let	O
me	O
hear	O
sometime	O
from	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
treat	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
a	O
little	O
scandall	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
very	O
much	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
Names	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
And	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
affectionate	O
friend	O
Charles	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
6-2-6	O
4-10	O
--	O
1-2-6	O
10-15	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
71	O
st	O
.	O
Regt-	O
after	O
Vittoria	B-place
John	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
N	O
o	O
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
England	B-place
