TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
ye	O
12	O
th	O
Apl	O
1789	O
Your	O
Letter	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
tra	O
v	O
elled	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
before	O
it	O
reached	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
since	O
I	O
red	O
it	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
very	O
sincerly	O
,	O
&	O
join	O
return	O
m	O
y	O
congratulations	O
to	O
you	O
r	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Bleſsed	O
Event	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
Recovery	O
for	O
a	O
greater	O
Bleſsing	O
can	O
not	O
acc	O
r	O
ue	O
to	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
deeply	O
afflicted	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
body	O
must	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
every	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Domestic	O
Life	O
,	O
must	O
adore	O
him	O
&	O
doubly	O
feel	O
his	O
value	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Satisfact	O
ion	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
His	O
Mesy	O
never	O
looked	O
better	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
thinner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
after	O
such	O
an	O
illneſs	O
is	O
what	O
one	O
ought	O
to	O
expect	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
thank	O
God	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
who	O
supported	O
their	O
very	O
severe	O
Trial	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
proper	O
&	O
exemplary	O
manner	O
--	O
I	O
daresay	O
your	O
little	O
Girl	O
improves	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
She	O
will	O
now	O
grow	O
more	O
&	O
more	O
entertaining	O
,	O
both	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Comps	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
these	O
four	O
Months	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Heart	O
rejoices	O
,	O
my	O
poor	O
Chest	O
is	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
Cough	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
till	O
the	O
warm	O
Weather	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
give	O
him	O
your	O
Compliments	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
&	O
all	O
your	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
desire	O
theirs	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Sincely	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Comps	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
