TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
--	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
idle	O
as	O
to	O
wan	O
need	O
that	O
consideration	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
so	O
sincerely	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
with	O
pleasure	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
of	O
Yours	O
last	O
Sunday	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
more	O
before	O
we	O
leave	O
Mapledurham	B-place
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
my	O
dear	O
Fanny	B-pers
well	O
--	O
&	O
of	O
finding	O
all	O
our	O
friends	O
well	O
so	O
,	O
little	O
George	B-pers
very	O
much	O
improved	O
he	O
looks	O
quite	O
robust	O
&	O
healthy	O
&	O
is	O
fat	O
&	O
lively	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
fellow	O
,	O
much	O
more	O
resembles	O
Pappa	O
than	O
Mamma	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
she	O
promised	O
her	O
maid	O
should	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
given	O
us	O
any	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
will	O
beg	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
infor	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
your	O
Mamma	O
does	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
sees	O
her	O
frequently	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
just	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
we	O
shall	O
find	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
amended	O
;	O
It	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
spirits	O
in	O
James	O
Street	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
St	B-place
:	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
quite	O
au	O
fait	O
en	O
tout	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
breakfast	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
often	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
let	O
me	O
at	O
least	O
begin	O
some	O
happy	O
days	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
What	O
an	O
alteration	O
must	O
a	O
Year	O
probably	O
make	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
our	O
Caterina	B-pers
settled	O
within	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happier	O
than	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
--	O
our	O
way	O
through	O
this	O
life	O
is	O
neceſsarily	O
perplexed	O
&	O
our	O
supports	O
,	O
are	O
weak	O
,	O
&	O
few	O
--	O
the	O
married	O
state	O
,	O
combining	O
the	O
interests	O
&	O
strength	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
gives	O
aſsurance	O
&	O
comfort	O
to	O
both	O
--	O
I	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
that	O
Caterina	B-pers
will	O
still	O
be	O
yours	O
and	O
mine	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
poſsible	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
lose	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
lose	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
will	O
derive	O
new	O
happineſs	O
from	O
hers	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
--	O
or	O
will	O
soon	O
see	O
our	O
dear	O
Leonidas	B-pers
--	O
he	O
loves	O
you	O
--	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
affection	O
you	O
can	O
desire	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
esteem	O
you	O
deserve	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
estimate	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
great	O
share	O
in	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
this	O
You	O
forgot	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
Virgil	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
minded	O
your	O
not	O
remembering	O
it	O
more	O
then	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
the	O
Entertainment	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Adventurer	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
agreeably	O
entertained	O
with	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
read	O
?	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
reading	O
is	O
often	O
of	O
the	O
serious	O
kind	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
happy	O
here	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
or	O
ride	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
take	O
delight	O
in	O
long	O
Walks	O
through	O
Woods	O
--	O
&	O
Vales	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
no	O
Hill	O
too	O
steep	O
to	O
climb	O
which	O
rewards	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
--	O
here	O
are	O
Scenes	O
,	O
worthy	O
any	O
Pencil	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
indeed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
Countries	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
Barnard	B-pers
sends	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
hers	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
her	O
Love	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
j	O
unites	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
always	O
the	O
Same	O
--	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
A	B-pers
C	I-pers
Maple-durham	B-place
Oct	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
--	O
1778	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
