TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
23	O
rd	O
:	O
March	O
1789	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
22	O
nd	O
-	O
Decr	O
.	O
1788	O
,	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
one	O
day	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
since	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
&	O
it	O
has	O
remained	O
unanswered	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
wish	O
of	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
my	O
Irish	O
Business	O
was	O
settled	O
.	O
The	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
last	O
Janry-	O
was	O
appointed	O
for	O
the	O
Hearing	O
of	O
my	O
Cause	O
.	O
The	O
determination	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
reached	O
Me	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
have	O
extracted	O
£200	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
since	O
the	O
commencement	O
of	O
this	O
Year	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
fairly	O
tired	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
reproach	O
myself	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
long	O
negligent	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
inclination	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
good	O
News	O
.	O
The	O
happy	O
change	O
in	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
our	O
Excellent	O
King	B-pers
gives	O
universal	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
During	O
his	O
melancholy	O
illneſs	O
,	O
Party	O
ran	O
very	O
high	O
.	O
The	O
Majority	O
of	O
people	O
were	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
&	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
friends	O
of	O
his	O
Enemies	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
forced	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
profeſsions	O
they	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
relish	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
You	O
in	O
regretting	O
Ld-	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
situation	O
.	O
I	O
beleive	O
him	O
cold	O
and	O
without	O
sincere	O
friendship	O
.	O
When	O
Interest	O
points	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
line	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
pursue	O
,	O
he	O
may	O
fawn	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
difficult	O
to	O
point	O
out	O
one	O
single	O
act	O
of	O
disinterestedneſs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
his	O
political	O
existence	O
.	O
You	O
well	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
obligations	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
likewise	O
recollect	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
supported	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
General	O
Election	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
political	O
wishes	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
private	O
interest	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
written	O
Circular	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	O
Peers	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
notifying	O
my	O
intention	O
of	O
offering	O
myself	O
to	O
their	O
Patronage	O
&	O
Protection	O
,	O
whenever	O
a	O
General	O
Election	O
may	O
take	O
place	O
.	O
Cathcart	B-pers
answered	O
my	O
Letter	O
with	O
more	O
warmth	O
of	O
friendship	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
expected	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
answer	O
,	O
was	O
uncivil	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
impertinent	O
.	O
My	O
family	O
connections	O
in	O
the	O
Peerage	O
were	O
numerous	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
probability	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
power	O
,	O
were	O
likely	O
to	O
retire	O
from	O
their	O
Offices	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
wished	O
to	O
strengthen	O
any	O
claim	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Aſsistance	O
of	O
future	O
Ministers	O
,	O
by	O
placeing	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
oblige	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
attentive	O
Me	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
shall	O
persist	O
in	O
my	O
desire	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
Parliament	O
(	O
now	O
that	O
my	O
friends	O
remain	O
in	O
their	O
Ministerial	O
Capacities	O
)	O
is	O
very	O
doubtfull	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
(	O
like	O
Yourself	O
)	O
saucy	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Domestick	O
Comfort	O
&	O
Quiet	O
,	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
placed	O
in	O
any	O
situation	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
annoy	O
or	O
disturb	O
Me	O
or	O
Mine	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
within	O
these	O
Ten	O
Days	O
walked	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
residence	O
of	O
the	O
Alisons	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
very	O
cold	O
&	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
obey	O
your	O
Commands	O
sooner	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
,	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
delivered	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
who	O
desired	O
Me	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
All	O
was	O
Peace	O
between	O
You	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
you	O
deserved	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
produced	O
a	O
third	O
Daughter	O
.	O
What	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
or	O
what	O
situation	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
learn	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
far	O
from	O
knowing	O
what	O
affluence	O
is	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
very	O
partial	O
to	O
your	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Much	O
vanity	O
,	O
much	O
ostentation	O
&	O
pride	O
,	O
was	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
be	O
hid	O
under	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
being	O
learned	O
&	O
of	O
protecting	O
indigent	O
Merit	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
drawing	O
the	O
Tribe	O
of	O
Blue	O
Stockings	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
honestly	O
confeſs	O
myself	O
unable	O
to	O
quote	O
Horace	O
or	O
to	O
Scratch	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
comfort	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
hollow	O
Tooth	O
has	O
been	O
Extracted	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
been	O
of	O
a	O
perverse	O
disposition	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
your	O
Allum	O
Recipe	O
.	O
Your	O
poor	O
little	O
Godchild	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Death	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
A	O
fever	O
&	O
inflammation	O
in	O
the	O
Glands	O
of	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
had	O
nearly	O
proved	O
fatal	O
.	O
A	O
Dyſsentery	O
has	O
succeeded	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
too	O
far	O
,	O
but	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
restoring	O
her	O
to	O
health	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
an	O
enviable	O
Child	O
&	O
was	O
remarkably	O
forward	O
both	O
in	O
walking	O
&	O
speaking	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
wishes	O
&	O
those	O
of	O
Maria	B-pers
ever	O
attend	O
Your	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
little	O
one	O
.	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
faithfully	O
your	O
Affect	O
.	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
Sisters	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
mine	O
was	O
Married	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxall	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derby	B-place
