TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
lamented	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
send	O
of	O
my	O
Letters	O
to	O
you	O
regularly	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
dearest	O
Wife	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
ye	O
only	O
pleasure	O
I	O
could	O
here	O
enjoy	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
thinking	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
wh	O
.	O
indeed	O
I	O
enjoy	O
every	O
moment	O
--	O
Oh	O
my	O
Mary	B-pers
!	O
I	O
wish	O
yr	O
D——	B-pers
could	O
imitate	O
that	O
excellent	O
Example	O
which	O
you	O
set	O
before	O
him	O
--	O
do	O
n't	O
despair	O
of	O
working	O
a	O
thorough	O
Reformation	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
always	O
pay	O
the	O
utmost	O
deference	O
to	O
your	O
advice	O
--	O
which	O
,	O
without	O
compliment	O
I	O
can	O
truly	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
just	O
and	O
perfectly	O
right	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
dear	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
and	O
no	O
Language	O
can	O
express	O
ho	O
w	O
sinc	O
erely	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
My	O
good	O
adieu	O
my	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
am	O
you	O
r	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
undutiful	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sisters	O
are	O
near	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
where	O
you	O
will	O
reign	O
for	O
ever	O
Sole	O
Empreſs	O
--	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
Adieu	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Cheshire	B-place
To	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
Jno	B-pers
:	I-pers
Goddard	I-pers
Fountain	O
Market	O
Street	O
Lan	O
e	O
Manchester	B-place
