TOKEN	NE
Wolverton	B-place
January	O
3	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
accommodating	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
Thursday	O
I	O
have	O
secured	O
myself	O
a	O
bed	O
at	O
a	O
Certain	O
Magpie	O
Inn	O
Woburn	B-place
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
snug	O
little	O
place	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
dine	O
&	O
dreſs	O
there	O
&	O
get	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
from	O
the	O
Newport	B-place
side	O
to	O
pick	O
me	O
up	O
&	O
drop	O
me	O
enpaſsant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
equally	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
offer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
indeed	O
fully	O
promised	O
myself	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
Leighton	O
House	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
cruelly	O
deranged	O
by	O
being	O
drawn	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
from	O
home	O
&	O
however	O
gratified	O
by	O
doing	O
what	O
is	O
required	O
of	O
me	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
sad	O
reluctance	O
I	O
quit	O
this	O
house	O
on	O
monday	O
next	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
say	O
Mrs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Child	O
are	O
both	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
Except	O
most	O
heartily	O
wishing	O
you	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
many	O
happy	O
new	O
years	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
we	O
meet	O
but	O
Ever	O
your	O
most	O
Affect	O
Cousin	O
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
In	O
truth	O
this	O
was	O
written	O
last	O
night	O
late	O
,	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
makes	O
me	O
fear	O
Thursday	O
will	O
fall	O
short	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzard	I-place
