TOKEN	NE
Stanley	O
House	O
1	O
Oct	O
..	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
thanking	O
my	O
Dear	O
Hble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
for	O
her	O
obliging	O
and	O
entertaining	O
letter	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
so	O
quick	O
but	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
Honble	B-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
's	O
being	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
frank	O
it	O
,	O
tempted	O
me	O
to	O
intrude	O
so	O
soon	O
on	O
your	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
pleased	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
London	B-place
and	O
likly	O
to	O
continue	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
flatter	O
ourselves	O
with	O
hopes	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
on	O
our	O
arrival	O
,	O
the	O
distance	O
being	O
so	O
easy	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
we	O
propose	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
Novr	O
.	O
therefore	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
110	O
Park	O
Street	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
disposed	O
,	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
good	O
example	O
in	O
answering	O
me	O
directly	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
Stanley	O
House	O
,	O
near	O
Perth	B-place
--	O
without	O
enclosing	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Gen	O
:	O
is	O
going	O
South	O
:	O
therefore	O
,	O
any	O
under	O
his	O
cover	O
,	O
would	O
travell	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
your	O
Anecdotes	O
entertained	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
did	O
not	O
surprise	O
;	O
as	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
loseing	O
her	O
memory	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
and	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
odd	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
degree	O
so	O
no	O
wonder	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
Saxons	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
for	O
that	O
of	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
it	O
from	O
those	O
personaly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Tweedale	I-pers
had	O
been	O
a	O
footman	O
very	O
low	O
and	O
illiterate	O
.	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
fortune	O
in	O
the	O
S	O
.	O
Sea	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
fortune	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
that	O
Exellent	O
Woman	O
Sir	B-pers
Mathew	I-pers
Decker	I-pers
that	O
we	O
all	O
remember	O
but	O
that	O
,	O
niether	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
better	O
scholar	O
,	O
nor	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
..	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
and	O
the	O
celebrated	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Germaine	I-pers
,	O
then	O
Rector	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
aſsist	O
him	O
.	O
but	O
on	O
coming	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
totaly	O
ignorant	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
and	O
believing	O
in	O
nothing	O
.	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
atempt	O
teaching	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
,	O
therefore	O
asked	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
which	O
being	O
accepted	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
our	O
Savr	O
.	O
Sermon	O
on	O
the	O
mount	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
and	O
sd	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
exellent	O
book	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
wrote	O
it	O
?	O
Sr	O
.	O
Mathew	O
replied	O
Doctor	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
never	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Saint	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
replied	O
indeed	O
!	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
answer	O
surprised	O
the	O
Doctor	O
but	O
nothing	O
more	O
paſst	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
occurr	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
confused	O
the	O
Saint	O
and	O
the	O
Sir	O
.	O
but	O
on	O
every	O
body	O
's	O
surprise	O
at	O
the	O
clause	O
,	O
then	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
Dtr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
recollected	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
circumstance	O
that	O
most	O
likly	O
ocasioned	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
apologise	O
for	O
having	O
begun	O
this	O
letter	O
on	O
a	O
half	O
sheet	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	B-pers
Mathew	I-pers
,	O
in	O
writting	O
yesterday	O
,	O
had	O
tore	O
it	O
off	O
so	O
neatly	O
,	O
that	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
turn	O
over	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
out	O
part	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
--	O
The	O
influenca	O
has	O
been	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
country	O
even	O
the	O
Highlands	O
have	O
not	O
escaped	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
familly	O
at	O
Atholl	B-place
House	I-place
have	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
Doctor	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
and	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
--	O
her	O
Grace	O
is	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
soon	O
adding	O
another	O
Bon	O
n	O
y	O
Lad	O
,	O
or	O
Laſs	O
(	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
Scots	O
poets	O
expreſsion	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
she	O
is	O
already	O
bleſt	O
with	O
:	O
but	O
continues	O
as	O
yet	O
in	O
perfect	O
good	O
health	O
--	O
Dutcheſs	B-pers
has	O
paſst	O
the	O
Last	O
holidays	O
at	O
my	O
Brother	O
s	O
with	O
his	O
two	O
School-fellows	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
.	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
Ockham	B-place
and	O
that	O
his	O
has	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
among	O
the	O
Highlands	O
it	O
must	O
apear	O
like	O
a	O
differrent	O
world	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
you	O
give	O
but	O
a	O
Melancholy	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
R	O
.	O
Familly	O
the	O
poor	O
Princeſses	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
sufferr	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
is	O
got	O
well	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
apear	O
Lord	B-pers
Tullibardine	I-pers
is	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
pleasing	O
every	O
body	O
is	O
interested	O
in	O
her	O
health	O
,	O
which	O
seems	O
but	O
very	O
bad	O
--	O
.	O
Ps	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
does	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
please	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
expected	O
,	O
having	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Follies	O
of	O
Youth	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
foriegn	O
Hauteur	O
to	O
paſs	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
and	O
serves	O
to	O
sett	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
s	O
to	O
more	O
advantage	O
who	O
is	O
more	O
Easy	O
--	O
his	O
late	O
purchase	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
prince	O
there	O
is	O
just	O
Elbow	O
room	O
sufficient	O
for	O
amusement	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
com̄and	O
to	O
give	O
jealousy	O
or	O
distance	O
from	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
tales	O
and	O
reports	O
prevail	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
contradicted	O
--	O
pray	O
do	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Ps	B-pers
.	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
a	O
storry	O
has	O
prevailed	O
that	O
he	O
stript	O
the	O
D	O
.	O
Palace	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
valuables	O
converted	O
it	O
into	O
money	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
sett	O
off	O
for	O
Italy	O
with	O
a	O
Venus	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
for	O
your	O
recom̄endation	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
try	O
and	O
get	O
from	O
Perth	B-place
but	O
fear	O
of	O
succeſs	O
as	O
their	O
librarys	O
are	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
we	O
generaly	O
find	O
it	O
easier	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
things	O
from	O
London	B-place
than	O
Edinburgh	B-place
--	O
the	O
adition	O
to	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
letters	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
acquisition	O
if	O
they	O
can	O
be	O
fairly	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
stile	O
will	O
soon	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
genuine	O
or	O
not	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
act	O
.	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Memoires	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
P.E	B-pers
.	I-pers
if	O
fairly	O
well	O
told	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
not	O
only	O
amusing	O
but	O
interesting	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
busy	O
life	O
among	O
all	O
ranks	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
thought	O
her	O
Estate	O
in	O
Ruſsia	B-place
tho	O
'	O
a	O
tract	O
almost	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
England	B-place
will	O
sell	O
for	O
sufficient	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
legacies	O
she	O
has	O
bequeathed	O
--	O
her	O
death	O
was	O
ocasioned	O
by	O
the	O
paſsion	O
she	O
put	O
herself	O
into	O
on	O
being	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
law	O
suits	O
was	O
likly	O
to	O
be	O
decided	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
agitation	O
broke	O
a	O
blood	O
Veſsell	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
next	O
day	O
--	O
her	O
house	O
near	O
Calais	B-place
she	O
has	O
left	O
in	O
its	O
present	O
state	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
com̄andant	O
in	O
being	O
--	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Sevignée	I-pers
's	O
choice	O
seems	O
to	O
promise	O
happineſs	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
familly	O
has	O
been	O
always	O
marked	O
as	O
amiable	O
well	O
behaved	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
Educated	O
--	O
without	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
behaviour	O
and	O
Character	O
is	O
always	O
precarious	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
read	O
The	O
Sisters	O
wrote	O
by	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Kingston	I-pers
(	O
Lord	B-pers
Carmarthen	I-pers
s	O
daughter	O
.	O
)	O
where	O
that	O
lecon	O
is	O
strongly	O
incuculated	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
wrote	O
in	O
a	O
pleasant	O
stile	O
,	O
and	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
usual	O
style	O
of	O
Novels	O
--	O
my	O
paper	O
is	O
near	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
before	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
we	O
have	O
taken	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
neice	O
during	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Lisbon	B-place
on	O
the	O
hope	O
of	O
recovering	O
his	O
Eldest	O
daughter	O
a	O
beautifull	O
Girl	O
of	O
18.	O
he	O
has	O
burried	O
his	O
wife	O
(	O
the	O
Captain	O
s	O
Sister	O
)	O
and	O
nine	O
children	O
of	O
consumption	O
and	O
having	O
only	O
two	O
left	O
has	O
separated	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
youngest	O
catching	O
the	O
cough	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
finish	O
her	O
masters	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
returned	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hervey	I-pers
much	O
improved	O
my	O
good	O
Husband	O
&	O
Sister	O
joyn	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Yr	O
Self	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
not	O
forgetting	O
the	O
fair	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farquharson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
yrs	O
.	O
affectly	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
