TOKEN	NE
Horton	B-place
July	O
5	O
th	O
1787	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
Where	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
que	O
faites	O
vous	O
?	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
never	O
write	O
--	O
you	O
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
,	O
weeks	O
,	O
nay	O
I	O
believe	O
Month	O
's	O
ago	O
which	O
I	O
answered	O
immediatly	O
,	O
promising	O
me	O
a	O
longer	O
letter	O
soon	O
--	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
distreſs	O
,	O
in	O
anxiety	O
about	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
Father	O
who	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
fall	O
--	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
quite	O
recovered	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
have	O
forgot	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
source	O
of	O
your	O
misery	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
all	O
happy	O
all	O
well	O
!	O
I	O
like	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
please	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
but	O
why	O
will	O
you	O
not	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
account	O
,	O
the	O
confirmation	O
of	O
your	O
happineſs	O
from	O
yourself	O
.	O
pray	O
,	O
pray	O
write	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
surely	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
forgot	O
that	O
your	O
letters	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
somethi	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
depuis	O
deux	O
jours	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
fortnight	O
here	O
immediatly	O
after	O
the	O
Birthday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
Bell	B-pers
down	O
;	O
whom	O
my	O
Father	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
leave	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
begin	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
May	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
fix	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
London	B-place
for	O
a	O
Drawingroom	O
&	O
staid	O
almost	O
a	O
fortnig	O
ht	O
&	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
--	O
Summer	O
it	O
is	O
thank	O
God	O
at	O
last	O
--	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
in	O
June	O
we	O
had	O
fires	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
now	O
indeed	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
heavenly	O
,	O
intensely	O
hot	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
keep	O
ourselves	O
perfectly	O
cool	O
in	O
the	O
Salloon	O
,	O
where	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
our	O
comfortable	O
etabliſsement	O
,	O
&	O
where	O
we	O
loll	O
,	O
&	O
indulge	O
our	O
disposition	O
to	O
idleneſs	O
for	O
hours	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
here	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
,	O
Bell	B-pers
says	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
vastly	O
grown	O
&	O
improve	O
d	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
this	O
Evening	O
to	O
Courteenhall	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
visit	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
made	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
comfortable	O
conversa	O
tion	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
London	B-place
we	O
met	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
morning	O
visit	O
is	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
the	O
other	O
morning	O
at	O
Chapel	O
at	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
stayed	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
an	O
opportunity	O
afterwards	O
of	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
&	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
--	O
she	O
looked	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
pitied	O
her	O
from	O
my	O
Soul	O
.	O
tell	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
what	O
are	O
your	O
Plans	O
for	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
far	O
I	O
shall	O
enter	O
into	O
them	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
destination	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
without	O
any	O
interruption	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
then	O
return	O
for	O
two	O
fortnights	O
,	O
one	O
about	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
September	O
&	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
&	O
one	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
&	O
begin	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
November	O
--	O
Now	O
my	O
dear	O
tell	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
for	O
I	O
conclude	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
under	O
some	O
promises	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
and	O
the	B-pers
Cathcarts	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
we	O
have	O
entered	O
into	O
your	O
plans	O
--	O
we	O
depend	O
on	O
seeing	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
shall	O
really	O
be	O
seriously	O
angry	O
with	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
whilst	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
hope	O
for	O
--	O
think	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
that	O
you	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
as	O
often	O
in	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
,	O
&	O
yet	O
that	O
3	O
hours	O
are	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
paſsed	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
thank	O
God	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
recovering	O
my	O
looks	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
delighted	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
dreſsing	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
11	O
&	O
to	O
breathe	O
fresh	O
air	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
happy	O
,	O
in	O
excellen	O
t	O
spiri	O
ts	O
,	O
singing	O
&	O
laughing	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
do	O
y	O
ou	O
know	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
from	O
this	O
descript	O
ion	O
come	O
&	O
see	O
how	O
you	O
like	O
me	O
--	O
come	O
amongst	O
us	O
&	O
make	O
us	O
happy	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
&	O
continue	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
long	O
,	O
long	O
all	O
the	O
Bleſsings	O
you	O
enjoy	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
join	O
&	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Compts	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
adieu	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
your	O
affec	O
CMGunning	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
single	O
Sheet	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
July	O
1787	O
