TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
March	O
29	O
th	O
1781	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
inclosed	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
.	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
had	O
done	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
apartments	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
meeting	O
wth	O
:	O
me	O
left	O
this	O
writing	O
upon	O
my	O
table	O
.	O
“	O
Tell	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
answer	O
her	O
letter	O
,	O
she	O
makes	O
me	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
a	O
com̄andment	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
envy	O
her	O
writing	O
so	O
well	O
”	O
Extract	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
)	O
from	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
Sea	O
Houses	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
Suſsex	I-place
July	O
1780	O
