TOKEN	NE
Chelsea	B-place
Farm	O
May	O
11	O
th	O
:	O
My	O
Dearst	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
kind	O
Letter	O
I	O
recd	O
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
&	O
as	O
no	O
Post	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
ansr	O
:	O
it	O
till	O
to	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
alarmed	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
told	O
Ly.-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
of	O
yr	O
:	O
kind	O
anxiety	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
her	O
Letter	O
must	O
have	O
miscarried	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
wrote	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
one	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
write	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Comfort	O
however	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
very	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
looked	O
remarkably	O
well	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
Marianne	B-pers
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
both	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Ranelagh	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
set	O
yr	O
:	O
friendly	O
Heart	O
at	O
ease	O
upon	O
their	O
account	O
;	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
also	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
dear	O
Rich	B-pers
during	O
the	O
Easter	O
Holidays	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
having	O
great	O
comfort	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
Your	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Celebration	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
King	B-pers
's	O
Recovery	O
pleased	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
Husband	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
rejoiced	O
at	O
seeing	O
your	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
admiring	O
Grandpapa	O
&	O
Mama	O
dancing	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
you	O
were	O
more	O
chearful	O
tha	O
t	O
n	O
the	O
Pantheon	O
Company	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Opera	O
House	O
Ball	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
one	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
of	O
the	O
Heat	O
&	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
&	O
seem	O
rather	O
more	O
disappointed	O
than	O
pleased	O
.	O
The	O
Poor	O
Cottager	O
's	O
Illumination	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
touching	O
&	O
affecting	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Poor	O
Cobler	O
in	O
London	B-place
who	O
had	O
continued	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
Oiled	O
Paper	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Transparency	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
words	O
only	O
,	O
“	O
Thank	O
God	O
.	O
”	O
Another	O
poor	O
Creature	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
Home	O
or	O
settled	O
Lodging	O
,	O
walked	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
quiet	O
manner	O
with	O
2	O
farthing	O
Candles	O
stuck	O
upon	O
a	O
Board	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
he	O
carried	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
Chairman	O
lighted	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
an	O
Old	O
Sedan	O
Chair	O
,	O
with	O
five	O
Candles	O
stuck	O
in	O
Clay	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
shewing	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
some	O
Verses	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
who	O
aſsisted	O
a	O
Poor	O
Mantua	O
Maker	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Cloathing	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
the	O
School	O
of	O
Industry	O
--	O
Oh	O
!	O
how	O
I	O
do	O
wish	O
you	O
cd	O
:	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
:	O
of	O
March	O
2	O
3	O
8	O
little	O
Girls	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
cloathed	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
besides	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
Apparel	O
as	O
Gown	O
,	O
Shift	O
&	O
c	O
each	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Black	O
Bonnet	O
,	O
white	O
Tippet	O
&	O
white	O
Thread	O
Gloves	O
&	O
white	O
Bibs	O
&	O
aprons	O
--	O
wh	O
:	O
made	O
them	O
look	O
very	O
neat	O
indeed	O
--	O
They	O
walked	O
2	O
&	O
2	O
--	O
from	O
near	O
Ranelagh	B-place
where	O
They	O
dined	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Room	O
--	O
followed	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Schools	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
other	O
Ch	O
Sc	O
hool	O
in	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
378	O
Children	O
--	O
&	O
they	O
were	O
placed	O
in	O
Rows	O
upon	O
the	O
Lawn	O
to	O
sing	O
“	O
God	O
save	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
”	O
to	O
a	O
Band	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Music	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
Chapel	O
with	O
them	O
first	O
where	O
they	O
Sung	O
a	O
Hymn	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
Occasio	O
n	O
&	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
littl	O
e	O
Children	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Old	O
Soldiers	O
o	O
n	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
quite	O
affecting	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
thankful	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Pew	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
:	O
shed	O
my	O
Tears	O
,	O
unperceived	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
who	O
was	O
moved	O
almost	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Wedy-	O
By	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
wh	O
:	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
recd	O
:	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
but	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
exerted	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
much	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
paſsed	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
the	O
crowded	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
the	O
Honr	O
:	O
&	O
infinite	O
pleasure	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Entertainment	O
wh	O
:	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
King	B-pers
gave	O
after	O
his	O
Illness	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
Bed	O
till	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
Ill	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
since	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
next	O
Monday	O
sennight	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
thank	O
God	O
pure	O
well	O
--	O
he	O
begs	O
his	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Joins	O
me	O
in	O
kindest	O
Comps	O
:	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
we	O
hope	O
is	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
--	O
&	O
yr	O
:	O
dr	O
:	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
tomorrow	O
&	O
will	O
give	O
yr	O
:	O
Meſsage	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
cd	O
:	O
do	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
--	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
's	O
Brother	O
had	O
every	O
Thing	O
given	O
up	O
to	O
Him	O
--	O
before	O
I	O
Rec	O
'd	O
yr	O
:	O
Letter	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
She	O
had	O
(	O
poor	O
dr	O
:	O
Woman	O
)	O
another	O
Brother	O
&	O
a	O
Sister	O
an	O
equal	O
Division	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
--	O
I	O
wd	O
:	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
without	O
offering	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
wd	O
:	O
have	O
allowed	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
all	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
you	O
wd	O
:	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
otherwise	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
yr	O
:	O
kind	O
Intention	O
.	O
My	O
Paper	O
obliges	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
Adieu	O
&	O
Believe	O
me	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
Yrs	O
:	O
very	O
Affectly	O
PC	B-pers
I	O
detained	O
this	O
Letter	O
for	O
a	O
Frank	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
it	O
away	O
without	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
me	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Book	O
you	O
mention	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
