TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
St-	O
My	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
last	O
stolen	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
the	O
Regulator	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
several	O
often	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
taken	O
up	O
of	O
late	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
made	O
it	O
utterly	O
impoſsible	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
now	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stedfast	O
Resolution	O
to	O
scl	O
scold	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
bluster	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
attempt	O
is	O
vain	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
find	O
my	O
Heart	O
open	O
only	O
to	O
softer	O
emotions	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
as	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
from	O
us	O
3	O
Weeks.	O
!	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
but	O
know	O
the	O
mortification	O
I	O
receive	O
by	O
your	O
absence	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
pity	O
me	O
;	O
perhaps	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
curb	O
that	O
presumptuous	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
suffer	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
hurried	O
away	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
experienced	O
more	O
pleasure	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
London	B-place
till	O
Christmas	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
was	O
that	O
all	O
overset	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
few	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
I	O
learned	O
by	O
a	O
Letter	O
you	O
wrote	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
remain	O
at	O
town	B-place
.	O
I	O
wish	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	O
would	O
content	O
herself	O
with	O
her	O
shells	O
and	O
foſsils	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
monopolize	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
blameing	O
in	O
her	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
do	O
myself	O
had	O
I	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Love	O
,	O
pity	O
,	O
or	O
compaſsion	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
pray	O
return	O
soon	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
leave	O
pleasanter	O
scenes	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
at	O
least	O
this	O
Consolation	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
bring	O
happineſs	O
to	O
many	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
can	O
answer	O
for	O
one	O
.	O
But	O
since	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
take	O
some	O
little	O
interest	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pro	O
proceed	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Proceedings	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
my	O
time	O
very	O
agreeably	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
happily	O
was	O
I	O
but	O
bleſsed	O
with	O
your	O
company	O
.	O
My	O
me	O
mornings	O
are	O
spent	O
as	O
usual	O
in	O
Study	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Mare	O
in	O
Bulstrode	B-place
I	O
employ	O
the	O
time	O
from	O
about	O
2	O
o	O
clock	O
till	O
3½	O
in	O
riding	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
generally	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
as	O
constant	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Spent	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
Evenings	O
after	O
Tea	O
from	O
Home	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
short	O
stretch	O
of	O
my	O
day	O
,	O
every	O
Hour	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
considered	O
as	O
lost	O
time	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
am	O
deprived	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
her	O
whose	O
society	O
I	O
count	O
above	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
once	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
bring	O
myself	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
intended	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
near	O
your	O
House	O
till	O
you	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
C——	I-pers
and	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
very	O
comfortable	O
Apartments	O
in	O
our	O
new	O
Mansion	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
Floor	O
for	O
our	O
Studies	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Bed	O
chambers	O
above	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
we	O
have	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
your	O
Welfare	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Evening	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
who	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
W	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
other	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Town	B-place
tho	O
I	O
recollect	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
paſsed	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
would	O
certainly	O
have	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
requested	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
he	O
you	O
away	O
from	O
City	B-place
.	O
My	O
Pen	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
perfect	O
stranger	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
nobody	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
sincere	O
a	O
Love	O
and	O
Respect	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
for	O
ever	O
shew	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Actions	O
.	O
Time	O
will	O
not	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
reluctantly	O
conclude	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
most	O
amiable	O
of	O
Women	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
most	O
sincere	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Friend	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
wrote	O
in	O
such	O
haste	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
slip	O
the	O
opportunity	O
tho	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
shall	O
entreat	O
you	O
to	O
answer	O
this	O
in	O
Person	O
;	O
How	O
grieved	O
I	O
was	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
upon	O
you	O
the	O
Morning	O
you	O
went	O
it	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
neglect	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wanted	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
and	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
nothing	O
but	O
Scenes	O
of	O
happineſs	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
destroy	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
envy	O
every	O
Body	O
who	O
I	O
see	O
with	O
those	O
they	O
most	O
Love	O
and	O
think	O
how	O
different	O
is	O
my	O
Lot	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
A——	I-pers
L——	B-pers
D——	I-pers
L——	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
instance	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
attend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
s	O
Philosophical	O
Lectures	O
from	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
receive	O
much	O
pleasure	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
expect	O
an	O
answer	O
from	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
pray	O
send	O
me	O
word	O
thro	O
'	O
some	O
Channel	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
may	O
expect	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
write	O
forever	O
would	O
my	O
time	O
&	O
Paper	O
last	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
excuse	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
for	O
convenience	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
Bulstrode	O
Park	O
Gerards	O
Croſs	O
.	O
Bulstrode	B-place
