TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
July	O
1779	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
deferr	O
'd	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
much	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
intended	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
partly	O
occasioned	O
by	O
our	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
before	O
their	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
;	O
we	O
called	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
heard	O
of	O
their	O
arrival	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
card	O
from	O
them	O
apologizing	O
for	O
their	O
not	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Latour	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
embark	O
for	O
England	B-place
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
that	O
they	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
in	O
Country	O
where	O
we	O
are	O
under	O
the	O
most	O
alarming	O
apprehensions	O
;	O
having	O
more	O
to	O
fear	O
,	O
shou	O
'd	O
an	O
invasion	O
take	O
place	O
from	O
our	O
internal	O
enemies	O
than	O
from	O
our	O
Invaders	O
;	O
the	O
Country	O
which	O
was	O
miserable	O
enough	O
before	O
,	O
is	O
hurt	O
extremely	O
by	O
the	O
expectation	O
of	O
that	O
formidable	O
event	O
.	O
Wherever	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
Son	O
is	O
great	O
attention	O
must	O
neceſsarily	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
that	O
at	O
this	O
perilous	O
crisis	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
time	O
for	O
ceremonials	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
regarded	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
conduct	O
in	O
general	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
Dependants	O
to	O
be	O
superiorly	O
judicious	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
very	O
gracious	O
;	O
had	O
it	O
fortunately	O
been	O
my	O
lot	O
to	O
have	O
remained	O
so	O
long	O
under	O
her	O
observation	O
as	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
foundation	O
of	O
my	O
expectations	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
neglected	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
have	O
cause	O
to	O
lament	O
at	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
50	O
,	O
that	O
royal	O
Promises	O
,	O
so	O
often	O
repeated	O
,	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
effect	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
I	O
bear	O
a	O
Name	O
which	O
serves	O
only	O
to	O
remind	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
singularly	O
unfortunate	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
speak	O
my	O
sentiments	O
to	O
you	O
without	O
reserve	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
therefore	O
make	O
no	O
apology	O
for	O
doing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
be	O
aſsured	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
sincerely	O
interested	O
in	O
your	O
welfare	O
I	O
was	O
formerly	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
Lyte	I-pers
and	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
regard	O
&	O
affection	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
Mr	B-pers
Huband	I-pers
will	O
soon	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
another	O
remittance	O
,	O
if	O
money	O
is	O
as	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
in	O
England	B-place
as	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
surprized	O
at	O
his	O
delay	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
for	O
these	O
ten	O
days	O
past	O
the	O
hottest	O
weather	O
that	O
was	O
ever	O
rememberd	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
beautiful	O
situation	O
in	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
a	O
delightful	O
Bay	O
,	O
the	O
heat	O
is	O
moderated	O
by	O
refreshing	O
breezes	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
lament	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
did	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
Villa	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
struck	O
with	O
its	O
beauty	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
these	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
savage	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
sort	O
of	O
intercourse	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
She	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
him	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
remonstrances	O
;	O
My	O
second	O
Daughter	O
is	O
a	O
charmin	O
g	O
Girl	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
with	O
excellent	O
abilities	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
perfe	O
ctly	O
recover	O
'd	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
fine	O
looking	O
Boy	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	B-pers
,	O
why	O
name	O
him	O
Frederick	O
!	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
belive	O
me	O
ever	O
Your	O
Most	O
faithful	O
and	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
July	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1779	O
Latour	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Prince	O
Ernest	O
's	O
House	O
Kew	B-place
Surry	B-place
