TOKEN	NE
From	O
Miss	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
As	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
express	O
a	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
folio	O
sheet	O
which	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
fill	O
with	O
the	O
few	O
observations	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
in	O
our	O
delighful	O
little	O
tour	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
we	O
left	O
Birch	B-place
was	O
very	O
unfavorable	O
.	O
The	O
rain	O
was	O
almost	O
inceſsant	O
for	O
near	O
two	O
stages	O
,	O
&	O
prevented	O
our	O
seeing	O
some	O
beautiful	O
views	O
with	O
which	O
this	O
mountainous	O
country	O
abounds	O
.	O
we	O
dined	O
at	O
Chorley	B-place
and	O
paſsed	O
thro	O
the	O
charming	O
village	B-place
of	I-place
Walton	I-place
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Preston	B-place
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
Haughton	I-pers
has	O
a	O
good	O
house	O
near	O
Walton	B-place
,	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Fortune	O
reside	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
The	O
church	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fine	O
old	O
building	O
situated	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
hill	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Ribble	O
winds	O
its	O
way	O
in	O
great	O
beauty	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
Preston	B-place
as	O
we	O
only	O
changed	O
horses	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
trade	O
there	O
in	O
that	O
town	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
remarkable	O
for	O
nothing	O
but	O
par	O
party	O
animosities	O
which	O
are	O
sometimes	O
carried	O
to	O
an	O
extravagant	O
height	O
--	O
We	O
slept	O
at	O
Garstange	B-place
&	O
arrived	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
time	O
at	O
Lancaster	B-place
to	O
take	O
a	O
compleat	O
view	O
of	O
that	O
venerable	O
old	O
Town	O
.	O
Unfortunately	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
castle	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
object	O
that	O
attracts	O
the	O
attention	O
of	O
all	O
inquisitive	O
strangers	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Gate	O
of	O
these	O
venerable	O
remains	O
of	O
antiquity	O
we	O
found	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
unfortunate	O
flocked	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
formality	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
being	O
locked	O
the	O
clanking	O
of	O
the	O
chains	O
&	O
the	O
Idea	O
that	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
to	O
suffer	O
entirely	O
overset	O
my	O
weak	O
spirits	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
indeed	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
towers	O
where	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
noble	O
extensive	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
surrounding	O
country	O
but	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
the	O
horrors	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
had	O
so	O
entirely	O
occupied	O
my	O
mind	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
shoud	O
have	O
fainted	O
upon	O
the	O
leads	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
foolish	O
but	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
houses	O
in	O
Lancaster	B-place
are	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
built	O
of	O
a	O
beautiful	O
stone	O
finely	O
variegated	O
but	O
the	O
town	O
is	O
extremely	O
irregular	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
two	O
almshouses	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
founded	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Dennison	I-pers
for	O
Eight	O
Old	O
Maids	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
for	O
12	O
widows	O
&	O
widowers	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
extremely	O
neat	O
&	O
simple	O
&	O
seemd	O
well	O
regulated	O
.	O
The	O
Church	O
appears	O
a	O
fine	O
old	O
building	O
,	O
the	O
Steeple	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
antient	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
delighted	O
with	O
a	O
walk	O
along	O
the	O
sea	O
shore	O
which	O
revived	O
,	O
&	O
did	O
me	O
infinite	O
service	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
left	O
Lancaster	B-place
to	O
croſs	O
over	O
the	O
sands	O
,	O
I	O
exerted	O
all	O
my	O
resolution	O
to	O
brave	O
the	O
danger	O
;	O
I	O
once	O
felt	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
as	O
the	O
carriage	O
before	O
us	O
seem	O
'd	O
raised	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
stream	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
retreat	O
I	O
resignd	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
&	O
Thank	O
God	O
we	O
came	O
over	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
danger	O
or	O
even	O
risk	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Flookburgh	B-place
where	O
we	O
intend	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
yesterday	O
to	O
see	O
Lord	B-pers
George	I-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
's	O
House	O
at	O
Holker	B-place
.	O
The	O
paintings	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
very	O
valuable	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
dont	O
understand	O
them	O
,	O
my	O
mentioning	O
those	O
I	O
liked	O
the	O
best	O
wd	O
be	O
very	O
uninteresting	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
w	O
rode	O
to	O
see	O
Cartmel	O
Church	O
which	O
belonged	O
once	O
to	O
a	O
priory	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
vestages	O
left	O
except	O
an	O
old	O
gate	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
antiquarians	O
are	O
undecided	O
about	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
this	O
place	O
extremely	O
,	O
the	O
natives	O
are	O
open	O
hearted	O
,	O
modest	O
simple	O
&	O
unaſsuming	O
in	O
their	O
manner	O
&	O
they	O
greet	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
cordiality	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
the	O
respect	O
of	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
distinction	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
so	O
well	O
preserved	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
Cotton	O
Manufactory	O
establishd	O
in	O
this	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
advocates	O
for	O
trade	O
are	O
highly	O
pleased	O
with	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
thinking	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
are	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
opinion	O
.	O
They	O
in	O
general	O
observe	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
maintain	O
themselves	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
their	O
gains	O
were	O
trifling	O
in	O
comparison	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
now	O
are	O
,	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
provisi	O
ons	O
were	O
then	O
proportionable	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
children	O
were	O
well	O
educated	O
,	O
their	O
religious	O
princip	O
al	O
le	O
s	O
attended	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
churches	O
frequented	O
.	O
The	O
unhappy	O
reverse	O
of	O
this	O
is	O
now	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
works	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
bringing	O
many	O
strangers	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
whose	O
irregular	O
lives	O
will	O
in	O
time	O
corrupt	O
the	O
virtue	O
&	O
the	O
manners	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
education	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
measure	O
neglected	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
wealth	O
which	O
will	O
naturally	O
accompany	O
an	O
extensive	O
trade	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
introducing	O
vice	O
,	O
immorality	O
,	O
&	O
extravagance	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
these	O
reasons	O
conclusive	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
they	O
have	O
great	O
weight	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
intend	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ulverston	B-place
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
propose	O
seeing	O
the	O
Priory	O
,	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Bryddal	I-pers
.	O
it	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
fine	O
old	O
building	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
repair	O
.	O
Monday	O
is	O
the	O
fixed	O
on	O
to	O
begin	O
our	O
journey	O
to	O
the	B-place
lakes	I-place
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
weather	O
will	O
be	O
favorable	O
as	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
views	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
will	O
be	O
determined	O
by	O
that	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
suppose	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
long	O
absent	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
this	O
letter	O
to	O
Manchester	B-place
.	O
or	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
written	O
still	O
more	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
so	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
in	O
remarkable	O
spirits	O
the	O
waters	O
agree	O
extremely	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
drink	O
a	O
little	O
but	O
I	O
act	O
very	O
cautiously	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
exceed	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
quantity	O
.	O
The	O
marsh	O
which	O
lies	O
very	O
near	O
us	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
some	O
parts	O
as	O
soft	O
&	O
even	O
as	O
a	O
bowling	O
green	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
4	O
miles	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
also	O
tell	O
you	O
Mrs	B-pers
M——	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
car	O
upon	O
the	O
sands	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Friday	O
evening	O
&	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
amused	O
&	O
dilighted	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
an	O
old	O
tower	O
which	O
formally	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Baronet	O
or	O
Knight	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Harrington	B-pers
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
now	O
remaining	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
antient	O
grandeur	O
,	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
pulled	O
down	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
farm	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
intelligence	O
I	O
coud	O
collect	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
coud	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
anything	O
new	O
or	O
interesting	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
looked	O
about	O
for	O
sea	O
weed	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
on	O
these	O
sands	O
;	O
the	O
plants	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
kinds	O
of	O
those	O
about	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
seen	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
timber	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
(	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
in	O
Ld	B-pers
George	I-pers
s	O
Park	O
)	O
is	O
poor	O
&	O
considering	O
owing	O
perhaps	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
breezes	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
fruit	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
fish	O
,	O
particularly	O
Cockles	O
&	O
Salmon	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
perfection	O
I	O
often	O
wish	O
for	O
you	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
things	O
you	O
wd	O
not	O
entirely	O
relish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Birch	B-place
&	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
about	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
as	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
tolerable	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
commended	O
for	O
my	O
improved	O
looks	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Please	O
God	O
I	O
shall	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
enjoy	O
a	O
better	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
or	O
perhaps	O
more	O
properly	O
of	O
mind	O
as	O
the	O
one	O
is	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
entirely	O
regulated	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
affectionately	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
every	O
situation	O
your	O
sister	O
&	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
endearing	O
sense	O
.	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
To	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goulbourne	I-pers
's	O
King	O
Street	O
Manchester	B-place
