TOKEN	NE
Q	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
June	O
1780	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
When	O
a	O
Child	O
is	O
naughty	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
parent	O
corrects	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
the	O
better	O
behaved	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
can	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
?	O
what	O
punishment	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Physician	O
recommends	O
bathing	O
in	O
the	O
Sea	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
complied	O
with	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
impatient	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
point	O
determined	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
I	O
intend	O
practising	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
certain	O
Miſs	O
.	O
M.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
promised	O
Dr-	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
to	O
wash	O
herself	O
quite	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
since	O
her	O
arrival	O
at	O
Eastbourne	B-place
pretends	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
fearfull	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
which	O
begins	O
with	O
a	O
C	O
.	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Shocking	O
Your	O
delicacy	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
more	O
--	O
anxious	O
to	O
avoid	O
as	O
at	O
best	O
my	O
correspondence	O
can	O
be	O
but	O
little	O
entertaining	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
You	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
Friends	O
which	O
are	O
such	O
good	O
scribes	O
and	O
can	O
make	O
their	O
letters	O
so	O
much	O
more	O
interesting	O
.	O
Our	O
head	O
quarters	O
are	O
still	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
very	O
likely	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
will	O
leave	O
it	O
soon	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
not	O
so	O
agreable	O
as	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
yet	O
to	O
a	O
well	O
thinking	O
mind	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
pleasing	O
to	O
fulfill	O
its	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
fulfilling	O
that	O
duty	O
is	O
very	O
often	O
connected	O
with	O
difficulty	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
nevertheless	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
secret	O
inward	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
whic	O
h	O
none	O
but	O
those	O
that	O
act	O
right	O
can	O
enjoy	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
no	O
Earthly	O
power	O
can	O
deprive	O
us	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
we	O
wont	O
any	O
better	O
approbation	O
than	O
Our	O
ow	O
Conscience	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
!	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
sincerest	O
friend	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
endeavour	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
all	O
alive	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
my	O
indolence	O
should	O
make	O
it	O
slumber	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
fears	O
should	O
prevent	O
me	O
ever	O
waking	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
pity	O
them	O
sincerely	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
avoid	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
difficulty	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
is	O
come	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
She	O
intends	O
leading	O
a	O
very	O
retired	O
life	O
and	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
all	O
her	O
Family	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Harper	I-pers
is	O
however	O
by	O
the	O
“	O
directions	O
--	O
or	O
orders	O
”	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
deprive	O
her	O
Mother	O
of	O
this	O
pleasure	O
,	O
which	O
makeſ	O
both	O
parties	O
very	O
unhappy	O
.	O
il	O
y	O
a	O
du	O
pour	O
&	O
du	O
contre	O
dans	O
tout	O
ceci	O
:	O
the	O
duty	O
's	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
to	O
a	O
parent	O
is	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
making	O
oneself	O
a	O
party	O
in	O
the	O
indiscretions	O
of	O
a	O
Mother	O
is	O
another	O
,	O
this	O
last	O
can̄ot	O
happen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
car	O
je	O
ne	O
voit	O
pas	O
que	O
la	O
mauvaise	O
conduite	O
d'une	O
Mere	O
,	O
excuse	O
l'enfant	O
a	O
remplir	O
ses	O
devoirs	O
vis	O
a	O
vis	O
d'Elle	O
.	O
this	O
remains	O
amongst	O
Ourselves	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
must	O
feel	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
wrong	O
in	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
Court	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Your	O
old	O
Friend	O
seems	O
to	O
recover	O
both	O
good	O
looks	O
&	O
strengths	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
she	O
bore	O
the	O
heat	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
even	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
young	O
people	O
present	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
also	O
at	O
court	O
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
looks	O
well	O
&	O
talks	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
of	O
being	O
settled	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
looked	O
beautiful	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
court	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
backwards	O
&	O
forwards	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
the	O
air	O
seems	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Daschkow	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
still	O
intends	O
travelling	O
two	O
years	O
longer	O
in	O
France	B-place
,	O
Italy	B-place
&	O
Germany	B-place
.	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
delicate	O
a	O
Lady	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
mentioning	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Egremont	I-pers
when	O
talking	O
upon	O
about	O
the	O
riots	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
natural	O
brother	O
of	O
hers	O
played	O
acted	O
a	O
very	O
ungentlemanlike	O
part	O
at	O
Monsieur	B-pers
Cordon	I-pers
s.	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
je	O
ne	O
serai	O
pas	O
faché	O
Milady	O
de	O
le	O
voir	O
un	O
peut	O
pendue	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
sisterly	O
&	O
feelingly	O
expreſsed	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
sorry	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
one	O
thouroyghly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
es	O
superior	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
appears	O
to	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
above	O
heumanity	O
&	O
feeling	O
.	O
Pray	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
let	O
not	O
this	O
Paper	O
be	O
read	O
by	O
any	O
Body	O
but	O
Yourself	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
faults	O
both	O
in	O
expreſsions	O
and	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
would	O
correct	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
Miſtreſs	O
of	O
that	O
nor	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
therefore	O
excuse	O
the	O
faults	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
expose	O
my	O
ignorance	O
or	O
rather	O
my	O
--	O
innattention	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
