TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
21	O
March	O
1794	O
Your	O
letter	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
had	O
been	O
long	O
wishd	O
for	O
and	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
,	O
especiely	O
as	O
it	O
raises	O
my	O
hopes	O
that	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
air	O
,	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
Society	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
conquer	O
Your	O
complaints	O
;	O
and	O
enable	O
You	O
to	O
enjoy	O
health	O
and	O
friends	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
sooner	O
have	O
acknowledged	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
had	O
not	O
my	O
mind	O
been	O
too	O
much	O
bustled	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
agreable	O
correspondent	O
;	O
My	O
Husband	O
was	O
kept	O
wind	O
bound	O
,	O
at	O
Spithead	B-place
and	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
ever	O
since	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
obtain	O
leave	O
of	O
absence	O
(	O
being	O
under	O
Sailing	O
Orders	O
)	O
even	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
see	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
any	O
buſsineſs	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
plenty	O
of	O
--	O
the	O
General	O
poor	O
Man	O
growing	O
every	O
day	O
weaker	O
and	O
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
marrying	O
in	O
such	O
haste	O
compleeted	O
the	O
bustle	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
choice	O
that	O
every	O
body	O
aproves	O
:	O
and	O
makes	O
his	O
Sisters	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	O
bears	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Character	O
and	O
is	O
such	O
an	O
intimate	O
friend	O
of	O
theirs	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
only	O
prove	O
happineſs	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
but	O
to	O
all	O
his	O
familly	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
prety	O
Woman	O
and	O
has	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
children	O
is	O
two	O
and	O
thirty	O
so	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
proper	O
age	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
companion	O
to	O
him	O
who	O
is	O
39	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
his	O
daughters	O
perhaps	O
You	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
constent	O
atention	O
she	O
paid	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
during	O
his	O
life	O
has	O
raised	O
her	O
Character	O
very	O
high	O
as	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trust	O
she	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
shine	O
in	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
adition	O
of	O
being	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
a	O
Mother	O
in	O
law	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
to	O
be	O
aprehended	O
is	O
her	O
health	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
delicate	O
construction	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
Lord	B-pers
MacLeod	I-pers
,	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
and	O
Y	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
S	O
.	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
Ladies	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
who	O
performed	O
the	O
ceremony	O
Miſs	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
George	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
Tullibardine	I-pers
James	B-pers
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Bride	O
away	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
the	O
ceremony	O
was	O
perfformed	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
all	O
dispersed	O
and	O
the	O
Bride	O
and	O
Bridegroom	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
to	O
Caen-wood	O
where	O
they	O
remained	O
some	O
days	O
and	O
then	O
sett	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
North	O
.	O
--	O
Colo.	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
talks	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
next	O
week	O
--	O
poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
we	O
have	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
he	O
died	O
retaining	O
his	O
fortitude	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
--	O
indeed	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
shock	O
to	O
my	O
feeling	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
twenty	O
Year	O
and	O
his	O
death	O
has	O
renewed	O
feelings	O
I	O
had	O
endevor	O
'd	O
to	O
compose	O
for	O
the	O
Loſs	O
of	O
another	O
Brother	O
for	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
only	O
quited	O
Mourning	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
the	O
papers	O
amuse	O
themselves	O
with	O
a	O
1000	O
lies	O
about	O
him	O
all	O
without	O
foundation	O
:	O
but	O
not	O
worth	O
refuting	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
know	O
his	O
Value	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
Strangers	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
amusement	O
in	O
reading	O
pros	O
and	O
cons	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
subject	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
under	O
the	O
greatest	O
anxiety	O
,	O
for	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
third	O
Sister	O
to	O
Gen.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
last	O
Year	O
to	O
Jamaica	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Major	O
in	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
unfortunately	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
last	O
Decr	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
a	O
truely	O
disconsolate	O
widow	O
,	O
without	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
there	O
:	O
Lady	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
the	O
Lt	O
.	O
Govr	O
.	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
and	O
have	O
treated	O
her	O
with	O
every	O
atention	O
and	O
kindneſs	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
to	O
bestow	O
,	O
or	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
known	O
Hospitality	O
and	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
their	O
hearts	O
which	O
is	O
too	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
need	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
in	O
praise	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
this	O
poor	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
William	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
return	O
home	O
:	O
and	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
that	O
shocking	O
Wreck	O
on	O
the	O
Sands	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
assured	O
no	O
life	O
is	O
lost	O
.	O
but	O
we	O
are	O
entirely	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
are	O
in	O
daily	O
hopes	O
she	O
will	O
arrive	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
fortunate	O
ships	O
that	O
have	O
escaped	O
the	O
Danger	O
of	O
the	O
Sea	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Enemy	O
but	O
till	O
She	O
does	O
arrive	O
we	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
anxious	O
:	O
God	O
knows	O
what	O
is	O
best	O
for	O
Us	O
Blind	O
Mortals	O
:	O
and	O
We	O
must	O
receive	O
these	O
misfortunes	O
with	O
humility	O
and	O
not	O
repine	O
at	O
the	O
Bleſsings	O
He	O
sees	O
fit	O
to	O
deprive	O
us	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
very	O
thankfull	O
for	O
those	O
He	O
is	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
continue	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
bustle	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
Husband	O
return	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
by	O
the	O
wind	O
I	O
concluded	O
he	O
was	O
sail	O
'd	O
to	O
Torbay	B-place
--	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
expreſs	O
by	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
Glory	O
,	O
and	O
sail	O
very	O
soon	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
destination	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
this	O
instent	O
informed	O
that	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
is	O
safe	O
arriv	O
'd	O
at	O
Portsmouth	B-place
God	O
grant	O
the	O
news	O
may	O
be	O
true	O
!	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
excuse	O
this	O
stupid	O
letter	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
but	O
though	O
my	O
Nerves	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
excercise	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
have	O
excerted	O
them	O
and	O
shall	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Manner	O
that	O
will	O
intitle	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
continuance	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
aprobation	O
and	O
among	O
that	O
number	O
my	O
Dear	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Amelia	I-pers
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
rank	O
You	O
I	O
return	O
the	O
Clever	O
paraphrase	O
enclosed	O
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
You	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
and	O
in	O
return	O
send	O
You	O
a	O
song	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
fashonable	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
very	O
good	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
You	O
will	O
think	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
--	O
pray	O
write	O
soon	O
,	O
very	O
soon	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
about	O
Yourself	O
and	O
La	O
Charmante	O
Lady	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Commodore	O
joyns	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
self	O
in	O
compts	O
and	O
every	O
good	O
wish	O
to	O
You	O
and	O
Yours	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
in	O
all	O
situations	O
My	O
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
Your	O
Affectionate	O
and	O
Sincere	O
Friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
