TOKEN	NE
Wolverton	B-place
Septr	O
18	O
1807	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
It	O
will	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
your	O
kind	O
Invitation	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
waiting	O
on	O
you	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
of	O
next	O
month	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
equally	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
attention	O
in	O
thinking	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
she	O
finds	O
it	O
eſsential	O
situated	O
at	O
no	O
great	O
distance	O
from	O
many	O
Friends	O
to	O
keep	O
invariably	O
the	O
resolution	O
of	O
not	O
sleeping	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
Many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
congratulations	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
never	O
doubted	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Brother	O
would	O
do	O
justice	O
to	O
the	O
confidence	O
reposed	O
in	O
him	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
degree	O
elated	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
terminated	O
the	O
difficult	O
busineſs	O
alotted	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
hand	O
so	O
masterly	O
that	O
History	O
will	O
perpetuate	O
the	O
recollection	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
of	O
course	O
can	O
feel	O
no	O
ailment	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
well	O
lately	O
however	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
our	O
good	O
Friend	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
but	O
I	O
seldom	O
hear	O
from	O
him	O
regularly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
so	O
glad	O
when	O
I	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
one	O
who	O
knows	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
regards	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
remain	O
most	O
Affectly	O
Yrs	O
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
