TOKEN	NE
Clifton	B-place
June	O
5	O
th	O
:	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
hottest	O
,	O
&	O
most	O
dusty	O
of	O
all	O
Journeys	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
arrived	O
,	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
,	O
safe	O
and	O
well	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
beautiful	O
&	O
delicious	O
Spot	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
Garden	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
--	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
more	O
beautiful	O
than	O
ever	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
this	O
Season	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
lodged	O
quite	O
to	O
my	O
hearts	O
'	O
content	O
in	O
a	O
quiet	O
retired	O
Spot	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
House	O
(	O
thanks	O
to	O
my	O
Indulgent	O
&	O
generous	O
Husband	O
,	O
)	O
quite	O
to	O
myself	O
it	O
is	O
shaded	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
by	O
Trees	O
,	O
belonging	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
House	O
built	O
by	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Draper	I-pers
(	O
of	O
these	O
Trees	O
perhaps	O
I	O
shall	O
tell	O
you	O
more	O
presently	O
;	O
)	O
&	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
there	O
are	O
Hay	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
spent	O
some	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Air	O
upon	O
the	B-place
Downs	I-place
;	O
&	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
delightful	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
--	O
who	O
was	O
sadly	O
heated	O
by	O
the	O
Journey	O
(	O
but	O
as	O
patient	O
as	O
a	O
little	O
Gellert	O
.	O
)	O
seems	O
quite	O
refreshed	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
have	O
regained	O
her	O
spirits	O
--	O
patient	O
little	O
Creature	O
!	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Blisters	O
with	O
the	O
violent	O
heat	O
upon	O
her	O
Lip	O
;	O
&	O
she	O
never	O
once	O
made	O
a	O
Complaint	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
Coach	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
She	O
looked	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
cheeks	O
quite	O
scarlet	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
laid	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
describing	O
her	O
moving	O
Face	O
,	O
&	O
pathetic	O
tones	O
of	O
Voice	O
--	O
pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
for	O
this	O
Anecdote	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
asking	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
cough	O
is	O
better	O
today	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
cough	O
at	O
times	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
this	O
fine	O
air	O
,	O
&	O
quiet	O
will	O
soon	O
set	O
me	O
quite	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
here	O
,	O
to	O
hinder	O
my	O
perfect	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
Friend	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
worth	O
all	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
I	O
sd	O
:	O
be	O
likely	O
to	O
have	O
here	O
)	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Sister	O
of	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Husband	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
here	O
for	O
her	O
health	O
;	O
but	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
her	O
well	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
great	O
strength	O
of	O
mind	O
;	O
an	O
uncommonly	O
good	O
Understanding	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
affectionate	O
warm	O
heart	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
half	O
the	O
profeſsions	O
,	O
that	O
people	O
who	O
feel	O
little	O
often	O
do	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
gentle	O
,	O
manners	O
;	O
or	O
tender	O
feelings	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
;	O
but	O
is	O
as	O
nobly	O
generous	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
warmly	O
liberal	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
smiling	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
an	O
Eloge	O
I	O
have	O
wri	O
tten	O
upon	O
my	O
Husband	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
;	O
&	O
write	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
morng	O
:	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
prevented	O
taking	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
right	O
,	O
to	O
hold	O
down	O
the	O
head	O
long	O
after	O
drinking	O
them	O
--	O
so	O
you	O
must	O
only	O
expect	O
Scraps	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
heart	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
(	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
says	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J.	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
talks	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
sweet	O
Trees	O
I	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thickly	O
planted	O
round	O
a	O
Monument	O
,	O
raised	O
by	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Draper	I-pers
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
who	O
fell	O
in	O
Asia	B-place
1760	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
a	O
Porch	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
fashioned	O
seat	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
I	O
indulge	O
myself	O
every	O
Evening	O
sitting	O
,	O
&	O
overlooking	O
this	O
beautiful	O
&	O
melancholy	O
spot	O
,	O
&	O
thinking	O
of	O
my	O
sweet	O
dr	O
:	O
dr	O
:	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
I	O
paſs	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
as	O
quickly	O
over	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
the	O
sad	O
hours	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
declining	O
day	O
after	O
Day	O
--	O
&	O
endeavour	O
to	O
raise	O
my	O
mind	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
trust	O
he	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
an	O
Angel	O
--	O
a	O
bleſsed	O
Spirit	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
Sin	O
&	O
Sorrow	O
;	O
&	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
much	O
good	O
this	O
seems	O
to	O
do	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
it	O
will	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
If	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ly.-	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
last	O
account	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
--	O
I	O
sen	O
d	O
t	O
you	O
a	O
verbal	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
really	O
had	O
no	O
t	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
does	O
not	O
suffer	O
by	O
the	O
hot	O
weather	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Princeſses	I-pers
are	O
well	O
--	O
If	O
they	O
ever	O
mention	O
me	O
,	O
pray	O
present	O
my	O
duty	O
.	O
&	O
tell	O
them	O
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
their	O
gracious	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
D	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
expect	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
immediately	O
--	O
Yrs	O
:	O
sincerely	O
PD	B-pers
--	O
June	O
6	O
th	O
:	O
I	O
hear	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hattons	I-pers
a	O
tolerable	O
acct	O
:	O
their	O
me	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Letters	O
--	O
June	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
1781	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Clifton	B-place
near	O
Bristol	B-place
I	O
heard	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
from	O
Holyhead	B-place
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
he	O
ar	O
from	O
Dublin	B-place
soon	O
--	O
