TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
December	O
21	O
st	O
:	O
1787	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
/	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
your	O
Letter	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
give	O
a	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
Acount	O
of	O
yourself	O
,	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
little	O
Daughter	O
;	O
and	O
mention	O
a	O
Design	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
prevented	O
from	O
putting	O
into	O
Execution	O
:	O
I	O
mean	O
that	O
of	O
visiting	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
introduc	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
pretty	O
Cousin	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Bye	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
like	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Doubt	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
though	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
spoil	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
great	O
Merit	O
,	O
for	O
Children	O
at	O
her	O
age	O
,	O
are	O
so	O
engaging	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
refuse	O
them	O
their	O
own	O
Way	O
in	O
almost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
make	O
a	O
pretty	O
Governeſs	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
say	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
plac	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
he	O
will	O
remain	O
Abroad	O
,	O
is	O
uncertain	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
him./	O
My	O
Sister	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
Nancy	B-place
:	O
she	O
rather	O
chose	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Winter	O
there	O
than	O
at	O
Geneva	B-place
.	O
She	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
Friends	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
Abroad	O
upon	O
a	O
similar	O
Plan	O
to	O
her	O
's	O
--	O
Œconomy	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
letter	O
we	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
were	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lik	O
'd	O
her	O
Situation./	O
We	O
are	O
in	O
great	O
Confusion	O
,	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
remove	O
into	O
our	O
new	O
House	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
ready	O
for	O
our	O
Reception	O
,	O
at	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
Builders	O
hardly	O
ever	O
are	O
punctual./	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
your	O
Engravings	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
make	O
too	O
large	O
a	O
Packet	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Frank	O
:	O
besides	O
,	O
folding	O
them	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
injure	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
though	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
one	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
Woman	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
spend	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Daniell	I-pers
,	O
next	O
Summer	O
:	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Visit	O
,	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Daniell	I-pers
is	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
Woman./	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
rather	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
)	O
learning	O
a	O
Part	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
's	O
Theatre	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Isabella	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Comedy	O
of	O
the	O
Wonder	O
:	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
busy	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
Part	O
pretty	O
perfectly	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
rehears	O
'd	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
to	O
acquit	O
myself	O
well	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
receiv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
handsomest	O
Manner	O
poſsible	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Parties	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Play	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
perform	O
'd	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Duke	O
means	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
Theatre	O
,	O
which	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
finish	O
'd	O
sooner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
this	O
Season	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
indispos	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
Music	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
;	O
and	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
hear	O
me	O
sing	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Music	O
Parties	O
yet	O
,	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
such	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
Busineſs	O
,	O
relating	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
House./	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
happy	O
.	O
This	O
Letter	O
will	O
reach	O
you	O
in	O
proper	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Direction	O
on	O
the	O
Frank	O
is	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
stupid	O
as	O
to	O
mistake	O
your	O
Direction	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
wrote	O
last./	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
--	O
Give	O
my	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
's	O
affectionately	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
1787	O
