TOKEN	NE
both	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
Edinburgh	B-place
March	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
1774	O
The	O
morning	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
favored	O
with	O
My	O
Dear	O
Ward	O
s	O
letter	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
who	O
I	O
scolded	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
buſy	O
in	O
election	O
matters	O
&	O
indeed	O
so	O
has	O
all	O
the	O
men	O
of	O
buſineſs	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
that	O
we	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
buſineſs	O
that	O
way	O
can	O
get	O
not	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
you	O
this	O
week	O
&	O
satisfy	O
all	O
your	O
demands	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
packing	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
Ci	O
t	O
y	O
where	O
reigns	O
nonſenſe	O
noise	O
hurry	O
&	O
impertinance	O
in	O
absolute	O
Authority	O
&	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
controle	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
Money	O
holds	O
out	O
.	O
Apropos	O
to	O
Money	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
flush	O
.	O
Patch	O
Cloe	O
&	O
Fairry	O
,	O
quite	O
a	O
family	O
peice	O
Fanshon	O
should	O
most	O
certainly	O
have	O
been	O
included	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
peice	O
complete	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Birds	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
wh-	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Capital	O
painting	O
just	O
arrived	O
from	O
Rome	B-place
done	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
hand	O
in	O
that	O
best	O
of	O
poſsible	O
City	O
's	O
.	O
So	O
My	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
thought	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
her	O
too	O
,	O
no	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
fear	O
of	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
act	O
up	O
to	O
that	O
good	O
sense	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
Mistriſs	O
off	O
&	O
if	O
that	O
should	O
ever	O
fail	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
more	O
angry	O
with	O
myself	O
than	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
taken	O
in	O
&	O
disappointed	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
So	O
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
disappointed	O
your	O
Mama	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
London	B-place
not	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
picture	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
yea	O
or	O
nay	O
.	O
But	O
be	O
aſsured	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Apology	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
serve	O
either	O
You	O
or	O
Your	O
Mama	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
that	O
your	O
Health	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
long	O
may	O
it	O
continue	O
so	O
is	O
our	O
sincere	O
Wish	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
wishing	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
ſure	O
you	O
would	O
than	O
be	O
in	O
Your	O
element	O
only	O
think	O
of	O
being	O
surrounded	O
with	O
about	O
ten	O
thousand	O
v	O
olumes	O
of	O
Books	O
sorting	O
them	O
&	O
puting	O
them	O
in	O
order	O
with	O
a	O
book	O
binder	O
geting	O
ſome	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
bind	O
thus	O
have	O
I	O
been	O
employed	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
cost	O
me	O
ſome	O
few	O
more	O
before	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
dont	O
your	O
teeth	O
water	O
?	O
as	O
the	O
ſaying	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
setting	O
aside	O
all	O
ye	O
other	O
fine	O
things	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
ſaid	O
on	O
ſuch	O
an	O
opening	O
--	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
to	O
me	O
but	O
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
best	O
&	O
most	O
respectfull	O
manner	O
poſsible	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
divine	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
married	O
yet	O
or	O
when	O
is	O
she	O
to	O
be	O
noosed	O
News	O
My	O
dear	O
Girl	O
I	O
want	O
news	O
from	O
the	O
good	O
town	O
of	O
Northampton	B-place
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
is	O
he	O
still	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
hear	O
not	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
when	O
in	O
town	O
otherwise	O
we	O
should	O
most	O
certainly	O
have	O
employ	O
'd	O
you	O
without	O
apology	O
but	O
we	O
both	O
beg	O
nay	O
command	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
self	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
safe	O
return	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
calm	O
delights	O
of	O
Northampton	B-place
News	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
nay	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
from	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
dont	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
here	O
but	O
in	O
General	O
We	O
have	O
miffs	O
,	O
misfortunes	O
,	O
divorces	O
,	O
Love	O
adventures	O
,	O
marriages	O
,	O
disappointments	O
,	O
Balls	O
,	O
Plays	O
,	O
routs	O
,	O
concerts	O
and	O
Aſsemblys	O
as	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
in	O
this	O
good	O
Island	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Britain	I-place
,	O
&	O
yet	O
stupid	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
ſince	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
excepting	O
a	O
dancing	O
School	O
Ball	O
to	O
see	O
ſome	O
of	O
my	O
Young	O
Folks	O
dance	O
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
so	O
very	O
good	O
a	O
Wife	O
that	O
she	O
stays	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
every	O
night	O
so	O
you	O
ſee	O
our	O
party	O
's	O
are	O
entirely	O
domesstick	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
vanity	O
of	O
vanity	O
's	O
so	O
wishing	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
good	O
Mama	O
all	O
health	O
&	O
Happiness	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
most	O
Affct-	O
&	O
most	O
ſincere	O
friend	O
--	O
N——	B-pers
