TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
long	O
left	O
off	O
that	O
Childish	O
thing	O
called	O
Wonder	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
I	O
own	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
very	O
much	O
this	O
Morning	O
at	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
y̅r	O
Letter	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
is	O
totally	O
incomprehensible	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
conscious	O
“	O
of	O
not	O
having	O
answered	O
your	O
Letters	O
,	O
or	O
ceased	O
to	O
allow	O
you	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
my	O
request	O
,	O
”	O
nor	O
can	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
yourself	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
recollect	O
one	O
Instance	O
that	O
deserves	O
that	O
Imputation	O
since	O
I	O
first	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
yr̅	O
Acquaintance	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
but	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
must	O
have	O
mistaken	O
about	O
the	O
Meſsages	O
wc̅h	O
she	O
troubled	O
you	O
with	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
must	O
for	O
I	O
certainly	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
giving	O
you	O
any	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
wc̅h	O
answered	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
which	O
my	O
Name	O
was	O
not	O
even	O
mentioned	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
red	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
both	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
's	O
direction	O
,	O
&	O
sent	O
her	O
the	O
last	O
Quarter	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
you	O
all	O
Health	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
&	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
faithful	O
H	O
St	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
