TOKEN	NE
Caldas	B-place
.	O
June	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
fell	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
s	O
being	O
unfortunately	O
sail	O
'd	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
but	O
36	O
hours	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
arrived	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
rejoiced	O
&	O
surprised	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
ſee	O
him	O
at	O
Caldes	B-place
(	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
immediately	O
,	O
)	O
our	O
Disappointment	O
&	O
Regret	O
about	O
her	O
absence	O
,	O
counterbalanced	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
it	O
would	O
otherwise	O
have	O
afforded	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Comfort	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
She	O
must	O
remain	O
ignorant	O
of	O
it	O
during	O
her	O
Paſsage	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
which	O
(	O
please	O
God	O
She	O
performs	O
it	O
safely	O
,	O
)	O
she	O
will	O
meet	O
I	O
hope	O
with	O
many	O
Comforts	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
her	O
Thoughts	O
in	O
some	O
Measure	O
from	O
this	O
unlucky	O
Contre	O
temps	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
no	O
Letter	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
could	O
give	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
clearer	O
Account	O
of	O
us	O
by	O
word	O
of	O
Mouth	O
,	O
but	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
afterwards	O
,	O
of	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
tender	O
and	O
kind	O
Anxiety	O
&	O
Expreſ	O
sions	O
about	O
my	O
Distreſses	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
they	O
are	O
greatly	O
relieved	O
,	O
by	O
Seeing	O
my	O
Son	O
restored	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
be	O
perfectly	O
so	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
much	O
still	O
remains	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
wil	O
have	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Waters	O
here	O
are	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
efficacious	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
for	O
Six	O
Days	O
been	O
very	O
regular	O
in	O
drinking	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
requires	O
near	O
as	O
many	O
Weeks	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
trial	O
of	O
their	O
efficacy	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
wait	O
before	O
we	O
can	O
determine	O
on	O
what	O
steps	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
our	O
future	O
Motions	O
.	O
Your	O
first	O
Letter	O
to	O
Falmouth	B-place
was	O
received	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
you	O
mention	O
,	O
(	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
shd	O
have	O
received	O
infinite	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
expected	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
&	O
fear	O
now	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
never	O
reach	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
pray	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
believe	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
pleasure	O
any	O
Letter	O
of	O
yours	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
feel	O
infinitely	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Interesting	O
Scenes	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
engaged	O
,	O
indeed	O
no	O
Circumstance	O
can	O
be	O
trifling	O
that	O
regards	O
those	O
one	O
Loves	O
&	O
Honours	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
those	O
you	O
are	O
surrounded	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
these	O
Sensations	O
in	O
me	O
are	O
increas	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Distance	O
&	O
Absence	O
I	O
never	O
cease	O
to	O
regret	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
expreſs	O
what	O
I	O
felt	O
at	O
reading	O
the	O
Paragraph	O
in	O
your	O
Letter	O
concerning	O
the	O
dear	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
Gracious	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
love	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
shd	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
such	O
Expreſsions	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
will	O
best	O
convey	O
the	O
Gratitude	O
&	O
Affection	O
of	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
united	O
with	O
that	O
Respect	O
I	O
owe	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
settled	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
;	O
how	O
differently	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
are	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
situated	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
last	O
Year	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
roving	O
about	O
on	O
the	B-place
Suſsex	I-place
Downs	I-place
with	O
our	O
little	O
Roy	O
People	O
.	O
nothing	O
is	O
so	O
striking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
our	O
Ignorance	O
of	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
&	O
surely	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
greater	O
Proof	O
that	O
Providence	O
that	O
ordains	O
all	O
things	O
for	O
our	O
happineſs	O
&	O
peace	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
for	O
how	O
would	O
the	O
certainty	O
of	O
any	O
Approaching	O
Evil	O
,	O
darken	O
the	O
brightest	O
Scenes	O
&	O
Extinguish	O
all	O
the	O
powers	O
of	O
Enjoyment	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
now	O
&	O
ever	O
Most	O
Affly	O
.	O
&	O
Faithfully	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
quite	O
close	O
my	O
Letter	O
without	O
adding	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
concerning	O
the	O
Friendly	O
behaviour	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
to	O
my	O
Son	O
on	O
his	O
illneſs	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
us	O
ever	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
infinite	O
Satisfaction	O
I	O
felt	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
s	O
having	O
made	O
her	O
Voyage	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
She	O
is	O
quite	O
charm	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
from	O
the	O
little	O
I	O
could	O
ſee	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
pleasing	O
engaging	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
by	O
this	O
same	O
opportunity	O
--	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
