TOKEN	NE
For	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
High	O
Commiſsioner	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
Aſsembly	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
(	O
Kirk	O
)	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
will	O
carefully	O
preserve	O
the	O
Tenpence	O
Sterling	O
,	O
so	O
punctually	O
returned	O
to	O
His	O
Grace	O
(	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
begs	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
informed	O
how	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
,	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
April	O
1808	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Privilege	O
of	O
enumerating	O
so	O
many	O
more	O
Days	O
than	O
any	O
former	O
Month	O
of	O
April	O
had	O
been	O
allowed	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
Paper	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Tenpence	O
were	O
remitted	O
bearing	O
Date	O
the	O
37	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
1808	O
.	O
The	O
Triumvirate	O
arrived	O
safe	O
in	O
Edinburgh	B-place
yesterday	O
before	O
Dinner	O
,	O
&	O
found	O
all	O
Well	O
.	O
“	O
Love	O
to	O
all	O
“	O
at	O
Buzzard	O
Hall	O
.	O
”	O
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
May	O
1808	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Ed	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
38	O
Notingham	O
Place	O
New	O
Road	O
Marybone	B-place
