TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
7	O
Aug	O
:	O
1794	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
receiving	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
kind	O
letter	O
gave	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
knows	O
too	O
well	O
herself	O
the	O
feelings	O
it	O
ocasions	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
a	O
valued	O
Friend	O
whose	O
silence	O
has	O
given	O
pain	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
for	O
being	O
ocasioned	O
by	O
her	O
ill	O
health	O
:	O
the	O
acount	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
give	O
of	O
it	O
makes	O
us	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
hope	O
there	O
is	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
flatter	O
ourselves	O
that	O
your	O
long	O
and	O
painful	O
complaint	O
is	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
enjoy	O
many	O
years	O
of	O
health	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
comforts	O
you	O
so	O
well	O
deserve	O
--	O
your	O
scheme	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
both	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
health	O
and	O
the	O
fair	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
improvement	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
nothing	O
will	O
interfere	O
with	O
its	O
being	O
executed	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
are	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
at	O
Blair	B-place
but	O
leave	O
it	O
the	O
2	O
4	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
to	O
return	O
South	O
and	O
supose	O
by	O
Oct	O
:	O
will	O
be	O
resettled	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
George	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
but	O
will	O
return	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
I	O
understand	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
does	O
--	O
the	O
acount	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
is	O
the	O
general	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
more	O
uniform	O
and	O
general	O
great	O
Character	O
than	O
she	O
has	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
Elegant	O
preaty	O
Woman	O
but	O
Delicate	O
in	O
health	O
and	O
make	O
,	O
is	O
two	O
and	O
thirty	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
proper	O
age	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
agreable	O
friend	O
and	O
companion	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
f	O
proper	O
age	O
and	O
experience	O
to	O
introduce	O
and	O
Educate	O
his	O
Children	O
--	O
her	O
behaviour	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Mcleod	I-pers
who	O
was	O
old	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
during	O
her	O
widowhood	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
what	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
hope	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
prove	O
a	O
happy	O
choice	O
for	O
themselves	O
and	O
All	O
Concerned	O
:	O
the	O
Duke	O
is	O
deserving	O
of	O
every	O
domestic	O
happineſs	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
man	O
more	O
so	O
his	O
atention	O
to	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
which	O
living	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
good	O
judge	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
his	O
children	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
admired	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
is	O
unhappy	O
with	O
him	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
fault	O
:	O
at	O
his	O
time	O
of	O
life	O
and	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
familly	O
of	O
Children	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
and	O
the	O
properest	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
aſsured	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
his	O
choice	O
without	O
anxiously	O
endevoring	O
to	O
promote	O
his	O
childrens	O
happineſs	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
rewarded	O
as	O
he	O
deserves	O
--	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
delicate	O
constitution	O
alarms	O
her	O
friends	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
attack	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
intelligence	O
as	O
every	O
body	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
difficulty	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
by	O
a	O
Girl	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Porter	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
only	O
knew	O
the	O
familly	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Caen	O
wood	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
plain	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
--	O
the	O
great	O
fortune	O
Lady	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
has	O
disposed	O
of	O
herself	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Sir	B-pers
James	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
(	O
now	O
Pulteney	O
)	O
--	O
if	O
She	O
will	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
power	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
he	O
will	O
do	O
honor	O
to	O
her	O
choice	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
Fortune	O
they	O
poſseſs	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
generous	O
on	O
his	O
small	O
paternal	O
one	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
generous	O
heart	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
several	O
traits	O
another	O
great	O
fortune	O
(	O
in	O
expectation	O
)	O
is	O
agoing	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
herself	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
of	I-pers
Logie	I-pers
Almond	I-pers
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
young	O
man	O
Nephew	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dunmore	I-pers
--	O
if	O
She	O
turns	O
out	O
the	O
fortune	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Match	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
disapointed	O
of	O
it	O
will	O
prove	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
for	O
Both	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Extravagancy	O
and	O
gaity	O
she	O
has	O
is	O
but	O
ill	O
suited	O
to	O
marry	O
and	O
retire	O
into	O
Perthshire	B-place
upon	O
a	O
moderate	O
income	O
.	O
I	O
supose	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
her	O
mother	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Boone	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
first	O
married	O
a	O
great	O
fortune	O
,	O
a	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
s	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
a	O
shewy	O
Young	O
Woman	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
only	O
two	O
daughters	O
one	O
suposed	O
far	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
decline	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
rich	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
tye	O
himself	O
down	O
so	O
time	O
must	O
shew	O
how	O
it	O
will	O
turn	O
out	O
--	O
H	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
separation	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fitzherbert	I-pers
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
wonder	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
wonder	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
place	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
event	O
clearly	O
proves	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
that	O
never	O
allowed	O
the	O
coniction	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
matrimonial	O
one	O
--	O
those	O
that	O
so	O
obseqiously	O
bowed	O
to	O
a	O
Princeſs	O
must	O
feel	O
very	O
small	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
their	O
Affair	O
--	O
luckily	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
scrap	O
e	O
never	O
chuseing	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
such	O
quondam	O
Princeſses	O
nothing	O
is	O
here	O
said	O
about	O
his	O
marrying	O
--	O
an	O
attatchment	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
is	O
much	O
talked	O
of	O
;	O
which	O
from	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
her	O
beauty	O
and	O
adreſs	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
likly	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
!	O
Lord	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
being	O
anxious	O
for	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Windsor	B-place
confirms	O
the	O
report	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
odd	O
thing	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
age	O
should	O
always	O
prove	O
so	O
charming	O
!	O
--	O
politics	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
none	O
;	O
the	O
World	O
seems	O
so	O
involved	O
in	O
trouble	O
and	O
perplexity	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
globe	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
wonderfull	O
and	O
nothing	O
can	O
acount	O
for	O
it	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Decrees	O
of	O
Providence	O
are	O
fullfilling	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
high	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
understand	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
sure	O
comfort	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
su	O
ch	O
times	O
is	O
a	O
firm	O
reliance	O
on	O
His	O
goodneſs	O
who	O
over	O
rul	O
es	O
All	O
things	O
that	O
He	O
will	O
save	O
and	O
protect	O
those	O
who	O
tru	O
st	O
in	O
Him	O
and	O
suddenly	O
turn	O
and	O
grant	O
us	O
peace	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
now	O
Rear	O
Admiral	O
of	O
the	O
Red	O
and	O
has	O
the	O
command	O
at	O
Halifax	B-place
for	O
which	O
station	O
he	O
sailed	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
no	O
acount	O
has	O
come	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
the	O
next	O
packet	O
will	O
bring	O
us	O
good	O
acounts	O
it	O
seems	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
endevor	O
to	O
amuse	O
myself	O
with	O
music	O
drawing	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
thought	O
but	O
spight	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
time	O
apear	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
slow	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
comfort	O
myself	O
that	O
no	O
news	O
is	O
good	O
news	O
as	O
the	O
bad	O
always	O
flies	O
--	O
this	O
year	O
has	O
certainly	O
called	O
forth	O
great	O
excersions	O
of	O
spirits	O
to	O
suport	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
to	O
mourn	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
s	O
brother	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
events	O
that	O
have	O
gradualy	O
followed	O
each	O
other	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
mourner	O
since	O
Novr	O
.	O
till	O
just	O
now	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
sent	O
into	O
this	O
world	O
for	O
our	O
pleasure	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
look	O
round	O
certainly	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
bleſsings	O
to	O
the	O
thankfull	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
ingratitude	O
to	O
repine	O
at	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
lot	O
of	O
Man	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
requires	O
resolution	O
to	O
be	O
thankfull	O
&	O
submit	O
with	O
chearfullneſs	O
--	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
looks	O
very	O
well	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
very	O
thin	O
and	O
so	O
does	O
P.	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
--	O
the	O
others	O
all	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
think	O
the	B-pers
P.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
&	O
D.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Clarence	I-pers
very	O
much	O
alter	O
'd	O
--	O
P.	B-pers
Ernest	I-pers
is	O
very	O
tall	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
face	O
has	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
in	O
a	O
sling	O
--	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
this	O
act	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
drawing	O
room	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
expected	O
duty	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
other	O
public	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
reconcile	O
it	O
a	O
right	O
thing	O
when	O
those	O
we	O
are	O
most	O
nearly	O
concerned	O
for	O
may	O
be	O
God	O
knows	O
in	O
what	O
situation	O
to	O
be	O
flirting	O
about	O
at	O
idle	O
places	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
children	O
to	O
amuse	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
at	O
them	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
in	O
much	O
better	O
looks	O
&	O
health	O
than	O
formly	O
tho	O
'	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
far	O
from	O
good	O
health	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
is	O
much	O
improved	O
--	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
pleasant	O
tour	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
delightfull	O
and	O
the	O
country	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
with	O
in	O
Westmorland	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
propose	O
to	O
turn	O
over	O
a	O
new	O
leaf	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
content	O
to	O
experience	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Oldest	O
Book	O
that	O
I	O
mean	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
write	O
often	O
to	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
affectionate	O
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
My	O
Sister	O
joyns	O
me	O
in	O
love	O
to	O
yrself	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
3-17-0	O
3-15-9	O
½	O
0-	O
1-2	O
½	O
1-0-0	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Liverpool	B-place
a	O
single	O
sheet	O
