TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
It	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
My	O
Power	O
to	O
Attend	O
you	O
to	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
till	O
Thursday	O
;	O
If	O
that	O
Day	O
will	O
be	O
agreable	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
before	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
Hear	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
fixed	O
on	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
three	O
,	O
this	O
Morning	O
;	O
&	O
to	O
Hear	O
the	O
dreaded	O
Interview	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
Both	O
Parties	O
,	O
I	O
Hope	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Behaved	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Most	O
Affecly	O
--	O
Frances	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Monday	O
