TOKEN	NE
Hambledon	B-place
December	O
29	O
th	O
:	O
-14	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
/	O
I	O
feel	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
request	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
your	O
kind	O
Note	O
received	O
Yesterday	O
&	O
beg	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
much	O
pleasure	O
in	O
attending	O
her	O
as	O
Bride	O
's	O
Maid	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
menti	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
nothing	O
will	O
occur	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
doing	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
before	O
that	O
time/	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
depend	O
on	O
my	O
not	O
naming	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
this	O
family	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
beg	O
to	O
unite	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
affect	O
:	O
regards	O
&	O
congratulations	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
our	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
your	O
all	O
enjoying	O
many	O
happy	O
returns	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
season	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
Yr	O
:	O
sincerely	O
obliged	O
&	O
affect	O
:	O
LC.S.Hamilton	B-pers
Turn	O
P	O
:	O
S	O
:	O
As	O
near	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Plowden	I-pers
s	O
,	O
you	O
of	O
course	O
know	O
how	O
greatly	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
poor	O
Jane	B-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
has	O
increased	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
say	O
our	O
latest	O
accounts	O
are	O
rather	O
more	O
favorable	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
dare	O
not	O
hope	O
too	O
confidently	O
!	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
has	O
just	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
giving	O
his	O
love	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
&	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
Cake	O
is	O
proportionate	O
to	O
his	O
regard	O
for	O
your	O
family	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
entitled	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
piece	O
.	O
Pray	O
aſsure	O
my	O
Cousin	O
that	O
I	O
forgive	O
her	O
silence	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
moment	O
,	O
being	O
aware	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
much	O
to	O
employ	O
her	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
No	O
:	O
32	O
.	O
