TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
by	O
the	O
last	O
Post	O
informing	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
loſs	O
you	O
had	O
sustain	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
your	O
Mother	O
.	O
From	O
your	O
dutiful	O
attachment	O
to	O
an	O
affectionate	O
Parent	O
&	O
the	O
great	O
sensibility	O
of	O
your	O
disposition	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
will	O
stand	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
interposition	O
of	O
your	O
Friends	O
to	O
exhort	O
you	O
to	O
moderate	O
your	O
affliction	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
fortunately	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Friends	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
worth	O
&	O
sincerity	O
I	O
mean	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
who	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
will	O
inforce	O
every	O
proper	O
argument	O
of	O
consolation	O
.	O
As	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
observation	O
this	O
melancholy	O
event	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
upon	O
you	O
by	O
surprize	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
prepared	O
to	O
bear	O
the	O
shock	O
.	O
When	O
your	O
mind	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
calm	O
'd	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
every	O
sentiment	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
sincere	O
regard	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
offer	O
her	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Compts	O
.	O
Latour	O
December	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
1778	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
