TOKEN	NE
28	O
August	O
84	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
You	O
were	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
either	O
this	O
Morg	O
or	O
to	O
morrow	O
as	O
soon	O
after	O
twelve	O
as	O
is	O
convenient	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	B-place
a	O
few	O
days	O
but	O
confined	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
&	O
am	O
only	O
now	O
got	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
however	O
still	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
begin	O
my	O
long	O
Journey	O
on	O
Tuesdy	O
Morg	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
Affy	O
Yr-	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Kings	O
Mews	O
Saturdy-	O
Mg	O
