TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
as	O
you	O
desir	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
consents	O
very	O
readily	O
to	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
Town	B-place
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
better	O
.	O
Ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Kew	B-place
Saturday	O
Night	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
