TOKEN	NE
Hampton	O
Court	O
Palace	O
Sepbr-	O
4	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
nature	O
grateful	O
,	O
and	O
flatterd	O
by	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
therefore	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
how	O
obliged	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
the	O
Brace	O
of	O
Partridges	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
sorry	O
my	O
thanks	O
will	O
cost	O
you	O
four	O
Pence	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
here	O
deal	O
in	O
Members	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
offerd	O
you	O
my	O
thanks	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
relate	O
worth	O
one	O
farthing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
Week	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
dutiful	O
Inquires	O
.	O
and	O
call	O
u	O
p	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
Intimates	O
who	O
are	O
there	O
on	O
melancholy	O
Attendance	O
.	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
Miſs	B-pers
Golsworthy	I-pers
,	O
looking	O
uncommonly	O
well	O
.	O
but	O
deafer	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
.	O
she	O
quite	O
shock	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
hear	O
one	O
word	O
in	O
ten	O
,	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Trumpet	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
and	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
have	O
you	O
Danced	O
Louisa	B-pers
into	O
his	O
Grave	O
?	O
or	O
does	O
he	O
Live	O
to	O
be	O
admir	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
your	O
taste	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Saloon	O
for	O
all	O
Frederick	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
's	O
Curiositys	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Neig	O
hbourhood	O
of	O
,	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
Obliged	O
,	O
and	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
HCecilia	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
