TOKEN	NE
in	O
book	O
But	O
to	O
be	O
typed	O
in	O
time	O
Nerots	O
Hotel	O
Kings	O
Street	O
Tuesday	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
178	O
3	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Letter	O
inviting	O
us	O
again	O
to	O
Bullstrode	B-place
because	O
Charles	B-pers
&	O
I	O
fully	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
answerd	O
it	O
in	O
Person	O
at	O
Bullstrode	B-place
.	O
yesterday	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
said	O
he	O
woud	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
paſs	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Week	O
--	O
Saturday	O
we	O
had	O
fixed	O
for	O
paying	O
our	O
respects	O
to	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
absent	O
myself	O
myself	O
from	O
Town	B-place
,	O
as	O
my	O
intelligence	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
good	O
quarter	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
then	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
you	O
can	O
imagine	O
to	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
that	O
is	O
most	O
respectfull	O
and	O
aſsure	O
Her	O
Grace	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
m	O
y	O
u	O
ch	O
disappointed	O
as	O
I	O
realy	O
was	O
made	O
happy	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
paſsed	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
wished	O
much	O
to	O
have	O
repeated	O
the	O
visit	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
comes	O
to	O
Town	B-place
I	O
will	O
wait	O
upon	O
Her	O
&	O
shew	O
Her	O
Her	O
the	O
Vase	O
which	O
from	O
Mr-	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
's	O
report	O
will	O
have	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Her	O
Grace	O
is	O
eager	O
to	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
called	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
most	O
affectionately	O
yrs	O
.	O
WH	B-pers
