TOKEN	NE
Stanhope	O
Street	O
Feby	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
Madam	O
my	O
Lady	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
influenza	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
much	O
better	O
her	O
Eyes	O
oblige	O
her	O
to	O
abstain	O
from	O
writing	O
,	O
She	O
therefore	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
Say	O
that	O
She	O
gave	O
miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
which	O
you	O
Sent	O
her	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
mrs	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
who	O
expects	O
her	O
in	O
town	B-place
this	O
day	O
She	O
much	O
laments	O
that	O
it	O
Came	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
obtain	O
what	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
wished	O
;	O
thank	O
God	O
your	O
beloved	O
Friend	O
died	O
as	O
She	O
lived	O
,	O
in	O
Chearfull	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
her	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Benevolence	O
and	O
Sweet	O
Charity	O
to	O
all	O
human	O
kind	O
.	O
my	O
Lady	O
has	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
Silk	O
which	O
mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Sent	O
here	O
Some	O
time	O
ago	O
and	O
desire	O
d	O
when	O
She	O
Died	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Sent	O
to	O
miſs	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
my	O
Lady	O
therefore	O
begs	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
and	O
where	O
She	O
Shall	O
Send	O
it	O
Her	O
Ladyship	O
is	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
all	O
escaped	O
the	O
Influenza	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
So	O
prevalent	O
in	O
Town	B-place
and	O
begs	O
her	O
best	O
wishes	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
madam	O
your	O
most	O
obedient	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Eliz	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
my	O
Lord	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
thank	O
God	O
