TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
Janry	O
:	O
21	O
st	O
:	O
1771	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
before	O
you	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
worst	O
Correspondent	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
but	O
how	O
is	O
it	O
poſsible	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
wish	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
this	O
little	O
retirement	O
can	O
find	O
nothing	O
,	O
which	O
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
?	O
my	O
whole	O
employment	O
is	O
my	O
Family	O
&	O
Children	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
divert	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
pleasing	O
to	O
a	O
fond	O
Mother	O
,	O
is	O
too	O
insignificant	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
paper	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
nothing	O
triffling	O
,	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
in	O
return	O
procure	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
gueſs	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
bearer	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
complexion	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
great	O
disadvantages	O
by	O
being	O
brought	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
Country	O
School	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
fine	O
Town	O
will	O
polish	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
'	O
l	O
excuse	O
me	O
not	O
saying	O
more	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
woud	O
not	O
let	O
this	O
opportunity	O
slip	O
by	O
without	O
paying	O
my	O
compts-	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Anxiety	O
upon	O
parting	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
Boy	O
.	O
Sally	B-pers
often	O
talks	O
of	O
you	O
with	O
pleasure	O
&	O
gratitude	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Your	O
Affect	O
&	O
oblig	O
'd	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
desires	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
his	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
