TOKEN	NE
From	O
Novr	O
.	O
30	O
:	O
1783	O
to	O
Decr	O
..	O
5	O
.	O
.	O
1783	O
Sunday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
1783	O
Continued	O
she	O
breakfasted	O
,	O
only	O
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
ye	O
Bell	O
for	O
prayers	O
was	O
rung	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
talkd	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
my	O
first	O
acquaintance	O
there	O
Uncle	O
&	O
c.	O
read	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Letter	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mackay	I-pers
ye	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
ask	O
wt	O
.	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
dinner	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
about	O
Lord	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Bentinck	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife/	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
that	O
was	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
is	O
wth	O
.	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
P	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Gallery	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
converse	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apartment	O
went	O
to	O
Chapel	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
preach	O
a	O
good	O
sermon	O
.	O
After	O
C	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
(	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
or	O
have	O
prayers	O
till	O
next	O
Sunday	O
.	O
After	O
C	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
.	O
my	O
Journal	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
3	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
wth	O
.	O
&	O
just	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
original	O
drawings	O
of	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Letitia	I-pers
Busche	I-pers
a	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
an	O
Amiable	O
Woman	O
both	O
these	O
ladies	O
were	O
great	O
friends	O
of	O
&	O
lived	O
much	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
very	O
sensibly	O
&	O
ingenious	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
told	O
in	O
what	O
a	O
pleasant	O
stile	O
she	O
lived	O
--	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
--	O
in	O
her	O
drawing	O
room	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
room	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
fine	O
View	O
from	O
ye	O
Window	O
.	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
were	O
books	O
,	O
Musical	O
instruments	O
,	O
different	O
kinds	O
of	O
Works	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
Round	O
table	O
wch	O
.	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
people	O
might	O
sit	O
round	O
.	O
upon	O
wch	O
.	O
Pen	O
ink	O
.	O
Paper	O
.	O
Materials	O
for	O
Drawing	O
;	O
siſsars	O
for	O
Cutting	O
out	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
looking	O
over	O
this	O
drawing	O
till	O
4	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pretty	O
one	O
.	O
the	O
Servts	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
lay	O
ye	O
.	O
Cloth	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
dine	O
quietly	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
let	O
Blood	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
I	O
quitted	O
her	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
whilst	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
drawing	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
together	O
.	O
&	O
sat	O
talking	O
for	O
near	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
upon	O
different	O
subjects	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
our	O
conversation	O
was	O
chiefly	O
of	O
Spa	B-place
.	O
Convents	O
.	O
religious	O
orders	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
y	O
Dr	O
:	O
Room	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
6	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
there	O
.	O
she	O
aſsured	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
blooded	O
.	O
the	O
afternoon	O
&	O
Eveg	O
.	O
was	O
spent	O
as	O
agreeably	O
as	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
former	O
ones	O
have	O
been	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
finished	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscript	O
Diary	O
--	O
or	O
she	O
Ldy	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
terms	O
it	O
ye	O
.	O
Chronicles	O
--	O
of	O
that	O
Lady	O
.	O
many	O
curious	O
anecdotes	O
it	O
contains	O
her	O
persecutions	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
poſseſs	O
ions	O
in	O
Cumberland	B-place
death	O
of	O
L	O
Chi	O
&	O
James	B-pers
ye	I-pers
2d	I-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
abt	O
.	O
ten	O
was	O
to	O
sup	O
below	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
&	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
read	O
me	O
a	O
Curious	O
account	O
in	O
Manuscript	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carlisles	I-pers
y	O
e	O
.	O
present	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
s	O
Mothers	O
writing	O
of	O
Buxton	B-place
ye	O
stile	O
of	O
living	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
prose	O
written	O
with	O
some	O
humour	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
written	O
.	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
again	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
mine	O
till	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
came	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
might	O
wish	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
alone	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
leave	O
us	O
tomorrow	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
finish	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
I	O
read	O
some	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
Manuscripts	O
letters	O
of	O
Prior	B-pers
's	O
wch	O
..	O
ye	O
.	O
ducheſs	O
had	O
left	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
has	O
many	O
valuable	O
Manuscripts	O
in	O
her	O
poſseſsion	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
inherited	O
from	O
her	O
father	O
Lord	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
.	O
this	O
Nobleman	O
was	O
a	O
poet	O
friend	O
of	O
Prior	B-pers
s	O
.	O
she	O
returnd	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
¾	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
sat	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
Prior	B-pers
,	O
his	O
origin	O
In	O
ye	O
.	O
Course	O
of	O
conversation	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
said	O
Bagley	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
hers	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
orford	I-pers
.	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
scorbutic	O
tumour	O
broke	O
out	O
upon	O
his	O
Stomack	O
an	O
ignorant	O
Apothecary	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Mercurial	O
Girdle	O
,	O
this	O
drew	O
ye	O
.	O
humour	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
poor	O
Man	O
was	O
insane	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
still	O
odd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
lived	O
&	O
does	O
I	O
believe	O
still	O
live	O
wth	O
him	O
,	O
her	O
tenderneſs	O
attention	O
&	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
during	O
his	O
illneſs	O
--	O
&	O
related	O
an	O
anecdote	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
does	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
Woman	O
great	O
honor	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
1500	O
Pd	O
.	O
before	O
his	O
insanity	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
ye	O
management	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
&	O
used	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Bills	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
no	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
discharge	O
ye	O
Bills	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
have	O
left	O
unpaid	O
she	O
expended	O
all	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
discharge	O
of	O
House	O
Accounts	O
.	O
what	O
does	O
this	O
faithful	O
woman	O
merit	O
from	O
his	O
family	O
for	O
her	O
disinterested	O
attention	O
!	O
Blast	O
ye	O
too	O
rigid	O
unfeeling	O
Moralists	O
--	O
this	O
Woman	O
has	O
surely	O
more	O
real	O
Virtue	O
than	O
many	O
honorable	O
females	O
I	O
could	O
Mention	O
.	O
had	O
I	O
time	O
or	O
ye	O
.	O
Memory	O
I	O
wish	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
useful	O
,	O
entertaining	O
anecdotes	O
I	O
could	O
embellish	O
my	O
Journal	O
with	O
during	O
my	O
Abode	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
of	O
farewell	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
wish	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
good	O
night	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
.	O
11.	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
undreſsing	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
s	O
Conversation	O
--	O
surely	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
&	O
laudable	O
vanity	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
commendations	O
of	O
this	O
Sort	O
not	O
only	O
as	O
it	O
encourages	O
one	O
to	O
continue	O
endeavour	O
to	O
render	O
oneself	O
worthy	O
of	O
being	O
esteemd	O
but	O
gives	O
such	O
universal	O
satisfaction	O
by	O
behaving	O
in	O
a	O
civil	O
pleasing	O
manner	O
towards	O
every	O
individual	O
of	O
Society	O
.	O
it	O
seems	O
all	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Servants	O
are	O
quite	O
delighted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
give	O
so	O
fair	O
a	O
report	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
that	O
they	O
contrive	O
to	O
put	O
themselves	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
example	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Room	O
this	O
Morng	O
the	O
Man	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
enquire	O
wt	O
.	O
she	O
chose	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
addreſs	O
myself	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
add	O
something	O
to	O
wt	O
.	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
--	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
quite	O
charm	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
use	O
Betty	B-pers
s	O
words	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
credit	O
to	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Housekeeper	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
could	O
prevail	O
with	O
me	O
always	O
to	O
live	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
to	O
which	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Stewards	O
Room	O
join	O
'd	O
them	O
Betty	B-pers
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
120	O
Rooms	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
&	O
above	O
70	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
Bed	O
&	O
sat	O
up	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
till	O
one	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
AMaria	B-pers
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
The	O
Ducheſs	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
a	O
Box	O
wch	O
.	O
contain	O
'd	O
4	O
Pictures	O
finely	O
Painted	O
by	O
Zink	B-pers
s	O
enamel	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
was	O
highly	O
finished	O
&	O
still	O
like	O
new	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
s	O
Lady	B-pers
Andover	I-pers
s.	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
Bullstrode	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
:	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
heard	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
greatly	O
good	O
Night	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
wrote	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Journal	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Maid	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
had	O
found	O
benifit	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
bleeding	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
it	O
was	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
room	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
rather	O
low	O
.	O
during	O
B	O
.	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
ye	O
.	O
obligations	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
favorable	O
Portrait	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	O
s	O
Wife	O
.	O
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
made	O
judicious	O
remarks	O
.	O
upon	O
artful	O
characters	O
.	O
Gave	O
me	O
excellent	O
advice	O
how	O
to	O
guard	O
against	O
them	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
by	O
meeting	O
wth	O
.	O
one	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Lansdowne	I-pers
her	O
Uncle	O
s	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
oClock	O
Came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
ye	O
.	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
Chambers	O
there	O
who	O
was	O
placing	O
my	O
Candles	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
..	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
the	O
Housekeeper	O
sent	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
by	O
Betty	B-pers
to	O
say	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
she	O
came	O
was	O
very	O
civil	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
books	O
&	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
to	O
copy	O
,	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
course	O
of	O
conversation	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
meant	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
Letters	O
&	O
papers	O
to	O
the	O
Eldest	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
&	O
her	O
pictures	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
&	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
circumstance	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
did	O
him	O
much	O
honor	O
as	O
it	O
proved	O
his	O
disinterestedneſs	O
.	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
ride	O
&	O
orderd	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Grooms	O
whom	O
she	O
most	O
confid	O
ing	O
ed	O
h	O
in	O
for	O
ease	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
ready	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
ride	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
friend	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
read	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscripts	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
had	O
lent	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
began	O
to	O
copy	O
those	O
she	O
had	O
permitted	O
me	O
to	O
transcribe	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
foggy	O
day	O
&	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
airing	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
upstairs	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
much	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
writing	O
letters	O
but	O
to	O
come	O
backwards	O
&	O
forwards	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
but	O
poorly	O
.	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
meeting	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
at	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
c	O
his	O
marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
late	O
Duke	O
,	O
ye	O
number	O
of	O
offers	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
character	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
duke	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
his	O
two	O
Sisters	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
work	O
table	O
till	O
just	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
change	O
my	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
after	O
dinner	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
..	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
uneasineſs	O
she	O
had	O
respecting	O
Mrs	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
.	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
ym	O
.	O
their	O
art	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
reasons	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
not	O
being	O
invited	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
join	O
her	O
Daughters	O
.	O
a	O
falsity	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
&	O
many	O
other	O
circumstances	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
Evelina	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
folded	O
up	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
letters	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
impreſsions	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
seals	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
conversed	O
abt	O
education	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
opinion	O
respecting	O
ye	O
telling	O
children	O
&	O
given	O
ym	O
.	O
only	O
true	O
stories	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
wth	O
me	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
both	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
their	O
disapprobation	O
of	O
Young	O
Peoples	O
acting	O
Plays	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
she	O
had	O
fatigued	O
herself	O
wth	O
.	O
writing	O
.	O
we	O
parted	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
2	O
oClock	O
writing	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
had	O
lent	O
me	O
to	O
copy	O
2	O
d	O
Decbr	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
supper	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
spoke	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
gave	O
a	O
high	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
an	O
affection	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
Miſs	O
Murrays	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Sisters	O
they	O
were	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
People	O
(	O
Miſs	O
Murrays	O
)	O
wth	O
.	O
whom	O
she	O
kept	O
up	O
a	O
correspondence	O
except	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Rockingham	I-pers
her	O
love	O
for	O
Politics	O
--	O
yt	O
she	O
&	O
her	O
late	O
Lord	O
did	O
not	O
always	O
agree	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
folly	O
of	O
Women	O
entering	O
into	O
Politicks	O
.	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
nine	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
room	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
breakfasted	O
,	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
conversed	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
danger	O
of	O
aſsociating	O
wth	O
unworthy	O
diſsipated	O
People	O
&	O
various	O
other	O
Subjects	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
News	O
Papers	O
to	O
her	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
upstairs	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Chaise	O
took	O
an	O
airing	O
for	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
said	O
how	O
much	O
satisfaction	O
it	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
strong	O
attachment	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
had	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
lookd	O
forward	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
productive	O
of	O
great	O
comfort	O
to	O
her	O
friend	O
.	O
she	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
interesting	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
early	O
acquaintance	O
she	O
had	O
wth	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
F	I-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
&	O
related	O
ye	O
circumstances	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
s	O
(	O
her	O
fathers	O
older	O
Brother	O
being	O
confined	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Tower	O
)	O
her	O
father	O
having	O
been	O
apprehended	O
.	O
--	O
the	O
Affection	O
of	O
her	O
Aunt	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
(	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
S——	I-pers
Wife	O
)	O
her	O
living	O
with	O
them	O
her	O
retiring	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
for	O
3	O
years	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
we	O
prevaild	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
only	O
&	O
then	O
met	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Book	O
of	O
Volcanos	O
,	O
--	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
told	O
us	O
how	O
busy	O
she	O
was	O
settling	O
accounts	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
3	O
--	O
brought	O
me	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Marlbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
Book	O
of	O
Gems	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
.	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
work	O
'd	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
dinner	O
was	O
ready	O
--	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wld	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
change	O
my	O
dreſs	O
--	O
she	O
also	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
ye-	O
same	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
till	O
near	O
5.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
many	O
curious	O
things	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Laplanders	O
works	O
of	O
ingenuity	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Americans	O
,	O
Othehite	O
&	O
c	O
Chinese	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Prints	O
of	O
Gems	O
in	O
her	O
Collection	O
.	O
(	O
before	O
dinner	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
curious	O
Birds	O
nests	O
Birds	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
very	O
pretty	O
drawings	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chinese	O
dreſseſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
100	O
pages	O
of	O
Evelina	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
supper	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
birds	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
y	O
e	O
.	O
groom	O
of	O
ye	O
Chamber	O
lit	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
rooms	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
give	O
himself	O
ye	O
.	O
trouble	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
her	O
Pictures	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
made	O
me	O
uneasy	O
abt	O
.	O
something	O
she	O
has	O
heard	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
c	O
wrote	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
made	O
my	O
Heart	O
ache	O
Bullstrode	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
Decbr	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1783	O
Allegory	O
Rev	O
d	O
Baily	O
Got	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
a	O
great	O
fog	O
wch	O
made	O
ye	O
Morning	O
appear	O
dark	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
though	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
as	O
usual	O
for	O
ye	O
morning	O
a	O
riding	O
Habit	O
.	O
sent	O
also	O
as	O
usual	O
(	O
as	O
favourite	O
a	O
word	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
journal	O
as	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
my	O
&	O
c	O
's	O
are	O
more	O
expreſsive	O
as	O
they	O
often	O
mean	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
trust	O
to	O
paper	O
)	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
night	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
ye	O
.	O
Breakfast	O
hour	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
alone	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
before	O
we	O
always	O
breakfast	O
in	O
her	O
Dreſsing	O
room	O
.	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
spirits	O
&	O
looking	O
vastly	O
better	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
letters	O
are	O
always	O
brought	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
breakfast	O
things	O
read	O
part	O
of	O
its	O
contents	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
conversed	O
she	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
history	O
&	O
indeed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
curious	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Marriage	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pendarves	I-pers
her	O
first	O
husband	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Uncles	O
at	O
Long	O
Leate	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
sent	O
as	O
usual	O
her	O
Chamber	O
Maid	O
wth	O
.	O
enquiries	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
brought	O
ye	O
.	O
Newspaper	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
's	O
footmen	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
choze	O
to	O
ride	O
on	O
horseback	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
if	O
ye	O
.	O
fog	O
dispersed	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
sent	O
us	O
a	O
comical	O
meſsage	O
abt	O
.	O
seeing	O
ye	O
.	O
Moon	O
wch	O
.	O
proved	O
ye	O
Sun	O
struggling	O
thro	O
'	O
ye	O
..	O
fog	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Moments	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
library	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
for	O
ye	O
Papers	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
s	O
Essays	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
7	O
days	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Week	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
brought	O
me	O
drawings	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouths	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Chinese	O
.	O
look	O
over	O
they	O
were	O
highly	O
finish	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
&	O
last	O
letter	O
of	O
Wey-	B-pers
mouth	I-pers
s	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
Lakes	B-place
of	I-place
Cumberland	I-place
.	O
The	O
Dſs	O
.	O
was	O
then	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Drawing	O
's	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
of	O
Weymouth	B-pers
her	O
graces	O
House	O
Steward	O
&	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Lettice	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Gardiner	O
of	O
Shells	O
--	O
Birds	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
parted	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
past	O
dinner	O
time	O
I	O
just	O
changed	O
my	O
riding	O
Skirt	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Habit	O
again	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Levers	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
Brought	O
me	O
a	O
large	O
collection	O
of	O
Seals	O
--	O
to	O
take	O
impreſsions	O
from	O
--	O
I	O
finished	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Vol	O
of	O
Evelina	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Agnew	I-pers
wch	O
:	O
I	O
finished	O
in	O
ye	O
Dr	O
room	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
conversed	O
--	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
dumb	O
waiters	O
&	O
no	O
servts	O
.	O
to	O
wait	O
at	O
Supper	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Windsor	O
Castle	O
.	O
miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
England	B-place
.	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
parted	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
ye	O
Dining	O
Room	O
Screen	O
brought	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
repair	O
.	O
Decbr	O
4th	O
1783	O
Thursday	O
found	O
dr	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
good	O
look	O
&	O
spirits	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Breakfas	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
till	O
¼	O
of	O
Eleven	O
--	O
she	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
beginning	O
&	O
end	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
wth	O
Dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
Dr	O
.	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Dalhousie	O
family	O
Wyndham	O
Miſs	B-pers
Halley	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Halley	I-pers
Leicester	O
House	O
.	O
--	O
her	O
very	O
shocking	O
conduct	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Pendarvis	I-pers
sent	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
Pſs	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
horse	O
&	O
groom	O
were	O
ready	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
heavenly	O
ye-	O
Sun	O
bright	O
--	O
took	O
a	O
most	O
delightful	O
Ride	O
.	O
a	O
sensible	O
kind	O
Groom	O
--	O
met	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
air	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
offerd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
ye	O
Carriage	O
,	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pursued	O
my	O
Ride	O
came	O
in	O
20	O
Min	O
after	O
12	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
:	O
wch	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
walk	O
'd	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
found	O
upon	O
my	O
Table	O
a	O
Work	O
Bag	O
wth	O
a	O
paper	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
importing	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
ye	O
air	O
Balloon	O
from	O
Paris	B-place
.	O
also	O
some	O
fine	O
myrtle	O
in	O
a	O
Tumbler	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Gallantrie	O
.	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
melancholy	O
Story	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
attachment	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
his	O
death	O
(	O
&	O
c	O
see	O
Cover	O
of	O
this	O
for	O
names	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs	B-pers
D——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
told	O
us	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
was	O
having	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Saturday	O
she	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
Longheath	B-place
--	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
having	O
no	O
Lady	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
attending	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
who	O
is	O
dying	O
of	O
a	O
consumption	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Holderneſse	I-pers
in	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
Ill	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
attending	O
Lady	B-pers
Egremont	I-pers
who	O
is	O
dying	O
Lady	B-pers
Effingham	I-pers
abroad	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
her	O
Daughter	O
who	O
is	O
ill	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
left	O
me	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
airing	O
I	O
remand	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
Took	O
emp	O
walk	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
Lady	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
eat	O
oysters	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
went	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
her	O
during	O
their	O
airing	O
had	O
only	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
say	O
--	O
I	O
requested	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
ever	O
perceived	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
in	O
my	O
conduct	O
,	O
expreſsions	O
or	O
manners	O
.	O
&	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
w	O
d	O
.	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
when	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
her	O
daughter	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
aſsured	O
she	O
thought	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
woud	O
not	O
for	O
ye	O
world	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
part	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
before	O
tuesday	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
tell	O
her	O
wht	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
work	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
Bird	O
in	O
worstead	O
&	O
flowers	O
in	O
silk	O
on	O
wt	O
.	O
Satting	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
also	O
ye	O
additional	O
catalogue	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
read	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
Evelina	O
,	O
then	O
ran	O
down	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
D	O
:	O
room	O
found	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
alone	O
.	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
&	O
saw	O
two	O
Horses	O
close	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
eating	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
abt	O
.	O
going	O
on	O
Satry	O
.	O
that	O
ye	O
..	O
Dſs	O
.	O
would	O
not	O
listen	O
to	O
it	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
aſsure	O
me	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
came	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
oClock	O
.	O
after	O
Dinner	O
.	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
our	O
converse	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
beggars	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
said	O
how	O
wrong	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
encourage	O
those	O
poor	O
who	O
beg	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Streets	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Dining	O
Room	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
ye	O
Dſs	O
.	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
related	O
a	O
story	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
old	O
Porter	O
&	O
his	O
Blind	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
to	O
repose	O
--	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
quite	O
shock	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
one	O
is	O
deceived	O
in	O
Characters	O
!	O
after	O
tea	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
prevented	O
further	O
conversation	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
Evelina	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
After	O
supper	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
upon	O
different	O
subjects	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
her	O
daughters	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
A	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
ducheſs	O
not	O
only	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
&	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
going	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Cooley	I-pers
came	O
,	O
but	O
earnestly	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
till	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
she	O
said	O
wth	O
.	O
tears	O
perhaps	O
--	O
we	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
comfort	O
of	O
meeting	O
again	O
think	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
prevaild	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
&	O
she	O
cordially	O
embraced	O
me	O
when	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
came	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
&	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
mutually	O
happy	O
.	O
rebelion	O
1715	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
x	O
Twyford	O
x	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tucker	B-pers
in	O
--	O
G	O
Gloucester	B-place
--	O
+	O
Somerset	O
shire	O
