TOKEN	NE
8	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1781	O
Thank	O
you	O
my	O
Love	O
for	O
the	O
Sattin	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
write	O
a	O
line	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
my	O
Spirits	O
are	O
so	O
agitated	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
just	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
Yo	O
.	O
will	O
feel	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
You	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
is	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
Yesterday	O
--	O
his	O
complaint	O
is	O
ye	O
Gout	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
wch	O
.	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
alarming	O
disorder	O
but	O
at	O
his	O
Years	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
just	O
turn	O
'd	O
seventy	O
)	O
then	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
fear	O
the	O
worst	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
calld	O
to	O
Dinner	O
Adieu	O
I	O
send	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
MMary	I-pers
HHume	I-pers
return	O
it	O
--	O
Ad	O
ieu	O
October	O
8	O
th	O
1781	O
