TOKEN	NE
My	O
good	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
so	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Pacquet	O
which	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
myself	O
as	O
bound	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Post	O
to	O
return	O
you	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
.	O
I	O
very	O
frequently	O
lament	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
opportunities	O
of	O
paying	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Tis	O
an	O
odd	O
circumstance	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
are	O
engaged	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
within	O
a	O
distance	O
leſs	O
than	O
twenty	O
miles	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
strangers	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
Countries	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
handwriting	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
no	O
leſs	O
pleased	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
very	O
valuable	O
woman	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
whom	O
to	O
know	O
is	O
to	O
admire	O
.	O
Her	O
Letter	O
was	O
particularly	O
pleasing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
anxious	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
several	O
weeks	O
,	O
past	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
learn	O
a	O
syllable	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchelsea	I-pers
in	O
this	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
enclose	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
other	O
Letter	O
you	O
entrusted	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
principal	O
subject	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
delicate	O
a	O
matter	O
to	O
venture	O
to	O
recommend	O
a	O
person	O
for	O
so	O
important	O
a	O
Charge	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
ought	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
greatest	O
care	O
&	O
circumspection	O
:	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
paying	O
my	O
respects	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
,	O
but	O
shall	O
say	O
nothing	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
unleſs	O
it	O
is	O
first	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
opportunity	O
will	O
present	O
itself	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Collegue	O
is	O
upon	O
his	O
leave	O
of	O
absence	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
without	O
hopes	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
visit	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
as	O
P.E	B-pers
.	I-pers
expects	O
to	O
be	O
summoned	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.B	B-pers
.	I-pers
gives	O
me	O
to	O
understand	O
,	O
he	O
beleives	O
my	O
attendance	O
will	O
be	O
dispensed	O
with	O
.	O
One	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
enclosed	O
to	O
me	O
pained	O
me	O
much	O
;	O
Tis	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
great	O
anxiety	O
is	O
expreſsed	O
about	O
your	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
God	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
reason	O
why	O
your	O
friend	O
should	O
be	O
alarmed	O
.	O
Pray	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
yourself	O
on	O
the	O
approaching	O
Festivity	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
suffer	O
for	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
consumption	O
of	O
spirits	O
,	O
&	O
exertion	O
on	O
that	O
joyous	O
occasion	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
trespaſsing	O
upon	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
could	O
be	O
much	O
better	O
employed	O
:	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
conclude	O
with	O
signing	O
my	O
self	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
much	O
obliged	O
most	O
obedient	O
Servant	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Bryuyeres	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
