TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	O
--	O
Nov	O
--	O
29	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
really	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
authorised	O
to	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
pronouncing	O
to	O
our	O
good	O
Friends	O
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
,	O
that	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
Prescription	O
has	O
done	O
some	O
good	O
,	O
where	O
He	O
so	O
much	O
wished	O
it	O
to	O
succeed	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
attributing	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
removal	O
&	O
ceſsation	O
of	O
Pain	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
who	O
is	O
always	O
disappointed	O
on	O
every	O
new	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
restore	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
more	O
perceptible	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
inclined	O
to	O
allow	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
done	O
much	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
grateful	O
for	O
your	O
earnest	O
endevors	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
come	O
down-stairs	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
small	O
Bed	O
fixed	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
horizontal	O
Posture	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
most	O
irksome	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
is	O
continued	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
He	O
is	O
at	O
his	O
Meals	O
.	O
The	O
Swelling	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
is	O
rather	O
leſsened	O
,	O
his	O
appetite	O
is	O
extraordinarily	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
He	O
begins	O
to	O
look	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
chearful	O
,	O
if	O
He	O
could	O
banish	O
that	O
sad	O
reflection	O
which	O
is	O
perpetually	O
recurring	O
,	O
that	O
He	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
.	O
This	O
perswasion	O
keeps	O
him	O
dejected	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
great	O
inconvenience	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
getting	O
in	O
&	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
being	O
cramped	O
by	O
sitting	O
above	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
at	O
present	O
think	O
poor	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
the	O
Worst	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
She	O
suffers	O
so	O
much	O
from	O
her	O
Eyes	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
at	O
last	O
submitted	O
to	O
a	O
perpetual	O
Blister	O
on	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
she	O
will	O
recieve	O
benefit	O
for	O
this	O
a	O
is	O
a	O
melancholy	O
&	O
sore	O
aggravation	O
to	O
her	O
other	O
affliction	O
which	O
was	O
quite	O
enough	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
account	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
warmer	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
more	O
chearing	O
&	O
advising	O
friends	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
can	O
so	O
little	O
judge	O
how	O
equal	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
to	O
a	O
journey	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
much	O
prospect	O
of	O
our	O
removal	O
.	O
--	O
Little	O
Catharine	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
lively	O
&	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
improves	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
William	I-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
-	O
Asaph	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
remarkably	O
attached	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
&	O
happy	O
together	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
stroke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
low	O
Fever	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
left	O
him	O
8	O
Children	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
return	O
the	O
verses	O
I	O
enclose	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
unite	O
in	O
affectionate	O
Compliments	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
Your	O
Much	O
Obliged	O
Friend	O
E.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
