TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
After	O
having	O
troubled	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
second	O
letter	O
bearing	O
the	O
same	O
date	O
with	O
yours	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
received	O
,	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
myself	O
inexcusable	O
in	O
not	O
embracing	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
to	O
return	O
you	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
having	O
relieved	O
me	O
from	O
very	O
great	O
anxiety	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
express	O
'd	O
pretty	O
strongly	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
;	O
my	O
mind	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
state	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
my	O
Bankers	O
who	O
have	O
some	O
obligations	O
to	O
me	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
well	O
have	O
refused	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
application	O
to	O
them	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
me	O
exceedingly	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
well	O
aſsured	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
every	O
poſsible	O
regard	O
to	O
your	O
interest	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
suffer	O
any	O
material	O
inconvenience	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
so	O
liberal	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
friendship	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
busineſs	O
will	O
be	O
transacted	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
a	O
secret	O
pleasure	O
in	O
letting	O
them	O
see	O
the	O
forward	O
part	O
you	O
bear	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
found	O
benefit	O
by	O
sea	O
bathing	O
.	O
If	O
London	B-place
is	O
in	O
your	O
speculation	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sincerely	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
much	O
obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
249	O
October	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
