TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
in	O
sending	O
me	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
Grouse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
condition	O
.	O
We	O
propose	O
quitting	O
our	O
House	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
Square	I-place
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
having	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thos	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
a	O
Banker	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
remove	O
to	O
n	O
o	O
.	O
248	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Street	O
,	O
contiguous	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
building	O
a	O
House	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
lot	O
of	O
Ground	O
which	O
stands	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
&	O
commands	O
a	O
most	O
magnificent	O
view	O
of	O
Hyde	B-place
Park	I-place
.	O
This	O
when	O
completed	O
will	O
serve	O
for	O
both	O
a	O
Town	O
&	O
Country	O
House	O
&	O
will	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
be	O
a	O
much	O
leſs	O
remote	O
situation	O
than	O
Bedford	B-place
Square	I-place
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
us	O
all	O
most	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
condole	O
very	O
sincerely	O
on	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
excellent	O
Friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
are	O
subjects	O
I	O
am	O
inclined	O
to	O
avoid	O
,	O
knowing	O
how	O
little	O
can	O
be	O
said	O
to	O
mitigate	O
real	O
affliction	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
amazingly	O
grown	O
,	O
we	O
expect	O
him	O
this	O
Evening	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
Square	I-place
with	O
a	O
large	O
Squadron	O
of	O
Boys	O
to	O
celebrate	O
his	O
Birth	O
Day	O
,	O
having	O
now	O
enterd	O
his	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
year	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chauvet	I-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
general	O
much	O
liked	O
by	O
his	O
Companions	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
at	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
North	I-pers
's	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
her	O
Br	O
.	O
Col.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
arrived	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
from	O
India	B-place
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
upon	O
no	O
frivolous	O
busineſs	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
ill	O
&	O
much	O
thinner	O
than	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
18	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
's	O
,	O
my	O
surprise	O
was	O
in	O
deed	O
very	O
great	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
6	O
Months	O
on	O
his	O
paſsage	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
informed	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cornwallis	I-pers
's	O
Appointment	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
prevented	O
his	O
return	O
.	O
Next	O
Week	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Scene	O
of	O
some	O
confusion	O
removing	O
my	O
Effects	O
and	O
my	O
Family	O
to	O
my	O
new	O
Habitation	O
Adieu	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sir	O
believe	O
me	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
August	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
prepared	O
upon	O
the	O
busineſs	O
of	O
the	O
Aſsignment	O
of	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
Honbl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ld	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
August	O
1786	O
