TOKEN	NE
As	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
respecting	O
Osyiris	B-pers
or	O
rather	O
what	O
you	O
hear	O
said	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
wrong	O
to	O
detiremine	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
imagine	O
ye	O
.	O
amusement	O
he	O
takes	O
is	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
his	O
mind	O
wld	O
.	O
otherwise	O
be	O
oppreſs	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
After	O
all	O
perhaps	O
tis	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
Children	O
that	O
he	O
promotes	O
&	O
enters	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
Public	O
affairs	O
but	O
what	O
you	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
get	O
intelligence	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Melsom	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
