TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
at	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
at	O
little	B-place
grove	I-place
,	O
enclosing	O
one	O
from	O
Col.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Dragoons	O
now	O
at	O
Leicester	B-place
notifying	O
the	O
vacancy	O
of	O
a	O
Cornetcy	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
General	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
's	O
desire	O
is	O
offerd	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
consequence	O
directed	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Meſs	O
rs	O
.	O
Cox	O
&	O
Greenwood	O
Agents	O
to	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
£1,102	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
limited	O
price	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Regulation	O
.	O
The	O
Recommendation	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sent	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Secretary	O
at	O
War	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
approbation	O
till	O
the	O
Money	O
is	O
actually	O
deposited	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
aſsure	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
notice	O
when	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
latest	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
payment	O
can	O
with	O
propriety	O
be	O
deferr	O
'd	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
your	O
last	O
with	O
the	O
Deed	O
--	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
notice	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Balfour	I-pers
that	O
he	O
expects	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
next	O
,	O
Martinmas	O
Day	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
in	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
lending	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
perceive	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sir	O
that	O
this	O
money	O
wou	O
'd	O
come	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
present	O
purpose	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
with	O
credit	O
,	O
there	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
no	O
delay	O
in	O
my	O
lodging	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
therefore	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
gratitude	O
accept	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
offer	O
;	O
and	O
will	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
most	O
scrupulously	O
for	O
your	O
security	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
punctual	O
repayment	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
will	O
prescribe	O
.	O
Shou	O
'd	O
it	O
happen	O
to	O
occur	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
eligible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
lend	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
upon	O
the	O
Security	O
of	O
the	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
with	O
a	O
Collateral	O
Bond	O
on	O
the	O
Security	O
of	O
my	O
Personal	O
Property	O
,	O
obliging	O
myself	O
&	O
Heirs	O
to	O
repay	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
six	O
months	O
notice	O
,	O
the	O
busineſs	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
easily	O
settled	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
by	O
this	O
offer	O
I	O
mean	O
your	O
own	O
accommodation	O
solely	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
vacancy	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
your	O
generous	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
;	O
these	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
will	O
be	O
subjects	O
of	O
the	O
utmost	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
received	O
benefit	O
from	O
sea	O
bathing	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
soon	O
weary	O
of	O
that	O
detestable	O
place	O
Park	B-place
Gate	I-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
Daughter	O
&	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
desire	O
to	O
offer	O
their	O
affectionate	O
Compts	O
.	O
with	O
mine	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
you	O
receive	O
from	O
your	O
little	O
Girl	O
&	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
St	O
.	O
249	O
September	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chester	B-place
Chapel	B-place
de	I-place
la	I-place
Frith	I-place
