TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
hunted	O
every	O
where	O
in	O
vain	O
for	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
to	O
send	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
succeeding	O
I	O
determin	O
'd	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
disappointed	O
&	O
have	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
One	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
at	O
yr	O
Service	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
amuse	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
mending	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
rejoice	O
to	O
ſee	O
you	O
well	O
again	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
all	O
shall	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
beg	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
throw	O
away	O
a	O
thought	O
upon	O
my	O
Attendence	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
Succeſsful	O
with	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
who	O
I	O
think	O
will	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
beauty	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
&	O
Harriet	B-pers
send	O
their	O
Love	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Sincerest	O
Affection	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
St	O
James	O
's	O
Thursday	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
