TOKEN	NE
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
6	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1783	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
present	O
the	O
inclosed	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Will	O
you	O
never	O
leave	O
off	O
drawing	O
me	O
into	O
Correspondencies	O
?	O
Remember	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
Since	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
but	O
Feast	O
.	O
The	O
affectionate	O
reception	O
I	O
meet	O
with	O
from	O
my	O
Friends	O
here	O
amply	O
makes	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
cold	O
insipidity	O
of	O
my	O
London	B-place
Relations	O
.	O
Talk	O
not	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
English	O
politeneſs	O
,	O
which	O
consists	O
of	O
a	O
stiff	O
Curtsey	O
or	O
bow	O
and	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
a	O
Route	O
.	O
Compare	O
this	O
with	O
a	O
clean	O
Hearth	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Fire	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Dinner	O
&	O
a	O
hearty	O
welcome	O
.	O
Blush	O
for	O
your	O
English	O
Breeding	O
,	O
&	O
allow	O
that	O
we	O
excel	O
John	O
Bull	O
in	O
real	O
hospitality	O
.	O
Neither	O
are	O
our	O
Miſses	O
more	O
forward	O
than	O
Yours	O
(	O
recollect	O
your	O
conversation	O
with	O
me	O
)	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
they	O
neither	O
Paint	O
,	O
nor	O
drive	O
the	O
expreſsion	O
of	O
their	O
feelings	O
from	O
their	O
countenance	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
esteem	O
You	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
--	O
Now	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Have	O
been	O
displeased	O
&	O
determined	O
never	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
second	O
offer	O
to	O
Her	O
.	O
When	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
secresy	O
was	O
required	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
kep't	O
it	O
inviolably	O
.	O
She	O
or	O
her	O
friends	O
(	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
proposal	O
)	O
have	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Relations	O
.	O
Gueſs	O
my	O
surprise	O
when	O
within	O
twenty	O
four	O
Hours	O
of	O
my	O
arrival	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
four	O
different	O
People	O
.	O
Some	O
approving	O
&	O
vice	O
versa	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
visited	O
her	O
twice	O
&	O
am	O
much	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
by	O
her	O
Relations	O
,	O
have	O
handed	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
&	O
to	O
her	O
Chair	O
at	O
a	O
Private	O
Ball	O
&	O
can	O
be	O
as	O
indifferent	O
as	O
the	B-pers
D.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
I	O
dined	O
&	O
supped	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Aunt	O
s	O
.	O
Her	O
father	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
My	O
spirits	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
afloat	O
&	O
I	O
flirted	O
openly	O
with	O
another	O
Lady	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
admirable	O
.	O
No	O
accounts	O
yet	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Your	O
advice	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
Execution	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evening	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Fielding	B-pers
s	O
Men	O
&	O
to	O
offer	O
a	O
reward	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
most	O
distant	O
idea	O
of	O
recovering	O
it	O
.	O
Your	O
conjecture	O
about	O
my	O
Nerves	O
was	O
ill	O
founded	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
wrote	O
to	O
is	O
expected	O
in	O
England	B-place
with	O
the	O
first	O
fleet	O
from	O
Canada	B-place
.	O
Had	O
You	O
been	O
present	O
at	O
my	O
Adventure	O
,	O
an	O
unconcerned	O
Spectator	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
amused	O
You	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
conversation	O
lasted	O
full	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
begs	O
her	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
her	O
Breadth	O
considerably	O
exceeds	O
her	O
Length	O
.	O
Next	O
Month	O
she	O
intends	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
an	O
Uncle	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
good	O
Health	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
most	O
flattering	O
hopes	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
more	O
fortunate	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
last	O
time	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
long	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
never	O
more	O
sincere	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
add	O
Your	O
Affect	O
:	O
Brother	O
and	O
Friend	O
N——	B-pers
