TOKEN	NE
27	O
July	O
1789	O
--	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
letter	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
omit	O
another	O
post	O
--	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
unleſs	O
I	O
steal	O
a	O
short	O
space	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
before	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morng	O
or	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
--	O
the	O
day	O
slips	O
away	O
to	O
my	O
astonishment	O
&	O
you	O
are	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Lurch	O
--	O
tho	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Mind	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
exactly	O
20	O
minutes	O
to	O
spare	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
fraction	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
Amusement	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dearly	O
beloved	O
Wife	O
--	O
And	O
so	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Yellow	I-pers
Face	O
your	O
natural	O
curiosity	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
alive	O
&	O
restleſs	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
agreeable	O
,	O
charming	O
,	O
pleasant	O
woman	O
is	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
take	O
compaſsion	O
upon	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
Absence	O
--	O
in	O
this	O
instance	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
gratify	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
those	O
kind	O
of	O
aſsignations	O
are	O
always	O
kept	O
inviolably	O
secret	O
by	O
Men	O
of	O
Honor	O
--	O
Not	O
to	O
distreſs	O
you	O
by	O
enlarging	O
upon	O
my	O
felicity	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
pure	O
compassion	O
,	O
return	O
to	O
my	O
Journal	O
&	O
shall	O
raise	O
another	O
conjecture	O
in	O
your	O
Mind	O
to	O
inform	O
yourself	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
dined	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
an	O
Unmarried	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
profeſses	O
herself	O
an	O
admirer	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
Snug	O
--	O
the	O
invitation	O
was	O
communicated	O
in	O
a	O
secret	O
manner	O
--	O
lest	O
too	O
great	O
pleasure	O
shd	O
satiate	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Inamorata	O
at	O
7	O
oClock	O
--	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Herschell	I-pers
's	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
leſson	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
attend	O
a	O
private	O
Concert	O
to	O
play	O
Quartettos	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
invited	O
&	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
as	O
my	O
Drawing	O
Master	O
expected	O
me	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Isted	I-pers
that	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
her	O
daughters	O
dined	O
there	O
also	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
spoke	O
very	O
handsomely	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
She	O
never	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
She	O
thought	O
so	O
amiable	O
&	O
so	O
accomplished	O
and	O
could	O
almost	O
say	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
glad	O
She	O
had	O
known	O
so	O
little	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
for	O
She	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
regretted	O
your	O
leaving	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
so	O
much	O
the	O
more	O
“	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
handsome	O
&	O
dresses	O
as	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
should	O
do	O
,	O
suitable	O
to	O
her	O
age	O
--	O
my	O
Manners	O
seem	O
to	O
please	O
this	O
family	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
reckon	O
upon	O
being	O
a	O
favorite	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
said	O
She	O
never	O
invited	O
any	O
person	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
that	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
very	O
agreeable	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
myself	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
but	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
good	O
humour	O
&	O
little	O
attentions	O
,	O
which	O
flow	O
from	O
the	O
heart	O
,	O
will	O
often	O
gain	O
the	O
poſseſsor	O
admittance	O
into	O
families	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
the	O
Door	O
is	O
shut	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Talents	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
28	O
/	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundel	I-pers
;	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
as	O
usual	O
&	O
after	O
Tea	O
walked	O
with	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
She	O
seems	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
call	O
whenever	O
I	O
can	O
--	O
tho	O
it	O
be	O
only	O
for	O
5	O
minutes	O
--	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
I	O
have	O
endeavored	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Vanbrughs	I-pers
but	O
really	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
--	O
you	O
would	O
laugh	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
posting	O
away	O
from	O
one	O
Master	O
to	O
another	O
--	O
my	O
Mind	O
is	O
fully	O
employed	O
&	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
happy	O
--	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
at	O
7	O
(	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Piozzi	I-pers
's	O
Travels	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
dont	O
admire	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
reading	O
&	O
thats	O
all	O
)	O
from	O
7	O
to	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
exerc	O
i	O
ise	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
dreſsing	O
&	O
breakfast	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Italian	O
Master	O
--	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
leſson	O
from	O
Rauzzini	B-pers
which	O
is	O
throwing	O
money	O
away	O
--	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Herschell	B-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
my	O
drawing	O
Master	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
&	O
returned	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
scribble	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
dreſs	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
between	O
7	O
&	O
8	O
we	O
all	O
marched	O
to	O
the	O
Villa	O
gardens	O
to	O
see	O
Fireworks	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
were	O
disappointed	O
,	O
as	O
something	O
had	O
happened	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
postpone	O
this	O
raree	O
show	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
however	O
--	O
30	O
/	O
I	O
was	O
this	O
morning	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
sorts	O
by	O
your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
26	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
that	O
nothing	O
can	O
make	O
amends	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
your	O
Society	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
yr-	O
generous	O
heart	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
confeſs	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
for	O
several	O
reasons	O
--	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
poſsible	O
State	O
of	O
health	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
s	O
Medicine	O
has	O
entirely	O
removed	O
the	O
Irrittation	O
--	O
the	O
waters	O
now	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
look	O
so	O
well	O
in	O
yr-	O
life	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
same	O
medicine	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
very	O
pleasant	O
by	O
diluting	O
with	O
water	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
upon	O
our	O
lovely	O
Child	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
consider	O
the	O
expence	O
which	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
avoided	O
for	O
reasons	O
which	O
my	O
Love	O
for	O
you	O
dictates	O
--	O
&	O
if	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
love	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
contribute	O
something	O
towards	O
a	O
short	O
sejour	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
which	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
wiſhes	O
may	O
take	O
place	O
--	O
then	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
infinitely	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
can	O
have	O
the	O
delight	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
Society	O
--	O
however	O
my	O
return	O
shall	O
be	O
determined	O
by	O
my	O
good	O
friend	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
seems	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
constitution	O
more	O
exactly	O
than	O
any	O
person	O
I	O
ever	O
consulted	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
Weymouth	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
visit	O
the	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
&	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
7	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
who	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pe	O
ti	O
tioned	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
this	O
Sheet	O
&	O
she	O
granted	O
the	O
prayer	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
mentioned	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
consulted	O
Fothergill	B-pers
--	O
perhaps	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
please	O
--	O
when	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
meet	O
again	O
I	O
shall	O
consult	O
him	O
about	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
will	O
endeavor	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
prescription	O
from	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
&	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
The	O
Irritation	O
on	O
my	O
Skin	O
is	O
entirely	O
subsided	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
once	O
more	O
quite	O
comfortable	O
--	O
my	O
sleep	O
is	O
uninterrupted	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
dreſs	O
my	O
self	O
without	O
a	O
batch	O
of	O
Scratching	O
for	O
--	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
upon	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
immediate	O
one	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
I	O
had	O
fixed	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
till	O
this	O
day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
the	O
three	O
weeks	O
you	O
desire	O
--	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
prolong	O
my	O
stay	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
C	O
o	O
.	O
to	O
follow	O
their	O
own	O
pursuits	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
who	O
had	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Gardens	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Ladies	O
there	O
who	O
's	O
Names	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
separated	O
--	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Villa	O
Gardens	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Fireworks	O
which	O
were	O
very	O
pretty	O
--	O
31	O
/	O
after	O
breakfast	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Pickwick	O
to	O
visit	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Now	O
My	O
dearest	O
&	O
best	O
friend	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
Tour	O
to	O
Corsham	B-place
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
--	O
Adieu	O
then	O
my	O
charming	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
Embrace	O
our	O
dear	O
Child	O
for	O
me	O
very	O
very	O
often	O
--	O
and	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
one	O
person	O
to	O
love	O
another	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
love	O
You	O
--	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Ever	O
Moſt	O
Affy	O
J.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pray	O
mention	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kindeſt	O
and	O
most	O
Affe	O
manner	O
to	O
Ampa	B-pers
--	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
is	O
not	O
forgot	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
always	O
my	O
good	O
wishes	O
--	O
R/	O
Tincture	O
of	O
Red	O
Roses	O
--	O
7	O
oz	O
Spirits	O
of	O
sea	O
salt	O
--	O
1	O
Drachm	O
Syrup	O
of	O
Violets	O
--	O
6	O
Drachms	O
Mix	O
--	O
of	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
at	O
first	O
a	O
Wine	O
glaſs	O
full	O
every	O
5	O
hours	O
--	O
now	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
glaſs	O
the	O
first	O
&	O
last	O
thing	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
--	O
&	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
aid	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
contrive	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
palatable	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
might	O
try	O
it	O
in	O
very	O
small	O
quantities	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
's	O
youngest	O
girl	O
s	O
legs	O
were	O
so	O
crooked	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
as	O
uneasy	O
about	O
them	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
by	O
all	O
accts	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
worse	O
--	O
now	O
no	O
persons	O
legs	O
are	O
straiter	O
31	O
/	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
irritation	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
give	O
her	O
Lime	O
Water	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
put	O
/	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
unslacked	O
Lime	O
into	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
water	O
--	O
let	O
it	O
stand	O
24	O
hours	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Film	O
&	O
bottle	O
it	O
--	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Louisa	B-pers
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
at	O
each	O
time	O
add	O
a	O
Table	O
spoonful	O
of	O
Milk	O
--	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
ye	O
palpitation	O
of	O
yr	O
heart	O
,	O
pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
de	O
al	O
of	O
exercise	O
&	O
not	O
drink	O
Tea	O
--	O
Dr	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
wishes	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
Tea	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
certainly	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
he	O
recommends	O
Tapioca	O
.	O
1	O
)	O
Pray	O
inquire	O
if	O
the	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
Coach	O
stops	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
(	O
in	O
its	O
way	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
)	O
all	O
night	O
as	O
it	O
does	O
coming	O
this	O
way	O
--	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
yesterday	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beavoir	I-pers
s	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
yr-	O
enquiries	O
2	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
I	O
was	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
--	O
&	O
knew	O
you	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
never	O
give	O
up	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
or	O
friend	O
particularly	O
(	O
however	O
plausible	O
they	O
might	O
make	O
their	O
story	O
)	O
without	O
having	O
good	O
grounds	O
for	O
your	O
proceedings	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
was	O
extensive	O
enough	O
without	O
enrolling	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beavoir	I-pers
in	O
that	O
number	O
3	O
)	O
This	O
day	O
is	O
so	O
exceſsively	O
bad	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
&	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
general	O
rain	O
--	O
My	O
Dr	O
Madam	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
has	O
flattered	O
us	O
with	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
diſsapoint	O
us	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
seeing	O
yourself	O
&	O
your	O
Dr	O
Loisa	B-pers
I	O
hope	O
to	O
write	O
more	O
very	O
soon	O
I	O
am	O
Dr	O
Madam	O
your	O
very	O
obliged	O
M.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
/	O
My	O
dr-	O
Ms	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Your	O
husband	O
is	O
wonderfully	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
excellent	O
spirits	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
full	O
employ	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
specific	O
against	O
langour	O
--	O
He	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
uneasy	O
about	O
him	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
look	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
legs	O
are	O
crooked	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
suspect	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
tendancy	O
to	O
rickets	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
bathe	O
her	O
legs	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
warm	O
water	O
,	O
rubbing	O
them	O
well	O
with	O
neats	O
foot	O
oil	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
every	O
other	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
every	O
night	O
--	O
&	O
give	O
a	O
little	O
physich	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
other	O
signs	O
of	O
rickets	O
than	O
the	O
legs	O
then	O
only	O
use	O
the	O
oil	O
&	O
good	O
rubbing	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
bow	O
will	O
go	O
off	O
as	O
she	O
gains	O
strength	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
May	O
all	O
comfort	O
attend	O
you	O
prays	O
your	O
affecte	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
E	I-pers
:	I-pers
R	I-pers
Single	O
Sheet	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Manr	B-place
.	I-place
Taxal	B-place
X	O
post	O
--	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
