TOKEN	NE
Harleyford	O
Novr	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Diconson	I-pers
I	O
know	O
your	O
disposition	O
to	O
oblige	O
makes	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
the	O
request	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
almost	O
unneceſsary	O
.	O
but	O
still	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
intrude	O
on	O
your	O
time	O
without	O
making	O
a	O
proper	O
excuse	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
the	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gay	I-pers
a	O
great	O
friend	O
of	O
this	O
family	O
's	O
&	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
Family	O
&	O
some	O
Fortune	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
&	O
wishes	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
obtain	O
from	O
some	O
Relation	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
should	O
introduce	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
&	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
notice	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
travel	O
'd	O
already	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
man	O
&	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
introducing	O
no	O
disagreable	O
person	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
if	O
I	O
could	O
obtain	O
of	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
.	O
it	O
would	O
very	O
greatly	O
oblige	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
troublesome	O
or	O
improper	O
request	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
it	O
.	O
if	O
not	O
I	O
will	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
enclose	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Harleyford	O
Marlow	B-place
Bucks	B-place
.	I-place
when	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
family	O
are	O
well	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
complimts	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Diconson	I-pers
&	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
hear	O
my	O
little	O
namessake	O
keeps	O
her	O
rosy	O
cheeks	O
&	O
improves	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
to	O
your	O
wishes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
in	O
attendance	O
on	O
George	B-pers
who	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
slow	O
&	O
dangerous	O
illneſs	O
but	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
may	O
hope	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
recovering	O
from	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Diconson	I-pers
with	O
great	O
regard	O
much	O
yrs	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Louisa	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
For	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Diconson	I-pers
