TOKEN	NE
August	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Wednesday	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Br	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
sat	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
stai	O
rs	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
sent	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
&	O
excuse	O
my	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
recd	O
.	O
an	O
answer	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
chatted	O
&	O
scribbled	O
--	O
I	O
added	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
screens	O
&	O
wrote	O
--	O
letters	O
--	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
(	O
a	O
long	O
one	O
)	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
.	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
again	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
he	O
intreated	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
moments	O
leisure	O
as	O
he	O
much	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
--	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
came	O
in	O
we	O
made	O
her	O
sit	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
drank	O
a	O
glaſs	O
of	O
wine	O
after	O
her	O
walk	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
was	O
rather	O
disappointed	O
not	O
to	O
receive	O
one	O
from	O
D——shire	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
by	O
this	O
Post	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Picture	O
was	O
not	O
sent	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
At	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
expe	O
except	O
George	B-pers
,	O
Chs	B-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
Nurse	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
till	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
my	O
our	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
&	O
Cousin	O
Chs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
yesterday	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
prepare	O
them	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
my	O
Uncle	O
was	O
much	O
satisfied	O
,	O
h	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
head	O
I	O
should	O
might	O
accept	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——w——	I-pers
would	O
offer	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
suited	O
to	O
my	O
disposition	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
he	O
first	O
paid	O
his	O
compts	O
.	O
&	O
left	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
at	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
Lord	O
's	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
told	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
subject	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
debate	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
interesting	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
but	O
not	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
note	O
down	O
here	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
opinion	O
of	O
learning	O
&	O
of	O
Learned	O
Ladies	O
.	O
he	O
paid	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
a	O
just	O
compt	O
.	O
in	O
saying	O
he	O
thought	O
her	O
sufficiently	O
accomplished	O
in	O
language	O
for	O
any	O
Woman	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
perfect	O
miſstreſs	O
of	O
French	O
&	O
speaks	O
as	O
if	O
born	O
in	O
Paris	O
--	O
understands	O
Italian	O
&	O
has	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
German	O
&	O
Ruſsian	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
English	O
tongue	O
.	O
We	O
talkd	O
of	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
day	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
she	O
thought	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
forward	O
&	O
c	O
many	O
other	O
topics	O
were	O
discuſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
wanted	O
us	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
party	O
to	O
go	O
Abroad	O
--	O
he	O
&	O
I	O
were	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Idea	O
but	O
my	O
Cousin	O
was	O
averse	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
--	O
(	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Coach	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
C——	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
a	O
little	O
Note	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
my	O
society	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
she	O
suffer	O
'd	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
attend	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
tomorrow	O
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
tomorrows	O
Post	O
--	O
read	O
in	O
Cook	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
.	O
August	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Thursday	O
Got	O
up	O
early	O
dreſs	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
but	O
poorly	O
gave	O
her	O
breakfast	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
10	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
met	O
her	O
Brother	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
hair	O
dreſsers	O
hand	O
&	O
had	O
several	O
people	O
on	O
busineſs	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
orders	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
chose	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
of	O
a	O
fan	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
(	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Pages	O
)	O
he	O
seemd	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
begged	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
me	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
however	O
she	O
aſsured	O
me	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
me	O
revived	O
&	O
did	O
her	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
arranged	O
&	O
pasted	O
some	O
Prints	O
in	O
her	O
books	O
of	O
Prints	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——son	I-pers
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
w	O
h	O
ether	O
ye	O
.	O
report	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
m	O
arried	O
was	O
true	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
infor	O
med	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
she	O
believd	O
so	O
soon	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
as	O
people	O
had	O
chose	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
was	O
so	O
glad	O
to	O
expreſs	O
herself	O
very	O
kindly	O
about	O
me	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
acted	O
very	O
wisely	O
not	O
to	O
sacrifice	O
my	O
happineſs	O
by	O
accepting	O
offers	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
heart	O
&	O
Mind	O
were	O
averse	O
to	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——s	I-pers
as	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
--	O
we	O
excused	O
this	O
failure	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
hurried	O
&	O
taken	O
up	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
at	O
¼	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
ye	O
.	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
another	O
Gown	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
Dr	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
bed	O
side	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
ad	O
ed	O
advised	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Apothecary	O
to	O
nurse	O
herself	O
)	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
but	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
engagement	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
dine	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
excuses	O
to	O
my	O
U	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
--	O
my	O
U——	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
Brother	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Yesterday	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——son	I-pers
--	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
satisfactory	O
.	O
I	O
m	O
ust	O
own	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
succeſsful	O
in	O
making	O
all	O
the	O
folks	O
approve	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
like	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
made	O
me	O
some	O
long	O
fine	O
speeches	O
--	O
“	O
every	O
“	O
one	O
will	O
give	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
credit	O
in	O
“	O
supposing	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
“	O
improper	O
choice	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
My	O
Cousin	O
to	O
play	O
&	O
sing	O
&	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
silenced	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
s	O
prating	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
as	O
Richard	B-pers
did	O
not	O
bring	O
me	O
any	O
Note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
as	O
she	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
one	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
wch	O
.	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
carried	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
early	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
her	O
time	O
to	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
--	O
she	O
goes	O
back	O
to	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
tomorrow	O
&	O
comes	O
up	O
again	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
fortnight	O
--	O
she	O
also	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
congratulate	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
on	O
my	O
marri	O
a	O
ge	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
&	O
a	O
1000	O
questions	O
that	O
embaraſsed	O
her	O
to	O
hear	O
.	O
had	O
I	O
conceived	O
that	O
my	O
friends	O
would	O
have	O
forgot	O
my	O
injunctions	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
my	O
engagement	O
to	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
till	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
affairs	O
were	O
settled	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
entrusted	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
confidence	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
now	O
be	O
remedied	O
submit	O
wth	O
.	O
good	O
grace	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
of	O
furnishing	O
conversation	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
delight	O
&	O
happineſs	O
of	O
having	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
blush	O
at	O
the	O
choice	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
therefore	O
they	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
wch	O
.	O
would	O
pain	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
as	O
my	O
choice	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
approved	O
by	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
reasonable	O
World	O
from	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
Dr	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
in	O
bed	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
orderd	O
some	O
bread	O
Gruel	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
little	O
Supper	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
bed	O
side	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
Cold	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
reading	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
No	O
letter	O
from	O
D——shire	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Thursday	O
--	O
at	O
8	O
had	O
my	O
Hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
so	O
well	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
her	O
usual	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
B——	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
if	O
poſsible	O
call	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
today	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
Park	O
Place	O
--	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
next	O
Wednesday	O
then	O
remain	O
in	O
Town	B-place
till	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmaker	O
brought	O
home	O
ye	O
.	O
enam̅eldenammeled	O
Chain	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
repair	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Stormont	B-pers
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
&	O
I	O
sat	O
below	O
with	O
Dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
11	O
till	O
3	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
pourd	O
such	O
a	O
deluge	O
of	O
Rain	O
all	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
send	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
or	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
&	O
left	O
a	O
letter	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Rhapsodies	O
,	O
beg̅dbeggd	O
to	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
&	O
I	O
allowed	O
him	O
a	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
till	O
4.	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
.	O
Sai	O
Said	O
all	O
yt	O
.	O
his	O
heart	O
&	O
Soul	O
felt	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
cold	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
talk	O
'd	O
wrote	O
extracts	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
letters	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
from	O
Buxton	B-place
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
--	O
my	O
Taxal	O
friends	O
--	O
invited	O
me	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Place	O
at	O
Welsbourne	B-place
in	O
Warwickshire	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
--	O
brought	O
me	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
from	O
Goslings	O
--	O
I	O
treated	O
him	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
perform	O
'd	O
by	O
Gentlemen	O
&	O
Ladies	O
at	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
--	O
at	O
night	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
indifferent	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
left	O
me	O
before	O
11	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
12	O
Saturday	O
21	O
st	O
August	O
--	O
84	O
Breakfast	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
dreſsd	O
at	O
9	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
better	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Watchmaker	O
came	O
&	O
brought	O
home	O
ye	O
.	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
--	O
paid	O
him	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
busy	O
but	O
sent	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
30	O
£	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
1	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
M	O
r	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
down	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
wth	O
..	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
we	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
She	O
in	O
Pasting	O
paper	O
over	O
a	O
Box	O
&	O
I	O
in	O
settling	O
&	O
pasting	O
Prints	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
follios	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thynne	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
wish	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
private	O
busineſs	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
where	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
or	O
an	O
hour	O
reading	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
T——	I-pers
came	O
&	O
paid	O
their	O
Compts	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
always	O
goodhumour	O
'd	O
&	O
obliging	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
congratulating	O
her	O
upon	O
Mis	B-pers
..	I-pers
S——	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
s	O
approaching	O
marriage	O
.	O
After	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
resumed	O
our	O
employment	O
.	O
my	O
amiable	O
friend	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
her	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
its	O
contents	O
&	O
desired	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
friend	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Margate	B-place
.	O
Our	O
conversation	O
was	O
very	O
interesting	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
future	O
State	O
&	O
c	O
serious	O
but	O
not	O
gloomy	O
were	O
this	O
angelic	O
womans	O
reflections	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Music	O
for	O
a	O
Young	O
lady	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Mother	O
at	O
5	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
pursue	O
my	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
(	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
repose	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
her	O
usual	O
custom	O
)	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Maitland	I-pers
came	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
invited	O
them	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
as	O
she	O
knew	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
entertain	O
her	O
friend	O
Company	O
for	O
any	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
At	O
6	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
my	O
charming	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D——	I-pers
I	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
enjoying	O
a	O
Domestic	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
they	O
were	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
its	O
pretty	O
little	O
bed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
enclosed	O
for	O
me	O
by	O
yesterdays	O
Post	O
from	O
my	O
Dickenson	B-pers
--	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
--	O
After	O
tea	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
left	O
us	O
till	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
went	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
Room	O
&	O
read	O
my	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
all	O
pleasant	O
except	O
hearing	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
packet	O
of	O
Diary	O
I	O
sent	O
ye	O
:	O
10	O
th	O
:	O
when	O
Dr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
went	O
away	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
&	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
unnlucky	O
unlucky	O
circumstance	O
she	O
consoled	O
me	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
&	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
immediately	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
every	O
enquiry	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
my	O
letter	O
down	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
frank	O
&	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
letters	O
to	O
her	O
Servt	O
.	O
for	O
this	O
nights	O
post	O
--	O
I	O
composed	O
my	O
mind	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
chatted	O
on	O
different	O
topics	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
answers	O
to	O
her	O
letters	O
from	O
her	O
Sister	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
relative	O
to	O
my	O
engagement	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
that	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
thousand	O
friendly	O
things	O
&	O
sent	O
every	O
kind	O
wish	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
soon	O
acquainted	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Object	O
of	O
my	O
Choice	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
8	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
related	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
that	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
between	O
their	O
Majesties	O
&	O
him	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
whether	O
he	O
went	O
alone	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
at	O
last	O
fairly	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
bid	O
her	O
fish	O
out	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
-	I-pers
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
careful	O
whom	O
he	O
chose	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q——	I-pers
replied	O
I	O
believe	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
bad	O
opinion	O
of	O
Our	O
Sex	O
--	O
he	O
aſsured	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
ye	O
.	O
Case	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
happy	O
22	O
years	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
fearful	O
not	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
fate	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
question	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
after	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
his	O
affairs	O
in	O
Wales	O
.	O
Well	O
&	O
who	O
shall	O
you	O
make	O
Your	O
Heir	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
Your	O
Nephew	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
next	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
.	O
he	O
however	O
answer	O
'd	O
this	O
improper	O
.	O
question	O
very	O
properly	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
certainly	O
keep	O
that	O
secret	O
to	O
himself	O
--	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
had	O
any	O
claim	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
paternal	O
inheritance	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
Gift	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
left	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
at	O
10	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
have	O
--	O
sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
much	O
better	O
she	O
shared	O
in	O
my	O
concern	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
loſs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Packet	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Sunday	O
22	O
August	O
1784	O
Betty	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
after	O
7	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
Riding	O
Habit	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Dreſsing	O
room	O
made	O
&	O
had	O
her	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
I	O
was	O
shown	O
in	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Library	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
wh	O
.	O
him	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
Edition	O
of	O
Orlando	O
Furioso	O
--	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
beautiful	O
Prints	O
whilst	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
went	O
to	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
recovered	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
up	O
early	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
disturb	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Post-	O
chaise	O
for	O
Highgate	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
dull	O
Rainy	O
Morng	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
information	O
respecting	O
a	O
sejour	O
at	O
Rome	B-place
&	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
Rome	B-place
is	O
ye	O
.	O
cheapest	O
place	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
managed	O
there	O
when	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
hopes	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
some	O
part	O
or	O
other	O
of	O
our	O
lives	O
to	O
travel	O
&	O
reside	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
abroad	O
I	O
made	O
myself	O
mistreſs	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
expence	O
&	O
shall	O
have	O
good	O
authority	O
to	O
consult	O
&	O
follow	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
.	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Highgate	O
Church	O
in	O
40	O
minutes	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
Service	O
began	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
2	O
Sisters	O
&	O
his	O
Daughter	O
&	O
Master	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
ready	O
to	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Pew	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
an	O
excellent	O
discourse	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Charity	O
Sermon	O
--	O
his	O
delivery	O
was	O
good	O
&	O
he	O
both	O
persuaded	O
&	O
enforced	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Mind	O
of	O
his	O
Auditors	O
ye	O
.	O
Duties	O
of	O
Charity	O
.	O
we	O
all	O
gave	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Door	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
only	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
triffle	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
eldest	O
Sister	O
.	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Master	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Marj	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Highgate	O
Church	O
--	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
Lord	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
s	O
Farm	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
House	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Murrays	O
carried	O
me	O
all	O
over	O
it	O
to	O
shew	O
ye	O
.	O
Rooms	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
&	O
convenient	O
House	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
fine	O
room	O
--	O
an	O
Oval	O
form	O
of	O
60	O
feet	O
long	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
30	O
I	O
imagine	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
front	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
is	O
300	O
feet	O
--	O
this	O
includes	O
a	O
Green	O
house	O
of	O
60	O
feet	O
wch	O
.	O
answers	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
of	O
60.	O
before	O
dinner	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
.	O
We	O
conversed	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
Prints	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
also	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Terrace	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
front	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
wch	O
.	O
notwithstanding	O
ye	O
.	O
Rain	O
that	O
had	O
fallen	O
was	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Grounds	O
&	O
View	O
some	O
other	O
time	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
is	O
more	O
favorable	O
--	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
through	O
ye	O
mist	O
was	O
charming	O
.	O
We	O
dined	O
at	O
4	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Saloon	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
dinner	O
&	O
attendants	O
suitable	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
regretted	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
absence	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
his	O
company	O
&	O
conversation	O
was	O
were	O
only	O
wanting	O
.	O
little	O
William	B-pers
had	O
written	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
his	O
Great	O
Uncle	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
we	O
read	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
style	O
was	O
easy	O
&	O
flowing	O
ye	O
.	O
language	O
perfectly	O
good	O
--	O
no	O
one	O
wd	O
.	O
imagine	O
this	O
letter	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
very	O
astonishing	O
abilities	O
&	O
quickneſs	O
of	O
comprehension	O
equally	O
surprising	O
for	O
his	O
age	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
(	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
forget	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
3	O
d	O
Son	O
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
--	O
little	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
day	O
was	O
3	O
Years	O
complete	O
)	O
we	O
drank	O
his	O
health	O
)	O
with	O
playing	O
at	O
what	O
is	O
is	O
like	O
.	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
more	O
ready	O
than	O
William	B-pers
with	O
answers	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
quit	O
ye	O
.	O
Sal	O
l	O
oon	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
soon	O
had	O
our	O
tea	O
&	O
Coffee	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
to	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
works	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
3	O
beautiful	O
aprons	O
she	O
was	O
About	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
remarkably	O
nice	O
worker	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
Musician	O
for	O
she	O
not	O
only	O
plays	O
in	O
a	O
Masterly	O
manner	O
but	O
is	O
a	O
composer	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
came	O
in	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
.	O
we	O
paid	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Compts	O
.	O
he	O
deserved	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
excellent	O
Sermon	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
encomiums	O
modestly	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
friendly	O
&	O
polite	O
reception	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Sisters	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
still	O
bear	O
ye	O
.	O
title	O
of	O
Miſs	O
Murrays	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
an	O
age	O
to	O
claim	O
that	O
of	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
respectable	O
characters	O
--	O
sensible	O
easy	O
&	O
attentive	O
in	O
their	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
extremely	O
chearful	O
&	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
airs	O
,	O
no	O
affection	O
,	O
their	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
dreſs	O
properly	O
correspond	O
to	O
their	O
age	O
&	O
situation	O
in	O
life	O
.	O
they	O
very	O
kindly	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
soon	O
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
In	O
coming	O
home	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
his	O
Sisters	O
&	O
spoke	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
proved	O
his	O
esteem	O
&	O
affection	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
we	O
spoke	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
we	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
only	O
little	O
George	B-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
vain	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Idea	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
entertain	O
'd	O
&	O
kept	O
his	O
Mamma	O
company	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
babe	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
hitherto	O
been	O
Sir	B-pers
.	I-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
Col	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
in	O
Our	O
Uncle	O
said	O
it	O
made	O
him	O
appear	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
surrounded	O
with	O
such	O
well	O
grown	O
Nephews	O
&	O
Nieces	O
&	O
what	O
was	O
more	O
mortifying	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Great	O
Uncle	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
had	O
prevented	O
his	O
staying	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
--	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Conway	I-pers
s	O
&	O
return	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Court	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
he	O
enqui	O
r	O
ed	O
to	O
whom	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
change	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
said	O
very	O
handsome	O
things	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
warm	O
&	O
friendly	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
told	O
his	O
R	O
:	O
H	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
report	O
was	O
true	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
&	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
approved	O
my	O
choice	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
event	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
take	O
place	O
very	O
soon	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
conversing	O
on	O
different	O
topic	O
s	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
Coach	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
left	O
her	O
addreſs	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Devonshire	B-place
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
Dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
infinitely	O
better	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
almost	O
gone	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
S	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
Miſs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
seems	O
well	O
temper	O
'd	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
n	O
useful	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
understanding	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
&	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
sent	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Kitty	B-pers
She	O
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Poetic	O
humour	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
repeating	O
Paſsages	O
from	O
Milton	B-pers
Pope	B-pers
&	O
c	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
was	O
vastly	O
delighted	O
for	O
she	O
listened	O
to	O
our	O
fine	O
declamation	O
with	O
seeming	O
pain	O
pleasure	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
&	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
Monday	O
23	O
d	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
finished	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
sent	O
both	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
little	O
note	O
written	O
by	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
my	O
Cold	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
wrote	O
her	O
an	O
answer	O
--	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
was	O
wet	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
Nurse	O
myself	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Niece	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
so	O
far	O
I	O
have	O
gain	O
'd	O
my	O
point	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Sister	O
Dow.g	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
was	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
to	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
call	O
&	O
inform	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
engagement	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
this	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
doing	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
me	O
entering	O
into	O
a	O
detail	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
say	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
proper	O
for	O
my	O
not	O
having	O
sent	O
her	O
an	O
earlier	O
information	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
(	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bristol	O
s	O
Widow	O
came	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
people	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Palace	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
&	O
came	O
from	O
Kew	B-place
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
aſsure	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
cordial	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
many	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
things	O
she	O
said	O
--	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
her	O
villa	O
&	O
also	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
impatient	O
to	O
be	O
introduced	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
&	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Town	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sudden	O
&	O
unexpected	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
in	O
Law	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
affecting	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
left	O
3	O
Young	O
Children	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Eldest	O
6	O
ye	O
.	O
Youngest	O
only	O
6	O
Months	O
old	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Friday	O
&	O
dead	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Monday	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
.ye	O
.	O
prime	O
of	O
life	O
only	O
28	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
--	O
beloved	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
Child	O
of	O
a	O
Mother	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Widow	O
only	O
6	O
Months	O
--	O
&	O
poſseſsing	O
every	O
advantage	O
of	O
fortune	O
&	O
circumstance	O
to	O
render	O
this	O
World	O
most	O
agreeable	O
.	O
When	O
good	O
Mrs.	B-pers
N	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
idle	O
as	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
quite	O
inflamed	O
with	O
my	O
Cold	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
old	O
Friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
--	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
&	O
she	O
tho	O
'	O
wth	O
..	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
difficulty	O
to	O
herself	O
wrote	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
This	O
mark	O
of	O
her	O
affection	O
was	O
quite	O
touching	O
--	O
the	O
characters	O
were	O
hardly	O
legible	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
they	O
convey	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
tenderest	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
happineſs	O
.	O
what	O
a	O
large	O
debt	O
of	O
gratitude	O
have	O
I	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
so	O
many	O
kind	O
&	O
tender	O
friends	O
--	O
O	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
prove	O
worthy	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
goodneſs	O
towards	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
afternoon	O
--	O
I	O
employed	O
myself	O
in	O
winding	O
silk	O
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
word	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
was	O
better	O
&	O
sent	O
me	O
4	O
2	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
enclosed	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
the	O
one	O
was	O
from	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
from	O
Tunbridge	B-place
in	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
enclosed	O
one	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
contain	O
'd	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
happineſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
from	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
it	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
one	O
for	O
it	O
conveyed	O
every	O
tender	O
sentiment	O
of	O
real	O
affection	O
&	O
a	O
charming	O
character	O
of	O
his	O
Dr	O
Father	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
also	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
frm	O
..	O
him	O
that	O
my	O
letter	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
10	O
was	O
come	O
safe	O
to	O
hand	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
D	B-pers
s	O
——	B-pers
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
related	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
beyond	O
expression	O
,	O
made	O
happy	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
aſsurance	O
of	O
his	O
regard	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
answer	O
it	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
--	O
after	O
spending	O
a	O
delightful	O
quiet	O
Eveg	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
24	O
August	O
1784	O
Br	O
with	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
's	O
Father	O
's	O
character	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
nothing	O
left	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
--	O
My	O
Morning	O
was	O
spent	O
very	O
Idly	O
for	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
so	O
affected	O
wth-	O
my	O
Cold	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
painful	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
write	O
or	O
work	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
better	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
this	O
dear	O
Woman	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
again	O
--	O
the	O
Morng	O
.	O
was	O
wet	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
to	O
her	O
Chair	O
hire	O
is	O
expensive	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
prudent	O
.	O
there	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Moor	O
Game	O
from	O
Derbyshire	B-place
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
oblige	O
some	O
one	O
of	O
friends	O
by	O
sending	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
insisted	O
that	O
Bell	B-pers
and	O
She	O
should	O
keep	O
it	O
ye	O
.	O
dispute	O
remain	O
'd	O
undecided	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Portland	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
of	O
Henry	O
Murray	O
's	O
christening	O
is	O
quoted	O
at	O
length	O
in	O
Anson	O
&	O
Anson	O
(	O
1925	O
:	O
246-8	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shewn	O
into	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
room	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wch	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
recd	O
enclosed	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
were	O
aſsembled	O
--	O
The	O
Deep	O
Mourning	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
was	O
thrown	O
aside	O
for	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
every	O
one	O
look	O
'd	O
gay	O
&	O
smart	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
2	O
Sisters	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
(	O
his	O
daughter	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
Brother	O
Coll	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
our	O
Cousins	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Col	B-pers
..	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Langlois	I-pers
--	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
--	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
man	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Master	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
at	O
4	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
the	O
dinner	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Desert	O
ye	O
.	O
Wines	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
attendants	O
all	O
in	O
style	O
&	O
proper	O
.	O
the	O
conversation	O
easy	O
&	O
cheerful	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
sat	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
head	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
&	O
acquitted	O
herself	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
good	O
grace	O
.	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
made	O
their	O
appearance	O
at	O
Desert	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
Coffee	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dining	O
Room	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
as	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
Infant	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
becoming	O
Manner	O
&	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
look	O
so	O
beautiful	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
seated	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Chair	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
covered	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
white	O
Drapery	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
large	O
flounces	O
of	O
fine	O
Lace	O
&	O
Muslin	O
--	O
her	O
feet	O
were	O
raised	O
upon	O
a	O
low	O
Stool	O
chair	O
&	O
.	O
were	O
hid	O
by	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Covering	O
of	O
Chintz	O
work	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Gold	O
&	O
gold	O
fringes	O
wch	O
.	O
cover	O
'd	O
her	O
lap	O
&	O
fell	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
back	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chair	O
--	O
&	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
middle	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
was	O
plased	O
a	O
table	O
Cover	O
'd	O
magnificently	O
wth	O
.	O
Crimson	O
Velvet	O
&	O
Cloth	O
of	O
Gold	O
a	O
Large	O
Cushion	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
to	O
rest	O
upon	O
fring	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
.	O
A	O
Gold	O
Cup	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
water	O
&	O
dish	O
of	O
an	O
elegant	O
form	O
'd	O
&	O
finely	O
wrought	O
were	O
also	O
placed	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
(	O
these	O
she	O
had	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Ambaſsadreſs	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
--	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
was	O
born	O
there	O
)	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
Our	O
Aunt	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
Godmother	O
--	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
compts	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
Niece	O
&	O
Great	O
Nephew	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
The	O
folding	O
Doors	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Inner	O
drawing	O
room	O
were	O
thrown	O
open	O
&	O
display	O
'd	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
Upper	O
Servants	O
Men	O
&	O
Women	O
in	O
their	O
best	O
attire	O
--	O
the	O
Clerk	O
came	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
began	O
the	O
ceremony	O
--	O
we	O
placed	O
ourselves	O
in	O
two	O
Rows	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
little	O
boys	O
were	O
present	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Nurse	O
stood	O
next	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Dry	O
Nurse	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
took	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
an	O
affectionate	O
Grace	O
of	O
manner	O
.	O
the	O
whole	O
scene	O
was	O
solemn	O
&	O
pleasingly	O
affecting	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
stood	O
for	O
his	O
Cousin	O
Sir	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lindsay	I-pers
&	O
Coll	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
for	O
his	O
Youngest	O
Brother	O
Archibald	B-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
was	O
named	O
Henry	O
.	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
ceremony	O
was	O
over	O
&	O
little	O
Henry	B-pers
had	O
received	O
a	O
kiſs	O
from	O
every	O
one	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
deserved	O
for	O
his	O
charming	O
behaviour	O
having	O
been	O
as	O
quiet	O
as	O
a	O
lamb	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
came	O
round	O
with	O
her	O
Caudle	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
refuse	O
though	O
we	O
had	O
just	O
dined	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
watchful	O
eye	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
each	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Xtning	O
Cake	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Groom	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chambers	O
had	O
brought	O
round	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
innocent	O
folly	O
&	O
superstition	O
of	O
these	O
Nurses	O
is	O
highly	O
entertaining	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
tea	O
as	O
the	O
3	O
Miſs	O
M——y	O
s	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
were	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Kenwood	O
William	B-pers
was	O
indulged	O
wth	O
.	O
staying	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
--	O
--	O
they	O
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
staid	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Uncle	O
F	B-pers
:	I-pers
yesterday	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
hear	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
united	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
high	O
an	O
opinion	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
merit	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
téte	O
á	O
têtes	O
--	O
She	O
with	O
her	O
Son	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
St	I-pers
:	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
so	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
converse	O
with	O
my	O
agreeable	O
Cousin	O
Coll	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
he	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
franks	O
--	O
dated	O
--	O
he	O
sets	O
out	O
for	O
Scotland	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
Meſsages	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Cathcarts	O
Atholls	O
Grahams	O
--	O
Murrays	O
&	O
Napiers	O
.	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
also	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
into	O
to	O
Nottinghamshire	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
take	O
any	O
Meſsage	O
or	O
Parcel	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
unhappy	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
.	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
½	O
hour	O
Coll	B-pers
..	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
L——	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
William	B-pers
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
&	O
I	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
wth	O
.	O
making	O
out	O
Puzzles	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
Coach	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Dearest	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
wonted	O
smiles	O
--	O
I	O
scribbled	O
a	O
few	O
limes	O
&	O
sent	O
a	O
packet	O
of	O
Diary	O
to	O
my	O
D	B-pers
:	I-pers
it	O
was	O
in	O
time	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell	O
man	O
I	O
Chatted	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
then	O
we	O
retired	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
began	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
finish	O
'd	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Col.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
sent	O
meſsages	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
Scotland	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
finishd	O
I	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Packet	O
to	O
Grosvenor	O
Place	O
--	O
before	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
11	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
prevented	O
going	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
wth	O
.	O
friendly	O
attention	O
sent	O
me	O
another	O
frank	O
unask	O
'd	O
for	O
Derbyshire	O
dated	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
till	O
then	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
It	O
pour	O
'd	O
torrents	O
of	O
rain	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
&	O
sent	O
a	O
continuance	O
of	O
Diary	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
last	O
letter	O
&	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
Richard	B-pers
took	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
herself	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Cold	O
still	O
lay	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
&	O
affected	O
my	O
eyes	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
painful	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
much	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
little	O
Henry	B-pers
very	O
well	O
&	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
worse	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
&	O
fatigue	O
of	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
foreigners	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Ralf	I-pers
Payne	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
drawing	O
room	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
ventured	O
down	O
stairs	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
comfortable	O
dumb	O
waiters	O
&	O
no	O
attendants	O
but	O
when	O
rung	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
change	O
ye	O
.	O
dishes	O
--	O
Our	O
Uncles	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
William	B-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
were	O
our	O
topics	O
--	O
we	O
both	O
spoke	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
with	O
that	O
affection	O
we	O
felt	O
&	O
she	O
deserved	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
at	O
Desert	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
(	O
Wm-	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Ken-Wood	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
)	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
long	O
at	O
table	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
impatient	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
her	O
lovely	O
Babe	O
She	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
Nurse	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
judicious	O
&	O
tender	O
Mother	O
;	O
playing	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
conversation	O
chiefly	O
relative	O
to	O
our	O
Relations	O
&	O
my	O
future	O
prospect	O
of	O
happineſs	O
in	O
a	O
Union	O
of	O
mutual	O
affection	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
our	O
time	O
till	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
came	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
abt	O
.	O
9.	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
entertain	O
'd	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
frie	O
disputes	O
(	O
friendly	O
ones	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
she	O
sent	O
by	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
who	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Margate	B-place
to	O
day	O
.	O
Thursday	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Thursday	O
Br	O
with	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
May	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Dow.g	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
they	O
were	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
my	O
Aunt	O
left	O
word	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
Ham	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
wth	O
whom	O
I	O
continued	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Morng	O
.	O
my	O
Cold	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
but	O
paste	O
Paper	O
on	O
Boxes	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
read	O
or	O
write	O
or	O
work	O
or	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
anxious	O
abt	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
well	O
enough	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
heard	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
&	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bulstrode	O
.	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
the	O
whole	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
wrote	O
&	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
--	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
Boxes	O
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Cooke	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Harpsicord	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
meſsage	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
gracious	O
Answer	O
&	O
return	O
'd	O
some	O
Books	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
me	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
came	O
&	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
House	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
was	O
come	O
very	O
ill	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
was	O
at	O
her	O
Brother	O
s	O
House	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Kings	O
Mewse	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Worcester	B-place
where	O
he	O
was	O
quarterd	O
for	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
.	O
after	O
spending	O
a	O
comfortable	O
quiet	O
day	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Friday	O
27	O
th	O
August	O
1784	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
myself	O
so	O
indifferent	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
to	O
excuse	O
my	O
dining	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
Brother	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
2	O
d	O
Husband	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
Coll	B-pers
..	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
I	O
also	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
tell	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
yt	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
till	O
12	O
--	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
amuse	O
myself	O
in	O
making	O
Boxes	O
&	O
winding	O
silk	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Apothecary	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
to	O
oblige	O
d	O
her	O
I	O
consulted	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
degree	O
of	O
fever	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
myself	O
quiet	O
&	O
orderd	O
me	O
some	O
draughts	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
he	O
seems	O
much	O
inclined	O
to	O
like	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
worthy	O
father	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
escape	O
a	O
persecution	O
by	O
not	O
dining	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
impatient	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
a	O
1000	O
questions	O
relative	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Worcester	B-place
wch	O
.	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
answer	O
&	O
promised	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
I	O
sat	O
with	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
&	O
we	O
.	O
continued	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Long	O
Parlour	O
I	O
with	O
my	O
paper	O
,	O
paste	O
.	O
&	O
boxes	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
--	O
they	O
wth	O
.	O
their	O
works	O
&	O
book	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
from	O
Horton	B-place
.	O
A	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
of	O
enquiry	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
herself	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng-	O
&	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
sat	O
10	O
minutes	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
tenderly	O
anxious	O
abt	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
an	O
excuse	O
for	O
not	O
coming	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
prevented	O
by	O
busineſs	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
&	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
kind	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
made	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
a	O
leſson	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
S——	I-pers
left	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
little	O
Supper	O
&	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
in	O
Cook	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
--	O
she	O
then	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
of	O
Scarlatti	B-pers
s	O
After	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
read	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
s	O
celebrated	O
Speeches	O
wch	O
..	O
insensibly	O
led	O
us	O
on	O
till	O
12	O
oClock	O
Saturday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
At	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
..	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
early	O
&	O
kind	O
Meſsages	O
of	O
enquiry	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
make	O
enquires	O
after	O
me	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
answer	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
writing	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
fever	O
--	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
eat	O
any	O
meat	O
or	O
drink	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
by	O
a	O
Visit	O
from	O
my	O
friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
he	O
arrived	O
in	O
Town	B-place
frm	O
.	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
Yesterday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
come	O
on	O
Busineſs	O
&	O
will	O
stay	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
he	O
aſsured	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
perfectly	O
happy	O
since	O
his	O
marriage	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
.	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
now	O
6	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
was	O
well	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
all	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
--	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
then	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
came	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
interrupt	O
á	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
&	O
away	O
she	O
flew	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
20	O
minutes	O
past	O
4	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
wch	O
.	O
sent	O
him	O
away	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
conversation	O
was	O
my	O
praises	O
--	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
turn	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
to	O
other	O
subjects	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
hear	O
his	O
opinion	O
--	O
of	O
my	O
Character	O
my	O
sentiments	O
--	O
today	O
he	O
also	O
favord	O
favoured	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
remarks	O
on	O
my	O
personal	O
attractions	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
praise	O
of	O
my	O
beauty	O
he	O
contented	O
himself	O
with	O
declaring	O
that	O
to	O
his	O
taste	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
every	O
charm	O
though	O
certainly	O
a	O
plain	O
Woman	O
--	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
said	O
&	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
expreſsing	O
himself	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
furnished	O
Mr.	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
an	O
excellent	O
comic	O
extravagant	O
Lover-like	O
speeches	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
sat	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
at	O
7	O
when	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
indisposed	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
join	O
much	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
amused	O
me	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Prints	O
of	O
Cooke	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
to	O
look	O
--	O
over	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
conversed	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
talk	O
over	O
--	O
Scotch	O
Politics	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
N——	I-pers
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
his	O
Cousin	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
My	O
U	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
abt	O
..	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
enquiries	O
made	O
after	O
me	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Grevilles	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
were	O
there	O
--	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
chearful	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
our	O
Youthful	O
days	O
&	O
the	O
innocent	O
pranks	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
,	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
me	O
by	O
this	O
post	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
I	O
dictated	O
Sunday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Night	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
some	O
,	O
&	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
hers	O
.	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
chatted	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Coll	B-pers
..	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
up	O
&	O
not	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
detain	O
him	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
word	O
I	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
soon	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
Dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charming	O
well	O
.	O
She	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
kindest	O
solicitude	O
abt-	O
me	O
gave	O
me	O
many	O
strict	O
charges	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
myself	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
not	O
on	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
now	O
only	O
accountable	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
but	O
to	O
My	O
D——son	B-pers
&	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
double	O
duty	O
of	O
affection	O
to	O
induce	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
attentive	O
to	O
my	O
Health	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
&	O
paid	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
they	O
both	O
agreed	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
kind	O
lectures	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
was	O
married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
yesterday	O
Morng	O
--	O
yt	O
.	O
ye	O
wedding	O
was	O
private	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
he	O
,	O
aided	O
&	O
abbeted	O
,	O
by	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
found	O
fault	O
&	O
preach	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
sitting	O
up	O
late	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
write	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
nervous	O
fever	O
&	O
after	O
feeling	O
my	O
pulse	O
enquired	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
agitate	O
&	O
h	O
u	O
rry	O
my	O
spirits	O
or	O
give	O
me	O
uneasineſs	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
great	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
Skill	O
.	O
for	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
cause	O
of	O
uneasineſs	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
my	O
complaint	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
on	O
by	O
a	O
h	O
u	O
rry	O
of	O
spirits	O
.	O
&	O
having	O
had	O
my	O
Mind	O
agitated	O
--	O
So	O
poor	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
has	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
herself	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
out	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
was	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
--	O
she	O
saw	O
little	O
Henry	B-pers
&	O
George	B-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
.	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
till	O
3	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Cook	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
hours	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
.	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Affection	O
of	O
a	O
fond	O
Mother	O
--	O
I	O
congratulated	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
Grandaughter	O
Lady	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
she	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
to	O
fix	O
my	O
time	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
sooner	O
I	O
came	O
&	O
the	O
longer	O
I	O
staid	O
ye	O
.	O
happier	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
them	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
fact	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
them	O
her	O
from	O
next	O
Week	O
till	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
London	B-place
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
Decbr	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
having	O
any	O
scruples	O
abt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
she	O
wd	O
.	O
invite	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Bulstrode	O
&	O
as	O
her	O
Chaise	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
commands	O
--	O
I	O
might	O
when	O
I	O
chose	O
come	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
&	O
also	O
if	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
came	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
&	O
be	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
her	O
Grace	O
to	O
comply	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
requests	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
an	O
obligation	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Harewood	B-place
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
--	O
to	O
each	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
ten	O
Days	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
&	O
would	O
stay	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
at	O
Margate	B-place
&	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
unfortunate	O
&	O
unhappy	O
circumstance	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Valet	O
de	O
Chambres	O
having	O
gone	O
raving	O
mad	O
--	O
this	O
poor	O
Man	O
frm	O
.	O
wht	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
learn	O
lost	O
his	O
senses	O
upon	O
Receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
(	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Native	O
)	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
infidelity	O
of	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
he	O
loved	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
me	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
interesting	O
letters	O
from	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
lay	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Bed	O
&	O
had	O
½	O
an	O
hours	O
sleep	O
wch	O
.	O
refreshed	O
&	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
of	O
enquiry	O
.	O
I	O
stole	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
scribbling	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
&	O
reading	O
a	O
little	O
as	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
busy	O
not	O
wth.-	O
me	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Fr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
accompanied	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
who	O
had	O
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
charitable	O
Visit	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
confined	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
my	O
Brother	O
began	O
to	O
scold	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
fancied	O
frm	O
.	O
seeing	O
Pens	O
Ink	O
&	O
Books	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
e	O
ing	O
my	O
Eyes	O
he	O
threatnen	O
'd	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Derbyshire	B-place
&	O
give	O
a	O
few	O
instructions	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
&	O
above	O
all	O
things	O
never	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
own	O
way	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
chearful	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Cousin	O
my	O
two	O
Cases	O
of	O
Bells	O
Ed	O
:	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
english	O
Poets	O
to	O
sort	O
--	O
this	O
employ	O
'd	O
us	O
all	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
letters	O
Monday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
I	O
felt	O
quite	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
with	O
dear	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
she	O
only	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Farnborough	B-place
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
expected	O
--	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
was	O
there	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
fortnight	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
at	O
Sandleford	O
our	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
there	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
had	O
spoke	O
handsomely	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
kind	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
made	O
me	O
write	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
invite	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
next	O
Sunday	O
&	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
only	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
many	O
questions	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
grateful	O
Creature	O
(	O
a	O
Page	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
)	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
meſsage	O
of	O
enquiry	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
..	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
.	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
in	O
settling	O
my	O
Work	O
drawer	O
--	O
Visits	O
from	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
without	O
fever	O
--	O
allowed	O
me	O
to	O
eat	O
meat	O
--	O
but	O
charged	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
write	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
affect	O
not	O
only	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
Nerves	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
prevented	O
my	O
sleeping	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
had	O
been	O
so	O
kindly	O
illnatured	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
formal	O
complaint	O
against	O
my	O
useing	O
my	O
Eyes	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
ought	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
leſsons	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
&	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
enclosed	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
also	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
continued	O
below	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
allowed	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
cards	O
of	O
Congratulation	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
--	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Thynnes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
c	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
took	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
to	O
desire	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
invitation	O
&	O
one	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sent	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
long	O
kind	O
Note	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Ducheſs	O
--	O
At	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
upstairs	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
tea	O
I	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
join	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
below	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
tea	O
things	O
was	O
were	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
table	O
.	O
he	O
readily	O
consented	O
to	O
pay	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
Converzatione	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
arrivd	O
from	O
Windor	B-place
where	O
he	O
went	O
Yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
therefore	O
had	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
Notes	O
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
&	O
that	O
he	O
wld	O
.	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
mistake	O
of	O
his	O
Servt	O
.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
yesterday	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lind	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Terrace	O
&	O
was	O
invited	O
by	O
their	O
Majesties	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
inner	O
Room	O
2	O
hours	O
&	O
½	O
(	O
standing	O
)	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Rooms	O
--	O
Uncover	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Chairs	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
s	O
work	O
Onyx	O
Tables	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
his	O
account	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
formal	O
dulneſs	O
reign	O
'd	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
--	O
viz	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
pſa-	O
seated	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
only	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
--	O
it	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
outward	O
room	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
Music	O
was	O
--	O
were	O
Lord	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Lt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Manners	O
(	O
ye	O
Equerry	O
in	O
waiting	O
)	O
.	O
&	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Mountagu	I-pers
.	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
he	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Castle	O
improvements	O
or	O
rather	O
non-improvements	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
My	O
Uncle	O
mention	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——son	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
hint	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
was	O
rather	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
..	O
not	O
approve	O
my	O
choice	O
--	O
He	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
aſsure	O
him	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
contrary	O
&	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
mistaken	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
&	O
said	O
many	O
things	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
advantages	O
of	O
travelling	O
&	O
nothing	O
opened	O
ye	O
.	O
mind	O
more	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
beyond	O
conception	O
how	O
it	O
furnished	O
ideas	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
natural	O
taste	O
&	O
observation	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
we	O
shoud	O
be	O
gratified	O
wth	O
..	O
seeing	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
productions	O
of	O
Art	O
in	O
Italy	B-place
&	O
yt	O
.	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
answer	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
detail	O
of	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
affairs	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
&	O
c	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
him	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
friend	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chevalier	I-pers
Sagramoso	I-pers
he	O
knows	O
him	O
intimately	O
&	O
esteems	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
lives	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
his	O
Society	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
of	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
one	O
hanging	O
to	O
his	O
button	O
hole	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
enclosed	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
these	O
words	O
“	O
the	O
reward	O
of	O
industry	O
”	O
--	O
written	O
by	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
own	O
hand	O
.	O
this	O
arose	O
frm	O
.	O
my	O
saying	O
in	O
just	O
one	O
day	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
was	O
busy	O
in	O
arranging	O
her	O
books	O
&	O
making	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
ym	O
.	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
settling	O
her	O
Prints	O
China	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
badge	O
of	O
honor	O
to	O
distinguish	O
us	O
as	O
her	O
favorites	O
in	O
being	O
favor	O
'd	O
with	O
doing	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
employ	O
others	O
in	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
order	O
was	O
an	O
elegant	O
small	O
locket	O
of	O
her	O
hair	O
on	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
hanging	O
to	O
a	O
Garter	O
blue	O
Ribbon	O
--	O
wth	O
.	O
this	O
Motto	O
“	O
win	O
it	O
&	O
wear	O
it	O
”	O
M	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
aged	O
84	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
delighted	O
wth	O
.	O
this	O
Dear	O
Woman	O
s	O
charming	O
vivacity	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
honor	O
we	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
.	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
as	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
use	O
my	O
Eyes	O
by	O
Candlelight	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Tuesday	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
¼	O
before	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
wth	O
..	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
(	O
to	O
our	O
surprise	O
at	O
9	O
as	O
she	O
seldom	O
come	O
s	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
before	O
we	O
have	O
finish	O
'd	O
)	O
Recd	O
.	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
Cards	O
of	O
Congratulation	O
I	O
sent	O
yesterday	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	O
T	O
's	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Ay	O
--	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
--	O
at	O
11	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
at	O
12	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
without	O
fever	O
&	O
c	O
my	O
Eyes	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
Employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
without	O
reading	O
writing	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
pay	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
visits	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
Meſsages	O
of	O
enquiry	O
from	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Murrays	O
--	O
&	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
set	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
friend	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
for	O
Bullstrode	O
She	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
large	O
book	O
of	O
loose	O
Prints	O
to	O
arrange	O
&	O
paste	O
in	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
dined	O
wth	O
..	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
in	O
knotting	O
&	O
making	O
fringe	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
7	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
came	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
come	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
invited	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
to	O
come	O
upstairs	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
--	O
talking	O
&	O
looking	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Prints	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
time	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
my	O
Uncle	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
Dr	O
:	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
ague	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
pain	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
something	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
Prints	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
1	O
st	O
:	O
Septr	O
.	O
1784	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
felt	O
quite	O
well	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
almost	O
recovered	O
of	O
the	O
inflammation	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
&	O
free	O
from	O
pain	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
before	O
10	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
diſsertation	O
on	O
Charity	O
towards	O
Mankind	O
&	O
our	O
Neighbours	O
we	O
consider	O
'd	O
it	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
Moral	O
&	O
religious	O
sense	O
.	O
at	O
11	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
had	O
been	O
.	O
he	O
aſsured	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
soon	O
conquer	O
this	O
obstinate	O
Ague	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
continue	O
ye	O
.	O
Bark	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
myself	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
fever	O
was	O
quite	O
gone	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
need	O
only	O
take	O
two	O
more	O
draughts	O
&	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
inflammation	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
was	O
nearly	O
gone	O
.	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
perfectly	O
so	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
them	O
too	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
anxious	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
well	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
indulged	O
myself	O
in	O
my	O
most	O
favorite	O
amusement	O
of	O
reading	O
&	O
c	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
she	O
says	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
you	O
are	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
how	O
to	O
contrive	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
again	O
before	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Wandworth	O
Hill	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
Friday	O
To	O
day	O
we	O
dine	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Visits	O
therefore	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
send	O
to	O
You	O
any	O
time	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
our	O
Horses	O
will	O
all	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
to	O
comfort	O
me	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
promise	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
You	O
are	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
disengaged	O
we	O
expect	O
no	O
Company	O
unleſs	O
we	O
can	O
tempt	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
stay	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
one	O
night	O
Adieu	O
let	O
me	O
how	O
You	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
Henry	B-pers
thrives	O
&	O
improves	O
daily	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
believe	O
goes	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
W——	O
Hill	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
be	O
hurry	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
ready	O
for	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
having	O
literally	O
done	O
nothing	O
but	O
nurse	O
Henry	B-pers
since	O
I	O
saw	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
eyes	O
off	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
makes	O
me	O
quite	O
idle	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
answer	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Evg	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
doing	O
triffling	O
things	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
affect	O
my	O
Eyes	O
--	O
Dr	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
every	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
spy	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
together	O
--	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
till	O
7	O
--	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
(	O
who	O
came	O
frm	O
.	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
to	O
day	O
to	O
attend	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
tomorrow	O
)	O
came	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
friendly	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
till	O
9	O
oClock	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
dined	O
at	O
Courteenhall	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
future	O
establishment	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
anxious	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Mr.	B-pers
D'son	I-pers
&	O
very	O
solicituous	O
to	O
be	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
every	O
particular	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
My	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
said	O
she	O
thought	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
ever	O
had	O
a	O
chance	O
of	O
happineſs	O
in	O
the	O
married	O
State	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
was	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
represented	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
abt	O
:	O
ye	O
:	O
Nor——tonshire	O
folks	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Wakes	O
Thursbys	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
over	O
our	O
Man	O
Servt	O
.	O
home	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
Chair	O
as	O
hers	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
10	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
send	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
me	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
scolded	O
but	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
long	O
Note	O
to	O
say	O
answer	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Portland	O
place	O
as	O
I	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
there	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
by	O
this	O
Post	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
came	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Room	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
reproved	O
him	O
for	O
coming	O
so	O
late	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
merit	O
of	O
coming	O
at	O
all	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
,	O
left	O
agreeable	O
people	O
&	O
had	O
refused	O
to	O
join	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Supper	O
party	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
quarrelling	O
we	O
sat	O
comfortable	O
down	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
confidential	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
--	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
detail	O
of	O
this	O
his	O
present	O
situation	O
--	O
his	O
opinion	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
affairs	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
pleasing	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
poſseſsed	O
his	O
confidence	O
as	O
entire	O
as	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
he	O
&	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
will	O
be	O
good	O
friends	O
--	O
for	O
though	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
affection	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
N——	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
would	O
have	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
accept	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Husband	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
had	O
for	O
him	O
ye	O
.	O
Affection	O
of	O
a	O
Sister	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
treated	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
favorite	O
one	O
--	O
every	O
secret	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
has	O
been	O
open	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
worthy	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
's	O
friendship	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
another	O
kind	O
note	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
&	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
D——shire	B-place
.	O
I	O
cd-	O
only	O
look	O
over	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
hastily	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Brother	O
was	O
so	O
provoking	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
..	O
not	O
leave	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
comfort	O
.	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
never	O
answers	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
humour	O
I	O
was	O
oblige	O
d	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
letter	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
&	O
listen	O
to	O
him	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
merit	O
of	O
leaving	O
me	O
to	O
enjoy	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
had	O
been	O
long	O
gone	O
to	O
theirs	O
,	O
after	O
reading	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
letter	O
over	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
&	O
recommending	O
him	O
&	O
myself	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
divine	O
Protection	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
Thursday	O
2	O
d	O
..	O
Septr	O
..	O
1784	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
join	O
'd	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
great	O
pleasure	O
by	O
communicating	O
to	O
her	O
what	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
of	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
of	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
our	O
whole	O
converse	O
was	O
relative	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
in	O
sett	O
sorting	O
&	O
pasting	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
book	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Prints	O
--	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
12	O
--	O
he	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
expected	O
People	O
on	O
Busineſ	O
s	O
&	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
King	B-pers
s	O
Levée	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
--	O
repeated	O
to	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
applaud	O
ed	O
my	O
Conduct	O
&	O
approved	O
of	O
my	O
D——son	B-pers
that	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
much	O
fairer	O
chance	O
of	O
happineſs	O
than	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
married	O
from	O
ambitious	O
or	O
interested	O
motives	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
extremely	O
&	O
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
China	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
the	O
family	O
Arms	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
&	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
he	O
said	O
he	O
supposed	O
ye	O
.	O
Service	O
was	O
not	O
complete	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
accept	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
useful	O
on	O
first	O
going	O
to	O
housekeeping	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
related	O
to	O
me	O
some	O
private	O
conversation	O
he	O
had	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
yesterday	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Levée	O
--	O
yt	O
.	O
his	O
M	O
:	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
wth	O
.	O
old	O
accustom̄	O
'd	O
confidence	O
.	O
said	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Stormonts	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
told	O
my	O
Uncle	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
served	O
as	O
when	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
in	O
office	O
&	O
never	O
had	O
had	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Carmarthen	I-pers
s	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
Visits	O
from	O
Dr	O
:	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
she	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
left	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
wth	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
--	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
to	O
paſs	O
ye	O
.	O
Night	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Solitary	O
Meal	O
--	O
Old	O
Ceasar	O
took	O
compaſsion	O
on	O
me	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
my	O
Side	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
time	O
--	O
Reading	O
over	O
my	O
D——	B-pers
letters	O
&	O
finishing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
book	O
of	O
Prints	O
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
friendly	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
this	O
Visit	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
both	O
going	O
&	O
coming	O
&	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
fatigue	O
wth	O
.	O
&	O
standing	O
through	O
a	O
long	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
at	O
Court	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
thought	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
this	O
however	O
was	O
not	O
ye	O
.	O
Case	O
as	O
they	O
pain	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
her	O
Brother	O
Sister	O
&	O
herself	O
had	O
thoughts	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Italy	B-place
next	O
Septr	O
.	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
leave	O
of	O
Absence	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
they	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Year	O
Abroad	O
--	O
see	O
every	O
thing	O
worth	O
Observation	O
en	O
Chemin	O
faisant	O
&	O
stay	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
Rome	B-place
--	O
she	O
said	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
enjoy	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
be	O
together	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
Rome	B-place
.	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
pleasure	O
into	O
this	O
Scheme	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
sometimes	O
pleasant	O
to	O
endulge	O
Airy	O
Visions	O
--	O
My	O
Friend	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
she	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
made	O
Cases	O
for	O
my	O
loose	O
Manuscripts	O
--	O
the	O
Servts	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
inform	O
us	O
an	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
we	O
ran	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
St	O
.	O
Door	O
&	O
saw	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
wch	O
.	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
pretty	O
Meteor	O
floating	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
Earth	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
3	O
Shilling	O
ones	O
let	O
off	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
End	O
of	O
our	O
Street	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
dozens	O
of	O
them	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1784	O
.	O
Friday	O
--	O
--	O
had	O
my	O
Hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
by	O
½	O
past	O
8.	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
came	O
before	O
10	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
upstairs	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
friendly	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Kew	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
5	O
Weeks	O
from	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
had	O
been	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Whi	I-place
Wight	I-place
to	O
see	O
his	O
Parents	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
fortnight	O
wth	O
..	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
at	O
Hampton	B-place
.	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Sea	O
Coast	O
,	O
30	O
Miles	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
I.	B-place
of	I-place
W	I-place
.	I-place
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
cheerful	O
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
doatingly	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
that	O
he	O
was	O
happier	O
than	O
he	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
15	O
,	O
or	O
1600	O
£	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
:	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
had	O
full	O
30000£	O
for	O
her	O
fortune	O
.	O
he	O
proposes	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Study	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Law	O
,	O
to	O
wch	O
.	O
profeſsion	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
it	O
was	O
proper	O
for	O
every	O
Man	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
pursuit	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
congratulated	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
&	O
c	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
last	O
night	O
he	O
saw	O
Monr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Guiffardierre	I-pers
--	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
reading	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
that	O
Eveg	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
“	O
I	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
that	O
her	O
friends	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
proper	O
&	O
prudent	O
Match	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
”	O
--	O
how	O
strange	O
that	O
her	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
should	O
talk	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
only	O
.	O
“	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
(	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
s	O
Govenor	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
regret	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
--	O
as	O
every	O
person	O
who	O
knew	O
me	O
said	O
kind	O
things	O
&	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
their	O
wishes	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
happy	O
--	O
after	O
this	O
topic	O
was	O
discuſs	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
related	O
some	O
curious	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
&	O
an	O
entertaining	O
quarrel	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
--	O
some	O
things	O
he	O
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
his	O
wanting	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
--	O
a	O
Visit	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
to	O
Windsor	B-place
last	O
week	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
long	O
closetted	O
wth	O
.	O
their	O
M	O
's	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
&	O
dinner	O
waiting	O
from	O
4	O
!	O
that	O
it	O
occasio	O
ned	O
much	O
speculation	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
particularly	O
too	O
as	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
seem	O
'd	O
much	O
agitated	O
--	O
Very	O
long	O
letters	O
have	O
also	O
lately	O
paſs	O
'd	O
come	O
between	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
P	I-pers
..	I-pers
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
was	O
some	O
hours	O
in	O
our	O
Street	O
yesterday	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
on	O
Sunday	O
he	O
fl	O
y	O
i	O
es	O
to	O
&	O
fro	O
from	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
but	O
--	O
pays	O
few	O
Visits	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
:	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
upstairs	O
&	O
he	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
got	O
into	O
a	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Westminster	O
Scrutiny	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
said	O
he	O
imagined	O
it	O
wd	O
take	O
7	O
Years	O
desciding	O
if	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
After	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
&	O
Churchill	B-pers
left	O
me	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
home	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
aſsured	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
Cold	O
by	O
sleeping	O
from	O
home	O
&	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
for	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
for	O
though	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
was	O
fine	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
walking	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Glaring	O
Sun	O
as	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
today	O
--	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
long	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
setting	O
out	O
for	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
--	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
stay	O
some	O
time	O
very	O
soon	O
&	O
that	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
could	O
call	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
write	O
soon	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Butler	O
came	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Deer	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
ye	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
ye	O
..	O
family	O
were	O
all	O
well	O
at	O
Tunbridge	B-place
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
each	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Visit	O
:	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
we	O
separated	O
from	O
6	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Charming	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
I	O
work	O
'd	O
plain	O
work	O
till	O
Candle	O
light	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
oblige	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
neither	O
read	O
wrote	O
or	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
read	O
aloud	O
--	O
I	O
sorted	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Prints	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
look	O
'd	O
them	O
over	O
--	O
the	O
Eveg	O
paſs	O
'd	O
away	O
agreeably	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
soon	O
after	O
11	O
Saturday	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
..	O
1784	O
At	O
9	O
'	O
join	O
'd	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
quite	O
well	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
before	O
B	O
.	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
Notable	O
plain	O
work	O
wch	O
.	O
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
came	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Patients	O
.	O
he	O
orderd	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
draughts	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
&	O
before	O
dinner	O
begun	O
a	O
letter	O
wch	O
..	O
I	O
dictated	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
she	O
finished	O
it	O
&	O
read	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
frm	O
.	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
--	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
when	O
we	O
hoped	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Harewood	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
good	O
old	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ruſsel	I-pers
came	O
just	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
made	O
her	O
sit	O
down	O
&	O
drink	O
a	O
glaſs	O
of	O
Wine	O
--	O
she	O
brought	O
us	O
some	O
fruit	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
from	O
5	O
6	O
till	O
7	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
Work	O
--	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Bullstrode	B-place
to	O
inform	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
well	O
&	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
Wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
William	B-pers
to	O
enquire	O
wht	O
.	O
hour	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
&	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
to	O
call	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Stormonts	O
at	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
at	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
an	O
Answer	O
--	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
taken	O
up	O
wth	O
.	O
People	O
on	O
busineſs	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
read	O
aloud	O
&	O
finish	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
s	O
Man	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
a	O
most	O
melancholy	O
picture	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
depravity	O
of	O
human	O
Nature	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
ye	O
.	O
Moral	O
defective	O
as	O
it	O
makes	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
Virtuous	O
wretched	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
