TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
am	O
infinitely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Enquiries	O
respecting	O
My	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
who	O
has	O
continued	O
progreſsively	O
recovering	O
daily	O
since	O
this	O
day	O
Se'night	O
when	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Our	O
Little	O
Girl	O
thrives	O
&	O
is	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
healthy	O
&	O
very	O
stout	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
particularly	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
told	O
,	O
&	O
inclined	O
to	O
beleive	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
pretty	O
--	O
Your	O
Friend	O
Caroline	B-pers
,	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
much	O
grown	O
,	O
&	O
much	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
delighted	O
with	O
the	O
many	O
kind	O
Enquiries	O
&	O
meſsages	O
which	O
your	O
Letter	O
has	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
Her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
Her	O
power	O
,	O
nor	O
ours	O
,	O
to	O
promise	O
a	O
speedy	O
Visit	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
your	O
Little	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
has	O
long	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
has	O
made	O
progreſs	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
where	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Shell	O
,	O
a	O
situation	O
of	O
some	O
distinction	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
much	O
grown	O
&	O
goes	O
on	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
are	O
now	O
in	O
Yorkshire	B-place
in	O
their	O
Way	O
to	O
Scotland	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
is	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Companion	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
--	O
Captn	B-pers
George	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
having	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
succeſsful	O
beginning	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
Regt	O
.	O
of	O
Life	O
Guards	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
collecting	O
Cavalry	O
knowledge	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
near	O
Windsor	B-place
with	O
the	O
flower	O
of	O
the	O
British	O
Cavalry	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
Aid	O
de	O
Camp	O
to	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dundas	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
all	O
the	O
manoeuvres	O
practiced	O
at	O
this	O
Camp	O
originate	O
--	O
an	O
appointment	O
most	O
flattering	O
to	O
Him	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
is	O
well	O
&	O
at	O
Broadstairs	B-place
--	O
My	O
Mother	O
My	O
Brother	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fredk	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
are	O
also	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
that	O
your	O
house	O
is	O
so	O
comfortable	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
lately	O
been	O
renderd	O
so	O
completely	O
so	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
kind	O
Wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Believe	O
me	O
always	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Yours	O
most	O
Truely	O
&	O
Faithfully	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
F.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
No	O
.	O
1	O
Gt	O
Cumberland	O
St	O
Augst	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
