TOKEN	NE
No	O
longer	O
Clandestinely	O
but	O
openly	O
do	O
I	O
adreſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
&	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
Angry	O
at	O
the	O
risks	O
you	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
run	O
yet	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
strongly	O
the	O
motive	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
pray	O
answer	O
me	O
as	O
honestly	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
really	O
?	O
&	O
how	O
does	O
all	O
the	O
standing	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
not	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
&	O
whenever	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
shall	O
perceive	O
it	O
--	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
anxious	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
,	O
how	O
ridiculous	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
if	O
you	O
all	O
come	O
&	O
settle	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
Quarantine	O
still	O
subsist	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shake	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
as	O
you	O
paſs	O
,	O
however	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
thank	O
God	O
the	O
dear	O
Children	O
are	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Infection	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
judge	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
yesterday	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
heard	O
&	O
shall	O
again	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
tempting	O
Weather	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
dying	O
with	O
the	O
Cold	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
Poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
has	O
been	O
confined	O
ever	O
since	O
Friday	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
able	O
she	O
removes	O
to	O
London	B-place
on	O
Thursday	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
kind	O
than	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Child	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sincerely	O
Your	O
Affct	O
MC	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
My	O
Meſsages	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
were	O
only	O
Answers	O
to	O
those	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
27	O
th	O
April	O
1779	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
Comps	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Guiffardier	I-pers
--	O
Charles	B-pers
de	I-pers
Guiffardière	I-pers
(	I-pers
de	I-pers
Guiffardieu	I-pers
)	I-pers
Queens	O
House	O
