TOKEN	NE
Boston	B-place
July	O
24	O
th	O
1768	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
Oportunity	O
to	O
Obey	O
yr	O
obligeing	O
commands	O
of	O
writeing	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
ho	O
pe	O
s	O
it	O
will	O
entitle	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
You	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
quite	O
Anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
enjoyd	O
more	O
Health	O
&	O
Satisfaction	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
than	O
has	O
faln	O
to	O
our	O
Share	O
be	O
asured	O
nothing	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
more	O
pleasing	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Occaſsion	O
of	O
Acknowledgeing	O
our	O
Grate	O
ful	O
Sensibility	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
prooffs	O
we	O
received	O
of	O
yr	O
friendship	O
whilest	O
in	O
yr	O
Neighbourhood	O
I	O
wont	O
call	O
it	O
Politeneſs	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
Something	O
much	O
beyond	O
it	O
&	O
much	O
more	O
agreeable	O
--	O
but	O
these	O
Days	O
are	O
past	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
not	O
soon	O
to	O
Return	O
for	O
ther	O
's	O
litle	O
Likelehood	O
of	O
our	O
leaveing	O
this	O
beffore	O
Octr	O
:	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
had	O
got	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
Petter	B-place
borough	I-place
--	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Seized	O
wt	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Heart=Burn	O
to	O
relieve	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Large	O
Draught	O
of	O
Chalk	O
&	O
Watter	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Gout	O
that	O
aild	O
him	O
it	O
imeditly	O
reduced	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
Alarming	O
Condition	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
worst	O
Inn	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
)	O
&	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
Inhuman	O
people	O
in	O
England	B-place
for	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
Send	O
to	O
provide	O
the	O
least	O
thing	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
an	O
Invallid	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
town	O
to	O
provide	O
Veall	O
&	O
Chickens	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Broths	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
we	O
were	O
paying	O
most	O
exhorbitant	O
Bills	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
mention	O
this	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
there	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
Shun	O
that	O
Inn	O
--	O
EGA	B-pers
continued	O
too	O
Ill	O
even	O
to	O
be	O
moved	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
House	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
Skilful	O
Apothecary	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Sort	O
of	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
rellieffe	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
the	O
third	O
Day	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
did	O
arrive	O
we	O
found	O
ourselves	O
arrived	O
in	O
the	O
Regions	O
of	O
Babel	O
which	O
are	O
by	O
many	O
degrees	O
worse	O
than	O
th	O
o	O
se	O
of	O
Babylon	B-place
--	O
for	O
we	O
Seemd	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
Aſsemblage	O
of	O
all	O
Tongues	O
&	O
Nations	O
collected	O
together	O
to	O
torment	O
us	O
:	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
had	O
his	O
Billet	O
but	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
remain	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Inns	O
being	O
more	O
th	O
a	O
n	O
full	O
Surrounded	O
at	O
all	O
Hours	O
wt	O
Justices	O
Constables	O
Tenants	O
Stewarts	O
Cottagers	O
Prisoners	O
Rioters	O
Attornies	O
Clerks	O
&	O
examination	O
of	O
Witneſs	O
's	O
in	O
every	O
corner	O
--	O
while	O
the	O
Inn	O
Yard	O
&	O
Stairs	O
were	O
so	O
fill	O
'd	O
wt	O
people	O
dureing	O
our	O
Stay	O
there	O
that	O
't	O
was	O
near	O
to	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
Stirr	O
--	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
Stun	O
'd	O
w	O
t	O
the	O
Bay	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
mixt	O
multitude	O
from	O
every	O
Corner	O
from	O
Monday	O
till	O
Fryday	O
was	O
we	O
so	O
shut	O
up	O
wt	O
the	O
Comfort	O
of	O
finding	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
House	O
nor	O
Lodgeing	O
to	O
be	O
Hired	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
--	O
at	O
last	O
our	O
good	O
Genious	O
apeard	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
who	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
pityeing	O
our	O
Situation	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
beg	O
our	O
Acceptance	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
four	O
Milles	O
distant	O
wch	O
was	O
ready	O
furnisht	O
--	O
&	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
use	O
for	O
as	O
his	O
Buſsineſs	O
detaind	O
him	O
always	O
in	O
Boston	B-place
--	O
so	O
here	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
his	O
Chateau	O
wch	O
we	O
should	O
like	O
greatly	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
us	O
pay	O
Rent	O
for	O
but	O
its	O
disagreeable	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
Strangers	O
to	O
whom	O
its	O
not	O
poſsible	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Return	O
--	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Im	O
happy	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
Stay	O
behind	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
very	O
Ill	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
he	O
begins	O
to	O
get	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
Mr	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
will	O
soon	O
be	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
for	O
two	O
days	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
familly	O
to	O
Stafford	B-place
where	O
he	O
has	O
hired	O
a	O
House	O
--	O
four	O
troops	O
stay	O
here	O
&	O
two	O
goes	O
there	O
till	O
further	O
orders	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
dilligent	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
extent	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
wch	O
proves	O
a	O
deeper	O
laid	O
Scheme	O
&	O
more	O
Mischivious	O
than	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
aprehended	O
however	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
trie	O
their	O
forces	O
wt	O
that	O
of	O
this	O
Regt	O
:	O
&	O
ye	O
Justices	O
very	O
wisely	O
have	O
hitherto	O
sent	O
only	O
Constables	O
&	O
Millitia	O
to	O
enforce	O
their	O
orders	O
where	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
Resisted	O
so	O
our	O
people	O
remain	O
in	O
Quiete	O
--	O
thus	O
have	O
I	O
obey	O
'd	O
yr	O
commands	O
an	O
long	O
et	O
an	O
Large	O
by	O
telling	O
you	O
ev'ry	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
hapned	O
us	O
if	O
it	O
fatigues	O
You	O
blame	O
yourself	O
for	O
engageing	O
in	O
a	O
Correspondance	O
too	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
easily	O
given	O
up	O
--	O
on	O
my	O
Side	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
about	O
Yourselves	O
&	O
a	O
litle	O
about	O
yr	O
Babylonians	O
our	O
friends	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
left	O
London	B-place
Col	B-pers
Douglaſs	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Children	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
offers	O
of	O
our	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Cust	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Says	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
again	O
so	O
does	O
her	O
Br	O
:	O
though	O
he	O
is	O
ashamed	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
contrive	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
fine	O
Romp	O
here	O
altogether	O
.	O
bellieve	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
most	O
Faithfull	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Mary	B-pers
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Boston	B-place
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Frank	O
for	O
this	O
Letter	O
.	O
