TOKEN	NE
Kew	B-place
.	O
Frid	O
.	O
morn	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1782	O
If	O
I	O
recollect	O
aright	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
lend	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Jos	I-pers
:	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
discourses	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
to	O
trouble	O
her	O
also	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
enclosed	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
be	O
good	O
enough	O
also	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
,	O
&	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
his	O
books	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
all	O
imaginable	O
care	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
much	O
progreſs	O
in	O
them	O
as	O
during	O
the	O
Prince	O
s	O
two	O
last	O
visits	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
The	O
Port	O
Folio	O
of	O
Drawings	O
arrived	O
safe	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
her	O
kind	O
Letter	O
&	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
subscribe	O
myself	O
her	O
Much	O
obliged	O
most	O
obedient	O
humble	O
Servant	O
J.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
My	O
Fellow	O
Labourer	O
is	O
considerably	O
better	O
.	O
All	O
Sun	O
Shine	O
chez	O
nous	O
.	O
