TOKEN	NE
Grosvenor	O
Place	O
Wednesday	O
receive	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
the	O
sincere	O
congratulations	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
self	O
in	O
which	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
included	O
.	O
may	O
the	O
event	O
that	O
has	O
taken	O
place	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
prove	O
so	O
Happy	O
as	O
We	O
wish	O
,	O
and	O
You	O
deserve	O
:	O
I	O
speak	O
experimentaly	O
if	O
You	O
are	O
rewarded	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
;	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
wishes	O
of	O
Your	O
friends	O
have	O
prevailed	O
:	O
we	O
beg	O
our	O
compts	O
to	O
Captain	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
and	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
aſsure	O
Him	O
how	O
sincerely	O
we	O
give	O
him	O
Joy	O
,	O
and	O
feel	O
interested	O
in	O
Your	O
Happineſs	O
:	O
which	O
now	O
includes	O
His	O
--	O
We	O
go	O
to	O
Ockham	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
our	O
return	O
shall	O
certainly	O
enquire	O
after	O
You	O
:	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
packed	O
up	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
flatter	O
myself	O
You	O
will	O
excuse	O
the	O
Dreſs	O
and	O
accept	O
the	O
personal	O
Congratulations	O
of	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
Sincere	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
