TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
your	O
letter	O
with	O
the	O
enclosed	O
which	O
has	O
perhaps	O
given	O
you	O
some	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
understand	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
swindling	O
piece	O
of	O
busineſs	O
in	O
which	O
your	O
name	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
defraud	O
some	O
credulous	O
fool	O
,	O
your	O
real	O
Christian	O
name	O
has	O
been	O
purposely	O
avoided	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
prosecution	O
for	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
propriety	O
to	O
apprise	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
's	I-pers
Cashier	O
of	O
the	O
intended	O
fraud	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
presented	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
payment	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
received	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
in	O
this	O
busineſs	O
but	O
remain	O
quiet	O
without	O
giving	O
yourself	O
the	O
smallest	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
any	O
further	O
letter	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
transmit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
your	O
Attorney	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
act	O
in	O
case	O
any	O
thing	O
shoud	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
myself	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
appear	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Berger	I-pers
the	O
dupe	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
Person	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
so	O
weak	O
to	O
advance	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
Draft	O
of	O
a	O
Persons	O
without	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
their	O
writing	O
or	O
Christian	O
names	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
pitied	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
supposing	O
Berger	B-pers
an	O
innocent	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
that	O
is	O
doubtful	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
will	O
clear	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
which	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
serious	O
consequence	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
lost	O
our	O
worthy	O
Friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
who	O
died	O
early	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
last	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
proper	O
inquiries	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
but	O
are	O
as	O
yet	O
ignorant	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
uneasy	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
poſseſs	O
'd	O
an	O
excellent	O
disposition	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
sincerely	O
interested	O
for	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
disappointed	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affect	O
.	O
Humble	O
ser	O
vant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
Novr	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
has	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
her	O
return	O
from	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
staid	O
only	O
8	O
days	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
on	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Dublin	B-place
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
explanation	O
you	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Cheshire	B-place
