TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
19	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1789	O
--	O
Ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
femme	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
last	O
arrived	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
and	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
Apartments	O
--	O
First	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
shall	O
begin	O
with	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
At	O
Buxton	B-place
I	O
found	O
my	O
Company	O
consisted	O
of	O
a	O
Little	O
lively	O
Italian	O
a	O
sickly	O
Frenchman	O
an	O
English	O
Bear	O
who	O
had	O
travelled	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
extremely	O
like	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
at	O
his	O
presumption	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
resemblance	O
to	O
be	O
equally	O
strong	O
in	O
temper	O
&	O
manners	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
Rider	O
--	O
at	O
Ashborn	B-place
a	O
woman	O
about	O
4	O
times	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
Betty	B-pers
Shallcroſs	I-pers
got	O
into	O
our	O
very	O
small	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
half	O
filled	O
--	O
And	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
an	O
intruder	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
admitted	O
her	O
--	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
post	O
there	O
from	O
Litchfield	B-place
to	O
Birmm	B-place
--	O
The	O
Air	O
was	O
intensely	O
t	O
ar	O
t	O
,	O
otherwise	O
that	O
mode	O
of	O
travelling	O
is	O
pleasant	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
may	O
see	O
more	O
of	O
a	O
Country	O
than	O
on	O
Horseback	O
--	O
ten	O
miles	O
from	O
Birmm	B-place
.	I-place
we	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
soon	O
entered	O
into	O
Conversation	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
entered	O
into	O
a	O
minute	O
detail	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
which	O
he	O
is	O
perfectly	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
bro-t	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
in	O
for	O
the	O
Town	O
--	O
wh	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
from	O
a	O
publick	O
Spirit	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
extremely	O
attached	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
&	O
would	O
now	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
serve	O
them	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
the	O
town	O
was	O
treated	O
vexed	O
him	O
&	O
having	O
his	O
Spirits	O
raised	O
with	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
unfortunately	O
gave	O
his	O
promise	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
which	O
tho	O
he	O
repented	O
,	O
he	O
Would	O
not	O
retreat	O
--	O
The	O
Sum	O
of	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
given	O
in	O
a	O
handsome	O
manner	O
at	O
a	O
particular	O
time	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
losing	O
his	O
Seat	O
--	O
but	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
W——	I-pers
thought	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
his	O
command	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Act	O
of	O
Attention	O
or	O
Civility	O
was	O
neceſsary	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
subservient	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
This	O
Man	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Wilmot	B-pers
,	O
Brother	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
of	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
painter	O
--	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
Opposition	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Ws	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
lost	O
a	O
place	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9000	O
L	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
resume	O
his	O
profession	O
in	O
Birmm-	B-place
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
off	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
all	O
interested	O
in	O
this	O
conversation	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pleasant	O
thing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Springs	O
of	O
Actions	O
--	O
At	O
Birmm-	B-place
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
Bristol	B-place
Coach	O
was	O
just	O
setting	O
out	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Coaches	O
go	O
only	O
on	O
three	O
days	O
a	O
Week	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
Thursday	O
morng	O
wh	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
I	O
engaged	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
to	O
wh	O
.	O
Inn	O
I	O
removed	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
afternoon	O
for	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
Opporty	O
of	O
seeing	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
circulating	O
Library	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Book	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
boy	O
of	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
--	O
he	O
answered	O
my	O
questions	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
laughing	O
&	O
supposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
aping	O
his	O
Master	O
who	O
probably	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
pedantick	O
Bookworm	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
fond	O
of	O
reading	O
?	O
O	O
yes	O
Sir	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
Plays	O
&	O
novels	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
O	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
read	O
such	O
books	O
as	O
those	O
--	O
pray	O
what	O
is	O
yr-	O
favorite	O
Study	O
?	O
Divinity	O
Sir	O
?	O
and	O
whose	O
book	O
's	O
do	O
like	O
best	O
?	O
Watts	B-pers
I	O
like	O
but	O
Watson	B-pers
is	O
my	O
favorite	O
Author	O
--	O
just	O
then	O
his	O
Mistreſs	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
--	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
“	O
that	O
the	O
little	O
old	O
Man	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Election	O
”	O
I	O
enquired	O
on	O
what	O
his	O
choice	O
had	O
fallen	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Anabaptist	O
Church	O
--	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
perfect	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Shop	O
taking	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
translation	O
of	O
Voltaire	B-pers
s	O
history	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
the	I-pers
great	I-pers
--	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
reading	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
have	O
much	O
conversation	O
with	O
this	O
religious	O
boy	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
book	O
--	O
There	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
there	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Master	O
was	O
so	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
without	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
1000L	O
&	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Child	O
&	O
his	O
only	O
one	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
greater	O
regard	O
for	O
him	O
--	O
The	O
boy	O
is	O
an	O
orphan	O
--	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
all	O
the	O
places	O
were	O
taken	O
--	O
As	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
I	O
consented	O
but	O
afterwards	O
repented	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
additional	O
seat	O
which	O
a	O
fifth	O
person	O
occasioned	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dissenting	O
Minister	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
agreeable	O
enough	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
also	O
a	O
ve	O
ry	O
s	O
illy	O
weak	O
woman	O
&	O
her	O
Abigail	O
--	O
who	O
sat	O
op	O
po	O
site	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
amusement	O
I	O
had	O
was	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
Maid	O
laugh	O
at	O
her	O
Mistreſs	O
's	O
Nonsense	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
reminding	O
her	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
with	O
my	O
knees	O
poor	O
Soul	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
Her	O
back	O
wd	O
.	O
ache	O
,	O
&	O
God	O
help	O
her	O
for	O
serving	O
such	O
a	O
Fool	O
--	O
We	O
supped	O
at	O
Worcester	B-place
I	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
from	O
Bromsgrove	B-place
&	O
found	O
it	O
extremely	O
pleasant	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
heavy	O
rain	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
dust	O
at	O
Tewksbury	B-place
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
quite	O
comfortable	O
as	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
some	O
Accident	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
almost	O
every	O
Night	O
lately	O
and	O
broken	O
bones	O
were	O
spoken	O
of	O
with	O
y-	O
utmost	O
indifference	O
--	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
&	O
her	O
sweet	O
Bedfellow	O
--	O
We	O
however	O
arrived	O
safe	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
at	O
7	O
OClock	O
--	O
after	O
being	O
15	O
hours	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
without	O
Sleep	O
and	O
having	O
plenty	O
of	O
disagreeable	O
expectations	O
,	O
no	O
conversation	O
,	O
my	O
companions	O
were	O
snoring	O
round	O
me	O
&	O
to	O
compleat	O
my	O
happineſs	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
rouse	O
a	O
Servant	O
till	O
8	O
OClock	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
hot	O
Water	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
Succedaneum	O
for	O
a	O
warm	O
bath	O
--	O
changed	O
my	O
Linnen	O
,	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
tolerably	O
refreshed	O
--	O
The	O
rain	O
fell	O
inceſsantly	O
till	O
10	O
OClock	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Hannah	B-pers
&	O
Patty	B-pers
were	O
absent	O
but	O
received	O
a	O
hearty	O
welcome	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
--	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
day	O
--	O
diner	O
en	O
famille	O
--	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
pleasant	O
conversation	O
&	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
regret	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
smart	O
run	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
time	O
for	O
my	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
more	O
about	O
this	O
visit	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
&	O
shall	O
only	O
now	O
say	O
that	O
They	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
little	O
doubt	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
's	O
having	O
married	O
a	O
common	O
Woman	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-place
many	O
year	O
's	O
ago	O
,	O
whh	O
.	O
Acct	O
.	O
they	O
had	O
from	O
their	O
own	O
Mother	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
indeed	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
at	O
6	O
yesterday	O
&	O
was	O
received	O
with	O
open	O
Arms	O
by	O
the	O
Rundells	B-pers
where	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
Evg	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
fixed	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
Queens	O
Square	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
say	O
that	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
bathing	O
will	O
relieve	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
irritation	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
Bile	O
's	O
being	O
thrown	O
to	O
the	O
outward	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
thick	O
to	O
paſs	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
pores	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
few	O
Drops	O
of	O
Laudanum	O
would	O
always	O
give	O
me	O
relief	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
he	O
loves	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
wishes	O
to	O
see	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Sally	B-pers
is	O
just	O
come	O
down	O
in	O
papillotes	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
Opera	O
house	O
is	O
burnt	O
down	O
&	O
I	O
'm	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
1000	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
yt-	O
She	O
lives	O
by	O
herself	O
&	O
that	O
her	O
Sisters	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
--	O
God	O
for	O
ever	O
bless	O
&	O
preserve	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
kiſs	O
our	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
herself	O
&	O
me	O
think	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
always	O
love	O
me	O
,	O
half	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
beloved	O
by	O
Yr	O
.	O
faithful	O
J.D	B-pers
--	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Sisters	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
Drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
or	O
bathe	O
till	O
Sunday	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Taxal	O
Chapel	O
le	O
frith	O
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
Post	O
.	O
--	O
