TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
shooting	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
killed	O
a	O
Landrail	O
&	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
--	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
morning	O
Service	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
to	O
hear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
--	O
desire	O
Louisa	B-pers
will	O
read	O
the	O
Absolution	O
aloud	O
with	O
a	O
perfect	O
Monsterous	O
tenor	O
&	O
pronounce	O
every	O
s.	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
a	O
zed	O
&	O
then	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
--	O
in	O
perfection	O
--	O
Monday	O
--	O
Went	O
a	O
Shooting	O
killed	O
a	O
Leveret	O
a	O
Hawk	O
&	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
Partridges	O
--	O
saw	O
some	O
Game	O
and	O
some	O
beautiful	O
Scenery	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
Went	O
a	O
fishing	O
after	O
breakfast	O
&	O
brought	O
home	O
14	O
Fish	O
--	O
I	O
mentioned	O
this	O
morning	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
thursday	O
but	O
so	O
much	O
was	O
said	O
about	O
my	O
spending	O
the	O
Week	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
point	O
&	O
shall	O
set	O
out	O
certainly	O
on	O
monday	O
for	O
Plymouth	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
just	O
going	O
a	O
per	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
on	O
busineſs	O
--	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
am	O
scribbling	O
post	O
haste	O
--	O
no	O
post	O
goes	O
to	O
day	O
from	O
Bampton	B-place
or	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
--	O
Had	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
You	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
on	O
thursday	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Ever	O
&	O
Aye	O
JD	B-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
