TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
18	O
th	O
=	O
Janry-	O
1791	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
The	O
execrability	O
of	O
the	O
Weather	O
having	O
confined	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Library	O
,	O
this	O
forenoon	O
,	O
&	O
finding	O
myself	O
rather	O
in	O
a	O
condescending	O
humour	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
prevailed	O
on	O
myself	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
insense	O
You	O
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
allow	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
folks	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
,	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
difficult	O
Task	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
been	O
domesticated	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Capital	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
poſsibly	O
retain	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
your	O
former	O
Indigo	O
corruption	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
flatter	O
yourself	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
acuteneſs	O
&	O
penetration	O
are	O
fully	O
sufficient	O
to	O
comprehend	O
&	O
unravel	O
the	O
Mysteries	O
of	O
Peerage	O
Politics	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
when	O
You	O
wrote	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Committee	O
of	O
Privileges	O
have	O
not	O
met	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
our	O
Election	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
busineſs	O
will	O
come	O
on	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
present	O
Receſs	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
may	O
poſsibly	O
amuse	O
their	O
Lordships	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Years	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
Our	O
Adversaries	O
object	O
to	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
the	O
Earls	O
of	O
Caithneſs	B-pers
,	O
Moray	B-pers
,	O
Rosebery	B-pers
,	O
De	B-pers
Loraine	I-pers
,	O
Visct-	B-pers
Dumblaine	I-pers
,	O
Lords	O
Ochiltree	B-pers
,	O
Sinclair	B-pers
,	O
Lindores	B-pers
,	O
Napier	B-pers
,	O
Fairfax	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Belhaven	B-pers
.	O
We	O
object	O
to	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Rothsay	I-pers
,	O
Earls	O
Dysart	B-pers
&	O
Caſsillis	B-pers
,	O
Lords	O
Cranstoun	B-pers
,	O
Newark	B-pers
,	O
Kinnaird	B-pers
.	O
Besides	O
these	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
objections	O
to	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
the	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Lothian	I-pers
&	O
Visct	B-pers
.	I-pers
Falkland	I-pers
,	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
reasons	O
for	O
not	O
stating	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
see	O
how	O
their	O
Lordships	O
in	O
the	O
Committee	O
will	O
treat	O
the	O
objections	O
,	O
of	O
our	O
Enemies	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
votes	O
of	O
the	O
Earls	O
of	O
Rosebery	B-pers
,	O
De	B-pers
Loraine	I-pers
,	O
Lords	O
Sinclair	B-pers
&	O
Fairfax	B-pers
.	O
The	O
real	O
Battle	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
be	O
fought	O
on	O
these	O
Votes	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
my	O
Friends	O
E.	B-pers
Caithneſs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
good	O
Vote	O
Moray	B-pers
,	O
Do-	O
V.	B-pers
Dumblane	I-pers
Do-	O
L.	B-pers
Ochiltree	I-pers
,	O
doubtfull	O
Lindores	B-pers
,	O
good	O
Napier	B-pers
,	O
good	O
Belhaven	B-pers
--	O
7	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
For	O
our	O
Adversaries	O
D.	B-pers
Rothsay	I-pers
--	O
bad	O
E.	B-pers
Dysart	I-pers
--	O
wont	O
be	O
counted	O
Caſsillis	B-pers
--	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
counted	O
L.	B-pers
Cranstoun	I-pers
,	O
wont	O
be	O
counted	O
Newark	B-pers
--	O
bad	O
Kinnaird	B-pers
--	O
6	O
wont	O
be	O
counted	O
.	O
Objections	O
by	O
the	O
Enemy	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
The	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Caithneſs	I-pers
has	O
presented	O
his	O
Claim	O
to	O
that	O
Peerage	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
decided	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Answer	O
,	O
the	O
claim	O
is	O
good	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
decided	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
2	O
nd	O
-	O
The	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Moray	I-pers
,	O
has	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
that	O
Title	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
Viscount	B-pers
Doune	I-pers
only	O
.	O
Answer	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
Right	O
to	O
that	O
Title	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
shew	O
his	O
Charter	O
.	O
3	O
rd	O
-	O
Viscount	B-pers
Dumblane	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
D.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Leeds	I-pers
)	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
since	O
the	O
Union	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
not	O
entitled	O
to	O
Vote	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
He	O
sits	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
as	O
D.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Leeds	I-pers
,	O
created	O
before	O
the	O
Union	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
as	O
Baron	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
created	O
since	O
the	O
Union	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
Vote	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Ochiltree	I-pers
has	O
presented	O
his	O
Claim	O
to	O
that	O
Peerage	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
decided	O
on	O
it	O
--	O
N.B	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
whether	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
his	O
Right	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
Lord	B-pers
Lindores	I-pers
,	O
has	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
that	O
Title	O
.	O
NB	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Lord	B-pers
Lindores	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Cousin	O
the	O
present	O
Lord	O
,	O
aſsumed	O
the	O
Title	O
without	O
petitioning	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Lawyers	O
that	O
his	O
right	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
Napier	O
is	O
Extinct	O
.	O
Answer	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
Extinct	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
present	O
Lord	O
,	O
has	O
his	O
Charter	O
ready	O
to	O
produce	O
,	O
to	O
show	O
that	O
it	O
exists	O
in	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
That	O
Lord	B-pers
Belhaven	I-pers
has	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
that	O
Title	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
opinion	O
I	O
subscribe	O
.	O
Objections	O
by	O
my	O
Friends	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
The	O
Patent	O
creating	O
the	O
first	O
D	O
.	O
of	O
Rothsay	O
does	O
not	O
exist	O
,	O
the	O
limitations	O
are	O
therefore	O
unknown	O
No	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
Scots	O
Parliament	O
exists	O
declaring	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Scotland	I-pers
,	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Rothsay	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Birth	O
.	O
No	O
Duke	O
of	O
Rothesay	O
ever	O
did	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
Parlt	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
That	O
Title	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
Union	O
Roll	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
added	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
by	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
.	O
The	O
Proxy	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prince	O
at	O
last	O
Election	O
,	O
was	O
defaced	O
&	O
informal	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
-	O
The	O
Proxy	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dysart	I-pers
was	O
defaced	O
&	O
informal	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
the	O
Peer	O
who	O
held	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
did	O
not	O
qualif	O
ied	O
y	O
to	O
vote	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
Proxy	O
of	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Caſsillis	I-pers
is	O
dated	O
in	O
July	O
1790	O
,	O
&	O
authorises	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
,	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
July	O
next	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
aſserted	O
to	O
mean	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1791	O
.	O
NB	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
a	O
quibble	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
this	O
vote	O
will	O
be	O
sustained	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
The	O
Peer	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Cranstoun	I-pers
gave	O
his	O
Proxy	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
qualify	O
to	O
vote	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
=	O
Lord	B-pers
Newark	I-pers
has	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
that	O
Title	O
;	O
the	O
Patent	O
on	O
Record	O
,	O
granting	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Heirs	O
Male	O
of	O
General	B-pers
David	I-pers
Lesly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Newark	I-pers
,	O
&	O
the	O
present	O
Lord	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Descendant	O
of	O
a	O
Female	O
heir	O
of	O
the	B-pers
first	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
s	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
Lord	B-pers
Kinnaird	I-pers
,	O
did	O
not	O
qualify	O
to	O
vote	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
,	O
whereby	O
his	O
own	O
Vote	O
,	O
&	O
those	O
he	O
gave	O
as	O
Proxy	O
for	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dysart	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
Cranstoun	I-pers
,	O
are	O
void	O
.	O
NB	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
laughable	O
fact	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Kinnaird	I-pers
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
signing	O
the	O
Oaths	O
,	O
has	O
actually	O
written	O
Kinnoul	O
instead	O
of	O
Kinnaird	O
to	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Kinnoul	I-pers
had	O
signed	O
immediately	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
instead	O
of	O
subscribing	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
copied	O
the	O
one	O
before	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
discovered	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
hunting	O
for	O
flaws	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
the	O
Lists	O
of	O
objections	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
be	O
found	O
to	O
stand	O
thus	O
;	O
We	O
shall	O
lose	O
Ochiltree	B-pers
&	O
Belhaven	B-pers
.	O
Our	O
Adversaries	O
willl	O
lose	O
,	O
Rothsay	B-pers
,	O
Dysart	B-pers
,	O
Cranstoun	B-pers
,	O
Newark	B-pers
&	O
Kinnaird	B-pers
.	O
This	O
will	O
take	O
off	O
two	O
from	O
our	O
Strength	O
&	O
five	O
from	O
theirs	O
.	O
The	O
objections	O
,	O
the	O
Enemy	O
make	O
to	O
,	O
Rosebery	B-pers
,	O
De	B-pers
Loraine	I-pers
,	O
Sinclair	B-pers
&	O
Fairfax	B-pers
,	O
are	O
applicable	O
to	O
Lothian	B-pers
&	O
Falkland	B-pers
,	O
on	O
their	O
Side	O
.	O
The	O
objection	O
arises	O
from	O
a	O
blunder	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Chancery	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
should	O
think	O
otherwise	O
,	O
those	O
votes	O
must	O
be	O
struck	O
off	O
,	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
case	O
we	O
shall	O
lose	O
Eight	O
Votes	O
&	O
they	O
will	O
lose	O
only	O
Seven	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
,	O
on	O
looking	O
at	O
my	O
Memorandums	O
the	O
Enemy	O
have	O
objections	O
to	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
Viscount	B-pers
Dumblane	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Lindores	I-pers
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Chancery	O
mistake	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
what	O
I	O
before	O
stated	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
Our	O
Lawyers	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Chancery	O
blunder	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
corrected	O
by	O
the	O
record	O
at	O
the	O
Petty	O
Bay	O
Office	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensberry	I-pers
&	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
claim	O
a	O
Right	O
of	O
voting	O
,	O
&	O
sent	O
Lists	O
to	O
the	O
Election	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
rejected	O
.	O
An	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Peer	O
claiming	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
by	O
a	O
Title	O
created	O
since	O
the	O
Union	O
,	O
shall	O
vote	O
at	O
our	O
Elections	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
abide	O
by	O
their	O
Resolution	O
,	O
Queensberry	B-pers
&	O
Abercorn	B-pers
can	O
have	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
Vote	O
.	O
Abercorn	B-pers
,	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
name	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
List	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
Cunninghame	I-pers
claimed	O
a	O
right	O
,	O
to	O
Vote	O
as	O
Lord	B-pers
Lyle	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
rejected	O
,	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
Lyle	O
not	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Union	O
Roll	O
.	O
Our	O
Adversaries	O
,	O
defend	O
this	O
Title	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
dormant	O
for	O
two	O
Centuries	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
should	O
establish	O
his	O
Right	O
,	O
yet	O
not	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Roll	O
,	O
no	O
vote	O
he	O
could	O
offer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Election	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
counted	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
Peerage	O
of	O
Scotland	O
&	O
their	O
Election	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
joy	O
of	O
the	O
Chevalier	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
's	O
visitation	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
of	O
your	O
relation	O
Colonel	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
who	O
lived	O
with	O
Lord	O
late	O
Lord	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
paper	O
today	O
announces	O
his	O
espousals	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Ewart	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
&	O
formerly	O
Companion	O
to	O
my	O
Sisters	O
.	O
Her	O
brother	O
is	O
Envoy	O
,	O
at	O
Berlin	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
once	O
,	O
flattered	O
herself	O
,	O
with	O
becoming	O
my	O
Rib	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
your	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
Closet	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
,	O
discharges	O
itself	O
into	O
the	O
Cold	O
Bath	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
Warm	O
Bath	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
,	O
the	O
Water	O
will	O
be	O
sufficiently	O
softened	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
partake	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Quality	O
of	O
Thames	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
consequently	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
Brewing	O
.	O
Your	O
Comfortable	O
Room	O
,	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
envied	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
converted	O
our	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
into	O
the	O
Nursery	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
largest	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
My	O
Library	O
into	O
the	O
Living	O
Room	O
&	O
the	O
late	O
Nursery	O
into	O
my	O
Library	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
peep	O
of	O
You	O
&	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
sorry	O
,	O
could	O
You	O
see	O
Us	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
fingers	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Cramp	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
Lords	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
humble	O
Ideas	O
have	O
been	O
driven	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Brains	O
.	O
Best	O
affections	O
from	O
Rib	O
&	O
Self	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
.	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affect	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Eighteenth	O
Janry=	O
1791	O
.	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derby	B-place
by	O
Carlisle	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
