TOKEN	NE
15	O
Sept	O
.	O
Sunday	O
1781	O
Babel	B-place
Dearest	O
friend	O
--	O
No	O
post	O
went	O
out	O
last	O
night	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
vindicate	O
my	O
seeming	O
neglect	O
--	O
indeed	O
my	O
love	O
I	O
wrote	O
on	O
friday	O
as	O
I	O
promised	O
at	O
Leuctra	B-place
&	O
gave	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
Chs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
--	O
he	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
forgot	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
--	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
done	O
so	O
--	O
pray	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Portman	O
Square	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
delay	O
sending	O
this	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
night	O
for	O
Tomorrow	O
I	O
return	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
letter	O
will	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
bye	O
&	O
bye	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
adieu	O
Sep	O
tember	O
