TOKEN	NE
Louvre	B-place
25	O
th	O
.	O
Thursday	O
Novbr	O
1779	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
write	O
this	O
dreadful	O
cold	O
has	O
now	O
lodged	O
itself	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
my	O
eyes	O
are	O
almost	O
closed	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
I	O
suffer	O
is	O
beyond	O
description	O
--	O
cld	O
.	O
yo	O
see	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
instant	O
you	O
wld	O
.	O
scold	O
me	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
write	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
told	O
me	O
yesterday	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
you	O
were	O
well	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
--	O
the	O
meeting	O
is	O
over	O
--	O
my	O
U	O
.	O
came	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Eveg	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
ten	O
1000	O
things	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
my	O
Head	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
agony	O
of	O
pain	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
Heaven	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
