TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
hasty	O
short	O
letter	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
--	O
in	O
fact	O
there	O
was	O
little	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
nothing	O
had	O
occurred	O
worth	O
relating	O
--	O
that	O
day	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynter	I-pers
had	O
appraised	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Neceſsity	O
of	O
some	O
Arrangement	O
taking	O
place	O
between	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
respecting	O
her	O
residence	O
here	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
refused	O
to	O
grant	O
her	O
a	O
Lease	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
wants	O
her	O
to	O
depend	O
on	O
his	O
honor	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
values	O
the	O
premi	O
se	O
at	O
six	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
thinks	O
it	O
worth	O
or	O
would	O
give	O
--	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
uncertainty	O
made	O
certain	O
&	O
if	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
place	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
decided	O
upon	O
without	O
delay	O
--	O
She	O
therefore	O
seeing	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
proper	O
light	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
little	O
Maid	O
on	O
the	O
poney	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
with	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
desire	O
Hayden	B-pers
to	O
come	O
here	O
whilst	O
I	O
staid	O
--	O
&	O
accordingly	O
he	O
came	O
here	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
Yesterday	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
early	O
as	O
I	O
promised	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
to	O
give	O
my	O
Opinion	O
about	O
the	O
picture	O
--	O
D	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
&	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Chancel	O
--	O
however	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Clerk	O
to	O
help	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
hoisted	O
it	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
&	O
still	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
effect	O
--	O
The	O
Subject	O
is	O
our	O
Saviour	O
bearing	O
his	O
Croſs	O
--	O
a	O
half	O
length	O
figure	O
--	O
the	O
head	O
&	O
Limbs	O
coloſsal	O
&	O
the	O
Executioner	O
holding	O
a	O
hammer	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
with	O
a	O
Countenance	O
expreſsive	O
of	O
malicious	O
pleasure	O
that	O
his	O
Office	O
afforded	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
dreſsed	O
as	O
a	O
Roman	O
Soldier	O
--	O
One	O
would	O
not	O
expect	O
such	O
malice	O
in	O
a	O
Roman	O
Soldier	O
--	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
natural	O
for	O
an	O
enthusiastic	O
Jew	O
--	O
The	O
face	O
of	O
this	O
Man	O
is	O
painted	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
place	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
poſsible	O
light	O
it	O
can	O
hardly	O
be	O
distinguished	O
&	O
some	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
Helmet	O
--	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
picture	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
figures	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
off	O
also	O
leading	O
the	O
two	O
Malefactors	O
sketched	O
in	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Cosway	B-pers
was	O
christened	O
in	O
this	O
Church	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
Nov	O
1742	O
--	O
&	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bath	I-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
born	O
in	O
this	O
parish	O
&	O
was	O
under	O
great	O
Obligations	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
who	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
beloved	O
&	O
most	O
deservedly	O
so	O
,	O
by	O
every	O
body	O
--	O
We	O
should	O
have	O
liked	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
uncommonly	O
fine	O
preacher	O
&	O
extremely	O
accomplished	O
&	O
his	O
Widow	O
makes	O
him	O
a	O
perfect	O
Angel	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
fishing	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
a	O
Saw	O
pit	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Sir	O
Mr.	B-pers
James	I-pers
does	O
not	O
like	O
fishing	O
or	O
shooting	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
runs	O
famously	O
after	O
a	O
Hare	O
a	O
Coursing	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
preacher	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
or	O
old	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
Country	O
that	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
preach	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
much	O
liked	O
if	O
his	O
Indolence	O
does	O
not	O
get	O
predominant	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
always	O
in	O
an	O
extreme	O
at	O
present	O
but	O
extremely	O
well	O
disposed	O
--	O
The	O
fishing	O
Season	O
is	O
over	O
--	O
I	O
caught	O
more	O
leaves	O
than	O
fish	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
excellent	O
sport	O
&	O
am	O
satisfied	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
&	O
two	O
others	O
dined	O
wh-	O
us	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Our	O
Conversation	O
was	O
principally	O
confined	O
to	O
the	O
good	O
News	O
from	O
Germany	B-place
--	O
The	O
Acct	O
.	O
you	O
mentioned	O
in	O
yr-	O
letter	O
of	O
Monday	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
,	O
is	O
not	O
confirmed	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
dispatches	O
are	O
not	O
arrived	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Allies	O
are	O
going	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
it	O
seems	O
very	O
probable	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
succeed	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
great	O
News	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wellington	I-pers
--	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sacrifice	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Sebastian	I-place
without	O
a	O
determination	O
to	O
proceed	O
into	O
France	B-place
&	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
infinite	O
Consequence	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
penetrate	O
as	O
far	O
a	O
s	O
Bourdeeaux	B-place
with	O
an	O
hostile	O
Army	O
--	O
Poor	O
Pill	O
Garlic	O
--	O
I	O
wonder	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
--	O
Cs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
hard	O
Service	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
if	O
his	O
Abilities	O
expand	O
wh-	O
his	O
Experience	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Officer	O
in	O
time	O
--	O
Morr	B-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
gratified	O
by	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
an	O
Anser	O
killed	O
or	O
wounded	O
--	O
the	O
black	O
Duck	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
favorite	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
thinks	O
he	O
dives	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
avoid	O
all	O
Danger	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
very	O
much	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
sensible	O
--	O
his	O
manners	O
are	O
uncommonly	O
gentle	O
&	O
mild	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
bred	O
&	O
agreeable	O
&	O
much	O
beloved	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
him	O
--	O
We	O
returned	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
at	O
first	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
twinkling	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
stars	O
&	O
our	O
Eyes	O
getting	O
by	O
degrees	O
accustomed	O
to	O
the	O
degree	O
of	O
borrowed	O
light	O
we	O
had	O
enabled	O
us	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
very	O
safe	O
--	O
We	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hayden	I-pers
Parkin	I-pers
here	O
Mr.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Paynter	I-pers
seems	O
very	O
weak	O
&	O
is	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
precarious	O
Situation	O
--	O
his	O
family	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
danger	O
or	O
they	O
wdnt	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
alone	O
&	O
teaze	O
him	O
with	O
busineſs	O
,	O
a	O
time	O
must	O
soon	O
come	O
when	O
they	O
must	O
supply	O
his	O
place	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
cheerful	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
&	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Bile	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
reaches	O
much	O
he	O
may	O
break	O
a	O
blood	O
Veſsel	O
again	O
&	O
go	O
off	O
immediately	O
--	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
the	O
Bird	O
did	O
not	O
arrive	O
eatable	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
feathers	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
--	O
James	B-pers
wished	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
2	O
Hares	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
declined	O
We	O
are	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
Coursing	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
to	O
scribble	O
to	O
my	O
Love	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Louisa	B-pers
made	O
a	O
lasting	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
--	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
delighted	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bigge	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
fortunate	O
--	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
She	O
was	O
well	O
at	O
first	O
--	O
I	O
didnt	O
expect	O
she	O
would	O
survive	O
the	O
Busineſs	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
reach	O
Plymouth	B-place
on	O
Tuesday	O
therefore	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
Stocks	O
on	O
Saturday	O
direct	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
Plymouth	B-place
Dock	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
again	O
after	O
Monday	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
long	O
Stay	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-place
I	O
only	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
place	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
will	O
satisfy	O
me	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
alone	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
Friday	O
are	O
the	O
days	O
for	O
seeing	O
Mount	B-place
Edgcumbe	I-place
--	O
I	O
shall	O
proceed	O
to	O
Clifton	B-place
after	O
satisfying	O
my	O
Curiosity	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-place
&	O
stay	O
there	O
two	O
days	O
&	O
then	O
direct	O
my	O
face	O
homewards	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
embrace	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
dearest	O
to	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
prepare	O
to	O
adonize	O
my	O
person	O
for	O
the	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
half	O
inclined	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salles	I-pers
before	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
as	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
Say	O
pretty	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
those	O
I	O
like	O
--	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Savile	I-pers
will	O
be	O
wh-	O
you	O
this	O
evening	O
at	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Affection	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
Minds	O
Eye	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
laugh	O
heartily	O
--	O
8	O
OClock	O
Good	O
morning	O
to	O
You	O
--	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
