TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
How	O
provoked	O
I	O
was	O
yesterday	O
!	O
--	O
after	O
stayi	O
n	O
g	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
by	O
two	O
--	O
but	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
on	O
whom	O
we	O
depended	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
us	O
till	O
near	O
three	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
miſsed	O
you	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
Town	B-place
early	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
&	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
on	O
Friday	O
--	O
there	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
in	O
November	O
&	O
have	O
many	O
hours	O
of	O
comfort	O
I	O
hope	O
--	O
write	O
me	O
word	O
of	O
your	O
plans	O
towards	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
affec	O
:	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
excuse	O
this	O
scrap	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
16	O
th	O
--	O
16	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
1788	O
Honble	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
