TOKEN	NE
Winchester	B-place
Sept——	O
11	O
th	O
--	O
My	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
Remember	O
that	O
you	O
desired	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
you	O
know	O
will	O
furnish	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
excuse	O
for	O
sending	O
you	O
a	O
dull	O
Letter	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
new	O
or	O
agreeable	O
to	O
relate	O
nothing	O
worthy	O
of	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
attention	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
scarcely	O
any	O
Bagatelle	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
relate	O
with	O
pleasure	O
to	O
you	O
may	O
I	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
hope	O
that	O
a	O
trifle	O
from	O
me	O
may	O
be	O
acceptable	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
pretty	O
motto	O
--	O
C'est	O
l'Amitie	O
qui	O
donne	O
le	O
prix	O
--	O
is	O
more	O
intelligible	O
to	O
you	O
than	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
deeply	O
engaged	O
in	O
musical	O
Entertainments	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
heard	O
two	O
Concerts	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
greatly	O
commend	O
,	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
--	O
the	O
Meſsiah	O
was	O
performed	O
in	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
--	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Choir	O
--	O
the	O
performers	O
were	O
attentive	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
degree	O
did	O
justice	O
to	O
this	O
sublime	O
Composition	O
--	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
heard	O
in	O
perfection	O
--	O
since	O
Handel	B-pers
conducted	O
the	O
Band	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
then	O
have	O
a	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
superiour	O
kind	O
to	O
experience	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
music	O
which	O
so	O
elevates	O
the	O
mind	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
particular	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Choruſses	O
--	O
which	O
have	O
an	O
astonishing	O
effect	O
--	O
&	O
really	O
seem	O
to	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
Milton	B-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
as	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
music	O
as	O
any	O
--	O
There	O
let	O
the	O
pealing	O
Organ	O
blow	O
To	O
the	O
full	O
voiced	O
choir	O
below	O
In	O
service	O
high	O
&	O
in	O
anthems	O
clear	O
,	O
As	O
may	O
with	O
sweetneſs	O
thro	O
'	O
mine	O
ear	O
Diſsolve	O
me	O
into	O
extacies	O
And	O
bring	O
all	O
Heav'n	O
before	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O
John	O
Milton	O
,	O
Il	O
Penseroso	O
.	O
the	O
echo	O
aſsisted	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
the	O
music	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
gained	O
credit	O
by	O
singing	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
songs	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
word	O
the	O
amateurs	O
were	O
pleased	O
--	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
an	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
tired	O
you	O
.	O
Today	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Oratorio	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
this	O
morn	O
at	O
eight	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
--	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
1	O
line	O
drawn	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
unfortunately	O
rain	O
prevented	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
regret	O
it	O
since	O
it	O
gives	O
me	O
leisure	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
one	O
--	O
&	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
I	O
enjoy	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sweetest	O
pleasures	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
--	O
I	O
recollect	O
with	O
pleasure	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
spent	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
&	O
which	O
your	O
society	O
made	O
as	O
agreeable	O
as	O
short	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
begun	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
injustice	O
to	O
deprive	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
stay	O
here	O
untill	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
this	O
family	O
with	O
regret	O
--	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
W——	I-pers
--	O
the	O
better	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
companion	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
those	O
winning	O
&	O
unaffected	O
manners	O
--	O
which	O
recommend	O
&	O
adorn	O
good	O
sense	O
&	O
learning	O
--	O
while	O
they	O
seem	O
to	O
conceal	O
these	O
excellencies	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
have	O
named	O
good	O
temper	O
seems	O
predominant	O
over	O
every	O
other	O
qualification	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
has	O
many	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
.	O
&	O
is	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
a	O
good	O
friend	O
--	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
an	O
amiable	O
wife	O
&	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
have	O
asked	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
his	O
Ode	O
to	O
fancy	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
pleased	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
should	O
think	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
Dodsley	B-pers
's	O
miscellanies	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
performed	O
with	O
music	O
the	O
first	O
Evening	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
i	O
s	O
a	O
fine	O
Ode	O
--	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
procure	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
literary	O
way	O
for	O
you	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
pleasure	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
--	O
hitherto	O
these	O
subjects	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
talked	O
of	O
--	O
We	O
saw	O
yesterday	O
some	O
drawings	O
in	O
Crayon	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
who	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
taught	O
,	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
struck	O
with	O
them	O
&	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
ought	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
master	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
has	O
copied	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
Guido	B-pers
--	O
I	O
believe	O
finely	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
head	O
of	O
our	O
Saviour	O
--	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Expreſsion	O
is	O
very	O
characteristic	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
so	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
woman	O
--	O
looks	O
sensible	O
&	O
agreeable	O
&	O
is	O
much	O
admired	O
here	O
--	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Collins	B-pers
,	O
A	O
Leonidas	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
are	O
both	O
well	O
&	O
unite	O
in	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
all	O
form	O
a	O
mutual	O
wish	O
--	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
us	O
could	O
it	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
accomplished	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
--	O
You	O
can	O
never	O
doubt	O
--	O
nor	O
never	O
need	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
of	O
my	O
Affection	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
Your	O
--	O
Anna-Maria	B-pers
