TOKEN	NE
1783	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
-	O
..	O
July	O
to	O
22	O
nd	O
-	O
..	O
Septr-	O
..	O
Les	O
Voyages	O
de	O
s	O
Klimius	O
en	O
la	O
Monde	O
Souterainne	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Thursday	O
that	O
d	O
--	O
like	O
d	O
th	O
.	O
great	O
to	O
every	O
probate	O
ye	O
next	O
day	O
ling	O
of	O
smoked	O
Kitchen	O
Maid	O
Tuesday	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Breakfasted	O
before	O
8	O
oClock	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
Whole	O
Morng	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
at	O
9	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
Ludvig	B-pers
Holberg	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
at	O
3	O
oClock	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
dined	O
only	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
her	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
7.	O
w	O
ent	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
ye	B-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Kings	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Codrington	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
St	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
filagree	O
paper	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Kensington	O
Gardens	O
walk	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
9.	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
some	O
Verses	O
out	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
at	O
10	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
sup	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
--	O
Wed	O
:	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
at	O
10	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
my	O
Cousin	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
&	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
--	O
Robert	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
came	O
to	O
inqure	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Letters	O
from	O
Madame	B-pers
Renaud	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
3	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
while	O
her	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
nes	I-pers
.	O
at	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
only	O
themselves	O
&	O
Children	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
my	O
Uncle	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Son	O
s	O
education	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
sat	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
I	O
W	O
e	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
&	O
sang	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
drank	O
tea	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
Frederick	B-pers
&	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Left	O
us	O
there	O
.	O
met	O
there	O
Hamilton	B-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
who	O
is	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
)	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
back	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Althorpe	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
eat	O
my	O
Bread	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Thursday	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
Miſs	B-pers
Molesworth	I-pers
at	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
wrote	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
conversed	O
till	O
3	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
again	O
he	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
came	O
away	O
at	O
7	O
when	O
Lucius	B-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
airing	O
.	O
Sat	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
till	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
we	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
&	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
ym	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Master	B-pers
Hamelton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
--	O
told	O
her	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Meſsage	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
but	O
miſs	O
'd	O
us	O
all	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
than	O
drove	O
me	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
crouded	O
with	O
Company	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
for	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
--	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
Country	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
drove	O
up	O
Constitution	O
Hill	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Amherst	I-pers
were	O
walking	O
before	O
their	O
door	O
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
sometime	O
to	O
converse	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
left	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
Supper	O
--	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
came	O
home	O
20	O
Min	O
past	O
11	O
oClock	O
Friday	O
18	O
July	O
1783	O
--	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
till	O
past	O
3	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
&	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
J	O
&	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
young	O
Mr	B-pers
came	O
in	O
before	O
dinner	O
&	O
Sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Tea	O
--	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
Man	O
:	O
Verses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
her	O
3	O
Sons	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
bread	O
&	O
Cheese	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
Man	O
:	O
letters	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
till	O
1	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Saturday	O
19	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
at	O
12	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
P—n	B-pers
(	O
his	O
sister	O
)	O
Mr	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
.	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Window	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boys	I-pers
paſs	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Vis	O
à	O
Vis	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
&	O
kiſs	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamelton	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
--	O
he	O
maintain	O
'd	O
an	O
argument	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
little	O
use	O
in	O
Reading	O
History	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
..	I-pers
P	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ws	I-pers
s	O
place	O
in	O
ye	B-place
.	I-place
Isle	I-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
&	O
c.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Col	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Cousin	O
s	O
Room	O
she	O
play	O
d	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
Sang	O
ye	O
Scotch	O
ballad	O
of	O
Auld	O
Robin	O
Gray	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tolomache	I-pers
came	O
in	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
went	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tating	I-pers
&	O
another	O
Lady	O
.	O
--	O
ye	O
eldest	O
Miſs	O
K	O
.	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
new	O
Prints	O
from	O
Dowg	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
drawings	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
wrote	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Emma	I-pers
Crewe	I-pers
came	O
soon	O
after	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
singular	O
story	O
relating	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
ye	O
Poet	O
&	O
a	O
Strange	O
Lady	O
whom	O
he	O
met	O
one	O
Night	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Play	O
house	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
stay	O
'd	O
Supper	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
brought	O
upstairs	O
--	O
we	O
separa	O
t	O
ed	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
Mr	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Sunday	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
word	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
finch	I-pers
s	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
violent	O
Heat	O
in	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
Thunder	O
&	O
Lightning	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
(	O
young	O
Mr	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
was	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
)	O
I	O
sup	O
'd	O
&	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burke	I-pers
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
Monday	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Morng	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
¼	O
before	O
4	O
went	O
and	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
--	O
Children	O
&	O
after	O
dinner	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
fainting	O
but	O
soon	O
recover	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
read	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
myself	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
to	O
read	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
Books	O
--	O
ye	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
Lake	O
of	O
Kalnary	O
&	O
c	O
Sup	O
'd	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
verses	O
after	O
Supper	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
Madame	B-pers
Renaud	I-pers
came	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
&	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bodinton	I-pers
is	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
s	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
10	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
at	O
3	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ditton	I-pers
.	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
together	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
went	O
at	O
4	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
only	O
themselves	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Boudoir	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
drove	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Little	O
Phaeton	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
P—	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
s	O
she	O
walk	O
'd	O
Back	O
again	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
Bardard	I-pers
s	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
lively	O
conversation	O
)	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
&	O
her	O
3	O
Sons	O
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
in	O
her	O
Phaeton	O
--	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
--	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
23	O
d	O
-	O
July	O
1783	O
at	O
11	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Phaeton	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
--	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Margate	B-place
to	O
day	O
--	O
we	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Phaeton	O
--	O
she	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
Grosvenor	O
Place	O
&	O
should	O
soon	O
be	O
back	O
to	O
receive	O
me	O
--	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr-	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
gave	O
them	O
their	O
dinner	O
--	O
a	O
little	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
(	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
tutor	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
brothers	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
from	O
town	O
we	O
strold	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
grounds	O
before	O
dinner	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Yard	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Ducks	O
&	O
fowls	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Rouen	B-place
Lady	B-pers
S—	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
c	O
+	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
me	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
after	O
Coffee	O
Mr.	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
walk	O
out	O
for	O
Some	O
time	O
--	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
we	O
spent	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
comfortably	O
together	O
conversed	O
about	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
c	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Netting	O
&	O
c	O
no	O
supper	O
but	O
wine	O
&	O
Water	O
&	O
bread	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
&	O
read	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
tutor	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Napiers	I-pers
Brothers	O
.	O
Thursday	O
July	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
Surry	B-place
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
sat	O
till	O
10	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Youngest	O
boys	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
little	O
card	O
carriages	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
12	O
Ldy	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Phaeton	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
4	O
little	O
Grays	O
to	O
Wimbleton	B-place
--	O
we	O
meant	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
none	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
w	O
e	O
re	O
down	O
but	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
little	O
Boy	O
whom	O
w	O
e	O
saw	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Grounds	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
very	O
beautiful	O
.	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
another	O
Gate	O
with	O
difficulty	O
got	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
who	O
kept	O
ye	O
Key	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
--	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
lane	O
before	O
we	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Phaeton	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
airing	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
had	O
--	O
some	O
Cold	O
Chicken	O
--	O
parted	O
at	O
3	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
one	O
Lady	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Althorpe	I-pers
Women	O
came	O
to	O
dreſs	O
my	O
hair	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
frederick	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Master	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
convers	O
ation	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
after	O
in	O
ye	O
Afternoon	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Council	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Autumn	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
&	O
Sang	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
or	O
near	O
8	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
left	O
alone	O
paſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
25	O
July	O
Wandsworth	O
Hill	O
.	O
Friday	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
B	O
:	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
...	I-pers
came	O
&	O
brought	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
desire	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
very	O
civil	O
&	O
attentive	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
play	O
'd	O
together	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
when	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
very	O
affectionately	O
--	O
on	O
Monday	O
next	O
--	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
Weymouth	B-place
for	O
6	O
Week	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
set	O
off	O
immediately	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
.	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
K	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
Lucius	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
out	O
I	O
merely	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
for	O
my	O
letters	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
&	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
near	O
nine	O
--	O
they	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
came	O
with	O
us	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
--	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Servants	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
K	B-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
read	O
till	O
late	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
.	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
.	O
London	B-place
.	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
11	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
.	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
near	O
4	O
walk	O
'd	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
enquired	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
G	O
Usher	O
)	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
also	O
after	O
dinner	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
upstairs	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
abt	O
.	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
(	O
Master	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
her	O
Sister	O
in	O
Law	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
their	O
quarrels	O
law	O
Suit	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
room	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
&	O
sang	O
we	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tom	I-pers
Pit	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
soon	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
after	O
8	O
I	O
took	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
she	O
was	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
airing	O
therefore	O
we	O
a	O
short	O
turn	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
.	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
sat	O
&	O
read	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
till	O
9	O
½	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
young	O
Brothers	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
very	O
agreeable	O
conversation	O
--	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
conduct	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
My	O
U	O
.	O
told	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
he	O
had	O
known	O
his	O
father	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
Took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Door	O
.	O
this	O
Eveg	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
with	O
half	O
ye	O
.	O
Verses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
an	O
invitat	O
ion	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
to	O
dine	O
there	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
Sunday	O
July	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
Church	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Phaeton	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Know	O
me	O
)	O
--	O
before	O
dinner	O
we	O
read	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
s	O
Epistle	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchelsea	I-pers
&	O
admired	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
deserved	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Youth	O
from	O
Westm-	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
also	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
we	O
went	O
Kensington	O
Gardens	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
eldest	O
Boy	O
who	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
cleverest	O
&	O
most	O
agreeable	O
Children	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
went	O
wth	O
us	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
5	O
.	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
retired	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
.	O
sat	O
sometime	O
upon	O
ye	O
Ground	O
under	O
ye	O
.	O
Shade	O
of	O
trees	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
where	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
goes	O
every	O
Morng	O
till	O
at	O
wth	O
..	O
her	O
Children	O
&	O
c	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
c	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Monday	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
July	O
1783	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chiswick	B-place
&	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
a	O
school	O
kept	O
by	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
detirmin	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
Son	O
There	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Frederick	B-pers
s	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
(	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Door	O
)	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Kitty	B-pers
was	O
out	O
.	O
M	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
tea	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
oClock	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
little	O
Mr	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
an	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
Phaeton	O
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
North	O
End	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
confin	O
'd	O
there	O
10	O
days	O
--	O
saw	O
Kitty	B-pers
who	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
us	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
still	O
keeps	O
his	O
bed	O
but	O
is	O
better	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nosely	I-pers
Ill	O
from	O
anxiety	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
11	O
Tuesday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
--	O
wrote	O
Letters	O
.	O
at	O
1	O
oClock	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
s	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
¼	O
of	O
4	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
only	O
his	O
family	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
at	O
6	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
she	O
sang	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
in	O
ye	O
Green	O
Park	O
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Nurse	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
--	O
found	O
her	O
&	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
hers	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
3	O
Girls	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
calling	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
9	O
oClock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
c	O
Wednesday	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
ashamed	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
therefore	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
&	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
read	O
&	O
workd	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
she	O
&	O
Frederick	B-pers
were	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
I	O
found	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
s	O
ode	O
to	O
Dragon	O
&	O
a	O
Paper	O
in	O
ye	O
Adventurer	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
fatiguing	O
her	O
&	O
left	O
her	O
¼	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
&	O
waited	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
return	O
--	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
s	O
little	O
boy	O
gave	O
him	O
money	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
&	O
Francis	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	I-pers
8th	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
with	O
her	O
his	B-pers
first	I-pers
known	I-pers
son	I-pers
went	O
away	O
my	O
Servt	O
.	O
attended	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
Supper	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
Thursday	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
oClock	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
street	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
Court	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Spa	B-place
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
whom	O
Miſs	B-pers
M—	I-pers
gave	O
orders	O
for	O
Medicines	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Journey	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
told	O
me	O
poor	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
died	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Devanyes	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
we	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
found	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Ladies	O
come	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
came	O
out	O
in	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
wth-	O
Lucius	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
&	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Devonshire	O
House	O
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Child	O
--	O
a	O
pretty	O
little	O
Girl	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
its	O
Cradle	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Shew	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
Child	O
s	O
fine	O
Christening	O
Suit	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
then	O
carried	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
home	O
again	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
parted	O
wth-	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
she	O
made	O
witneſs	O
ye	O
.	O
terms	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
correspond	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S—	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Pencil	O
case	O
to	O
wear	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
D—	I-pers
a	O
young	O
Lawer	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
when	O
Lucius	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
Lady	B-pers
D—	I-pers
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Chair	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
engaged	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
before	O
7	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
s	O
account	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
them	O
aloud	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepy	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
Lucan	B-pers
had	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
writing	O
desk	O
--	O
he	O
read	O
to	O
us	O
all	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
s	O
Epistle	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
10	O
before	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
lelf	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
staid	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
them	O
&	O
then	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
..	O
August	O
1783	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
till	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
P	I-pers
s	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
there	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
was	O
out	O
)	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
M.	B-pers
P.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
dusk	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
12	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
Saturday	O
--	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
Transcribing	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
book	O
.	O
at	O
3	O
little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morell	I-pers
--	O
poor	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
not	O
so	O
well	O
these	O
2	O
last	O
days	O
&	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
fruit	O
&	O
wine	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
sat	O
there	O
the	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
Mr	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
till	O
½	O
9	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
intention	O
of	O
Laying	O
in	O
in	O
ye	O
Country	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
Autumn	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jenny	I-pers
B—	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
B	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Chair	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
brought	O
away	O
&	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
ye	O
Country	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Sunday	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
August	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Brother	O
came	O
at	O
before	O
Church	O
time	O
they	O
reproach	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
near	O
them	O
so	O
long	O
--	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
we	O
sat	O
talking	O
after	O
my	O
Cousins	O
went	O
upstairs	O
till	O
7	O
oClock	O
.	O
conversing	O
abt	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
Brother	O
--	O
his	O
nearneſs	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
title	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Cousins	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
telling	O
me	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
apprehensions	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Absentee	O
Tax	O
projecting	O
for	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
c	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
&	O
sang	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
&	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
--	O
ye	O
parks	O
were	O
crouded	O
with	O
Company	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Woman	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Lodge	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
talked	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
whom	O
she	O
had	O
nursed	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
pretty	O
kind	O
of	O
woman	O
.	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
then	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
accompan	O
ed	O
ie	O
d	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
s	O
door	O
&	O
we	O
parted	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
her	O
eldest	O
&	O
youngest	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
returnd	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Country	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
since	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Brother	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
9	O
&	O
almost	O
dark	O
.	O
as	O
we	O
paſsed	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
Street	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
their	O
Window	O
we	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
we	O
paſs	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
poems	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
&	O
Village	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
.	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
c	O
Monday	O
4	O
th	O
..	O
August	O
1783	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandfords	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
--	O
she	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
books	O
whilst	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
my	O
uncle	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
2	O
--	O
sat	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
where	O
the	O
furniture	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
there	O
Mr.	B-pers
Crabbe	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s-page	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
old	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
had	O
carried	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Nicolia	I-pers
s	O
Scholole	O
at	O
Chiswick	B-place
this	O
morning	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
her	O
Sister	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
rather	O
better	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
s	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
had	O
not	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
ye	O
Country	O
(	O
Inglefield	B-place
Green	I-place
near	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
)	O
till	O
6	O
oClock	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
was	O
alone	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
--	O
wrote	O
Letters	O
&	O
c	O
Tuesday	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
.	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
some	O
books	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
said	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
had	O
been	O
ill	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Night	O
but	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
7	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
they	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
but	O
left	O
us	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
&	O
must	O
give	O
up	O
nursing	O
her	O
Child	O
--	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
--	O
when	O
her	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
of	O
absence	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
ye	O
little	O
boy	O
&	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
I	O
soon	O
came	O
away	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
attended	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
U	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
in	O
bo	O
d	O
n	O
d	O
street	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
Lodge	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
Dr	B-pers
J	I-pers
was	O
ill	O
.	O
my	O
U	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
fruit	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
all	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
expecting	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Searle	I-pers
to	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
Eſsex	B-place
--	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
desired	O
to	O
dinner	O
for	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
one	B-pers
of	I-pers
ye	I-pers
Grevilles	I-pers
from	O
Dover	B-place
wch	O
.	O
informed	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
had	O
been	O
taken	O
ill	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
&	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
their	O
journey	O
to	O
Spa	B-place
this	O
affected	O
my	O
Spirits	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
recd	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
inform	O
yt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
had	O
not	O
recd	O
my	O
letters	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
Wednesday	O
Thursday	O
6	O
7	O
th	O
August	O
1783	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
heard	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
had	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
of	O
a	O
Princeſs	O
wrote	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
her	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
2	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
he	O
staid	O
only	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
Commiſsions	O
--	O
till	O
4	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
&	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
6	O
--	O
sent	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
Wakes	I-pers
s	O
Porter	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
franks	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
then	O
went	O
out	O
&	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
Phaeton	O
a	O
¼	O
before	O
8	O
&	O
arrived	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Eſsex	B-place
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
ye	O
Moon	O
shone	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Eveg	O
--	O
found	O
Dr	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
&	O
all	O
her	O
4	O
Children	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
--	O
Little	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
my	O
bedfellow	O
.	O
Friday	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
--	O
Eſsex	B-place
Honey	O
lane	O
Upsh	O
.	O
Got	O
up	O
before	O
8	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
we	O
breakfast	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Little	O
boudoir	O
--	O
I	O
decorated	O
some	O
Plans	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Charlotte	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
Children	O
their	O
leſsons	O
drew	O
some	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Plans	O
--	O
read	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
P	O
&	O
Chapters	O
.	O
then	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Bliks	O
Ldy	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Eſsays	O
in	O
ye	O
Belles	O
Letters	O
at	O
1	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
wth	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
show	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
fine	O
Prospect	O
--	O
Blair	B-pers
then	O
join	O
us	O
&	O
we	O
walkd	O
till	O
2.	O
came	O
in	O
ye	B-pers
2	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
W	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
we	O
dine	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
upstairs	O
I	O
draw	O
for	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
she	O
wrote	O
letters	O
at	O
6	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
tea	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Catton	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
Horseback	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Phaeton	O
took	O
a	O
delightfull	O
airing	O
in	O
ye	O
forest	O
--	O
very	O
fine	O
views	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
till	O
past	O
9	O
by	O
Moonlight	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
ye	O
poor	O
Servt	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Eſsex	B-place
Saturday	O
10	O
th	O
August	O
1783	O
After	O
breakfast	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Seat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
by	O
myself	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
read	O
till	O
ten	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
at	O
12	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Waltham	B-place
Abbey	I-place
mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
in	O
ye	O
Phaeton	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Beate	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beate	I-pers
&	O
on	O
Horseback	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
rode	O
together	O
we	O
left	O
our	O
Horses	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Cock	O
inn	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
walk	O
'd	O
through	O
ye	O
Church	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
&	O
handsome	O
one	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
we	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
Abbey	I-place
--	O
this	O
Abbey	O
was	O
pulld	O
down	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
some	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
P	O
ond	O
wch	O
.	O
goes	O
round	O
a	O
Square	O
Garden	O
of	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
a	O
mile	O
we	O
drag	O
'd	O
for	O
fish	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
under	O
a	O
large	O
El	O
m	O
--	O
saw	O
ye	O
fine	O
tulip	O
tree	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
Little	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
went	O
after	O
dinner	O
to	O
a	O
Book	O
Club	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
rode	O
on	O
first	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
was	O
Kept	O
in	O
remembrance	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
8	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
NB	O
Waltham	B-place
is	O
abt	O
.	O
2	O
Miles	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
rents	O
ye	O
Abbey	O
Gardens	O
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Abbey	O
Garden	O
--	O
he	O
rents	O
ym-	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
Sunday	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
August	O
1783	O
Eſsex	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
very	O
Ill	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
--	O
we	O
fear	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
My	O
Room	O
after	O
breakfast	O
ye	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
Morng	O
..	O
Richard	B-pers
came	O
&	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
nursed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Apothecary	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
came	O
&	O
a	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
a	O
tradesman	O
from	O
Waltham	B-place
)	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
prescribed	O
a	O
Powder	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
after	O
tea	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
to	O
attend	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
kept	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
staid	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
When	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
some	O
of	O
Marianne	B-pers
s	O
Belles	O
Lettres	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
wch	O
was	O
at	O
9	O
Sr	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
soon	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Blair	B-pers
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
poorly	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
Monday	O
11	O
th	O
August	O
1783	O
Upshire	O
farm	O
Wm	B-pers
rather	O
better	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
&	O
had	O
little	O
Ldy	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
me	O
he	O
learnt	O
his	O
Leſson	O
&	O
I	O
decorated	O
Plans	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
out	O
at	O
2	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
alter	O
my	O
dreſs	O
--	O
at	O
3	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
Richard	B-pers
at	O
Charlotte	B-pers
s	O
di	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
&	O
dined	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
draw	O
ye	O
Plans	O
Mr	B-pers
Hillardon	I-pers
went	O
&	O
lay	O
down	O
from	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
till	O
6	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
Marianne	B-pers
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
tea	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Rutledge	I-pers
made	O
tea	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
drew	O
ye	O
Plans	O
.	O
made	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
eat	O
some	O
Cordial	O
--	O
Marianne	B-pers
&	O
c	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
9	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
11	O
OClock	O
Tuesday	O
12	O
--	O
Marianne	B-pers
rather	O
better	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
after	O
breakfast	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
--	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
consulted	O
me	O
abt	O
ye	O
Miſs	O
W—	O
s	O
going	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
c	O
at	O
1	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
call	O
upon	O
poor	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Cottage	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
&	O
was	O
Ill.	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
&	O
was	O
drove	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
thunder	O
storm	O
wch	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
last	O
long	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dreſs	O
me	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Mrs	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
and	O
her	O
daughters	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
room	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
bed	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
drank	O
tea	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
6.	O
then	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Jeſsop	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
towards	O
ye	O
forest	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
a	O
Hamlet	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
a	O
medicine	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
let	O
Lodgings	O
--	O
at	O
15	O
s	O
a	O
week	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
of	O
a	O
Lord	O
s	O
Son	O
&	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
last	O
--	O
we	O
prolong	O
'd	O
our	O
walk	O
till	O
8	O
--	O
came	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
in	O
Marianne	B-pers
s	O
Lectures	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dowset	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
had	O
leave	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
&	O
c	O
at	O
Supper	O
we	O
jok	O
'd	O
ye	O
Gentlem	O
e	O
n	O
abt	O
ye	O
.	O
Story	O
we	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
10	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beate	I-pers
went	O
up	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
powders	O
I	O
staid	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
&	O
wrote	O
my	O
Journal	O
.	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
we	O
took	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
turns	O
before	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
by	O
Moonlight	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
oClock	O
Wednesday	O
13	O
th	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dowset	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
2	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Miſs	O
W	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
fields	O
--	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
dreſs	O
at	O
2	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
out	O
on	O
horseback	O
&	O
little	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
&	O
I	O
was	O
entertaind	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
at	O
9	O
all	O
together	O
except	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
Thursday	O
14	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
therefore	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
as	O
we	O
had	O
intended	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
at	O
my	O
House	O
&	O
c.	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
town	B-place
wth	O
.	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
my	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Richard	B-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
a	O
--	O
walk	O
about	O
2	O
--	O
went	O
towards	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
s	O
farm	O
--	O
a	O
pretty	O
Hamlet	O
&	O
fields	O
&	O
c.	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
3	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
alter	O
my	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
him	O
whilst	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
c	O
w	O
en	O
t	O
upstairs	O
&	O
c.	O
till	O
6	O
had	O
him	O
movd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
room	O
&	O
made	O
him	O
stay	O
below	O
till	O
tea	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
carried	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Knowle	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
7.	O
took	O
a	O
delightful	O
walk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
forest	O
/	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
/	O
almost	O
lost	O
ourselves	O
--	O
gather	O
wild	O
flowers	O
sat	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Ground	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
found	O
us	O
out	O
&	O
conducted	O
us	O
home	O
.	O
came	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
Staid	O
&	O
talkd	O
wth-	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
after	O
my	O
Walk	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Friday	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
Upshire	O
Farm	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
sometime	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
who	O
was	O
Ill	O
in	O
bed	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Gout	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
work	O
'd	O
to	O
aſsist	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
doing	O
things	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
--	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
again	O
abt	O
.	O
5	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B—	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
tea	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
we	O
all	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
boudoir	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wakes	I-pers
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Bed	O
in	O
ye	O
next	O
Room	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
made	O
tea	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eve.g	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W—	I-pers
.	O
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
so	O
fine	O
that	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
open	O
Air	O
before	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
after	O
Supper	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
made	O
him	O
eat	O
some	O
toast	O
&	O
drink	O
some	O
wine	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
again	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
oClock	O
Saturday	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
not	O
better	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	B-place
--	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
--	O
executed	O
m	O
y	O
a	O
ny	O
Commiſsions	O
--	O
walk	O
to	O
Berckley	O
Square	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
went	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Daughters	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
to	O
place	O
ym	O
.	O
there	O
for	O
3	O
Months	O
till	O
she	O
gets	O
a	O
Governeſs	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
books	O
&	O
c	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
returnd	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
before	O
7	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
so	O
melancholy	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cs	I-pers
prevented	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
Town	B-place
till	O
near	O
8	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Post-boy	O
was	O
not	O
punctual	O
to	O
his	O
time	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Aven	O
for	O
fruits	O
bought	O
some	O
for	O
Betty	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
fine	O
I	O
gave	O
Miſs	B-pers
J	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Ldy-	B-pers
W—	I-pers
s	O
Epistle	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
to	O
read	O
.	O
we	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
friendship	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
other	O
Sex	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
arrived	O
at	O
Upshire	O
farm	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
in	O
bed	O
&	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Sunday	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
Eſsex	B-place
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
Great	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
prayers	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
Afternoon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
was	O
his	O
Cousin	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
New	B-place
York	I-place
where	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
--	O
mention	O
'd	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Skyles	I-pers
took	O
a	O
delightful	O
walk	O
--	O
up	O
an	O
aſsent	O
.	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
ye	O
graſs	O
saw	O
fine	O
&	O
extensive	O
Prospects	O
I	O
walk	O
wth	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
after	O
Supper	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
went	O
up	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
sat	O
&	O
talkd	O
wth	O
me	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
him	O
my	O
friendship	O
&	O
advice	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
bed	O
ye	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
day	O
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
after	O
dinner	O
Monday	O
18	O
--	O
August	O
Eſsex	B-place
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
still	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
We	O
were	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
aſ	O
poſsible	O
during	O
ye	O
day	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Evening	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Ride	O
in	O
ye	O
forest	O
wth-	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
little	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
wth-	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
.	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
boudoir	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Walk	O
--	O
had	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
do	O
up	O
my	O
Hair	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
Supper	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
upon	O
ye	O
similiarity	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sense	O
of	O
Smell	O
&	O
Taste	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
s	O
lectures	O
to	O
day	O
Tuesday	O
2	O
1	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Ldy-	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
very	O
ill	O
all	O
day	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
moved	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
bed	O
made	O
.	O
we	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
surprising	O
Meteor	O
of	O
a	O
ball	O
of	O
fire	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
by	O
Ldy-	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
many	O
other	O
people	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
ye	O
last	O
night	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
.	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
sat	O
wth	O
..	O
Blair	B-pers
in	O
ye	O
boudoir	O
Read	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Beete	I-pers
--	O
lectures	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
fruit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
&	O
sat	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
after	O
tea	O
for	O
busineſs	O
for	O
Blair	B-pers
&	O
c	O
Wm	B-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
Walk	O
after	O
8	O
oclock	O
--	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
Supper	O
.	O
after	O
Supper	O
we	O
paid	O
visits	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
gave	O
him	O
Gin	O
&	O
Milk	O
&	O
Water	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
book	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
After	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
was	O
in	O
bed	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
to	O
talk	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
Wednesday	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
afterward	O
sat	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
--	O
Next	O
about	O
12	O
read	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Lectures	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
better	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
on	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
out	O
on	O
horseback	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
staid	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
till	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt-	O
9	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
he	O
wrote	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
's	O
Narrative	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
walk	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
&	O
field	O
adjoining	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
Supper	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
wrote	O
letters	O
for	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
me	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
--	O
Thursday	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
better	O
.	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
write	O
letters	O
--	O
then	O
sat	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
we	O
read	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
near	O
3	O
.	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
of	O
Waltham	B-place
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
Blair	B-pers
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
Sat	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
(	O
6	O
oClock	O
)	O
after	O
tea	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Barwick	I-pers
&	O
I	O
rode	O
out	O
I	O
rode	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
horse	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
way	O
&	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
change	O
Horses	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Servt	O
.	O
as	O
Mine	O
stumbled	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
convers	O
ation	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
delightful	O
ride	O
--	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
forest	O
&	O
through	O
a	O
Plantation	O
--	O
fine	O
Views	O
&	O
c	O
came	O
home	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
staid	O
Supper	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
below	O
--	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
Good	O
night	O
Friday	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Morng	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
fields	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
below	O
.	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
by	O
Star	O
light	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ts	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Satry	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Morng	O
as	O
usual	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
up	O
&	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Ride	O
as	O
far	O
towards	O
Wood	O
Ridden	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
read	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
book	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
till	O
Supper	O
time	O
.	O
read	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
after	O
Supper	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sunday	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
to	O
Church	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
Read	O
Prayers	O
in	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Room	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
cold	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
.	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
below	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
sat	O
below	O
ye	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
Papers	O
--	O
it	O
raind	O
&	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
read	O
Richard	B-pers
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
me	O
till	O
supper	O
time	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
up	O
to	O
supper	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
&	O
conversed	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
respecting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Monday	O
25	O
th	O
..	O
August	O
1783	O
--	O
spent	O
ye	O
Morng	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Violent	O
Thunder	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Blair	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
got	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
read	O
Pope	B-pers
&	O
c.	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
was	O
dreſsing	O
my	O
Hair	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
read	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
translation	O
from	O
ye	O
french	O
play	O
of	O
Boneval	O
--	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
w	O
e	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
finish	O
it	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
Blair	B-pers
came	O
&	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
propose	O
riding	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
below	O
--	O
I	O
change	O
my	O
dreſs	O
&	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Ride	O
I	O
rode	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
s	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
an	B-pers
old	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
,	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
me	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
cool	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleansant	O
ride	O
in	O
ye	O
forest	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
dark	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
--	O
After	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
up	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Richard	B-pers
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
me	O
Tuesday	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
--	O
Eſsex	B-place
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
his	O
bed	O
side	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
&	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
him	O
below	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
him	O
in	O
drawing	O
Plans	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
ye	O
apothecary	O
came	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
wrote	O
letter	O
s	O
to	O
Blair	B-pers
.	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
below	O
after	O
Ten	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
rode	O
out	O
,	O
calld	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
ye	O
Entrance	O
into	O
Waltham	B-place
for	O
writing	O
Paper	O
--	O
got	O
of	O
my	O
Horse	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
prolong	O
'd	O
our	O
ride	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
dusk	O
the	O
forest	O
way	O
.	O
found	O
Hammond	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
both	O
low	O
&	O
c	O
Sup	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
Wm-	B-pers
read	O
a	O
few	O
pages	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
before	O
Supper	O
.	O
when	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
went	O
up	O
after	O
Supper	O
we	O
were	O
rather	O
merry	O
I	O
made	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
a	O
Cap	O
of	O
Paper	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Wednesday	O
27	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Blair	B-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
breakfast	O
in	O
ye	O
fields	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
time	O
to	O
breakfast	O
below	O
he	O
was	O
low	O
&	O
poorly	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
turn	O
in	O
garden	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
went	O
out	O
on	O
Horseback	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
whilst	O
her	O
Hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Rode	O
out	O
Blair	B-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
tea	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
what	O
I	O
desired	O
&	O
c	O
Richard	B-pers
went	O
into	O
ye	O
other	O
room	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
&	O
we	O
conversed	O
together	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Wm-	B-pers
till	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
their	O
ride	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
before	O
Supper	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Thursday	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
August	O
Eſsex	B-place
1783	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
Wm-	B-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
bed	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
tea	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
.	O
brought	O
Me	O
some	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Themes	O
--	O
read	O
also	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
s	O
Lectures	O
.	O
about	O
11	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
Blair	B-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
--	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
/	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
ye	O
Boudoir	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
Work	O
'd	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Blair	B-pers
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
rode	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Steward	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
went	O
to	O
sit	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
drawing	O
Room	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
them	O
Came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
had	O
conversation	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
we	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
ye	O
Afternoon	O
&	O
Evg	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
settling	O
about	O
our	O
Journey	O
into	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
Tommorrow	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
before	O
Supper	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
my	O
hair	O
.	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
ye	O
paper	O
wch	O
.	O
inclosed	O
it	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barden	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
Wm	B-pers
read	O
a	O
few	O
pages	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
we	O
then	O
all	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
after	O
Supper	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
read	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
he	O
had	O
written	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
went	O
upstairs	O
before	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
or	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Friday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
Eſsex	B-place
1783	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
Blair	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
7.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
down	O
Stairs	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
set	O
off	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
for	O
Courteenhall	B-place
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
attended	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
Stage	O
on	O
Horseback	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
&	O
Little	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
There	O
got	O
upon	O
his	O
little	O
Pony	O
&	O
rode	O
to	O
Hartford	B-place
--	O
at	O
Hartford	B-place
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
had	O
Coffee	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
parted	O
from	O
us	O
to	O
return	O
home	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
then	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
Chaise	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
talkd	O
&	O
read	O
(	O
had	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Promenades	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
s	O
Chymistry	O
for	O
Books	O
)	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Brickhill	B-place
where	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
when	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Stony	B-place
Stratford	I-place
to	O
change	O
horses	O
ask	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Women	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Inn	O
abt	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
Mile	O
from	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
saw	O
a	O
Coach	O
That	O
had	O
been	O
overturn	O
'd	O
--	O
Thompson	B-pers
ask	O
ye	O
.	O
Maid	O
Servt	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
aſsistance	O
&	O
c	O
ye	O
.	O
Family	O
s	O
Name	O
were	O
Fullers	O
Bankers	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
ye	O
Ladies	O
had	O
gone	O
on	O
in	O
Carriages	O
that	O
had	O
overtaken	O
them	O
.	O
Rouſseau	B-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
for	O
ye	O
Recovery	O
of	O
her	O
limbs	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
ye	O
use	O
of	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
age	O
of	O
40	O
--	O
met	O
Watson	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
3	O
Children	O
taking	O
an	O
airing	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
Stony	B-place
Strattford	I-place
She	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
3	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
ye	O
young	O
Child	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
we	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
got	O
to	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
abt	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
the	O
Morng	O
had	O
been	O
raining	O
--	O
but	O
h	O
e	O
ld	O
up	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Graftons	I-pers
&	O
I	O
Slept	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
little	O
bed	O
Chamber	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
August	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
1783	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
--	O
strol	O
'd	O
About	O
&	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
some	O
foſsils	O
in	O
ye	O
Gravel	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
settling	O
with	O
her	O
Servants	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
Garden	O
.	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Rooms	O
over	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Stables	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
&	O
Col	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
--	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
oClock	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
arranged	O
her	O
Drawers	O
--	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
ye	O
Things	O
from	O
London	B-place
for	O
ye	O
..	O
House	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
aſsisted	O
in	O
winding	O
Silk	O
&	O
c	O
wch	O
.	O
&	O
dr	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
held	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
dinner	O
did	O
not	O
dine	O
till	O
near	O
4.	O
after	O
dinner	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Store	O
Room	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
Garden	O
before	O
tea	O
.	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
6	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
something	O
more	O
to	O
ye	O
Medley	O
Screen	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Spring	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Manuscript	O
books	O
--	O
one	O
Subject	O
wch	O
she	O
had	O
treated	O
on	O
was	O
Marriage	O
ye	O
.	O
duties	O
of	O
a	O
Wife	O
--	O
&	O
She	O
then	O
read	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
letters	O
--	O
Show	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
upon	O
ye	O
Subject	O
of	O
Womans	O
being	O
learned	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
upstairs	O
in	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
ye	O
.	O
Conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
love	O
friendship	O
Marriage	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Sunday	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
August	O
Courteen	B-place
hall	I-place
dr	O
.	O
little	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
School	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
Ride	O
upon	O
his	O
little	O
Horse	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Northampton	B-place
&	O
Then	O
get	O
into	O
a	O
Chaise	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Gardiner	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
finished	O
our	O
breakfast	O
I	O
strol	O
'd	O
about	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
in	O
our	O
walk	O
had	O
our	O
hair	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
at	O
2	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
Preachd	O
&	O
read	O
Prayers	O
.	O
after	O
Church	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
Walk	O
till	O
dinner	O
was	O
ready	O
After	O
dinner	O
sat	O
sometime	O
talkd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
&	O
c	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
saw	O
his	O
Sister	O
himself	O
&	O
Brother	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
Garden	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
one	O
stor	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
fine	O
fruit	O
we	O
staid	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vokes	I-pers
s	O
Game	O
keeper	O
walk	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Gate	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bouvrie	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Plantation	O
&	O
Read	O
a	O
Paper	O
in	O
ye	O
World	O
.	O
a	O
threatning	O
Storm	O
drove	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
--	O
it	O
soon	O
Thunder	O
'd	O
&	O
Lightningd	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
was	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
violently	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vokes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
Dreſsing	O
Room	O
--	O
read	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
--	O
Bible	O
conversed	O
upon	O
different	O
Subjects	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
Sc	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
oClock	O
Monday	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
.	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
after	O
breakfast	O
we	O
Separated	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
as	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
farmers	O
&	O
c	O
on	O
busineſs	O
at	O
12	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
--	O
at	O
2	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
Horse	O
.	O
With	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
to	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
got	O
there	O
abt-	O
3	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
pretty	O
good	O
Health	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
her	O
)	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
cold	O
meat	O
&	O
c	O
brought	O
--	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vokes	I-pers
till	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
:	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
paſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Window	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
she	O
took	O
an	O
oppertunity	O
whilst	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
Room	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
Lace	O
to	O
trim	O
a	O
gown	O
..	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Saw	O
her	O
old	O
maid	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bennion	I-pers
&	O
her	O
2	O
3	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
got	O
on	O
my	O
Horse	O
&	O
rode	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
office	O
no	O
letters	O
.	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Locock	I-pers
--	O
(	O
ye	O
.	O
old	O
Clergyman	O
)	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
met	O
also	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
ye	O
Bookseller	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
at	O
b	O
y	O
ye	O
Croſs	O
in	O
Coming	O
home	O
ye	O
Horse	O
Threw	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
but	O
little	O
hurt	O
&	O
desired	O
Betty	B-pers
ye	O
Servt	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
Courteenhall	B-place
abt	O
.	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
reading	O
&	O
ye	O
Globes	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
had	O
Supper	O
&	O
e	O
arly	O
after	O
Supper	O
she	O
read	O
many	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
s	O
letters	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
was	O
Married	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
1783	O
Courteen	B-place
hall	I-place
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
ready	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
farm	O
yard	O
--	O
spoke	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartry	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Barley	O
field	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
Garden	O
.	O
gather	O
'd	O
Nosegay	O
fed	O
ye	O
Rabbits	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
Sat	O
together	O
reading	O
&	O
writing	O
till	O
we	O
parted	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
out	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
System	O
of	O
Religion	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Beete	I-pers
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
conversed	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Late	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Old	B-pers
Fravel	I-pers
&	O
Warden	B-pers
&	O
c.	O
we	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
Plantation	O
,	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Seat	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
two	O
first	O
Books	O
Cantos	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Rape	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Lock	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
finish	O
'd	O
our	O
Walk	O
--	O
gather	O
'd	O
what	O
flowers	O
we	O
could	O
came	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
6	O
--	O
After	O
Tea	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
whilst	O
Ldy	O
.	O
Settled	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Cook	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
--	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
--	O
I	O
added	O
to	O
ye	O
Medly	O
Screen	O
--	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
&	O
Read	O
to	O
me	O
Manuscripts	O
&	O
Extracts	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
out	O
before	O
her	O
Marriage	O
After	O
Supper	O
--	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
tickets	O
&	O
Coins	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
Books	O
&	O
settled	O
every	O
thing	O
for	O
our	O
Journey	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
parted	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1783	O
dr.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Courteenhall	B-place
abt	O
.	O
8	O
oClock	O
got	O
to	O
Cosgrove	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Wills	I-pers
s	O
abt	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
met	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Carriag	O
g	O
e	O
w	O
hen	O
we	O
got	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
slept	O
There	O
--	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
stood	O
Godmother	O
Yesterday	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
s	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mansell	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
received	O
us	O
very	O
kindly	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
There	O
--	O
saw	O
their	O
daughter	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
ab	O
.	O
3	O
years	O
&	O
½	O
&	O
a	O
lovely	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
abt	O
2	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
They	O
have	O
2	O
other	O
Boys	O
at	O
School	O
--	O
&	O
have	O
lost	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
we	O
left	O
Them	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
10.	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriage	O
again	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Albans	I-place
where	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Cold	O
dinner	O
&	O
staid	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Col	B-pers
M—	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
who	O
keeps	O
ye	O
.	O
Inn	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
long	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
by	O
Illneſs	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
White	O
frock	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Hertford	B-place
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
horses	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
whe	O
had	O
tea	O
&	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
near	O
8	O
oClock	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
&	O
rainy	O
Eve.g	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
uneasy	O
--	O
Coll	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
came	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
we	O
made	O
her	O
sit	O
down	O
&	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Rhyming	O
questions	O
&	O
c	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
farm	O
wth	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
horses	O
--	O
&	O
got	O
safe	O
there	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
given	O
over	O
expecting	O
us	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
but	O
came	O
down	O
we	O
had	O
supper	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
soon	O
after	O
Supper	O
&	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
below	O
--	O
got	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
found	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
very	O
wel	O
l	O
&	O
not	O
so	O
lame	O
as	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
past	O
Septr	O
..	O
4	O
th	O
..	O
Eſsex	B-place
1783	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
indisposed	O
by	O
not	O
having	O
slept	O
all	O
night	O
cold	O
in	O
my	O
limbs	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
my	O
breakfast	O
at	O
9	O
.	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
comb	O
'd	O
out	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
hair	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
Boudoir	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
wth	O
:	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
open	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
Room	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
came	O
&	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
Morng	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
s	O
(	O
his	O
late	O
Stewards	O
)	O
affairs	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
turn	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
garden	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
Cold	O
&	O
windy	O
&	O
damp	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
--	O
We	O
then	O
separated	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
as	O
usual	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Bird	O
wch	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
--	O
After	O
tea	O
Mr	B-pers
Barden	I-pers
read	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
me	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
begun	O
a	O
Drawing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
Supper	O
we	O
conversd	O
went	O
early	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
had	O
Fires	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Friday	O
--	O
The	O
Weather	O
cold	O
&	O
windy	O
--	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
till	O
near	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
employd	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Papers	O
--	O
had	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
gown	O
After	O
dinner	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Blair	B-pers
went	O
&	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
Walk	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
wth	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
farmers	O
&	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
ye	O
other	O
Room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
tea	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
an	O
Atorney	O
from	O
Waltham	B-place
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
.	O
an	O
agreeable	O
lively	O
Man	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
went	O
into	O
ye	O
dining	O
Room	O
to	O
settle	O
accounts	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jeſsop	I-pers
&	O
me	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
Supper	O
time	O
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
Mr	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
11	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
up	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
s	O
we	O
wrote	O
notes	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
us	O
we	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
4	O
Candles	O
to	O
his	O
bedside	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Saturday	O
--	O
High	O
wind	O
&	O
wrote	O
letters	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
to	O
dreſs	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
sat	O
on	O
with	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
while	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
a	O
little	O
Walk	O
&	O
c	O
Septr	O
.	O
7	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Septr	O
.	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
plans	O
to	O
shade	O
wth	O
.	O
colors	O
--	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
--	O
Room	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
came	O
at	O
6	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
After	O
tea	O
I	O
continued	O
shading	O
Plans	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W—	I-pers
did	O
t	O
h	O
is	O
Latin	O
Verses	O
Wm-	B-pers
read	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
room	O
settling	O
accounts	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
I	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
Supper	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
in	O
giving	O
each	O
other	O
Rhymes	O
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
Blair	B-pers
had	O
a	O
farmer	O
in	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I.	O
continued	O
our	O
Rhymes	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
wrote	O
notes	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
Septr	O
.	O
9	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Sunday	O
--	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
made	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
me	O
draw	O
Plans	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
Prayers	O
--	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
Prayers	O
.	O
continued	O
drawing	O
--	O
Plans	O
(	O
Colord	O
)	O
till	O
near	O
3.	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
me	O
before	O
dinner	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
a	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Son	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Counting	O
House	O
)	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
sat	O
by	O
ye	O
fire	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
Mr.	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
on	O
Self	O
Knowledge	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
Book	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
to	O
tea	O
&	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
cut	O
out	O
prints	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
sat	O
next	O
me	O
let	O
him	O
read	O
in	O
my	O
Manuscript	O
book	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
soon	O
after	O
Mason	B-pers
went	O
.	O
Monday	O
9	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
-	O
1783	O
Septr	O
..	O
Wind	O
&	O
Rain	O
.	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
till	O
my	O
Room	O
was	O
ready	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Mended	O
&	O
lookd	O
out	O
my	O
things	O
for	O
ye	O
Week	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
1	O
&	O
shaded	O
Plans	O
for	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
near	O
2	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Came	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dreſs	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Laid	O
down	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
finish	O
'd	O
another	O
plan	O
before	O
dinner	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
till	O
near	O
4	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
farmer	O
all	O
Morng	O
upon	O
Busineſs	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
farmer	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
a	O
sensible	O
old	O
Man	O
&	O
well	O
behaved	O
.	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
w	O
e	O
talk	O
upon	O
Shooting	O
&	O
c.	O
Separated	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
sometime	O
below	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
my	O
Journal	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
below	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6.	O
after	O
tea	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
read	O
in	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Work	O
'd	O
Wm	B-pers
cut	O
out	O
prints	O
for	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
who	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
then	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
was	O
uncomfortable	O
we	O
however	O
continued	O
our	O
Reading	O
&	O
c	O
till	O
Supper	O
½	O
past	O
9.	O
uncomfortable	O
conversation	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
undreſsing	O
&	O
c	O
Tuesday	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
--	O
cold	O
Wind	O
&	O
Rain	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
badneſs	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
going	O
to	O
Harlow	O
Bush	O
fair	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
busy	O
looking	O
over	O
papers	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
--	O
just	O
ran	O
up	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
put	O
on	O
another	O
Habit	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
shaded	O
Plans	O
(	O
in	O
ye	O
drawing	O
Room	O
)	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Political	O
paper	O
was	O
uncomfortable	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
but	O
poorly	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
down	O
at	O
our	O
request	O
read	O
a	O
few	O
pages	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
before	O
Supper	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
only	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
was	O
at	O
another	O
table	O
looking	O
over	O
accounts	O
--	O
he	O
soon	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
Silk	O
Needles	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
11	O
talk	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Septr	O
..	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Wednesday	O
Eſsex	B-place
ye	O
.	O
anniversary	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
father	O
s	O
death	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
my	O
B	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
upon	O
my	O
tea	O
Spoon	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
11	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
below	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
went	O
out	O
Shooting	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Harlow	O
Bush	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
read	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
below	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
dinner	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
after	O
dinner	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
towards	O
ye	O
.	O
forest	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
staid	O
behind	O
&	O
took	O
rather	O
a	O
longer	O
walk	O
.	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
tea	O
abt	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
room	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
in	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
we	O
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
Quarto	O
Sup	O
'd	O
rather	O
before	O
7	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
Eclipse	O
--	O
soon	O
after	O
Supper	O
left	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr-	B-pers
C	I-pers
Blair	B-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
till	O
1	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Eclipse	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Moon	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Septr	O
..	O
11	O
.	O
Eſsex	B-place
1783	O
Breakfast	O
rather	O
before	O
9	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
uncomfortable	O
.	O
after	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
staid	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
ye	O
Papers	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	O
fire	O
below	O
--	O
took	O
my	O
Work	O
--	O
sat	O
there	O
sometime	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
&	O
read	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Iliad	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
whilst	O
her	O
Hair	O
was	O
curling	O
read	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Annual	O
Reigister	O
--	O
just	O
chang	O
'd	O
my	O
dreſs	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
before	O
dinner	O
.	O
a	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
an	O
Anabaptist	O
Clergyman	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
who	O
smoked	O
his	O
pipe	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
wth	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
all	O
Morng	O
.	O
as	O
was	O
Homer	B-pers
abt	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
affairs	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
til	O
most	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
abt	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Polly	B-pers
s.	O
drank	O
tea	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barden	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
tea	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
9	O
fine	O
Moon	O
light	O
night	O
--	O
we	O
repeated	O
Verses	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
&	O
c.	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
abt	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
&	O
&	O
c	O
Sepbr	O
.	O
12	O
--	O
1783	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
then	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Colnett	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
wrote	O
letters	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
Room	O
below	O
--	O
&	O
Conversed	O
till	O
near	O
dinner	O
time	O
separated	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jeſsop	I-pers
had	O
a	O
holliday	O
he	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collnett	I-pers
went	O
out	O
Shooting	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
A—	O
Parson	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
but	O
Wm	B-pers
did	O
not	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Ride	O
only	O
accompanied	O
by	O
ye	O
Servt	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
till	O
7	O
ye	O
.	O
Ride	O
pleasant	O
--	O
but	O
ye	O
Wind	O
Cold	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
Mr	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
was	O
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Shooting	O
&	O
had	O
not	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
any	O
succeſs	O
&	O
after	O
Tea	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
went	O
to	O
leſsons	O
till	O
Supper	O
time	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
us	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
The	O
Eveg	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Sepr	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
dreſs	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
had	O
B	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
being	O
tired	O
with	O
my	O
Ride	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
Blair	B-pers
had	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
in	O
to	O
reprove	O
him	O
for	O
Shooting	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
post	O
Chaise	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
he	O
sat	O
me	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
--	O
him	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
was	O
pleased	O
at	O
seeing	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
when	O
Young	B-pers
Woolstanholmn	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
my	O
Uncle	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Door	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
10	O
.	O
--	O
made	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
imagine	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
expreſsd	O
great	O
concern	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
after	O
Supper	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
all	O
ye	O
.	O
news	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
abt	O
.	O
11	O
Septr	O
.	O
14	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
ask	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
.	O
After	O
B	O
.	O
staid	O
on	O
below	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
fire	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Church	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
as	O
did	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
plans	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Church	O
--	O
a	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
upstairs	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
whilst	O
she	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
did	O
my	O
hair	O
I	O
kept	O
on	O
my	O
habit	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
We	O
separated	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
for	O
½	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
After	O
tea	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
read	O
till	O
Supper	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
cut	O
out	O
prints	O
wrote	O
notes	O
&	O
c	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
taken	O
not	O
Well	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
took	O
drops	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
Supper	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
Soon	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
left	O
Mr.	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
we	O
put	O
a	O
f	O
l	O
annel	O
petycoat	O
round	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
s	O
head	O
whehn	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
15	O
Monday	O
Septr	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
After	O
B	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
&	O
mended	O
my	O
Things	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
she	O
went	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Waltham	B-place
I	O
drew	O
plans	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
..	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
at	O
2	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
home	O
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
no	O
one	O
at	O
home	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
--	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
nearly	O
din	O
'd	O
before	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beete	I-pers
came	O
in	O
from	O
shooting	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
succeſs	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
below	O
till	O
tea	O
time	O
at	O
tea	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
tea	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
to	O
Waltham	B-place
Mr	B-pers
C	I-pers
Lecture	O
.	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Took	O
her	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Cock	O
Inn	O
.	O
--	O
the	O
Lecture	O
vulgar	O
horrid	O
--	O
company	O
as	O
bad	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
Tuesday	O
15	O
th	O
..	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
as	O
usual	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
--	O
Wm	O
.	O
came	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
abt	O
1	O
.	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
.	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
Work	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
decorated	O
a	O
plan	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
as	O
Usual	O
after	O
tea	O
read	O
&	O
Work	O
'd	O
as	O
usual	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
wrote	O
by	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
rainy	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Monday	O
16	O
th	O
Novbr-	O
1781	O
--	O
The	O
family	O
came	O
to	O
settle	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
This	O
entry	O
is	O
written	O
upside	O
down	O
,	O
like	O
the	O
December	O
1781	O
dates	O
on	O
p.62	O
,	O
indicating	O
that	O
Mary	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
on	O
these	O
sheets	O
in	O
1781	O
before	O
re-using	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
entries	O
of	O
September	O
1783	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
17	O
th	O
Abt	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
