TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
enclosing	O
the	O
long	O
&	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
detail	O
of	O
the	O
Academy	O
at	O
Brunswick	B-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
carefully	O
lay	O
by	O
in	O
case	O
it	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
an	O
eligible	O
plan	O
some	O
time	O
hence	O
to	O
finish	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
education	O
there	O
;	O
at	O
present	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
no	O
objection	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
is	O
too	O
little	O
advanced	O
in	O
knowledge	O
to	O
receive	O
benefit	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
really	O
improving	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chauvet	I-pers
has	O
aſsured	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
satisfied	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
leſs	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
than	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
obliging	O
to	O
represent	O
the	O
small	O
attention	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
power	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
in	O
so	O
favorable	O
a	O
light	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
think	O
extremely	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
deserves	O
.	O
In	O
spight	O
of	O
the	O
Amusements	O
of	O
this	O
Town	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
his	O
impatience	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
your	O
society	O
was	O
visible	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
pay	O
£1025	O
being	O
the	O
Principal	O
&	O
Interest	O
due	O
upon	O
your	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
next	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
Bond	O
will	O
be	O
Personal	O
Property	O
which	O
I	O
may	O
convey	O
by	O
Will	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
please	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
shou	O
'd	O
make	O
a	O
Conveyance	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
some	O
Person	O
as	O
my	O
Trustee	O
,	O
to	O
guard	O
against	O
the	O
objection	O
of	O
my	O
appearing	O
both	O
Debitor	O
&	O
Creditor	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
Agent	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
the	O
proper	O
Instrument	O
&	O
instructions	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Blank	O
for	O
my	O
Trustee	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
fixed	O
upon	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
the	O
money	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
getting	O
a	O
proper	O
discharge	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Heretable	O
Bond	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
without	O
loſs	O
of	O
time	O
for	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
necessary	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
The	O
money	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	O
hands	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
convenient	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
without	O
putting	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
a	O
journey	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
all	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
terrible	O
alarm	O
,	O
which	O
thank	O
God	O
is	O
now	O
over	O
;	O
poor	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooke	I-pers
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
utmost	O
danger	O
at	O
Winchester	B-place
from	O
a	O
putrid	O
fever	O
&	O
sore	O
throat	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
&	O
James	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
days	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
was	O
also	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
no	O
plan	O
of	O
any	O
excursion	O
for	O
this	O
summer	O
&	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
stay	O
in	O
Town	B-place
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saving	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
attending	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
s	O
education	O
who	O
is	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
many	O
Masters	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
improving	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
being	O
told	O
so	O
by	O
others	O
who	O
may	O
be	O
better	O
judges	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
your	O
cousin	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
believing	O
me	O
ever	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
April	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
.	O
April	O
13	O
--	O
1786	O
