TOKEN	NE
Madam	O
,	O
After	O
so	O
long	O
silence	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
no	O
doubt	O
wonder	O
at	O
my	O
begging	O
leave	O
to	O
offer	O
you	O
these	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
lines	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
waiting	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
having	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
your	O
family	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
last	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
'have	O
hitherto	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
waited	O
in	O
vain	O
;	O
being	O
upon	O
Guard	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
week	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
newspaper	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
exceedingly	O
surprised	O
and	O
grieved	O
at	O
reading	O
a	O
paragraph	O
from	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Friend	O
and	O
acquaintence	O
as	O
the	O
late	O
Robt	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
was	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
imediately	O
resolved	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
sorrow	O
is	O
indeed	O
very	O
great	O
;	O
the	O
news	O
struck	O
me	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
little	O
expected	O
;	O
never	O
having	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
his	O
illneſs	O
till	O
then	O
:	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
nothing	O
can	O
aleviate	O
the	O
gri	O
e	O
f	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
welfare	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whome	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
most	O
sincere	O
complements	O
and	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
accept	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
most	O
obedient	O
and	O
most	O
Obliged	O
Servant	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Sept	O
:	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
:	O
1771	O
.	O
To	O
Robt	B-pers
:	I-pers
Keith	I-pers
