TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
5	O
Minutes	O
left	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Line	O
before	O
the	O
Post	O
goes	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
sad	O
Catastrophe	O
that	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Packet	O
being	O
taken	O
that	O
carried	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
&	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
are	O
involv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Distreſs	O
,	O
I	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
inform	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
that	O
they	O
are	O
safe	O
&	O
well	O
at	O
Vigo	B-place
in	O
Spain	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
landed	O
by	O
the	O
American	O
Privateer	O
(	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
sail	O
'd	O
)	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
herself	O
wrote	O
me	O
this	O
Account	O
.	O
't	O
is	O
probable	O
Mr	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
has	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Intelligence	O
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
but	O
as	O
all	O
Posts	O
are	O
attended	O
wth	O
.	O
uncertainties	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
a	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
to	O
have	O
such	O
Authentick	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Safety	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Story	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
we	O
know	O
,	O
my	O
Letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Sure	O
you	O
will	O
pity	O
us	O
all	O
for	O
this	O
distreſs	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C.Finch	B-pers
I	O
wrote	O
by	O
the	O
Packet	O
that	O
sail	O
'd	O
last	O
Sunday	O
July	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
both	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
.	O
Caldas	B-place
July	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
1781	O
--	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
