TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
110	O
Grosvr	O
.	O
Sqr-	O
Febry	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
health	O
and	O
spirits	O
,	O
will	O
plead	O
apology	O
for	O
teazing	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
when	O
perhaps	O
you	O
are	O
better	O
engaged	O
than	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
dull	O
letter	O
scrall	O
but	O
I	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
on	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
as	O
since	O
your	O
last	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
satisfied	O
about	O
you	O
--	O
Nervous	O
complaints	O
are	O
so	O
teazing	O
and	O
lingering	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
distreſst	O
about	O
you	O
having	O
seen	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
those	O
I	O
loved	O
--	O
therefore	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
I	O
try	O
to	O
comfort	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
often	O
true	O
idea	O
:	O
no	O
news	O
,	O
good	O
news	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
dont	O
always	O
satisfie	O
me	O
--	O
We	O
left	O
Scotland	B-place
in	O
very	O
severe	O
weather	O
the	O
ground	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Snow	O
and	O
the	O
ice	O
six	O
inches	O
deep	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
favorable	O
for	O
our	O
travelling	O
as	O
it	O
smooth	O
'd	O
the	O
rough	O
roads	O
and	O
enabled	O
us	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
four	O
days	O
&	O
half	O
from	O
Edinbr	B-place
.	I-place
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
ease	O
;	O
my	O
Sister	O
who	O
had	O
grown	O
fat	O
and	O
enjoyed	O
better	O
health	O
than	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
back	O
unfortunately	O
took	O
a	O
cold	O
by	O
a	O
cold	O
bed	O
at	O
Bowroughbridge	B-place
which	O
has	O
given	O
her	O
furr	O
and	O
relaxation	O
&	O
c	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
kept	O
house	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
getting	O
better	O
and	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
airing	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
--	O
as	O
among	O
other	O
complaints	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
deaff	O
,	O
it	O
confined	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
uncomfortable	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
,	O
therefore	O
dont	O
expect	O
much	O
acount	O
of	O
the	O
Grand-Monde	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
preparing	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
--	O
can	O
only	O
tell	O
you	O
coming	O
from	O
our	O
fine	O
clear	O
air	O
sharp	O
and	O
cold	O
into	O
this	O
smokey	O
region	O
with	O
weather	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
pleasant	O
and	O
suitable	O
to	O
April	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
so	O
hot	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
case	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
alarmed	O
and	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fever	O
--	O
but	O
joking	O
apart	O
I	O
dont	O
recollect	O
such	O
at	O
this	O
season	O
of	O
ye	O
year	O
,	O
sunday	O
,	O
last	O
:	O
Kensington	O
Gardens	O
was	O
crouded	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
every	O
body	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
Benches	O
,	O
Men	O
walking	O
with	O
Hats	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
and	O
others	O
carring	O
the	O
ladies	O
Muffs	O
who	O
having	O
dreſst	O
for	O
Feb	O
:	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
so	O
hot	O
a	O
sun	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
bare	O
trees	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
summer	O
day	O
:	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
continued	O
as	O
fine	O
every	O
since	O
but	O
the	O
wind	O
a	O
little	O
cooler	O
--	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
pitied	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
spite	O
of	O
the	O
Methodism	O
which	O
has	O
suported	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
and	O
well	O
she	O
must	O
feel	O
:	O
supose	O
you	O
know	O
Sir	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
went	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
I	O
think	O
East-bourn	B-place
and	O
then	O
saw	O
Miſs	B-pers
Monson	I-pers
s	O
maid	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
attatchment	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
off	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
a	O
daughter	O
he	O
wrote	O
for	O
a	O
special	O
licence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
refused	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
unusual	O
to	O
grant	O
unleſs	O
with	O
Familly	O
consent	O
--	O
upon	O
which	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
wrote	O
to	O
the	O
ArchBishop	O
saying	O
her	O
son	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
would	O
conduce	O
to	O
his	O
happineſs	O
that	O
indeed	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
the	O
only	O
recompense	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
the	O
Young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
good	O
sence	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
judge	O
of	O
what	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
happy	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
live	O
altogether	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
retired	O
having	O
rather	O
refused	O
with	O
hauteur	O
the	O
compt	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
familly	O
offerr	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
of	O
visiting	O
and	O
receiving	O
his	O
Lady	O
--	O
our	O
new	O
Dutcheſs	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
--	O
report	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
pleasing	O
,	O
very	O
little	O
and	O
very	O
civil	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
makes	O
a	O
better	O
Curtsey	O
than	O
has	O
been	O
seen	O
at	O
court	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
--	O
but	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
very	O
delicate	O
and	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
hours	O
:	O
so	O
has	O
her	O
dinner	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
;	O
sups	O
when	O
He	O
dines	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
he	O
goes	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
evening	O
amusement	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
finds	O
London	B-place
very	O
dull	O
,	O
and	O
dislikes	O
their	O
new	O
house	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
dont	O
wonder	O
at	O
--	O
was	O
always	O
surprised	O
at	O
their	O
changeing	O
,	O
for	O
surely	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
have	O
brought	O
such	O
an	O
adition	O
to	O
the	O
familly	O
as	O
that	O
a	O
house	O
built	O
for	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
would	O
not	O
hold	O
her	O
--	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
tis	O
no	O
wonder	O
they	O
say	O
she	O
dislikes	O
England	B-place
and	O
wishes	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
:	O
indeed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
wisest	O
thing	O
they	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
H.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
chuses	O
to	O
frequent	O
Brookes	B-place
's	I-place
and	O
loses	O
large	O
sums	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
should	O
always	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
contracted	O
the	O
extrordinary	O
method	O
of	O
receiving	O
when	O
he	O
wins	O
and	O
not	O
paying	O
when	O
he	O
loses	O
:	O
nobody	O
ought	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
loses	O
--	O
but	O
if	O
this	O
continues	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
they	O
will	O
cutt	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
imagined	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
Germany	B-place
and	O
take	O
up	O
his	O
Dignity	O
as	O
Bishop	O
--	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
since	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
enters	O
into	O
the	O
Grand-monde	O
--	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
happier	O
for	O
both	O
perhaps	O
if	O
she	O
declines	O
it	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
made	O
him	O
a	O
speech	O
when	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
that	O
must	O
have	O
surprised	O
him	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
bowed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Marlbro	I-pers
'	I-pers
has	O
at	O
last	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
so	O
all	O
parties	O
are	O
happy	O
.	O
the	B-pers
Old	I-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
still	O
lives	O
and	O
is	O
unoticed	O
by	O
those	O
who	O
ought	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
extrordinary	O
in	O
the	O
Childish	O
state	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
for	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
prevent	O
her	O
exposeing	O
herself	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
our	O
old	O
friend	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
new	O
lease	O
,	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
Tour	O
into	O
Somersetshire	B-place
last	O
summer	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
complaints	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
General	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
Staff	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
:	O
that	O
commiſsion	O
ends	O
in	O
Octr	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
visit	O
London	B-place
this	O
winter	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
news	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
ask	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
intent	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
apologise	O
for	O
its	O
stupidity	O
;	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
Husband	O
joyn	O
me	O
in	O
compts	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
La	O
Charmante	O
Louise	B-pers
which	O
concludes	O
me	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Yours	O
very	O
sincerely	O
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
