TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1805	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
much	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
reaching	O
the	O
Respondents	O
case	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
important	O
fishing	O
Cause	O
,	O
You	O
sent	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
some	O
pains	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
decypher	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
restore	O
it	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
You	O
may	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
eſsential	O
injustice	O
to	O
posterity	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
often	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
allow	O
You	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
imagine	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
comfortleſs	O
,	O
when	O
separated	O
from	O
my	O
family	O
.	O
There	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
consequence	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
command	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
obeyed	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
tyrannise	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
the	O
very	O
picture	O
of	O
insignificance	O
itself	O
.	O
This	O
present	O
week	O
,	O
is	O
rather	O
one	O
of	O
annoyance	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
on	O
friday	O
.	O
The	O
Event	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
hear	O
of	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
the	O
accounts	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
sells	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
will	O
force	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
many	O
more	O
Letters	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
inclination	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
habits	O
of	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Exeter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
delivering	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
Courtiers	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
de	I-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
intimate	O
friend	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Fitzherbert	I-pers
,	O
&	O
consequently	O
a	O
very	O
proper	O
Governeſs	O
for	O
the	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
and	O
her	O
place	O
is	O
filled	O
up	O
in	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
Establishment	O
,	O
but	O
why	O
,	O
how	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
story	O
about	O
poor	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
perfectly	O
true	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
Cathcart	O
Children	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
your	O
husband	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
your	O
daughter	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Morrison	B-pers
my	O
Countrywoman	O
&	O
your	O
Lumbago	O
'd	O
Self	O
,	O
I	O
send	O
my	O
Love	O
,	O
Compliments	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
s	O
faithful	O
friend	O
and	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Sixth	O
March	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
