TOKEN	NE
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
anſwered	O
yours	O
as	O
fully	O
as	O
poſsible	O
so	O
pray	O
my	O
dear	O
Girl	O
write	O
me	O
soon	O
,	O
nay	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
furnish	O
you	O
wt	O
a	O
Subject	O
so	O
no	O
excuse	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
taken	O
adieu	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
most	O
faithfull	O
&	O
sincere	O
friend	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
yr	O
name	O
on	O
yr	O
book	O
in	O
ye	O
new	O
fashioned	O
place	O
&	O
indeed	O
ye	O
best	O
place	O
where	O
poſsible	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
once	O
more	O
my	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
adieu	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Free	O
Ja	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dundas	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
