TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
It	O
requires	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
second	O
Sight	O
to	O
discover	O
why	O
You	O
dont	O
right	O
write	O
,	O
when	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Your	O
known	O
&	O
incurable	O
Indolence	O
will	O
furnish	O
a	O
full	O
answer	O
to	O
your	O
question	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
pray	O
observe	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
find	O
fault	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
about	O
writing	O
.	O
For	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
Justice	O
enough	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
composition	O
,	O
to	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
excuse	O
in	O
others	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
frequently	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
myself	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
prediction	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
relate	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
Revolution	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
connexion	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
“	O
A	O
captive	O
King	O
humbled	O
”	O
can	O
not	O
mean	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
Captive	O
.	O
The	O
Black	O
Eagle	O
can	O
not	O
mean	O
the	O
despicable	O
King	B-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
,	O
Austria	B-place
,	O
is	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
intended	O
by	O
that	O
sign	O
.	O
The	O
Lion	O
of	O
Leon	B-place
is	O
purple	O
.	O
May	O
not	O
purple	O
be	O
considered	O
as	O
black	O
.	O
Allowing	O
these	O
two	O
points	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prediction	O
will	O
import	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Infamous	O
Napoleon	B-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
demolished	O
,	O
by	O
Spain	B-place
&	O
Austria	B-place
.	O
The	O
captive	O
King	O
humbled	O
,	O
is	O
Ferdinand	B-pers
7th-	I-pers
;	O
humbled	O
,	O
by	O
having	O
been	O
forced	O
to	O
resign	O
his	O
pretensions	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
Spain	B-place
;	O
restored	O
by	O
the	O
Patriotism	O
of	O
the	O
Spaniards	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
,	O
is	O
just	O
as	O
plain	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prophecy	O
itself	O
.	O
Brunswic	B-place
's	O
Lion	O
is	O
.	O
Blue	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
remarkably	O
frisky	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
three	O
Weeks	O
Tour	O
in	O
the	B-place
Highlands	I-place
,	O
visiting	O
the	O
Trosachs	B-place
,	O
Loch	O
Earn	O
,	O
Duneira	O
,	O
Ochtertyne	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
No	O
sooner	O
did	O
we	O
return	O
from	O
that	O
excursion	O
,	O
than	O
off	O
I	O
set	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
another	O
Tour	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Roxburghshire	B-place
&	O
Selkirkshire	B-place
,	O
introducing	O
them	O
to	O
Thirlestane	O
,	O
the	O
ancient	O
Seat	O
of	O
their	O
Forefathers	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
-	O
Mary	O
's	O
Loch	O
,	O
Melrose	O
&	O
Dryburgh	O
Abbies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
During	O
this	O
last	O
excursion	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
unexpected	O
peice	O
of	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
Arriving	O
at	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
He	O
asked	O
very	O
particularly	O
after	O
my	O
Eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
my	O
replying	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
bluntly	O
said	O
“	O
then	O
You	O
dont	O
know	O
,	O
“	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
--	O
”	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
by	O
desiring	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
my	O
William	B-pers
,	O
dated	O
Ivica	B-place
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
This	O
rather	O
disconcerted	O
me	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
certainty	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
released	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
captivity	O
,	O
was	O
some	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
uneasineſs	O
about	O
him	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
himself	O
dated	O
Gibraltar	B-place
14	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
arrived	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
still	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
cause	O
,	O
or	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Letters	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
through	O
Spain	B-place
,	O
and	O
Barbary	B-place
,	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
reached	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
second	O
Boy	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
sailed	O
with	O
the	O
Expedition	O
under	O
Sir	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Wellesley	I-pers
.	O
We	O
have	O
ha	O
d	O
two	O
Letters	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
Cork	B-place
,	O
and	O
are	O
daily	O
expecting	O
some	O
accounts	O
of	O
the	O
landing	O
of	O
the	O
Troops	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
know	O
from	O
another	O
source	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
debarking	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Brothers	O
are	O
now	O
near	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
good	O
fortune	O
to	O
meet	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
Henrietta	B-pers
is	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
your	O
enquiries	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
can	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
personal	O
recollection	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yesterday	O
since	O
she	O
saw	O
You	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
.	O
As	O
Maiden	O
Ladies	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
time	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
fond	O
of	O
being	O
reminded	O
of	O
Occurrences	O
long	O
paſsed	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
dangerous	O
to	O
hint	O
that	O
She	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
You	O
,	O
were	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Memory	O
has	O
been	O
frequently	O
refreshed	O
on	O
that	O
subject	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
having	O
done	O
You	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
talking	O
of	O
You	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Your	O
Husband	O
&	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
My	O
Lady	O
's	O
civilities	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
make	O
a	O
formal	O
Compliment	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Grandpapa	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
My	O
Countrywoman	O
's	O
Letter	O
has	O
been	O
forwarded	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Second	O
September	O
1808	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
