TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
morng	O
7	O
Oclock	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mama	O
Mrs-	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sat	O
there	O
till	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
next	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
fine	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
her	O
manners	O
and	O
dreſs	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
;	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
is	O
not	O
pretty	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
pretty	O
figure	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
very	O
vulgar	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Chicksands	B-place
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Library	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
gothic	O
Room	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
O	I-pers
:	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Calder	I-pers
and	O
two	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
very	O
pleasing	O
,	O
unaffected	O
,	O
young	O
Women	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
very	O
polite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
soon	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
began	O
to	O
converse	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dreſs	O
--	O
the	O
party	O
at	O
dinner	O
consisted	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
Ladies	O
Colonel	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
(	O
not	O
unlike	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
)	O
Sir	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Calder	I-pers
,	O
son	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
about	O
19	O
very	O
chearful	O
and	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
's	O
Colonel	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
Uncle	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
's	O
are	O
Nieces	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Calder	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
joined	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Eveng	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
)	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
We	O
all	O
worked	O
,	O
talked	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
till	O
Eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
Mr-	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
young	O
Colonel	B-pers
.	I-pers
O	I-pers
:	I-pers
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
tired	O
and	O
soon	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
is	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Trees	O
this	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
yesterday	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
my	O
white	O
paper	O
Puzzles	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
delighted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
any	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
foreign	O
Gentleman	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
amuses	O
himself	O
with	O
drawing	O
he	O
puts	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
book	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
binding	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
me	O
pretty	O
sketches	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
help	O
smiling	O
,	O
such	O
attempts	O
at	O
drawing	O
!	O
Sir	B-pers
H.C	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
wild	O
about	O
shooting	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
Papa	O
liked	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
O	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
good	O
sport	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
boasted	O
that	O
Mr-	B-pers
Pickford	I-pers
kill	O
'd	O
17	O
brace	O
of	O
birds	O
before	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
Gentlemanlike	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
already	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
poacher	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
the	O
Weather	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
rains	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
races	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
Bedford	B-place
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
Rooms	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
being	O
number	O
'd	O
there	O
is	O
over	O
every	O
door	O
a	O
Greek	O
word	O
,	O
painted	O
on	O
the	O
Wall	O
to	O
distinguish	O
them	O
,	O
like	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
says	O
I	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
Monday	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
at	O
what	O
hour	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
return	O
in	O
a	O
Hack	O
:	O
Chaise	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mama	O
Yr	O
.	O
very	O
dutiful	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Daughter	O
LD	B-pers
:	I-pers
My	O
my	O
most	O
affecte-	O
love	O
to	O
dear	O
Papa	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Beds	B-place
:	I-place
