TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
seen	O
a	O
paragraph	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
wch	O
.	O
has	O
much	O
affected	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
being	O
true	O
--	O
the	O
sudden	O
death	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
apprehend	O
this	O
event	O
will	O
severely	O
afflict	O
M	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
take	O
ye	O
.	O
liberty	O
of	O
requesting	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
frm	O
.	O
your	O
Lordship	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
how	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
sustain	O
such	O
a	O
shock	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
convey	O
my	O
sincere	O
condolence	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Lord	O
ever	O
y	O
most	O
Affly-	O
Yours	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Decbr	O
.	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
