TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
Saffron	B-place
Walden	I-place
Eſsex	B-place
Febry	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
do	O
--	O
&	O
most	O
particulary	O
do	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
the	O
dear	O
Lou	B-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
now	O
feeling	O
recover	O
'd	O
--	O
not	O
long	O
ago	O
Mrs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
mention	O
'd	O
having	O
read	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
wherein	O
you	O
mention	O
state	O
,	O
that	O
yr	O
dear	O
Child	O
was	O
all	O
but	O
well	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
well	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
pronounce	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
so	O
--	O
these	O
longings	O
of	O
mine	O
cd	O
have	O
been	O
sooner	O
made	O
known	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
circumstances	O
,	O
viz	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
relapse	O
at	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
hard	O
frost	O
.	O
this	O
vex	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
recourse	O
to	O
Medicine	O
&	O
dine	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
&	O
recover	O
'd	O
very	O
Stupid	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Thing	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
our	O
Aunt	B-pers
Blosset	I-pers
.	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
--	O
&	O
alth	O
'	O
o	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
us	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
Property	O
,	O
yet	O
as	O
She	O
lived	O
&	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
ours	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
.	O
&	O
the	O
Lease	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
occupied	O
in	O
writing	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
death	O
&	O
my	O
orders	O
to	O
our	O
Agent	O
has	O
occasion	O
'd	O
our	O
making	O
a	O
discovery	O
not	O
very	O
favorable	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
formerly	O
Employ	O
'd	O
by	O
us	O
--	O
or	O
you	O
wd	O
actively	O
wonder	O
what	O
could	O
occupy	O
these	O
Sisters	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Selling	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
never	O
saw	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
love	O
to	O
investigate	O
very	O
deeply	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
therefore	O
obliged	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
constrain	O
them	O
from	O
being	O
too	O
open	O
,	O
besides	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
when	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
fine	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Whisky	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
our	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
too	O
apt	O
to	O
Goſsip	O
with	O
my	O
ing	O
Miſs	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
we	O
are	O
all	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
in	O
great	O
anxiety	O
for	O
her	O
Health	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
add	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
so	O
flourishing	O
a	O
state	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
--	O
she	O
grows	O
thin	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
weak	O
--	O
&	O
sometimes	O
Coughs	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
upon	O
our	O
knees	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
resists	O
unmercifully	O
--	O
but	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
discovery	O
does	O
this	O
make	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
so	O
good	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
delightful	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
Unpersuadable	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
melancholy	O
thing	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
human	O
nature	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
perfect	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
quite	O
understand	O
the	O
Politicks	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
seems	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
Pitt	B-pers
.	O
&	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
Supports	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
he	O
will	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
are	O
decided	O
opponents	O
.	O
to	O
poor	O
Addington	B-pers
--	O
&	O
are	O
not	O
very	O
gentle	O
in	O
their	O
A	O
d	O
Animadversions	O
on	O
his	O
Measures	O
--	O
we	O
pray	O
however	O
for	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
the	O
definitive	O
Treaty	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
one	O
report	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
Credit	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
credit	O
--	O
that	O
Ad——n	B-pers
gives	O
the	O
Princes	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
Just	O
as	O
much	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Treasury	O
as	O
they	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
&	O
to	O
Spend	O
--	O
this	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Idea	O
of	O
the	O
means	O
they	O
use	O
to	O
supplant	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Esteem	O
.	O
Last	O
Week	O
we	O
had	O
Mr	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
the	O
Member	O
for	O
Reading	B-place
--	O
&	O
after	O
his	O
departure	O
he	O
wrote	O
some	O
news	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
that	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
rais	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
——	O
debts	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
Fellow	O
&	O
were	O
Executors	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
if	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
wrote	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
--	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
wholly	O
Ad——n	B-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
told	O
a	O
different	O
Story	O
--	O
having	O
some	O
little	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
sincerity	O
--	O
The	O
pious	O
good	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
G——r	I-pers
has	O
proved	O
inconstant	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Almeria	I-pers
,	O
&	O
has	O
taken	O
to	O
himself	O
a	O
French	O
Marchneſs	O
his	O
former	O
Ta	O
ne	O
Weeps	O
:	O
(	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
compaſsion	O
)	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
his	O
present	O
favourite	O
lts	O
--	O
his	O
poor	O
ducheſs	O
--	O
can	O
neither	O
be	O
sorry	O
or	O
glad	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
time	O
remains	O
to	O
come	O
--	O
but	O
When	O
I	O
compare	O
this	O
man	O
with	O
my	O
Royal	O
Patron	O
the	B-pers
late	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
Triumph	O
in	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
--	O
he	O
always	O
treated	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
respect	O
.	O
whatever	O
his	O
private	O
amours	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
determine	O
but	O
the	O
exterior	O
was	O
decent	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fitzherbert	I-pers
is	O
Still	O
so	O
very	O
indifferent	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
general	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
recover	O
but	O
must	O
die	O
--	O
at	O
present	O
we	O
have	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
&	O
Aimiable	O
Woman	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
withhold	O
my	O
Pen	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
write	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
a	O
greater	O
reversal	O
of	O
fortune	O
never	O
was	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
Woman	O
--	O
nor	O
by	O
any	O
one	O
who	O
deserves	O
the	O
change	O
more	O
entirely	O
--	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
regret	O
her	O
extremely	O
--	O
I	O
intend	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Paragone	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
--	O
Mſ	B-pers
's	I-pers
I	I-pers
knew	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
with	O
her	O
since	O
Mrs	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
married	O
--	O
my	O
kind	O
love	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
s	O
Compts	O
&	O
the	O
dinner	O
Bell	O
--	O
obliges	O
me	O
to	O
conclude	O
my	O
self	O
yrs	O
ever	O
&	O
sincely	O
DBlosset	B-pers
Walden	B-place
Feb	O
.	O
five	O
.	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
--	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
GriffinBraybrooke	B-pers
