TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
From	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
and	O
affectionate	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
every	O
occasion	O
during	O
my	O
stay	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
arrived	O
safe	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
without	O
having	O
suffer	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
severe	O
weather	O
on	O
my	O
journey	O
and	O
a	O
rough	O
paſsage	O
;	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
early	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
an	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
expected	O
;	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
no	O
small	O
sensibility	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
judge	O
of	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
being	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
after	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
absence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
discover	O
'd	O
an	O
impatience	O
which	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
conceal	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
certainly	O
a	O
strange	O
return	O
for	O
your	O
aſsiduous	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
indeed	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
experienced	O
from	O
every	O
other	O
quarter	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
flatter	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
that	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
my	O
visit	O
to	O
England	B-place
has	O
been	O
answer	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
ample	O
compensation	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
trouble	O
it	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
posſibility	O
of	O
convincing	O
my	O
Friends	O
here	O
that	O
with	O
such	O
ostensible	O
family	O
connections	O
it	O
cou	O
'd	O
require	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
appearance	O
amongst	O
them	O
to	O
unite	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
explain	O
difficulties	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
easier	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
attempt	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
hopes	O
of	O
succeſs	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
suffer	O
the	O
constant	O
reproach	O
of	O
indolence	O
&	O
of	O
being	O
of	O
an	O
helpleſs	O
disposition	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
my	O
situation	O
precisely	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
therefore	O
unneceſsary	O
to	O
tire	O
you	O
with	O
any	O
further	O
detail	O
or	O
explanation	O
.	O
This	O
Country	O
is	O
disposed	O
to	O
be	O
perfectly	O
satisfied	O
with	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
clandestine	O
attempts	O
by	O
Persons	O
in	O
England	B-place
to	O
create	O
new	O
difficulties	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
generally	O
supposed	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
disappointed	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
writing	O
pray	O
remember	O
to	O
enclose	O
a	O
frank	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
my	O
letters	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
postage	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sackville	O
Street	O
,	O
Dublin	B-place
Jany	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
1780	O
