TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
Evg	O
--	O
11	O
oClock	O
21	O
June	O
89	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
ashamed	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
for	O
on	O
looking	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mistake	O
or	O
a	O
word	O
left	O
out	O
in	O
every	O
line	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
in	O
haste	O
&	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
better	O
--	O
a	O
thousand	O
things	O
were	O
omitted	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
delay	O
a	O
post	O
to	O
inform	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
of	O
my	O
arrival	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
That	O
Mr	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
proposed	O
to	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
W——	B-place
two	O
members	O
in	O
opposition	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
L——	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
nephew	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
&	O
great	O
interest	O
was	O
now	O
making	O
to	O
secure	O
their	O
election	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
day	O
with	O
the	B-pers
More	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
and	O
my	O
astonishment	O
was	O
great	O
to	O
hear	O
them	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
vulgar	O
expreſsions	O
in	O
common	O
conversation	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
think	O
their	O
Reading	O
&	O
Hannah	B-pers
's	O
observation	O
would	O
have	O
cleared	O
that	O
Rubish	O
from	O
such	O
pleasure	O
grounds	O
--	O
Sally	B-pers
has	O
a	O
lively	O
imagination	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
rises	O
into	O
the	O
third	O
Heaven	O
too	O
often	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
agreeable	O
woman	O
notwithstanding	O
--	O
The	O
Housekeeper	O
Betty	B-pers
has	O
a	O
notion	O
of	O
old	O
English	O
hospitality	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
loaded	O
my	O
plate	O
so	O
often	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
fight	O
rather	O
than	O
burst	O
--	O
They	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
drawings	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
educated	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
beautiful	O
She	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
Governeſs	O
or	O
rather	O
an	O
Usher	O
at	O
a	O
School	O
--	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
Maid	O
of	O
all	O
work	O
for	O
50	O
s	O
/	O
a	O
year	O
wages	O
--	O
The	O
young	O
Ladies	O
finding	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ingenious	O
,	O
set	O
her	O
copies	O
&	O
taught	O
her	O
to	O
write	O
some	O
instructed	O
in	O
one	O
thing	O
&	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
&	O
She	O
made	O
such	O
wonderful	O
improvements	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
thought	O
she	O
deserved	O
to	O
have	O
every	O
advantage	O
--	O
She	O
was	O
therefore	O
taught	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
useful	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
writes	O
an	O
uncommon	O
fine	O
hand	O
,	O
draws	O
well	O
,	O
dances	O
,	O
understands	O
needle	O
work	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
to	O
crown	O
their	O
generous	O
intentions	O
--	O
is	O
very	O
grateful	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Yearsley	I-pers
is	O
universally	O
despised	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
only	O
three	O
or	O
4	O
people	O
who	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
speaking	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
ought	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
justification	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
well	O
written	O
to	O
be	O
treated	O
with	O
contempt	O
,	O
however	O
fallacious	O
She	O
might	O
know	O
the	O
subject	O
to	O
be	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
of	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
but	O
Hannah	B-pers
thought	O
otherwise	O
--	O
Sally	B-pers
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
ten	O
Lines	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
(	O
just	O
of	O
facts	O
)	O
to	O
convince	O
the	O
world	O
of	O
the	O
injustice	O
of	O
the	O
accusations	O
,	O
to	O
clear	O
up	O
Hannah	B-pers
's	O
character	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
expose	O
the	O
notorious	O
falsehoods	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Y	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
publication	O
--	O
They	O
spoke	O
with	O
great	O
affection	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
who	O
now	O
resides	O
at	O
the	O
Hot	O
Wells	O
,	O
his	O
health	O
is	O
so	O
indifferent	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
up	O
his	O
Duty	O
in	O
ye-	O
Country	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
vastly	O
pleased	O
with	O
Hannah	B-pers
's	O
Elegy	O
on	O
his	O
excellent	O
Wife	O
Clara	B-pers
's	O
Husband	O
is	O
dying	O
of	O
a	O
loathsome	O
lingering	O
disease	O
--	O
She	O
all	O
Ease	O
&	O
Gaiety	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
at	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
&	O
shall	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
--	O
Monday	O
morng	O
6	O
oClock	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
other	O
page	O
last	O
Night	O
&	O
thanks	O
to	O
my	O
Candle	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
reading	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pamphlet	O
called	O
The	O
Royal	O
Interview	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
masterly	O
performance	O
&	O
very	O
scarce	O
it	O
supposes	O
a	O
Conversation	O
paſsed	O
between	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
P	B-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
in	O
which	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
points	O
out	O
the	O
impropriety	O
of	O
the	O
P	O
's	O
conduct	O
&	O
ye-	O
glorious	O
oppy	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
lost	O
of	O
becoming	O
the	O
Idol	O
of	O
the	O
British	O
Nation	O
of	O
attoneing	O
for	O
all	O
his	O
follies	O
&	O
being	O
admired	O
&	O
respected	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
enjoying	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
converse	O
with	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
dont	O
keep	O
very	O
bad	O
hours	O
--	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
bathed	O
this	O
morning	O
but	O
it	O
rains	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
defer	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pump	O
room	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
Water	O
is	O
comfortably	O
settled	O
in	O
my	O
Stomach	O
I	O
will	O
resume	O
my	O
Journal	O
--	O
First	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
&	O
c	O
made	O
a	O
thousand	O
friendly	O
enquiries	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
tall	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
6	O
feet	O
without	O
her	O
Shoes	O
--	O
Fanny	B-pers
is	O
grown	O
thin	O
&	O
tall	O
Margaret	B-pers
at	O
School	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
too	O
often	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
wont	O
force	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
--	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
asked	O
--	O
Sally	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
wished	O
me	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
room	O
enough	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
house	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
pleasant	O
situation	O
--	O
She	O
talks	O
of	O
leaving	O
Bath	B-place
in	O
ten	O
days	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
ye-	O
Letter	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
there	O
from	O
Jacson	B-pers
--	O
very	O
friendly	O
--	O
expreſsing	O
a	O
concern	O
for	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
Richmond	B-place
if	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
was	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
also	O
a	O
literal	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
questions	O
--	O
disapproving	O
of	O
the	O
Ton	O
line	O
&	O
speaking	O
of	O
Dear	O
Nanny	B-pers
s	O
versatility	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
gives	O
me	O
concern	O
as	O
I	O
see	O
he	O
never	O
will	O
forgive	O
her	O
leaving	O
us	O
last	O
summer	O
I	O
have	O
answered	O
his	O
Letter	O
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
--	O
Our	O
dame	O
Keeps	O
an	O
excellent	O
Table	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
--	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
a	O
wine	O
Merchant	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
civil	O
obliging	O
and	O
attentive	O
--	O
I	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
&	O
Dinner	O
&	O
Supper	O
&	O
Tea	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
if	O
I	O
choose	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
7/6	O
for	O
my	O
Bed	O
Room	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
called	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
's	I-pers
who	O
are	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
Cheltenham	B-place
--	O
They	O
seemed	O
a	O
little	O
hurt	O
that	O
your	O
Ladyship	O
had	O
not	O
wrote	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
tolerable	O
apology	O
,	O
aſsuring	O
Mrs	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
I	O
knew	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Esteem	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
wished	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
a	O
constant	O
correspondence	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
correspondents	O
wh	O
.	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
yr-	O
time	O
&	O
the	O
attention	O
you	O
paid	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
prevented	O
your	O
writing	O
to	O
many	O
of	O
yr-	O
friends	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
they	O
seemed	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
en	O
famille	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Herschell	I-pers
Frere	O
du	O
Philosophe	O
,	O
&	O
fixed	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
my	O
learning	O
to	O
play	O
upon	O
the	O
violincello	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
esteemed	O
a	O
good	O
master	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
polishing	O
Mirrors	O
,	O
he	O
makes	O
Telescopes	O
&	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Georgium	O
Sidus	O
his	O
Bror	O
.	O
is	O
making	O
one	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
40	O
feet	O
long	O
&	O
5	O
feet	O
in	O
Diameter	O
--	O
when	O
the	O
mirror	O
broke	O
which	O
the	O
Philosopher	O
had	O
been	O
polishing	O
for	O
14	O
days	O
&	O
nights	O
--	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
“	O
well	O
we	O
must	O
set	O
about	O
another	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
some	O
tea	O
first	O
”	O
--	O
20	O
--	O
Made	O
my	O
Coup	O
d'eſsai	O
on	O
the	O
violincello	O
&	O
have	O
some	O
hopes	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
likely	O
to	O
succeed	O
--	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
fair	O
prospects	O
--	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
an	O
Instrument	O
will	O
require	O
cash	O
my	O
sweet	O
friend	O
--	O
Called	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
says	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
hopes	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foote	I-pers
--	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
when	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
astonishment	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Sally	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
quite	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
after	O
paſsing	O
an	O
hour	O
a	O
mon	O
gré	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
awkward	O
reception	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
prevail	O
upon	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
Boy	O
to	O
announce	O
my	O
Name	O
--	O
two	O
people	O
stood	O
staring	O
at	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
paſsage	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
a	O
Lady	O
came	O
out	O
attended	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
who	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
who	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
Spectacles	O
saying	O
'who	O
is	O
it	O
!	O
who	O
is	O
it	O
'	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
Miſs	O
returned	O
&	O
was	O
comfortably	O
vulgar	O
,	O
sported	O
a	O
little	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
wit	O
on	O
the	O
fineneſs	O
of	O
my	O
complexion	O
&	O
concluded	O
by	O
a	O
preſsing	O
invitation	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
“	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
a	O
Lodgg	O
house	O
”	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
might	O
appear	O
so	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
declined	O
the	O
Honor	O
--	O
Good	O
God	O
!	O
what	O
a	O
difference	O
Manners	O
make	O
in	O
a	O
human	O
Being	O
--	O
how	O
bewitching	O
is	O
Elegance	O
and	O
an	O
unaffected	O
attention	O
&	O
how	O
disgusting	O
is	O
Vulgarity	O
--	O
!	O
21	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bathe	O
,	O
but	O
drank	O
the	O
Waters	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
concluded	O
yesterday	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
home	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Vanbrugh	I-pers
's	I-pers
are	O
not	O
you	O
sorry	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
hear	O
bears	O
his	O
loſs	O
with	O
great	O
composure	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V——	I-pers
's	O
Nerves	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
usually	O
agitated	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
always	O
very	O
figitty	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
seen	O
Accts	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
Opera	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
they	O
had	O
12,000	O
--	O
P	O
r	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Abbey	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
at	O
S.	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
's	O
Cards	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Earles	I-pers
where	O
I	O
dined	O
en	O
famille	O
with	O
very	O
little	O
additions	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
day	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
my	O
Father	O
it	O
has	O
poured	O
a	O
deluge	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
rains	O
almost	O
every	O
hour	O
&	O
setting	O
aside	O
climate	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
falls	O
as	O
much	O
rain	O
here	O
as	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
the	O
few	O
fields	O
of	O
graſs	O
that	O
are	O
cut	O
look	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
condition	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
seen	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
cleared	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
Worcester	B-place
.	O
All	O
sorts	O
of	O
Garden	O
stuff	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
highest	O
perfection	O
here	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
several	O
officers	O
--	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
an	O
Irishman	O
a	O
very	O
gentlemanlike	O
man	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
also	O
two	O
West	O
--	O
--	O
Indians	O
--	O
the	O
wildest	O
of	O
human	O
beings	O
--	O
indiscreet	O
thoughtless	O
,	O
good	O
humoured	O
,	O
inexhaustible	O
Spirits	O
hard	O
drinkers	O
,	O
irreligious	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
's	O
--	O
without	O
End	O
--	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
exceſsively	O
grieved	O
to	O
hear	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
said	O
of	O
yr-	O
friend	O
Ton	O
.	O
p——	O
Ah	O
my	O
dearest	O
Love	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Country	O
--	O
at	O
Bootles	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
said	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
drunk	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
York	B-pers
's	O
safety	O
upon	O
wch	O
.	O
great	O
numbers	O
followed	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
set	O
apart	O
for	O
royal	O
topers	O
--	O
some	O
climbed	O
on	O
benches	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
tables	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
what	O
paſsed	O
.	O
--	O
when	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
w	O
.	O
give	O
a	O
Toast	O
a	O
solemn	O
silence	O
prevailed	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
followg	O
words	O
were	O
uttered	O
by	O
the	O
Heir	O
to	O
the	O
Throne	O
--	O
“	O
Here	O
's	O
to	O
all	O
our	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
Damnation	O
to	O
those	O
Relations	O
who	O
dont	O
love	O
their	O
families	O
”	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
dutiful	O
compliment	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
meſsage	O
alluded	O
in	O
the	O
Letter	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
read	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
unmanly	O
,	O
too	O
infamous	O
&	O
too	O
obscene	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
basest	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
most	O
corrupted	O
heart	O
must	O
combine	O
to	O
invent	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
horrible	O
to	O
one	O
's	O
feelings	O
--	O
&	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
but	O
the	O
Gentm	O
.	O
being	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
general	O
wish	O
of	O
the	O
army	O
that	O
the	O
Ball	O
had	O
gone	O
thrō	O
the	B-pers
D——	I-pers
of	I-pers
Y——	I-pers
's	O
head	O
or	O
his	O
heart	O
--	O
22	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Hockiss	I-pers
who	O
resides	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
bathe	O
as	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
so	O
wet	O
--	O
Spent	O
the	O
day	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
our	O
Madcaps	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
are	O
returned	O
&	O
keep	O
us	O
all	O
alive	O
.	O
--	O
23	O
--	O
Bathed	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
high	O
wind	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
fair	O
--	O
at	O
one	O
I	O
drank	O
the	O
Waters	O
&	O
am	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
visits	O
--	O
Scraping	O
goes	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
My	O
bleſsing	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Duty	O
&	O
love	O
&	O
c	O
where	O
proper	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
inestimable	O
femme	O
--	O
Je	O
suis	O
toujours	O
le	O
Même	O
J.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
post	O
