TOKEN	NE
4	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
7	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
1802	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
this	O
dusty	O
,	O
expensive	O
Town	B-place
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
Inst-	O
.	O
Such	O
is	O
my	O
plan	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
dont	O
succeed	O
in	O
my	O
Views	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
either	O
occasion	O
my	O
departure	O
suddenly	O
,	O
or	O
delay	O
me	O
for	O
another	O
week	O
.	O
At	O
all	O
events	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
longer	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
today	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
my	O
matter	O
may	O
then	O
be	O
fixed	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
They	O
will	O
candidly	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
Ministers	O
You	O
know	O
are	O
callous	O
Animals	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
to	O
make	O
people	O
dance	O
after	O
them	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
This	O
suits	O
not	O
with	O
my	O
irritability	O
of	O
Temper	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
Royal	O
would	O
ask	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
such	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
would	O
excite	O
their	O
Curiosity	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
into	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
commanding	O
You	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
their	O
presence	O
.	O
When	O
You	O
left	O
the	O
Palace	O
,	O
my	O
advice	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
should	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
shewn	O
that	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
disgusted	O
with	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
willful	O
Miſs	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
bid	O
You	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
nettled	O
our	O
Gracious	O
Q	B-pers
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
will	O
remain	O
here	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
departure	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
she	O
knows	O
not	O
of	O
it	O
yet	O
.	O
Only	O
think	O
of	O
their	O
sleeping	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
without	O
telling	O
me	O
of	O
their	O
intention	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
easy	O
for	O
You	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
nothing	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
except	O
that	O
the	O
Cumberland	O
Counteſs	O
consents	O
to	O
the	O
Match	O
.	O
No	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
even	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
misnamed	O
the	O
Son	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
in	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Greys	O
.	O
The	O
Counteſs	O
herself	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
Frank	O
for	O
You	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Seventh	O
April	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
