TOKEN	NE
Greencroft	B-place
,	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1788	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
The	O
milk	O
of	O
human	O
kindneſs	O
is	O
so	O
predominant	O
in	O
my	O
disposition	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
disposes	O
Me	O
to	O
exercise	O
the	O
Christian	O
virtue	O
of	O
Forgiveneſs	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
find	O
no	O
difficulty	O
in	O
granting	O
Your	O
Petition	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
thought	O
th	O
at	O
ere	O
was	O
allmost	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
You	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
so	O
frequently	O
give	O
cause	O
for	O
complaining	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Negligence	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
aver	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
accused	O
You	O
of	O
having	O
altered	O
your	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
Me	O
or	O
Mine	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
is	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
perfectly	O
recovered	O
.	O
Her	O
indisposition	O
was	O
entirely	O
unexpected	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
happened	O
,	O
neither	O
can	O
I	O
yet	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
Aunt	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
(	O
who	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
is	O
a	O
Fool	O
)	O
prevailed	O
on	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Aſsize	O
Ball	O
at	O
Newcastle	B-place
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
entirely	O
prudent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
appear	O
Croſs	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
tacitly	O
consented	O
.	O
The	O
consequence	O
was	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
confined	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
blamed	O
the	O
Ball	O
,	O
&	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
was	O
convinced	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
sufficiently	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
regret	O
but	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
my	O
Second	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
intention	O
of	O
remaining	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
last	O
wrote	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
you	O
talked	O
only	O
of	O
a	O
Spring	O
Visit	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
are	O
tired	O
of	O
You	O
long	O
ago	O
.	O
You	O
and	O
your	O
Brat	O
must	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
good	O
company	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
Fortunately	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
You	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Richmond	B-place
.	O
Apropos	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
walk	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Governor	B-pers
Pownall	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Star	O
&	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
condescend	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
Me	O
if	O
it	O
stands	O
just	O
where	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
drove	O
my	B-pers
Porcupine	I-pers
the	O
Morning	O
we	O
were	O
Married	O
,	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
in	O
solitary	O
Retirement	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Barbarous	O
practice	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
civilized	O
Ages	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
since	O
called	O
the	O
place	O
Siberia	B-place
,	O
&	O
constantly	O
Vow	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Absurdity	O
when	O
I	O
marry	O
again	O
.	O
You	O
accuse	O
Me	O
of	O
Reserve	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
You	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	B-place
last	O
October	O
.	O
Truly	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
omitted	O
that	O
peice	O
of	O
intelligence	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Town	B-place
because	O
the	O
Order	O
for	O
all	O
Officers	O
to	O
join	O
their	O
Regiments	O
obliged	O
Me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
could	O
ob	O
tain	O
leave	O
wh	O
ich	O
was	O
not	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
dangled	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
Month	O
at	O
the	O
War	O
Office	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Journey	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
productive	O
of	O
Promises	O
without	O
Performances	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
laudable	O
Custom	O
of	O
all	O
Ministers	O
and	O
all	O
Administrations	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
promises	O
been	O
fullfilled	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
my	O
Own	O
Master	O
,	O
retired	O
from	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Service	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
heartily	O
satisfied	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
amend	O
the	O
reading	O
,	O
by	O
changing	O
the	O
of	O
into	O
a	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
adding	O
a	O
dis	O
before	O
satisfied	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
our	O
meeting	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Blue	O
Mantle	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
purse	O
will	O
not	O
permit	O
Me	O
to	O
indulge	O
my	O
penchant	O
for	O
travell	O
ing	O
.	O
A	O
journey	O
from	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
to	O
London	B-place
w	O
ould	O
cost	O
Me	O
,	O
en	O
famille	O
,	O
£100	O
,	O
Ditto	O
the	O
return	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
to	O
be	O
kep't	O
up	O
at	O
Edinr-	B-place
,	O
another	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
no	O
sinking	O
fund	O
to	O
draw	O
on	O
for	O
defraying	O
the	O
extraordinary	O
expence	O
.	O
If	O
ever	O
I	O
contrive	O
to	O
reach	O
the	O
Capital	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
must	O
remain	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
Boy	O
is	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
School	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
being	O
two	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
I	O
propose	O
educating	O
him	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
You	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
Blue	O
Stocking	O
Tribe	O
shall	O
certainly	O
consult	O
You	O
on	O
the	O
proper	O
mode	O
of	O
conducting	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
such	O
importance	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
affectionate	O
wish	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Kitten	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Maria	B-pers
begs	O
leave	O
to	O
join	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
Your	O
faithfull	O
friend	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Stormonts	O
still	O
Gracious	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
Axwell	O
Park	O
next	O
Saturday	O
and	O
to	O
Edinr-	B-place
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
--	O
Gateshead	B-place
August	O
twenty	O
eight	O
1788	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Esqr-	I-pers
Richmond	B-place
Surrey	B-place
Free	O
Tho	B-pers
:	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
