TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
You	O
will	O
no	O
doubt	O
have	O
been	O
surprised	O
that	O
we	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
permitted	O
you	O
to	O
remain	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
ignorance	O
of	O
what	O
has	O
become	O
of	O
us	O
since	O
we	O
left	O
you	O
;	O
prepare	O
now	O
for	O
a	O
still	O
greater	O
surprize	O
we	O
mean	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
England	B-place
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
for	O
Geneva	B-place
is	O
now	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
all	O
others	O
the	O
most	O
unfavourable	O
for	O
the	O
residence	O
of	O
Strangers	O
,	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
internal	O
divisions	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
subside	O
,	O
and	O
oppreſs	O
'd	O
by	O
crowds	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Troops	O
.	O
The	O
detail	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
events	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
witneſs	O
to	O
wou	O
'd	O
lead	O
me	O
beyond	O
the	O
bounds	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
defer	O
entering	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
till	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
.	O
The	O
objects	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
view	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
answerd	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
Geneva	B-place
I	O
therefore	O
judged	O
it	O
more	O
prudent	O
to	O
return	O
without	O
making	O
further	O
experiments	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
objections	O
to	O
France	B-place
,	O
&	O
still	O
greater	O
to	O
Italy	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
agreed	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Son	O
at	O
Geneva	B-place
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
universally	O
respected	O
he	O
is	O
Professor	O
of	O
the	O
Belles	O
Lettres	O
of	O
the	O
Accademy	O
&	O
has	O
educated	O
many	O
Persons	O
already	O
eminent	O
for	O
learning	O
&	O
abilities	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
aſsured	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
that	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
superior	O
advantages	O
cou	O
'd	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
without	O
my	O
Son	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
more	O
recover	O
'd	O
than	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
expected	O
&	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
soon	O
perfectly	O
well	O
she	O
desires	O
with	O
my	O
Daughter	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sécheron	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Geneva	I-place
July	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
