TOKEN	NE
Report	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
fall	O
,	O
1777	O
or	O
8	O
.	O
My	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
am	O
with	O
your	O
Mamma	O
,	O
she	O
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
to-day	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
unfortunately	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
chair	O
,	O
&	O
although	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
much	O
disordered	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
conveniently	O
stir	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
disappointed	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
drinking	O
tea	O
with	O
you	O
through	O
a	O
fatal	O
mistake	O
which	O
Debounaire	B-pers
will	O
explain	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
put	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
humour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
this	O
morning	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
deafneſs	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
come	O
on	O
suddenly	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
prevented	O
her	O
being	O
at	O
Court	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maul	I-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
relieve	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
inquired	O
much	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
Illneſs	O
has	O
been	O
uneasy	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
by	O
the	O
penny	O
post	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
not	O
received	O
any	O
answer	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
infinitely	O
obliged	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſses	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
pretty	O
Billet	O
;	O
the	O
intelligence	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Princeſs	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
,	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
daughter	O
is	O
very	O
interesting	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
forgive	O
you	O
for	O
concealing	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Monsieur	B-pers
le	I-pers
Compte	I-pers
,	O
yet	O
as	O
her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
has	O
permitted	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
she	O
is	O
aſsured	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
worthy	O
of	O
your	O
choice	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
congratulates	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
desires	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
her	O
Duty	O
,	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſses	I-pers
,	O
&	O
aſsure	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
to	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
fall	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
prevented	O
her	O
.	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
chere	O
Miranda	B-pers
Je	O
vous	O
aime	O
&	O
Je	O
vous	O
estime	O
toujours	O
infiniment	O
,	O
&	O
plus	O
que	O
Je	O
ne	O
vous	O
puiſse	O
le	O
dire	O
.	O
Nous	O
irons	O
demain	O
à	O
la	O
Campagne	O
où	O
Je	O
penserai	O
de	O
vous	O
.	O
James	O
Street	O
.	O
Thursday	O
Evening	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
explain	O
the	O
accident	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
her	O
chair	O
having	O
slipped	O
backwarder	O
than	O
she	O
imagined	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
only	O
hurt	O
her	O
leg	O
in	O
the	O
slightest	O
manner	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
has	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
this	O
morning	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
penny	O
post	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
fears	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
receive	O
it	O
--	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
history	O
of	O
his	O
disappointments	O
in	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
fill	O
up	O
a	O
folio	O
Catherine	B-pers
has	O
locked	O
up	O
her	O
pretty	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
an	O
influence	O
a	O
hint	O
from	O
your	O
Ladyship	O
has	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Prince	O
Ernest	O
's	O
Kew	B-place
