TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1790	O
.	O
How	O
dare	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
presume	O
to	O
find	O
fault	O
with	O
my	O
Pride	O
?	O
I	O
hourly	O
commend	O
myself	O
for	O
having	O
called	O
it	O
forth	O
to	O
convince	O
the	O
High	O
&	O
Mighty	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
care	O
not	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
True	O
,	O
my	O
election	O
is	O
not	O
secure	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
I	O
much	O
prefer	O
Trotter	O
down	O
hill	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
Walk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Mall	O
or	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
care	O
not	O
three	O
Sixpences	O
whether	O
ever	O
I	O
take	O
my	O
seat	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
of	O
Incurables	O
.	O
My	O
Chinese	O
Sow	O
on	O
the	O
Eve	O
of	O
Pigging	O
,	O
interests	O
me	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
all	O
the	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Fleets	O
of	O
Spain	O
or	O
France	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
failure	O
of	O
my	O
Carrot	O
crop	O
is	O
a	O
more	O
serious	O
vexation	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
double	O
Return	O
.	O
Politics	O
are	O
vile	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
more	O
I	O
see	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
dislike	O
them	O
.	O
Friendship	O
,	O
Relationship	O
,	O
honour	O
&	O
gratitude	O
must	O
be	O
sacrificed	O
to	O
keep	O
well	O
with	O
a	O
Party	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
court	O
You	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
find	O
it	O
their	O
interest	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
just	O
as	O
ready	O
to	O
drop	O
You	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
alert	O
in	O
taking	O
you	O
up	O
.	O
So	O
says	O
farmer	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
&	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
contradict	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
think	O
what	O
You	O
will	O
of	O
my	O
opinions	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
they	O
present	O
Me	O
with	O
a	O
genteel	O
sinecure	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Months	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
make	O
Senators	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
if	O
they	O
pleased	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
envious	O
.	O
The	O
prorogation	O
of	O
Parliament	O
will	O
keep	O
us	O
in	O
suspence	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
House	O
will	O
probably	O
not	O
meet	O
for	O
busineſs	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
Merits	O
of	O
our	O
Election	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
matter	O
is	O
decided	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
to	O
consult	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
advise	O
them	O
the	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Election	O
informal	O
,	O
&	O
order	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
for	O
Sixteen	O
.	O
Many	O
discoveries	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
since	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
July	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
ludicrous	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
party	O
like	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
putting	O
mischief	O
in	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
their	O
adversaries	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
,	O
he	O
pleases	O
to	O
call	O
himself	O
an	O
Independent	O
Peer	O
.	O
The	O
word	O
wants	O
explanation	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
voted	O
with	O
Ministry	O
,	O
he	O
expected	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
their	O
support	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gig	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
voting	O
for	O
everyone	O
of	O
their	O
friends	O
,	O
countenanced	O
the	O
opposition	O
Candidates	O
,	O
was	O
supported	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
calls	O
this	O
conduct	O
Independence	O
.	O
The	O
friends	O
of	O
the	O
Minister	O
,	O
refused	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
,	O
unleſs	O
on	O
the	O
footing	O
of	O
reciprocity	O
;	O
he	O
therefore	O
abuses	O
the	O
Minister	O
&	O
toasts	O
His	O
R—l	O
H—s	O
before	O
his	O
father	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
near	O
Relation	O
&	O
quondam	O
Guardian	O
,	O
his	O
refusing	O
to	O
vote	O
for	O
Me	O
,	O
shocked	O
&	O
mortified	O
Me	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
behaviour	O
has	O
almost	O
determined	O
Me	O
to	O
be	O
callous	O
to	O
every	O
kind	O
of	O
feeling	O
in	O
future	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
Election	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
visit	O
from	O
the	O
Pechell	O
's	O
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
vain	O
in	O
shewing	O
off	O
our	O
place	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
finding	O
they	O
approved	O
of	O
the	O
situation	O
.	O
We	O
likewise	O
expect	O
Lady	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Tynemouth	B-place
with	O
her	O
unfortunate	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
bathing	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
correct	O
(	O
if	O
poſsible	O
)	O
the	O
tendency	O
to	O
deformity	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
do	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
,	O
a	O
vast	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
,	O
to	O
explore	O
these	O
Northern	O
Regions	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
would	O
all	O
come	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
abusing	O
You	O
face	O
to	O
face	O
.	O
You	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
plan	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
like	O
all	O
other	O
Court	O
bred	O
Miſses	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
neglected	O
to	O
send	O
perfo	O
rm	O
your	O
promise	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Tenth	O
Septr=	O
1790	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derby	B-place
by	O
Carlisle	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
