TOKEN	NE
Hampton	B-place
.	O
Tuesday	O
19	O
th	O
:	O
July	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
My	O
Aunt	O
has	O
Commiſsion	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
you	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
been	O
favord	O
yesterday	O
Evening	O
,	O
by	O
another	O
Royal	O
Visit	O
!	O
About	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
your	O
leaving	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
my	O
Aunt	O
was	O
preparing	O
to	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Town	O
,	O
a	O
Note	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bunbury	I-pers
,	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
tThe	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dutcheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
by	O
half	O
past	O
Seven	O
.	O
Every	O
thing	O
was	O
Arrang	O
'd	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Shortneſs	O
of	O
the	O
Notice	O
would	O
Admit	O
:	O
Refreshments	O
were	O
Placed	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
very	O
humbly	O
supplying	O
your	O
Place	O
,	O
in	O
Dreſsing	O
the	O
Flower	O
Jars	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Their	O
Royal	O
Highneſses	O
came	O
earlier	O
then	O
their	O
Appointment	O
;	O
and	O
were	O
attended	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Fitzroy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evening	O
was	O
most	O
favorable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeard	O
highly	O
delighted	O
with	O
their	O
Reception	O
.	O
Nor	O
must	O
I	O
forget	O
to	O
mention	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
York	I-pers
expreſs	O
'd	O
his	O
concern	O
at	O
not	O
recollecting	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
longer	O
Intrude	O
on	O
your	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
present	O
You	O
with	O
my	O
Aunt	O
s	O
kind	O
Remembrance	O
;	O
And	O
to	O
beg	O
your	O
Acceptance	O
,	O
of	O
Mine	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
sincere	O
Wishes	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
long	O
continued	O
Happineſs	O
,	O
of	O
Yourself	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
your	O
sweet	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
not	O
forget	O
the	O
very	O
flattering	O
Regard	O
she	O
Profeſs	O
'd	O
for	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
Your	O
,	O
much	O
Obligd	O
very	O
humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
Emma	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
s	O
Pheasant	B-place
Grove	I-place
near	O
.	O
Chiselhurst	B-place
Kent	B-place
.	O
