TOKEN	NE
Madam	O
St.	B-place
Petersburg	I-place
Novr	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
-	O
1771	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
his	B-pers
Excellency	I-pers
's	O
desire	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
which	O
happened	O
upon	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
Instant	O
from	O
a	O
disorder	O
in	O
her	O
bowels	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
and	O
his	O
Children	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
the	O
utmost	O
affliction	O
are	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
be	O
Madam	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
obedient	O
and	O
most	O
humble	O
Servant	O
William	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
Honourable	B-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Her	O
Life	O
was	O
innocent	O
meritorious	O
&	O
Happy	O
.	O
Her	O
End	O
peaceful	O
glorious	O
&	O
triumphant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
poor	O
survivers	O
every	O
circumstance	O
of	O
Consolation	O
which	O
the	O
a	O
Catastrophy	O
so	O
total	O
could	O
poſsibly	O
permit	O
.	O
--	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honourable	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
ST	B-place
PETERSBOVRG	I-place
by	O
Northampton	B-place
From	O
London	B-place
Announcement	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
death	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
