TOKEN	NE
Somerset	O
Street	O
June	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1791	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
at	O
Bruſsells	B-place
where	O
it	O
was	O
transmitted	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
Nothing	O
that	O
falls	O
from	O
your	O
pen	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
can	O
offend	O
me	O
or	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
for	O
you	O
write	O
from	O
your	O
heart	O
and	O
that	O
fortunately	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
and	O
a	O
tender	O
One	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
liked	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
written	O
on	O
a	O
certain	O
delicate	O
Subject	O
&	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
very	O
much	O
alike	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
.	O
I	O
shoud	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
England	B-place
which	O
I	O
propose	O
doing	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
without	O
;	O
without	O
seeing	O
you	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
still	O
so	O
much	O
busineſs	O
to	O
do	O
here	O
&	O
perhaps	O
must	O
go	O
into	O
Wales	B-place
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
August	O
it	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
think	O
now	O
of	O
fishing	O
or	O
shooting	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
destiny	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
fighting	O
off	O
from	O
going	O
to	O
Wales	B-place
if	O
poſsible	O
.	O
My	O
old	O
Friends	O
drew	O
me	O
away	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
poor	O
Emma	B-pers
paſses	O
her	O
time	O
but	O
ill	O
here	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
the	O
good	O
sense	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
coud	O
not	O
be	O
otherwise	O
&	O
will	O
last	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
when	O
we	O
shall	O
get	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
good	O
Society	O
which	O
her	O
excellent	O
conduct	O
has	O
insured	O
her	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
Earth	O
she	O
wishes	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
yourself	O
nor	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
thinks	O
herself	O
so	O
much	O
obliged	O
Pray	O
tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
his	O
kindn	O
ess	O
&	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
allows	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
you	O
the	O
manner	O
I	O
am	O
lodged	O
will	O
be	O
perfectly	O
indifferent	O
to	O
me	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
how	O
have	O
been	O
&	O
am	O
still	O
hurry	O
'd	O
you	O
woud	O
pity	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
starved	O
with	O
cold	O
after	O
the	O
hot	O
weather	O
of	O
3	O
days	O
Ever	O
yrs	O
.	O
affectly	O
&	O
sincerely	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
near	O
Buxton	B-place
Derbyshire	B-place
