TOKEN	NE
Stanhope	B-place
St	I-place
:	I-place
Friday	O
Eveng	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
All	O
yesterday	O
Evening	O
I	O
expected	O
you	O
--	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
promise	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
wonder	O
what	O
Excuse	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
Sunday	O
&	O
Thursday	O
's	O
are	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
my	O
Holidays	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
dedicate	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
only	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
go	O
hand	O
in	O
hand	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
any	O
little	O
Occupation	O
or	O
Amusement	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
--	O
You	O
were	O
expected	O
in	O
this	O
light	O
;	O
&	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
was	O
to	O
have	O
said	O
over	O
his	O
Vieillard	O
,	O
&	O
Julia	B-pers
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Lottery	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
but	O
She	O
never	O
came	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
much	O
disappointed	O
.	O
--	O
after	O
Julia	B-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
sat	O
down	O
&	O
wrote	O
you	O
a	O
Letter	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
better	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
today	O
,	O
besides	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
account	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
whom	O
She	O
left	O
to	O
my	O
Care	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
where	O
this	O
poor	O
unfortunate	O
Young	O
Creature	O
lodged	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
advice	O
--	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
appoint	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
particular	O
hour	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
(	O
feeling	O
rather	O
aukward	O
in	O
accosting	O
this	O
once	O
fine	O
Lady	O
,	O
now	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
humble	O
Penitent	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
you	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
you	O
some	O
Money	O
which	O
She	O
left	O
for	O
you	O
..	O
when	O
with	O
the	O
Air	O
of	O
a	O
Bacelli	B-pers
,	O
She	O
said	O
“	O
Oh	O
!	O
Ma'am	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
vastly	O
mortified	O
that	O
we	O
“	O
were	O
out	O
when	O
your	O
Lash	O
:	O
did	O
us	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
calling	O
,	O
”	O
--	O
just	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
&	O
expected	O
She	O
should	O
return	O
my	O
Visit	O
.	O
--	O
this	O
a	O
little	O
disconcerted	O
me	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
rule	O
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
influenced	O
prejudiced	O
by	O
outward	O
appearances	O
,	O
I	O
resolved	O
to	O
talk	O
on	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
find	O
out	O
whether	O
her	O
Sentiments	O
corresponded	O
with	O
her	O
manner	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
more	O
affected	O
than	O
by	O
her	O
Conversation	O
,	O
her	O
gratitude	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
her	O
resolutions	O
of	O
amendment	O
,	O
&	O
total	O
Retirement	O
;	O
&	O
in	O
short	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
gives	O
me	O
hopes	O
She	O
is	O
sincere	O
,	O
one	O
thing	O
particularly	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
her	O
wish	O
for	O
Employment	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
supporting	O
herself	O
,	O
&	O
paſsing	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
otherwise	O
hang	O
heavily	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
indeed	O
the	O
Evenings	O
were	O
rather	O
dull	O
,	O
which	O
indeed	O
I	O
could	O
easily	O
believe	O
;	O
the	O
Society	O
consisting	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
Old	O
Woman	O
as	O
deaf	O
as	O
a	O
Post	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
Notable	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
lively	O
Idea	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Muslin	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
Frock	O
for	O
Julia	B-pers
--	O
(	O
She	O
has	O
already	O
puckered	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
Sattin	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
begin	O
&	O
read	O
the	O
Spectators	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Old	O
deaf	O
woman	O
whether	O
they	O
ever	O
read	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
;	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
My	O
Lady	O
--	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
is	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
Godly	O
Books	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
do	O
so	O
well	O
for	O
constant	O
reading	O
--	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Spectators	O
would	O
be	O
both	O
godly	O
&	O
amusing	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
made	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
her	O
beginning	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
am	O
quite	O
interested	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
poor	O
Thing	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
quite	O
happy	O
if	O
She	O
continues	O
,	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
She	O
now	O
promises	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
has	O
just	O
been	O
here	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
he	O
recd	O
:	O
lately	O
;	O
he	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
preached	O
a	O
Sermon	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Sufferers	O
by	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.-	I-place
Clements	I-place
&	O
amongst	O
a	O
full	O
Congregation	O
he	O
collected	O
only	O
between	O
19	O
&	O
20	O
pounds	O
--	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
recd	O
:	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
vulgar	O
hand	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Rector	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
-	O
Clements	O
,	O
London	B-place
--	O
one	O
would	O
think	O
Madm	O
:	O
said	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
thought	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
always	O
by	O
my	O
Church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
Letters	O
--	O
but	O
however	O
this	O
Direction	O
found	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
Letter	O
,	O
he	O
fo	O
it	O
contained	O
,	O
Sir	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
inclosed	O
may	O
be	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Sufferers	O
by	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
--	O
Yr.-	O
humble	O
:	O
Sert	O
:	O
A.	B-pers
Isleworth	I-pers
&	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
was	O
inclosed	O
,	O
under	O
this	O
strange	O
Direction	O
?	O
a	O
Hundred	O
pound	O
Bank	O
Note	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
is	O
distreſsed	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
whom	O
it	O
comes	O
from	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
feigned	O
name	O
--	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
a	O
Curious	O
Anecdote	O
.	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
meets	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
extraordinry	O
occurrences	O
,	O
that	O
ever	O
befell	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
his	O
particular	O
manner	O
of	O
telling	O
them	O
makes	O
them	O
appear	O
so	O
.	O
Adieu	O
the	O
Bell	O
Man	O
is	O
past	O
by	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
finish	O
this	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
is	O
just	O
flown	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
Day	O
;	O
She	O
begs	O
her	O
kind	O
Complime	O
nts	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
quite	O
revived	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
s	O
return	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
grown	O
quite	O
fat	O
.	O
&	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
looks	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
Planet	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
poor	O
Industrious	O
German	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
astonishment	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
great	O
Astronomers	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Herschel	I-pers
dined	O
last	O
Sunday	O
at	O
Greenwich	B-place
,	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
full	O
of	O
this	O
News	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
for	O
tonight	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Docr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maskelyne	I-pers
continues	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Herschel	I-pers
,	O
full	O
of	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
gracious	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
wanted	O
any	O
Artificial	O
Flowers	O
--	O
poor	O
Ly.-	B-pers
L.	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
makes	O
them	O
beautifully	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
Cheap	O
.	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
this	O
horrid	O
blot	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
buying	O
my	O
birth	O
day	O
Gown	O
.	O
Sat	O
:	O
Dr	O
:	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
Dinner	O
to	O
Celebrate	O
my	O
birthday	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
come	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fieldg	I-pers
:	I-pers
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
pray	O
give	O
mine	O
to	O
Dr	O
:	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ju	I-pers
.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
--	O
only	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
returned	O
to	O
us	O
again	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
happy	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
Affly	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
yours	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
To	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
