TOKEN	NE
that	O
dashed	O
around	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
alarm	O
&	O
terror	O
that	O
prevailed	O
,	O
stoped	O
my	O
sickneſs	O
,	O
&	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
fever	O
attended	O
by	O
a	O
small	O
degree	O
of	O
delirium	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
exhausted	O
&	O
reduced	O
in	O
strength	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
support	O
my	O
miserable	O
head	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
bed	O
nor	O
sopha	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
ho	O
use	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Idea	O
of	O
having	O
involved	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dorsand	I-pers
in	O
a	O
destruction	O
which	O
appeard	O
inevitable	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
mi	O
se	O
ry	O
and	O
wretchedneſs	O
I	O
kn	O
ew	O
our	O
loſs	O
woud	O
occasion	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
England	B-place
occasioned	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
extraordinary	O
agitati	O
on	O
of	O
my	O
nerv	O
es	O
and	O
which	O
sitting	O
near	O
30	O
hours	O
in	O
wet	O
Cloaths	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
tended	O
to	O
diminish	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
little	O
of	O
self	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
never	O
will	O
be	O
separated	O
from	O
a	O
human	O
being	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
ne	O
glected	O
to	O
serve	O
those	O
who	O
appeard	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
enfeebled	O
than	O
my-self	O
.	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
storm	O
--	O
Tho	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
persuade	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
to	O
bel	O
ieve	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
regret	O
having	O
been	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
sufferings	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
thro	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
scene	O
of	O
gr	O
and	O
sublimity	O
of	O
which	O
my	O
mind	O
had	O
no	O
conception	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
terror	O
prevaild	O
over	O
eve	O
ry	O
other	O
fe	O
eling	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
at	O
times	O
sufficiently	O
collect	O
ed	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
superintending	O
providence	O
of	O
the	O
almighty	O
--	O
When	O
light	O
appeard	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
held	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
&	O
watchd	O
the	O
storm	O
,	O
that	O
beautiful	O
line	O
of	O
Pope	B-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
describe	O
s	O
the	O
Indian	O
who	O
“	O
sees	O
God	O
in	O
Clouds	O
and	O
hears	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
wind	O
”	O
Alexander	O
Pope	O
,	O
An	O
Essay	O
on	O
Man	O
,	O
Epistle	O
I	O
.	O
occurrd	O
forcibly	O
to	O
my	O
recollection	O
and	O
insensibly	O
calm	O
'd	O
my	O
mind	O
&	O
renew	O
'd	O
my	O
hope	O
of	O
protection	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
reservd	O
the	O
numberleſs	O
occurrences	O
and	O
adventures	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
great	O
pleasure	O
o	O
f	O
again	O
embracing	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
how	O
affectionately	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
beloved	O
by	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
floras	O
respectful	O
duty	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
and	O
tell	O
her	O
she	O
flatters	O
herself	O
she	O
w	O
ill	O
be	O
like	O
desdemona	B-pers
,	O
and	O
love	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
dangers	O
she	O
has	O
paſsed	O
in	O
her	O
disastrous	O
voyage	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
finds	O
external	O
charms	O
have	O
no	O
influence	O
on	O
her	O
discerning	O
mind	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	O
all	O
my	O
letters	O
have	O
miscarried	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
of	O
12	O
Months	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
Neopolitan	O
democrates	O
have	O
far	O
exceeded	O
their	O
grand	O
prototipe	O
and	O
example	O
in	O
france	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
with	O
love	O
my	O
dear	O
sister	O
I	O
remain	O
your	O
affect	O
S	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
