TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
30	O
th	O
-	O
Decrr	O
1806	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Since	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
longer	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
franking	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
abridged	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
my	O
Correspondents	O
,	O
not	O
chusing	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
paying	O
for	O
my	O
dull	O
stupid	O
scrawls	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
You	O
would	O
have	O
early	O
intelligence	O
of	O
my	O
Defeat	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
not	O
conceive	O
that	O
You	O
would	O
have	O
expected	O
the	O
disagreeable	O
intelligence	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
Government	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
reflecting	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Opposition	O
was	O
honourable	O
to	O
Me	O
.	O
Would	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Name	O
inserted	O
in	O
the	O
Ministerial	O
List	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
having	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
presumed	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
own	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Will	O
not	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
Ministers	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Election	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
surprised	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
failed	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Majority	O
of	O
Peers	O
,	O
who	O
voted	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
favour	O
.	O
This	O
appears	O
odd	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Votes	O
were	O
chequered	O
.	O
My	O
supporters	O
were	O
,	O
the	O
Dukes	O
of	O
Buccleuch	B-pers
,	O
Lennox	B-pers
,	O
Gordon	B-pers
,	O
Argyll	B-pers
,	O
Atholl	B-pers
,	O
Montrose	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Earls	O
of	O
Craufurd	B-pers
,	O
Morton	B-pers
,	O
Caithneſs	B-pers
,	O
Moray	B-pers
,	O
Home	B-pers
,	O
Strathmore	B-pers
,	O
Abercorn	B-pers
,	O
Kellie	B-pers
,	O
Haddington	B-pers
,	O
Galloway	B-pers
,	O
Kinnoull	B-pers
,	O
Dalhousie	B-pers
,	O
Leven	B-pers
,	O
Balcarres	B-pers
,	O
Aboyne	B-pers
,	O
Aberdeen	B-pers
,	O
Dunmore	B-pers
,	O
Hyndford	B-pers
,	O
Glasgow	B-pers
,	O
Bute	B-pers
,	O
Hopetoun	B-pers
,	O
Deloraine	B-pers
,	O
Viscounts	O
Stormont	B-pers
,	O
Arbuthnot	B-pers
,	O
Lords	O
Cathcart	B-pers
,	O
Sinclair	B-pers
,	O
Torphichen	B-pers
,	O
Napier	B-pers
,	O
Reay	B-pers
&	O
Elibank	B-pers
.	O
36	O
.	O
My	O
opponents	O
were	O
,	O
The	O
Dukes	O
of	O
Rothsay	B-pers
,	O
P	B-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Earls	O
of	O
Queensberry	B-pers
,	O
Errol	B-pers
,	O
Eglinton	B-pers
,	O
Caſsillis	B-pers
,	O
Lauderdale	B-pers
,	O
Elgin	B-pers
,	O
Dysart	B-pers
,	O
Selkirk	B-pers
,	O
Northesk	B-pers
,	O
Dundonald	B-pers
,	O
Kintore	B-pers
,	O
Breadalbane	B-pers
,	O
Stair	B-pers
,	O
Roseberry	B-pers
,	O
Viscounts	O
Portmore	B-pers
,	O
Falkland	B-pers
,	O
Lords	O
Dunblane	B-pers
,	O
Forbes	B-pers
,	O
Sempill	B-pers
,	O
Elphinstone	B-pers
,	O
Somerville	B-pers
,	O
Blantyre	B-pers
,	O
Colvill	B-pers
,	O
Kirkcudbright	B-pers
,	O
Belhaven	B-pers
,	O
Rollo	B-pers
,	O
28	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
added	O
the	O
Claimant	O
of	O
the	O
Dukedom	O
of	O
Roxburgh	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Claimant	O
of	O
the	O
Earldom	O
of	O
Marchmont	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
voted	O
on	O
the	O
Ministerial	O
side	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
decided	O
on	O
their	O
Claims	O
.	O
On	O
comparing	O
the	O
Names	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
above	O
Lists	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
ashamed	O
at	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
my	O
Election	O
.	O
Whether	O
my	O
office	O
will	O
go	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
write	O
the	O
usual	O
Letter	O
of	O
application	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
presumed	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
Object	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Ministers	O
friends	O
.	O
The	O
probability	O
therefore	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
left	O
to	O
live	O
out	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
State	O
of	O
peaceful	O
retirement	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
You	O
dont	O
wander	O
to	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
long	O
enough	O
before	O
we	O
meet	O
again	O
.	O
Now	O
for	O
a	O
reply	O
to	O
all	O
your	O
Queries	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
Kinnaird	B-pers
--	O
My	O
Son	O
Colonel	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
is	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Imperieuse	O
Frigate	O
,	O
commanded	O
by	O
William	B-pers
,	O
and	O
is	O
too	O
keen	O
a	O
Sailor	O
to	O
waste	O
his	O
precious	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
journeying	O
to	O
this	O
Country	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Cochrane	I-pers
is	O
now	O
at	O
Dunira	O
,	O
with	O
The	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
--	O
Your	O
Letter	O
shall	O
be	O
burnt	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
Orders	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
any	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
more	O
especially	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Melville	I-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
(	O
late	O
Mrs	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
)	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
aſsociate	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
Estate	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
Brother	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
of	I-pers
Shawfield	I-pers
.	O
His	O
eldest	O
Son	O
married	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
daughter	O
the	B-pers
late	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyll	I-pers
--	O
As	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
Age	O
of	O
Wonders	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Frost	O
&	O
Snow	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
verdure	O
of	O
Spring	O
at	O
Christmas	O
.	O
The	O
frequent	O
Storms	O
of	O
Wind	O
&	O
Rain	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
tremendous	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
rendered	O
the	O
walking	O
about	O
intolerably	O
disagreeable	O
.	O
My	O
Lungs	O
play	O
best	O
,	O
in	O
clear	O
frosty	O
Weather	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
ardently	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
next	O
Midsummer	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Best	O
love	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Countrywoman	O
&	O
c	O
My	O
Rib	O
&	O
Progeny	O
are	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
affecte-	O
Brother	O
Louisa	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
When	O
You	O
are	O
idle	O
,	O
remember	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
grudge	O
postage	O
.	O
Napier	B-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
