TOKEN	NE
Kew	B-place
.	O
Thursday	O
21	O
st	O
August	O
1782	O
My	O
Drst	O
.	O
friend	O
The	O
melancholy	O
scene	O
closed	O
by	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Dr	O
.	O
Child	O
Yesterday	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
have	O
been	O
deeply	O
afflicted	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
thank	O
God	O
more	O
composed	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
in	O
their	O
health	O
.	O
they	O
quitted	O
Windsor	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
at	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
&	O
intend	O
staying	O
here	O
till	O
Friday	O
Sen̄ight	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
Charge	O
the	O
five	O
Pſs	O
's	O
.	O
&	O
Prince	B-pers
Octavious	I-pers
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
G-	I-pers
&	O
c	O
remain	O
at	O
W	B-place
.	I-place
--	O
Mlle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
is	O
here	O
to	O
attend	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
ones	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
will	O
be	O
inter	O
'd	O
privately	O
in	O
Westminster	O
Abbey	O
next	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
sufficiently	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
add	O
more	O
at	O
present	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
M	B-pers
H	I-pers
My	O
letters	O
will	O
be	O
forwarded	O
from	O
W——	B-place
daily	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
Yo	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
