TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	B-place
Andover	B-place
Sepbr	O
18	O
th	O
1788	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
/	O
This	O
mornings	O
post	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
charges	O
me	O
to	O
expreſs	O
along	O
wth	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
,	O
His	O
sense	O
of	O
Yrs	O
..	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
s	O
goodneſs	O
;	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
with	O
your	O
sweet	O
little	O
Girl	O
whose	O
company	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
additional	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
indeed	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
good	O
acct	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
;	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
air	O
&	O
water	O
of	O
Kedleston	B-place
have	O
afforded	O
that	O
releif	O
&	O
benefitt	O
they	O
so	O
much	O
wanted	O
.	O
poor	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
state	O
is	O
shocking	O
in	O
the	O
extreem	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
s	O
situation	O
most	O
deplorable	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
recourse	O
to	O
the	O
expedience	O
of	O
having	O
proper	O
attendants	O
on	O
her	O
Unhappy	O
friend	O
before	O
any	O
Mischief	O
happens	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
such	O
when	O
ever	O
it	O
pleases	O
God	O
to	O
Release	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
a	O
most	O
Mercyfull	O
dispensation	O
on	O
all	O
accts	O
.	O
certainly	O
.	O
but	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
sad	O
subject	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
very	O
pleasing	O
one	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
of	O
our	O
obligations	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
your	O
flattering	O
&	O
kind	O
compliance	O
wth	O
our	O
request	O
;	O
we	O
shall	O
hope	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
all	O
here	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
week	O
in	O
Octbr	O
:	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
such	O
accomodation	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
house	O
can	O
afford	O
,	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
most	O
cordial	O
reception	O
from	O
all	O
under	O
this	O
roof	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
thankfull	O
for	O
a	O
line	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
fix	O
the	O
day	O
for	O
coming	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
come	O
By	O
Andover	B-place
,	O
or	O
Sutton	B-place
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
send	O
horses	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
at	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
places	O
:	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
best	O
respects	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
beleive	O
me	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
with	O
unfeign	O
'd	O
regard	O
&	O
esteem	O
Your	O
much	O
obliged	O
&	O
affec	O
te	O
Servant	O
Penelope	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
St	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
&	O
his	O
family	O
in	O
our	O
near	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
will	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
;	O
as	O
Catherine	B-pers
does	O
most	O
particularly	O
in	O
ye	O
expectation	O
of	O
seeing	O
Miſs	O
D	O
your	O
d	O
ear	O
Daughter	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
tender	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
answer	O
;	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
J.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
Esq	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
27	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
London	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
Septr	O
.	O
18-	O
1788	O
