TOKEN	NE
Teingmouth	B-place
June	O
27	O
th	O
1785	O
.	O
/	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
./	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
really	O
was	O
nothing	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
communicate	O
,	O
worth	O
troubling	O
you	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
now	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Pen	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
,	O
having	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
to	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
Wishes	O
and	O
Congratulations	O
upon	O
your	O
Marriage	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
commiſsion	O
him	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
to	O
you	O
instead	O
of	O
writing	O
myself	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
/as	O
I	O
said	O
before/	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
communicate	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
/knowing	O
your	O
kind	O
friendship	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
/	O
that	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
rather	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
write./	O
We	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
Letter	O
dated	O
from	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
it	O
that	O
your	O
excellent	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
health	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
the	O
more	O
particularly	O
sorry	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
knew	O
it	O
must	O
vex	O
you	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
We	O
hope	O
however	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
benefit	O
by	O
his	O
excursion	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
directed	O
my	O
Letter	O
to	O
Sunning-Hill	B-place
,	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
has	O
reach	O
'd	O
her./	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
conclude	O
as	O
my	O
Mother	O
wishes	O
to	O
add	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
yours	O
affectionately./	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
./	O
Altho	O
'	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
might	O
justly	O
think	O
that	O
all	O
our	O
congratulations	O
shoud	O
have	O
been	O
expreſsed	O
by	O
one	O
only	O
of	O
a	O
family	O
knowing	O
how	O
much	O
your	O
leisure	O
must	O
at	O
present	O
be	O
engroſsed	O
upon	O
the	O
happy	O
occasion	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
shoud	O
not	O
have	O
felt	O
comfortable	O
had	O
I	O
commiſsioned	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
me	O
how	O
sincerely	O
I	O
partake	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
Satisfaction	O
with	O
your	O
other	O
friends	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
as	O
a	O
postscript	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
s	O
letter	O
hoping	O
you	O
will	O
answer	O
it	O
in	O
kind	O
,	O
without	O
troubling	O
yourself	O
with	O
a	O
separate	O
Sheet	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
principle	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
trust	O
to	O
your	O
supposing	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
every	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
and	O
future	O
happineſs	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
detained	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
perusal	O
of	O
pages	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
told	O
you	O
how	O
delighted	O
Robert	B-pers
was	O
with	O
your	O
Attention	O
to	O
Him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indeed	O
as	O
perfectly	O
Sensible	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
one	O
shoud	O
suppose	O
from	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
his	O
Heart	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
powerful	O
Rival	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
captivated	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
whole	O
history	O
of	O
his	O
Endeavors	O
to	O
Entertain	O
and	O
amuse	O
him	O
and	O
how	O
we	O
ll	O
he	O
succeeded	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
My	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
who	O
se	O
acquaintance	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
be	O
doubly	O
happy	O
to	O
improve	O
and	O
remain	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
regard	O
,	O
your	O
very	O
faithful	O
and	O
obliged	O
,	O
Hum	O
ble	O
-	O
Servant	O
R	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Teingmouth	B-place
27	O
th	O
June	O
85	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
June	O
1785	O
