TOKEN	NE
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
6	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1780	O
.	O
For	O
once	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
discovered	O
an	O
amazing	O
want	O
of	O
penetration	O
.	O
You	O
suppose	O
my	O
Heart	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
--	O
beleive	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
made	O
of	O
such	O
inflammable	O
matter	O
as	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
suspect	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
danger	O
from	O
the	O
Herts	B-place
Beauties	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
alarming	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
confeſs	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
clear	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
renounced	O
it	O
's	O
allegiance	O
to	O
M.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
idea	O
of	O
her	O
intrudes	O
upon	O
my	O
recollection	O
in	O
my	O
solitary	O
walks	O
more	O
frequently	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
the	O
letter	O
from	O
D——shire	B-place
.	O
It	O
leaves	O
you	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
pursue	O
your	O
own	O
inclinations	O
.	O
Your	O
situation	O
is	O
delicate	O
,	O
your	O
prudence	O
great	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
must	O
now	O
either	O
accept	O
or	O
absolutely	O
refuse	O
the	O
offer	O
.	O
I	O
proposed	O
the	O
plan	O
of	O
visiting	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
pleased	O
with	O
your	O
attention	O
and	O
I	O
beleive	O
very	O
little	O
persuasion	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
her	O
agree	O
to	O
the	O
expedition	O
.	O
Her	O
trip	O
into	O
Eſsex	B-place
will	O
take	O
place	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
attempted	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
without	O
effect	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
changing	O
Beds	B-place
at	O
her	O
time	O
of	O
Life	O
may	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
bad	O
consequences	O
;	O
however	O
she	O
is	O
determined	O
(	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
said	O
obstinate	O
)	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
The	O
Atholls	O
did	O
not	O
aquaint	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
thier	O
Daughter	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
neglecting	O
it	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
--	O
She	O
went	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
imagined	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
my	O
making	O
my	O
Visit	O
so	O
long	O
at	O
Tewin	B-place
.	O
I	O
wish	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
careleſs	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
civility	O
would	O
please	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
Bathing	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
do	O
you	O
good	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
brace	O
your	O
Nerves	O
&	O
prevent	O
Feverets	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
Riding	O
on	O
horseback	O
is	O
good	O
lik	O
ewise	O
good	O
,	O
when	O
people	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
seldom	O
affront	O
my	O
feet	O
.	O
Now	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
venture	O
to	O
drive	O
an	O
open	O
Chaise	O
with	O
one	O
old	O
blind	O
Cart	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
only	O
upon	O
very	O
particular	O
occasions	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
the	O
August	O
Birthday	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
publick	O
or	O
private	O
;	O
however	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
little	O
consequence	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
Your	O
's	O
very	O
sincerely	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
N	B-pers
Ld-	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
6	O
Augst	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
3	O
4	O
2	O
2	O
2	O
2	O
2	O
