TOKEN	NE
--	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
better	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
--	O
Oh	O
cd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
wth-	O
me	O
--	O
Adieu	O
not	O
a	O
moment	O
more	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
scrawl	O
!	O
but	O
My	O
Astrea	B-pers
will	O
take	O
it	O
well	O
of	O
me	O
&	O
receive	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
love	O
&	O
friendship	O
I	O
Letters	O
are	O
detain	O
'd	O
somewhere	O
or	O
other	O
certainly	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
will	O
please	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Rhea	B-pers
was	O
much	O
satisfied	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
answer	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
letter	O
for	O
in	O
one	O
yt	O
.	O
Perfecta	B-pers
recd	O
.	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
she	O
say	O
's	O
--	O
“	O
tell	O
MH	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
“	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
answer	O
her	O
letter	O
,	O
“	O
she	O
make	O
's	O
me	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
driving	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
Far——	I-pers
open	O
chaise	O
round	O
ye	O
Links	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
ground	O
(	O
enclosed	O
)	O
so	O
call	O
'd	O
)	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
B.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
to	O
Pevensey	B-place
--	O
&	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
on	O
Horseback	O
Mr.	B-pers
Far	I-pers
.	I-pers
accompinied	O
me	O
--	O
