TOKEN	NE
1	O
st	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
her	O
sister	O
in	O
law	O
Charles	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
wife	O
My	O
Dr	O
Sister	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
his	O
Gout	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
last	O
Letter	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
I	O
hope	O
his	O
Complaints	O
are	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
entirely	O
remov	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
Grieved	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
lose	O
you	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
loſs	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
particular	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
reconcile	O
My	O
self	O
to	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
pray	O
tell	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
setting	O
out	O
for	O
Naples	B-place
together	O
--	O
but	O
Alas	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
that	O
Scheme	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
upon	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	O
Building	O
System	O
--	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
See	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
we	O
set	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
you	O
both	O
do	O
before	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
go	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
line	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
anxious	O
about	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
Concer	O
ns	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
w	O
ant	O
ish	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
his	O
Gout	O
has	O
quite	O
left	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
My	O
thanks	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
you	O
for	O
two	O
Birds	O
which	O
Dolly	B-pers
has	O
wrote	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
I	O
shall	O
Value	O
them	O
Much	O
--	O
My	O
Love	O
Attends	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
Sister	O
most	O
Affecly	O
&	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
CHamilton	B-pers
I	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
H	I-pers
for	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
from	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
Saturday	O
