TOKEN	NE
could	O
form	O
no	O
judgment	O
--	O
Their	O
exterior	O
was	O
not	O
favorable	O
.	O
at	O
least	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
shine	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
Ladys	O
drawing	O
Room	O
Mr.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
was	O
attentive	O
,	O
polite	O
,	O
yet	O
silent	O
&	O
took	O
no	O
part	O
in	O
conversation	O
.	O
his	O
Tutor	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
off	O
--	O
his	O
countenance	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
sound	O
of	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
8	O
&	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
sober	O
Whist	O
party	O
,	O
at	O
wch	O
.	O
my	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
aſsisted	O
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
I	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
a	O
long	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Subject	O
was	O
America	B-place
as	O
I	O
intend	O
continuing	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
keep	O
these	O
scrawls	O
it	O
will	O
serve	O
sometime	O
hence	O
to	O
recall	O
past	O
days	O
&	O
furnish	O
us	O
subjects	O
of	O
conversation	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
You	O
my	O
friend	O
I	O
recd	O
Your	O
letter	O
directed	O
here	O
