TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
a	O
Coursing	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
often	O
happens	O
when	O
a	O
person	O
wishes	O
to	O
shew	O
diversion	O
they	O
are	O
disappointed	O
&	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
rode	O
Mr.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
Parkin	I-pers
s	O
blind	O
mare	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
sufft	O
.	O
Occupation	O
in	O
taking	O
Care	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
bones	O
back	O
safe	O
&	O
whole	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
her	O
115	O
miles	O
one	O
day	O
from	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
&	O
got	O
home	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
This	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
travelling	O
fast	O
--	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Cavalry	O
were	O
engaged	O
--	O
Poney	O
has	O
the	O
Strongles	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
Rest	O
somehow	O
occupied	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
ride	O
blindy	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
walk	O
so	O
much	O
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
After	O
breakfast	O
Hayden	B-pers
proposed	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
his	O
Estates	O
&	O
he	O
took	O
thro	O
his	O
Woods	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
excused	O
him	O
doing	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
suit	O
my	O
knee	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
worse	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
grumbles	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
what	O
from	O
my	O
Weakneſs	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
&	O
other	O
reasons	O
which	O
deter	O
me	O
from	O
jumping	O
off	O
the	O
Hedges	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
Shooting	O
as	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
suit	O
my	O
Antiquity	O
Hayden	B-pers
took	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
comparing	O
the	O
difference	O
of	O
his	O
Situation	O
with	O
his	O
Brothers	O
which	O
certainly	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
great	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
imprudent	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
no	O
experience	O
will	O
ever	O
make	O
him	O
steady	O
--	O
From	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
his	O
Mother	O
can	O
ever	O
accommodate	O
matters	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
pains	O
to	O
convince	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
imprudence	O
of	O
continuing	O
here	O
with	O
a	O
diminished	O
Income	O
James	B-pers
is	O
extremely	O
young	O
&	O
has	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
money	O
&	O
is	O
too	O
lately	O
returned	O
from	O
7	O
Years	O
residence	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
&	O
the	O
Society	O
&	O
Stile	O
of	O
living	O
of	O
young	O
Men	O
of	O
Fortune	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
attention	O
is	O
requisite	O
for	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
an	O
Establishment	O
--	O
Whilst	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
called	O
here	O
&	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
tomorrow	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Aſsistance	O
about	O
the	O
picture	O
Hayden	B-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Introduction	O
to	O
a	O
Gentn	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-place
wch	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
or	O
may	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Taunton	B-place
about	O
one	O
--	O
at	O
2	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
ride	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Paynter	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
under	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Woods	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynter	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
have	O
left	O
this	O
place	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
monday	O
morning	O
&	O
go	O
wh	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Chaise	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
which	O
will	O
save	O
him	O
one	O
night	O
&	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
journey	O
he	O
can	O
then	O
take	O
his	O
days	O
ride	O
without	O
so	O
much	O
fatigue	O
James	B-pers
proposes	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
somewhere	O
&	O
attend	O
him	O
to	O
Cornwall	B-place
about	O
90	O
miles	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
alone	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
post	O
Chaise	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
25	O
miles	O
&	O
then	O
take	O
the	O
Mail	O
as	O
other	O
Coach	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
are	O
plenty	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
&	O
shall	O
probably	O
get	O
to	O
that	O
place	O
before	O
you	O
are	O
up	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
&	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
sipping	O
yr-	O
Tea	O
you	O
may	O
conclude	O
my	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
the	O
greatest	O
distance	O
from	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
ever	O
has	O
been	O
yet	O
since	O
our	O
marriage	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Heart	O
remains	O
Stationary	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
Comfort	O
in	O
that	O
Reflection	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
again	O
&	O
have	O
felt	O
half	O
inclined	O
not	O
to	O
extend	O
my	O
journey	O
,	O
but	O
The	O
Weather	O
is	O
so	O
fine	O
that	O
it	O
induces	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
as	O
I	O
originally	O
proposed	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
few	O
miles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Way	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
Clifton	B-place
&	O
it	O
will	O
also	O
break	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
journey	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
palavering	O
Compy	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Shrewd	O
One	O
will	O
amuse	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Time	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
chere	O
Amie	O
Kiſs	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
me	O
--	O
Kind	O
Regards	O
to	O
Mor	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ever	O
Yours	O
Most	O
Affy	O
JD	B-pers
Nothing	O
can	O
exceed	O
the	O
Kindneſs	O
&	O
attention	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
this	O
family	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
