TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
A	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
,	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
offer	O
,	O
wch	O
we	O
are	O
Mortified	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
reap	O
any	O
benefit	O
o	O
from	O
particularly	O
as	O
we	O
leave	O
town	B-place
to	O
Morrow	O
Morn	O
:	O
we	O
are	O
ingaged	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lethieullier	I-pers
so	O
late	O
,	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
,	O
wch	O
makes	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
know	O
at	O
what	O
hour	O
we	O
shall	O
return	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
you	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
all	O
Join	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
&	O
the	O
Charming	O
Louisa	B-pers
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
all	O
at	O
Wherwell	B-place
when	O
ever	O
it	O
suits	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
that	O
pleasure	O
in	O
great	O
hast	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
your	O
most	O
faithfull	O
&	O
obliged	O
P	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
Wednesday	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
