TOKEN	NE
Stan	O
.	O
St	O
:	O
Sepr	O
:	O
13	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
Yr	O
:	O
kind	O
Letter	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
I	O
feel	O
grateful	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Offer	O
your	O
good	O
&	O
worthy	O
Husd	O
:	O
makes	O
of	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Dr	O
:	O
Son	O
--	O
but	O
alas	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
State	O
to	O
receive	O
comfort	O
or	O
Amusement	O
from	O
Company	O
--	O
even	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
likes	O
so	O
much	O
&	O
who	O
travelled	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
above	O
once	O
this	O
Week	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
Civility	O
--	O
His	O
greatest	O
Pleasure	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
,	O
either	O
alone	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
his	O
poor	O
Father	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
read	O
together	O
;	O
or	O
chat	O
as	O
he	O
calls	O
it	O
quietly	O
together	O
--	O
He	O
often	O
talks	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
has	O
planned	O
(	O
poor	O
Sweet	O
Soul	O
)	O
to	O
co	O
go	O
o	O
me	O
&	O
make	O
you	O
another	O
visit	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Instant	O
he	O
is	O
fast	O
asleep	O
--	O
&	O
his	O
Cough	O
has	O
been	O
rather	O
leſs	O
frequent	O
this	O
Morng	O
:	O
he	O
bore	O
his	O
Journey	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
wonderfully	O
,	O
&	O
feels	O
happy	O
in	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
indeed	O
infinitely	O
thankful	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
here	O
again	O
.	O
Docr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
attends	O
him	O
as	O
Warren	B-pers
is	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
--	O
&	O
his	O
Medicines	O
certainly	O
agree	O
with	O
Him	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
comfort	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
write	O
directly	O
.	O
God	O
Almighty	O
knows	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
best	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
his	O
Bleſsed	O
Will	O
be	O
done	O
Yrs	O
:	O
ever	O
Afft	O
&	O
gratefully	O
PC	B-pers
My	O
poor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
is	O
but	O
indifferent	O
--	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
amazing	O
that	O
either	O
He	O
or	O
I	O
are	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
--	O
God	O
Almighty	O
is	O
very	O
merciful	O
in	O
supporting	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
this	O
great	O
Affliction	O
as	O
He	O
does	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
yr	O
.	O
dr	O
Child	O
is	O
well	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
Dr	O
:	O
Parents	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
Sepr	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
I	O
hear	O
Dr	O
:	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
better	O
but	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
lost	O
her	O
Cough	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
have	O
directed	O
this	O
Letter	O
right	O
.	O
