TOKEN	NE
Boston	B-place
Octr	O
:	O
19	O
th	O
1768	O
Nothing	O
but	O
want	O
of	O
ability	O
to	O
write	O
should	O
so	O
long	O
have	O
prevented	O
my	O
thanking	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
for	O
her	O
obligeing	O
Letter	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
happy	O
with	O
the	O
good	O
Accounts	O
you	O
give	O
Us	O
of	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
's	O
Health	O
&	O
Congratulate	O
them	O
upon	O
haveing	O
conquer	O
'd	O
their	O
Gout	O
&	O
Rhumatism	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
Colds	O
I	O
dont	O
fear	O
much	O
from	O
them	O
&	O
hope	O
both	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
You	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
haveing	O
had	O
them	O
beffore	O
You	O
can	O
Receive	O
this	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
Sorry	O
the	O
Venison	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
;	O
proveably	O
the	O
Keeper	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
had	O
left	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
&	O
so	O
did	O
not	O
Kill	O
the	O
Buck	O
:	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
Ourselves	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
glad	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
so	O
very	O
Indifferent	O
about	O
our	O
Return	O
as	O
it	O
wont	O
give	O
him	O
Uneasineſs	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Troops	O
are	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
all	O
Winter	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
Horses	O
are	O
brought	O
from	O
Graſs	O
to	O
the	O
different	O
Quarters	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
therefore	O
beg	O
either	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
or	O
Mamma	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Mr	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
that	O
we	O
return	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Samuell	I-pers
would	O
have	O
wrote	O
so	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
write	O
this	O
from	O
his	O
bed	O
Side	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
confined	O
by	O
a	O
feverish	O
Indisposition	O
--	O
so	O
beg	O
they	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
this	O
Information	O
--	O
he	O
sayd	O
at	O
parting	O
he	O
'd	O
paint	O
the	O
Parlour	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Conveniency	O
whether	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
or	O
not	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
whether	O
we	O
came	O
or	O
Not	O
so	O
he	O
is	O
still	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
sooner	O
than	O
we	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
had	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
Asure	O
yourselves	O
we	O
regreate	O
much	O
being	O
so	O
far	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
shall	O
ever	O
retain	O
the	O
most	O
Gratefull	O
Sense	O
of	O
yr	O
Polite	O
&	O
friendly	O
attention	O
to	O
Us	O
while	O
with	O
You	O
--	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
asure	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
yourself	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
partiality	O
for	O
Northampton	B-place
nor	O
do	O
I	O
Sigh	O
after	O
Babylonish	O
Acquaintance	O
--	O
Intimacy	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
formed	O
there	O
but	O
with	O
Yourselves	O
:	O
much	O
do	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
each	O
other	O
Selfish	O
enough	O
you	O
'll	O
Say	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
Agreeable	O
friends	O
to	O
Nurse	O
me	O
when	O
confined	O
&	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
Spiritts	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
;	O
in	O
febry	O
or	O
March	O
--	O
I	O
'm	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
Danger	O
from	O
my	O
dangerous	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
Suffer	O
greatly	O
both	O
from	O
Situation	O
&	O
Uneasineſs	O
of	O
Mind	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
Harriot	B-pers
are	O
both	O
confined	O
to	O
their	O
room	O
mostly	O
to	O
bed	O
by	O
the	O
fever	O
&	O
Ague	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
touch	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
we	O
hope	O
she	O
'll	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
easily	O
--	O
we	O
hope	O
Mainie	B-pers
's	O
wont	O
last	O
either	O
I	O
've	O
heard	O
twice	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
where	O
our	O
friends	O
were	O
Well	O
&	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
their	O
Situation	O
&	O
Reception	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
seems	O
in	O
high	O
Spiritts	O
asure	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
wt	O
ever	O
be	O
c	O
ame	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
Br	O
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
him	O
beffore	O
he	O
left	O
London	B-place
because	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
bid	O
him	O
Adieu	O
&	O
to	O
thank	O
him	O
&	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
Us	O
wch	O
we	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
terms	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
deservd	O
Pray	O
is	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
yet	O
&	O
wt	O
has	O
she	O
got	O
?	O
its	O
yet	O
uncertain	O
whether	O
Head	O
Quarters	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
fixt	O
at	O
Lincoln	B-place
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
--	O
if	O
so	O
we	O
go	O
there	O
--	O
if	O
not	O
we	O
continue	O
where	O
we	O
are	O
--	O
Boston	B-place
affords	O
all	O
proper	O
Aſsistance	O
for	O
my	O
Situation	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
hear	O
good	O
Acts	O
from	O
you	O
wt	O
a	O
History	O
of	O
all	O
Memorable	O
transactions	O
amongst	O
You	O
;	O
all	O
our	O
best	O
respects	O
attend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Yourself	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
Heartily	O
sorry	O
its	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
long	O
beffore	O
we	O
Meet	O
:	O
however	O
we	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
pleasure	O
often	O
in	O
some	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
wherever	O
we	O
are	O
our	O
best	O
Wishes	O
are	O
Yours	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
--	O
bellieve	O
me	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Sincearly	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
