TOKEN	NE
Gaieties	O
criticized	O
Edinburgh	B-place
May	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
1774	O
yours	O
from	O
Chesterfield	O
Street	O
wtout	O
a	O
date	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
came	O
to	O
hand	O
last	O
post	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
anſwer	O
it	O
I	O
must	O
just	O
hint	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
you	O
take	O
so	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
satisfied	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
but	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
one	O
ought	O
to	O
satisfy	O
their	O
friends	O
likeways	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
make	O
them	O
uneaſy	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
yt	O
you	O
can	O
imagine	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
very	O
easy	O
upon	O
your	O
account	O
after	O
what	O
you	O
wrote	O
about	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
so	O
great	O
a	O
friendship	O
&	O
intimacy	O
with	O
a	O
Lady	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
ſay	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
suppose	O
she	O
loved	O
you	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
daughter	O
&	O
at	O
once	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
ſuch	O
a	O
distance	O
dont	O
hang	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
reason	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
worthy	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
reaſon	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
City	O
those	O
things	O
may	O
be	O
triffles	O
that	O
a	O
letter	O
any	O
day	O
may	O
set	O
right	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
so	O
little	O
consequence	O
what	O
an	O
Old	O
Maid	O
ſays	O
or	O
what	O
friends	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
may	O
think	O
.	O
you	O
see	O
My	O
dear	O
Girl	O
how	O
good	O
yr	O
Mama	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Barnet	B-place
wt	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
road	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
should	O
make	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
time	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
oblige	O
her	O
,	O
few	O
mothers	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
that	O
trouble	O
in	O
this	O
age	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
heart	O
,	O
be	O
gratefull	O
for	O
those	O
Bleſsings	O
you	O
receive	O
.	O
It	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pleaſure	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
well	O
ſince	O
you	O
left	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
her	O
so	O
very	O
soon	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
write	O
every	O
post	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
satisfaction	O
she	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
have	O
in	O
your	O
abſence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
glad	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
your	O
Uncle	O
Cathcart	B-pers
&	O
that	O
my	O
Young	O
Nieces	O
pleases	O
you	O
,	O
they	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Girls	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
turn	O
out	O
worthy	O
amiable	O
women	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
eldest	O
daughters	O
have	O
been	O
both	O
ill	O
of	O
Fevers	O
&	O
sore	O
throats	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
join	O
their	O
Brother	O
in	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
you	O
like	O
the	O
lines	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
mistake	O
the	O
author	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
Jane	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
,	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
ſame	O
hand	O
if	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
fault	O
please	O
correct	O
&	O
amend	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
at	O
least	O
oblige	O
me	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
no	O
other	O
hands	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
off	O
--	O
Plays	O
,	O
Operas	O
,	O
Pantheon	O
,	O
&	O
Renalagh	O
Good	O
God	O
is	O
not	O
thy	O
little	O
head	O
turned	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
nonsense	O
Play	O
&	O
Operas	O
I	O
will	O
allow	O
may	O
be	O
both	O
amusing	O
,	O
deverting	O
&	O
instructing	O
The	O
Pantheon	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
be	O
ſeen	O
for	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
may	O
be	O
allowable	O
but	O
Renalagh	O
insipit	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
night	O
will	O
always	O
continue	O
so	O
to	O
people	O
of	O
a	O
ſenſible	O
taste	O
few	O
very	O
few	O
I	O
am	O
ſorry	O
to	O
ſay	O
you	O
'll	O
meet	O
with	O
in	O
that	O
great	O
City	O
unleſs	O
greatly	O
altered	O
ſince	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
beau	O
monde	O
your	O
remarks	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
pleases	O
me	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
agree	O
exactly	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
opinion	O
which	O
is	O
always	O
flattering	O
when	O
one	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
makes	O
them	O
.	O
Most	O
parts	O
of	O
Young	O
Ladies	O
education	O
in	O
this	O
Age	O
are	O
extravagant	O
Muſic	O
&	O
drawing	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
improperly	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
that	O
many	O
fine	O
genious	O
's	O
are	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
lurch	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
honour	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
The	O
Masters	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
blame	O
as	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
make	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
The	O
rich	O
foolish	O
people	O
has	O
a	O
pride	O
in	O
learning	O
blockheads	O
of	O
Sons	O
&	O
dauthers	O
a	O
smattering	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
capacity	O
for	O
to	O
shew	O
their	O
superiority	O
of	O
Riches	O
and	O
ſenſible	O
people	O
must	O
pay	O
extravagantly	O
or	O
lose	O
their	O
accomplishments	O
they	O
are	O
fit	O
for	O
ſuch	O
is	O
my	O
dear	O
Girl	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
tide	O
runs	O
strong	O
we	O
must	O
give	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
to	O
it	O
like	O
the	O
Bulrush	O
otherwise	O
like	O
the	O
Oak	O
we	O
will	O
be	O
tore	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
roots	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
deſires	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
will	O
esteem	O
a	O
drawing	O
of	O
yours	O
greatly	O
as	O
she	O
knows	O
you	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
good	O
ſense	O
to	O
continue	O
learning	O
unleſs	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
profit	O
by	O
it	O
but	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
acceptable	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Catherine	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
's	O
acquaintance	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
esteemed	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
I	O
am	O
quite	O
ſure	O
they	O
are	O
deſerving	O
of	O
all	O
you	O
ſay	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
ſuch	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
off	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
a	O
better	O
woman	O
or	O
a	O
more	O
amiable	O
one	O
pray	O
remember	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
to	O
her	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
see	O
her	O
after	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
gets	O
to	O
NorthHampton	O
after	O
your	O
Bath	B-place
jaunt	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
remarks	O
of	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
c	O
As	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
s	O
scheme	O
for	O
his	O
daughter	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
adopt	O
your	O
good	O
ſense	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
judge	O
of	O
whats	O
fit	O
for	O
anothers	O
daughter	O
especially	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
buſineſs	O
in	O
the	O
affair	O
--	O
Well	O
Lady	B-pers
Dawtry	I-pers
at	O
a	O
Masquerade	O
,	O
Curiosity	O
thy	O
name	O
is	O
——	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
you	O
shall	O
ever	O
go	O
too	O
&	O
I	O
most	O
ſincerely	O
wish	O
you	O
well	O
at	O
Home	O
&	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
temptations	O
of	O
London	B-place
I	O
may	O
be	O
abused	O
for	O
this	O
by	O
your	O
Gay	O
friends	O
and	O
called	O
an	O
old	O
illnatured	O
creature	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
make	O
my	O
dear	O
ward	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
care	O
not	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
ſaid	O
otherwise	O
the	O
expence	O
two	O
thouſand	O
pounds	O
&	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
for	O
a	O
ticket	O
its	O
a	O
shame	O
conſidering	O
how	O
many	O
poor	O
miserable	O
creatures	O
it	O
might	O
make	O
happy	O
for	O
their	O
lives	O
&	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
a	O
nights	O
amusement	O
to	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
fools	O
that	O
has	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
Good	O
God	O
what	O
must	O
senſible	O
People	O
think	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
matter	O
its	O
taste	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
the	O
best	O
Company	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
apology	O
for	O
doing	O
a	O
despicable	O
nonſensical	O
thing	O
fit	O
only	O
for	O
children	O
at	O
a	O
dancing	O
School	O
&	O
not	O
for	O
rational	O
minds	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
my	O
dear	O
Girl	O
be	O
extremely	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
letter	O
dated	O
from	O
Northampton	B-place
&	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
have	O
returned	O
the	O
fine	O
ſenſible	O
amiable	O
Girl	O
as	O
formerly	O
otherwise	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
'll	O
curse	O
London	B-place
&	O
all	O
London	O
folks	O
for	O
your	O
sake	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
joins	O
the	O
young	O
folks	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
most	O
ſincerely	O
Yours	O
Mr-	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
expect	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
en	O
famille	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
here	O
Did	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
go	O
to	O
the	O
Masquerade	O
?	O
I	O
dare	O
anſwer	O
No	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
construed	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
not	O
liable	O
to	O
the	O
ſame	O
construction	O
