TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
&	O
waited	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
learn	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
letter	O
for	O
me	O
!	O
!	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
that	O
no	O
News	O
is	O
good	O
News	O
but	O
certainly	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
agreeable	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
particularly	O
distreſsing	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
it	O
never	O
happened	O
before	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
reduced	O
to	O
short	O
Commons	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Land	O
--	O
from	O
the	O
P	O
.	O
Office	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Marine	O
Barracks	O
at	O
Stonehouse	B-place
--	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Band	O
of	O
Music	O
much	O
boasted	O
of	O
--	O
Unluckily	O
for	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
Muster	O
Day	O
&	O
no	O
Music	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
to	O
the	O
Lancashire	O
Barracks	O
&	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
Dock	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Mail	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
which	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
Conveyance	O
to	O
Clifton	B-place
&	O
was	O
disappointed	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
promise	O
me	O
a	O
place	O
before	O
4	O
OClock	O
&	O
then	O
it	O
is	O
uncertain	O
--	O
&	O
during	O
my	O
walk	O
the	O
other	O
Coach	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
so	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
beguiling	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
writing	O
my	O
journal	O
&	O
scribbling	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
away	O
to	O
night	O
if	O
poſsible	O
as	O
my	O
purse	O
is	O
low	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
desire	O
Louisa	B-pers
will	O
send	O
me	O
5£	O
&	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
chooses	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
direct	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Clifton	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
convey	O
me	O
to	O
London	B-place
as	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
stopping	O
at	O
Clifton	B-place
--	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
provoked	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Comr	O
s	O
.	O
yesterday	O
to	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
Newspaper	O
before	O
the	O
family	O
entered	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
Driblets	O
consisting	O
of	O
Adml	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stopford	I-pers
--	O
Adl	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Daughters	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
--	O
The	O
party	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
after	O
finishing	O
&	O
losing	O
2	O
Rubbers	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
asked	O
Ad	B-pers
.	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
if	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
a	O
Water	O
Excursion	O
&	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
--	O
Frequently	O
a	O
party	O
go	O
es	O
on	O
the	O
River	B-place
Plym	I-place
to	O
a	O
place	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
miles	O
called	O
Wear	B-place
near	O
Tavistock	B-place
--	O
The	O
views	O
are	O
beautiful	O
&	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Salmon	O
Leap	O
at	O
Wear	B-place
--	O
this	O
is	O
managed	O
by	O
attending	O
to	O
the	O
Tides	O
,	O
Winds	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
agreeable	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
yesterday	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
durst	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
at	O
Comr	O
.	O
said	O
remember	O
5	O
at	O
parting	O
)	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
Mt	B-place
.	I-place
Edgcumbe	I-place
--	O
When	O
I	O
sent	O
up	O
my	O
Note	O
requesting	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Grounds	O
&	O
using	O
Ly	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
's	O
Name	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
an	O
Ansr	O
.	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
very	O
welcome	O
&	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
there	O
the	O
Sert	O
said	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mt	I-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
wished	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Gardens	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
special	O
favor	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
of	O
course	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
staring	O
at	O
the	O
astonishing	O
extent	O
&	O
variety	O
of	O
prospects	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Maker	O
Tower	O
where	O
the	O
Signal	O
posts	O
are	O
&	O
from	O
whence	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Dock	O
Yard	O
Shipping	O
,	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
extent	O
&	O
turng	O
round	O
one	O
sees	O
Cornwal	B-place
&	O
the	O
narrow	O
Isthmus	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
stand	O
Mt	B-place
.	I-place
Edg	I-place
.	I-place
&	O
also	O
an	O
immense	O
expanse	O
of	O
Ocean	O
--	O
The	O
Views	O
are	O
broken	O
in	O
the	O
plantations	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
Manner	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Loughborough	I-pers
after	O
seeing	O
Mt	B-place
.	I-place
E	I-place
.	I-place
said	O
to	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Comr	O
.	O
“	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
be	O
puffed	O
”	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
one	O
may	O
gather	O
was	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
unique	O
in	O
Situation	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
Key	O
a	O
Card	O
to	O
admit	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
L	O
5-	O
The	O
Gardener	O
shewed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
&	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
--	O
Opposite	O
the	O
Conservatory	O
I	O
saw	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mt	I-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
thanked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Civility	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
dear	O
Cis	B-pers
--	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
an	O
Italian	O
Garden	O
of	O
the	O
Spot	O
where	O
we	O
then	O
were	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
figures	O
on	O
pedestals	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
also	O
3	O
on	O
a	O
high	O
sort	O
of	O
parapet	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
propose	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
constructing	O
his	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
&	O
Wife	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Spot	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mt	I-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Gardener	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
himself	O
--	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
on	O
busineſs	O
&	O
meant	O
to	O
turn	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
Servt	O
.	O
--	O
These	O
Gardens	O
are	O
beautiful	O
&	O
very	O
pretty	O
too	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
buildings	O
one	O
contains	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Room	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
books	O
&	O
Pianoforte	O
&	O
c	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
magnificent	O
Magnolia	O
ferrugina	O
--	O
One	O
30	O
feet	O
high	O
in	O
flower	O
several	O
above	O
20	O
feet	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
agreeable	O
apendage	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
like	O
Mt	B-place
.	I-place
E	I-place
.	I-place
&	O
a	O
delightful	O
Retirement	O
in	O
good	O
Weather	O
--	O
The	O
little	O
Lord	O
stuck	O
to	O
his	O
Workman	O
&	O
we	O
cd	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
doing	O
tho	O
we	O
made	O
many	O
attempts	O
I	O
understand	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
particular	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
shewn	O
--	O
The	O
Gardener	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
prodigious	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Place	O
--	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
1400	O
on	O
one	O
day	O
frequently	O
1000	O
--	O
This	O
must	O
add	O
great	O
l	O
y	O
to	O
the	O
hilarity	O
of	O
the	O
Scene	O
--	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
dejection	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
I	O
loved	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
pleasure	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
communicating	O
my	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
grandeur	O
of	O
the	O
Scenes	O
before	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
on	O
Breakwater	O
--	O
that	O
stupendous	O
Work	O
--	O
making	O
across	O
the	O
Sound	O
--	O
Large	O
maſses	O
of	O
Rock	O
are	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
the	O
base	O
of	O
the	O
Column	O
is	O
400	O
feet	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
Surface	O
120	O
--	O
for	O
some	O
distance	O
it	O
already	O
is	O
above	O
low	O
water	O
mark	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
progreſs	O
about	O
14	O
months	O
&	O
in	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
years	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
completed	O
--	O
Cost	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Question	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
Calculation	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
conclude	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
probably	O
in	O
time	O
just	O
to	O
say	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
this	O
afternoon	O
not	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Noise	O
like	O
the	O
Scream	O
the	O
Apple	O
Women	O
make	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Men	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
at	O
2	O
OClock	O
,	O
to	O
attract	O
Customers	O
--	O
All	O
pill	O
Garlicks	O
poultry	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
make	O
so	O
discordant	O
a	O
Sound	O
--	O
The	O
Breakwater	O
is	O
intended	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
a	O
tremendous	O
Sea	O
that	O
is	O
driven	O
into	O
the	O
Sound	O
by	O
a	O
South	O
wind	O
&	O
renders	O
the	O
Harbour	O
so	O
dangerous	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
Fort	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
confined	O
)	O
upon	O
it	O
--	O
No	O
Masonry	O
can	O
resist	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Waves	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
this	O
afternoon	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
