TOKEN	NE
Burley	B-place
.	O
Decr	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1777	O
--	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Thō	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
will	O
probably	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
better	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
long-expected	O
Letter	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
must	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
it	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
thō	O
it	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
Circumstance	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
dear	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Loſs	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
the	O
most	O
to	O
be	O
lamented	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
the	O
least	O
be	O
repaired	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
all	O
my	O
Comforts	O
here	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
,	O
are	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
;	O
&	O
in	O
their	O
Society	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
paſs	O
'd	O
a	O
happy	O
&	O
chearful	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
My	O
time	O
now	O
draws	O
near	O
a	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
look	O
with	O
great	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
finding	O
all	O
I	O
I	O
am	O
interested	O
about	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
2	O
dear	O
Princeſses	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
post	O
enclosed	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
have	O
been	O
received	O
,	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
from	O
the	O
hurry	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
but	O
a	O
Short	O
Letter	O
.	O
Many	O
thanks	O
for	O
yr	O
kind	O
Congratulations	O
on	O
Lord	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
's	O
Account	O
,	O
&	O
accept	O
his	O
thanks	O
also	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
is	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
enter	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Study	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
She	O
hopes	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
interesting	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
Botany	O
was	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
me	O
We	O
shall	O
revive	O
our	O
attention	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
present	O
Season	O
invites	O
to	O
nothing	O
that	O
can	O
carry	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
unleſs	O
we	O
could	O
be	O
inspired	O
with	O
the	O
Paſsion	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
Hunting	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
here	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
glory	O
.	O
Your	O
Anecdote	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
d'Coventry	I-pers
is	O
very	O
moving	O
,	O
&	O
convinces	O
me	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
under	O
no	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
dep	O
a	O
rting	O
from	O
the	O
Truth	O
should	O
be	O
adopted	O
.	O
My	O
3	O
little	O
Babes	O
are	O
here	O
as	O
fresh	O
as	O
Roses	O
,	O
&	O
defy	O
all	O
Cold	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
succeed	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
our	O
Journey	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
present	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
much	O
improved	O
by	O
their	O
Country	O
Séjour	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
than	O
I	O
really	O
am	O
.	O
C.F	B-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamn	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
well	O
&	O
beg	O
my	O
Com̄ps	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
&	O
Thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Letter	O
.	O
Heigth	O
Height	O
