TOKEN	NE
Caserta	B-place
Decr	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
1780	O
I	O
have	O
fretted	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Silence	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
difficulty	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
important	O
question	O
in	O
your	O
last	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
principal	O
cause	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
times	O
,	O
&	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
as	O
many	O
,	O
&	O
perhaps	O
might	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
Your	O
own	O
good	O
Sense	O
will	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
have	O
directed	O
you	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
any	O
advice	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
I	O
could	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
give	O
you	O
--	O
We	O
know	O
your	O
heart	O
&	O
are	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
sure	O
that	O
gratefull	O
Monitor	O
will	O
never	O
suffer	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
which	O
can	O
be	O
displeasing	O
to	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
you	O
owe	O
(	O
not	O
only	O
)	O
so	O
much	O
Duty	O
(	O
but	O
)	O
love	O
&	O
Affection	O
for	O
Her	O
great	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
however	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
satisfied	O
without	O
hearing	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
too	O
near	O
my	O
heart	O
for	O
me	O
willingly	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
ignorance	O
of	O
what	O
concerns	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
my	O
request	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
constant	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
ones	O
except	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
anxiety	O
you	O
have	O
experienced	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
think	O
is	O
now	O
well	O
over	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
spent	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
months	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Shooting	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
likely	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
the	O
greater	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
.	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
diversion	O
are	O
practising	O
with	O
great	O
aſsiduity	O
a	O
Pantomime	O
Ballet	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
singing	O
.	O
The	O
Subject	O
is	O
the	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Paris	O
,	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
is	O
to	O
represent	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
&	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
Venus	O
,	O
The	O
French	O
Ambaſsador	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Apollo	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
Alas	O
!	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
setting	O
Sun	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
leſs	O
than	O
Sixty	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
,	O
The	O
Ruſsian	O
Minister	O
is	O
Mercury	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
characters	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
filld	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Bedchamber	O
&	O
Cameristes	O
,	O
the	O
Vienna	O
Minister	O
&	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
not	O
think	O
themselves	O
of	O
an	O
age	O
to	O
commence	O
Commedians	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
are	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
ballet	O
,	O
the	O
magnificence	O
I	O
hear	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
great	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
further	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
just	O
lost	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
cousin	O
Beckford	B-pers
who	O
is	O
sett	O
out	O
for	O
Venice	B-place
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
some	O
weeks	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
sorry	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
very	O
superior	O
parts	O
&	O
talents	O
,	O
his	O
extensive	O
knowledge	O
at	O
so	O
early	O
an	O
age	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
perpetual	O
Wit	O
&	O
good	O
humour	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
continual	O
amusement	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
given	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
Affection	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
this	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Ephingham	I-pers
whose	O
nephew	O
he	O
is	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
doing	O
him	O
justice	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
doing	O
so	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
double	O
pleasure	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
Ly	B-pers
Ephingham	I-pers
(	O
who	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
love	O
)	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
this	O
minute	O
had	O
a	O
flying	O
report	O
that	O
D'Estaing	B-pers
s	O
Fleet	O
was	O
dispersed	O
&	O
destroy	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Storm	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
may	O
prove	O
true	O
(	O
God	O
forgive	O
me	O
)	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
have	O
a	O
glorious	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
true	O
a	O
Briton	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
trust	O
we	O
never	O
shall	O
have	O
any	O
other	O
;	O
--	O
when	O
that	O
happens	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
must	O
beg	O
the	O
Kings	O
leave	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
to	O
Settle	O
our	O
private	O
Affairs	O
in	O
Wales	B-place
wch	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
are	O
going	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
our	O
Agent	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
&	O
several	O
farms	O
fallen	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
encroachments	O
made	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
lose	O
considerably	O
,	O
&	O
while	O
we	O
have	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
at	O
present	O
)	O
a	O
debt	O
of	O
Six	O
thousand	O
Pds	O
.	O
for	O
which	O
we	O
are	O
paying	O
five	O
per	O
cent	O
these	O
neglects	O
make	O
us	O
live	O
under	O
great	O
anxiety	O
--	O
if	O
my	O
health	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Climate	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
revisit	O
Dear	O
England	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
dread	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
suffer	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
--	O
however	O
my	O
desire	O
is	O
so	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
courage	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
interrupted	O
at	O
this	O
instant	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
in	O
hystericks	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
Palace	O
in	O
confusion	O
--	O
her	O
Death	O
was	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
cold	O
upon	O
her	O
breast	O
which	O
they	O
hoped	O
was	O
already	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
surpris	O
'd	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
difficulty	O
of	O
breathing	O
from	O
her	O
enormous	O
fat	O
(	O
&	O
beside	O
had	O
immense	O
swelld	O
legs	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
lasted	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
finish	O
My	O
letter	O
with	O
so	O
melancholy	O
a	O
Subject	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
seal	O
my	O
letter	O
it	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
without	O
begging	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
proper	O
oppertunity	O
to	O
Offer	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
and	O
My	O
Duty	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
in	O
the	O
most	O
respectfull	O
manner	O
--	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
ever	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
Yr	O
Most	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
desires	O
his	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
