TOKEN	NE
Febry	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1786	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Dear	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
has	O
had	O
an	O
answer	O
from	O
Doctor	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
Show	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
--	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
certainly	O
should	O
have	O
paid	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
if	O
I	O
really	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
nearly	O
hurried	O
into	O
a	O
second	O
illneſs	O
by	O
having	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
also	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
excuse	O
for	O
not	O
calling	O
on	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
must	O
aſsure	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
amiſs	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
letter	O
..	O
if	O
she	O
meant	O
that	O
paſsage	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Life	O
,	O
it	O
most	O
certainly	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
that	O
paſsage	O
for	O
the	O
plain	O
&	O
clear	O
fact	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
thinking	O
attentively	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
I	O
easily	O
saw	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
absolutely	O
no	O
materials	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
,	O
coming	O
,	O
especially	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
late	O
in	O
Life	O
into	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
all	O
knowing	O
the	O
busy	O
scenes	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
engaged	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
in	O
truth	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
the	O
a	O
Life	O
having	O
no	O
facts	O
to	O
build	O
upon	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
publication	O
of	O
the	O
peices	O
we	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
my	O
op	O
p	O
inion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
think	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
improper	O
to	O
publish	O
the	O
Memoires	O
though	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
curious	O
.	O
As	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
himself	O
mention	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
GloverCadell	I-pers
Cadell	O
for	O
as	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
imagine	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
right	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
am	O
griev	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
greatly	O
fear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
will	O
be	O
disappointed	O
in	O
what	O
the	O
booksellers	O
will	O
offer	O
for	O
the	O
Copy	O
.	O
For	O
Alaſs	O
the	O
real	O
&	O
intrinsic	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Peices	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
consider	O
'd	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
sell	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
If	O
the	O
second	O
part	O
of	O
Jason	O
should	O
be	O
acted	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
advantageous	O
.	O
Now	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
wrote	O
you	O
will	O
now	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cadell	I-pers
what	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Athenaid	O
he	O
enquired	O
the	O
length	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
thirty	O
Books	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
for	O
its	O
selling	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
curtail	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
undertake	O
to	O
publish	O
it	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
share	O
&	O
share	O
alike	O
in	O
the	O
profits	O
&	O
loſses	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
alter	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
print	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
fact	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
expence	O
,	O
anxiety	O
&	O
trouble	O
of	O
publishing	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
the	O
account	O
between	O
me	O
&	O
the	O
printer	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
settled	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
what	O
Dr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
says	O
about	O
Jason	O
,	O
Dr.	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Provost	O
of	O
Eton	O
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
think	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
not	O
to	O
publish	O
the	O
trajedies	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
print	O
the	O
Athenaid	O
alone	O
&	O
see	O
how	O
that	O
will	O
take	O
with	O
the	O
public	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
takes	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
publish	O
all	O
the	O
works	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
wonder	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
anxious	O
with	O
all	O
this	O
upon	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
here	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
your	O
thoughts	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
above	O
written	O
subject	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
perplex	O
'd	O
&	O
bewilder	O
'd	O
,	O
one	O
thing	O
I	O
am	O
resolv	O
'd	O
upon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
triffle	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
will	O
be	O
doing	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
s	O
memory	O
an	O
injury	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
Doctor	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
's	O
writing	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
preface	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
making	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
poem	O
&	O
saying	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Author	O
lived	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
shorten	O
'd	O
&	O
much	O
corrected	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
unwill	O
i	O
ng	O
for	O
the	O
public	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
poem	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
&	O
therefore	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
publish	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
present	O
incorrect	O
style	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
advice	O
,	O
knowing	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
with	O
sincerity	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
..	I-pers
W	I-pers
myself	O
,	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
shall	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
take	O
it	O
alternately	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
,	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
night	O
&	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
St	O
..	O
--	O
On	O
Friday	O
M	O
r	B-pers
..	I-pers
D——	I-pers
dines	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
cold	O
&	O
cough	O
she	O
is	O
grown	O
thinner	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
charming	O
Brother	O
never	O
comes	O
near	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
£950	O
a	O
year	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
keep	O
house	O
,	O
is	O
only	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
constantly	O
dines	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
yet	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
carriage	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
on	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
enquiries	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
dreadful	O
thing	O
to	O
have	O
bad	O
Children	O
,	O
Alas	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
experie	O
nced	O
it	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Amiable	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
will	O
be	O
happy	O
in	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
by	O
his	O
tender	O
behavior	O
&	O
aſsidous	O
care	O
to	O
please	O
her	O
,	O
tries	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
some	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
she	O
has	O
sustain	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
child	O
can	O
not	O
behave	O
too	O
grateful	O
,	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
parent	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
My	O
dearest	O
mother	O
behaves	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
my	O
board	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
exactly	O
as	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
when	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
living	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
does	O
nothing	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
we	O
grow	O
more	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
perfectly	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
charming	O
society	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
husband	O
has	O
improv	O
'd	O
her	O
spirits	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
in	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
never	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
talking	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
receives	O
your	O
letter	O
's	O
they	O
are	O
saluted	O
every	O
time	O
he	O
reads	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
all	O
men	O
were	O
like	O
your	O
Dickenson	B-pers
&	O
all	O
women	O
like	O
yourself	O
what	O
a	O
paradise	O
should	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
afraid	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
too	O
happy	O
for	O
this	O
mortal	O
life	O
.	O
God	O
preserve	O
you	O
long	O
for	O
each	O
other	O
is	O
the	O
ardent	O
wish	O
&	O
your	O
ever	O
oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
affection	O
ate	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
pray	O
present	O
our	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
M	O
Master	O
