TOKEN	NE
25	O
Feby-	O
1786	O
--	O
I	O
mounted	O
my	O
horse	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
and	O
called	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
at	O
Kensington	B-place
--	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
could	O
be	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
/	O
Schoolboy	O
like/	O
--	O
very	O
dirty	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
at	O
his	O
Age	O
is	O
very	O
desireable	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
--	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
and	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
there	O
--	O
Thomas	B-pers
has	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
painted	O
Glaſs	O
and	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
library	O
30	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
green	O
house	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
Rooms	O
over	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Accommodation	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
his	O
worthy	O
Tutor	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
many	O
very	O
pretty	O
speeches	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
oclock	O
I	O
galloped	O
home	O
,	O
dreſsed	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
latter	O
from	O
yr-	O
description	O
--	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
vouchsafe	O
to	O
honor	O
with	O
one	O
word	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
see	O
her	O
Eyes	O
a	O
little	O
inclined	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
very	O
frequently	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
began	O
to	O
be	O
impatient	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
the	O
pet	O
as	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
dinner	O
had	O
been	O
ready	O
half	O
and	O
hour	O
&	O
my	O
good	O
Lord	O
s	O
appetite	O
was	O
very	O
keen	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
his	O
Solicitude	O
on	O
that	O
Acct	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
same	O
Inclinations	O
--	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
my	O
Gallop	O
--	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
Lady	O
made	O
her	O
appearance	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
curious	O
one	O
it	O
was	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
dreſsed	O
in	O
une	O
Chemise	O
de	O
la	O
Reine	O
--	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
unbecoming	O
dreſs	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
we	O
were	O
amazed	O
by	O
looking	O
at	O
40	O
miniatures	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
L——n	I-pers
s	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
done	O
330	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
L——	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
left	O
us	O
early	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
went	O
also	O
to	O
a	O
whist	O
party	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Ball	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
dear	O
sweet	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
wrote	O
her	O
name	O
&	O
sent	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
every	O
thing	O
one	O
cd	O
.	O
wish	O
in	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
her	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
her	O
teeth	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
pretty	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
Angelick	O
in	O
her	O
Manner	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
all	O
gentleneſs	O
&	O
Innocence	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
home	O
--	O
26	O
--	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
our	O
Sister	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
called	O
on	O
Julia	B-pers
&	O
good	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
--	O
his	O
Room	O
smoked	O
&	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
s	O
Room	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
looking	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
Eyes	O
looked	O
different	O
ways	O
&	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
ridiculous	O
appearance	O
we	O
heard	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
G——	O
s	O
stories	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
--	O
Gl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
his	O
plan	O
of	O
in	O
Collecting	O
&	O
his	O
models	O
in	O
wood	O
of	O
Angles	O
octagons	O
&	O
c	O
wh	O
.	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
ground	O
work	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
true	O
judgement	O
of	O
Minerals	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
entertained	O
as	O
he	O
understands	O
the	O
Subject	O
so	O
perfectly	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
thrō	O
his	O
Chrystals	O
and	O
then	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
two	O
Ladies	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
a	O
Collector	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
ores	O
--	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
I	O
saw	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
otherwise	O
sd	O
.	O
have	O
done	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
--	O
his	O
Cabinets	O
are	O
curious	O
&	O
well	O
contrived	O
--	O
He	O
laughs	O
at	O
the	O
Portland	O
Collection	O
,	O
&	O
says	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
Specimen	O
that	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
purchase	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
tear	O
myself	O
away	O
as	O
Dear	O
Sir	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
dines	O
early	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
&	O
sd	O
.	O
take	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
shewing	O
me	O
his	O
Collection	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
5	O
Minutes	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
--	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
--	O
but	O
is	O
recovered	O
--	O
She	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
desired	O
their	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
O——	I-pers
shook	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
--	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
calling	O
upon	O
her	O
&	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
journey	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
O——	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
to	O
London	B-place
--	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smet	I-pers
very	O
well	O
--	O
thō	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
tormented	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Company	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
Letter	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
you	O
wrote	O
Smelt	B-pers
s	O
Character	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
it	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
wch	O
.	O
prevented	O
my	O
saying	O
any	O
more	O
on	O
yt-	O
subject	O
--	O
She	O
spoke	O
of	O
the	O
short	O
visit	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
on	O
friday	O
--	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
great	O
Reluctance	O
,	O
&	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
so	O
soon	O
if	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
--	O
She	O
concluded	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
usual	O
discernment	O
prompted	O
me	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
wished	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
private	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
on	O
friday	O
--	O
She	O
went	O
at	O
11	O
and	O
stayed	O
till	O
2	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
drawing	O
Room	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
led	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
apartment	O
--	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
asked	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
her	O
(	O
what	O
she	O
knew	O
before	O
)	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
your	O
friend	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
mentioned	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
your	O
visit	O
--	O
&	O
said	O
“	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
's	O
Father	O
proposed	O
it	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
said	O
“	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
never	O
forgets	O
her	O
freinds	O
and	O
always	O
acts	O
properly	O
”	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
--	O
“	O
I	O
shall	O
stand	O
up	O
for	O
my	O
freind	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
--	O
he	O
makes	O
an	O
excellent	O
Husband	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
him	O
deserving	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
D——	I-pers
”	O
That	O
my	O
Conduct	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
is	O
not	O
only	O
very	O
flattering	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
honor	O
to	O
yr-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
but	O
it	O
adds	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
happineſs	O
he	O
enjoys	O
in	O
being	O
your	O
husband	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Dickenson	B-pers
two	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
dined	O
there	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
Confusion	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Port	I-pers
asked	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandfords	I-pers
if	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
L——	O
from	O
you	O
giving	O
an	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.Port	I-pers
said	O
.	O
Yes	O
--	O
but	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
took	O
an	O
affte-	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
another	O
year	O
before	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
see	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.Port	I-pers
--	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
but	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
and	O
said	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
in	O
the	O
summer	O
to	O
finish	O
the	O
game	O
of	O
Cheſs	O
--	O
27	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
my	O
good	O
friends	O
last	O
night	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
6	O
this	O
morning	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
faithful	O
arms	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Wifes	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
it	O
snowed	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd/	O
be	O
Madneſs	O
to	O
venture	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
--	O
the	O
day	O
continues	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
poſsible	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
delay	O
a	O
moment	O
as	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
and	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
sincerely	O
you	O
are	O
beloved	O
by	O
Your	O
own	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
Dog	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
probable	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
shoot	O
next	O
year	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
become	O
very	O
indifferent	O
abt	O
.	O
it	O
--	O
therefore	O
Mary	B-pers
had	O
better	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
the	O
bell	O
rings	O
--	O
Who	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
mineralogist	O
?	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
?	O
Mr	B-pers
Grenville	I-pers
?	O
