TOKEN	NE
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
sweetest	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
remember	O
her	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
enough	O
in	O
your	O
society	O
to	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
the	O
manner	O
was	O
beyond	O
the	O
expreſsion	O
,	O
Miss	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
showed	O
me	O
your	O
Letter	O
&	O
said	O
&	O
did	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
obliging	O
during	O
my	O
visit	O
,	O
she	O
looks	O
thinner	O
&	O
has	O
not	O
I	O
fear	O
quite	O
regained	O
her	O
strength	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
day	O
preceding	O
before	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
only	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
the	B-pers
K——	I-pers
to	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Airing	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Q——	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Trustee	O
for	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
Maid	O
for	O
£30	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
Annuities	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesy	I-pers
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
this	O
Busineſs	O
&	O
wished	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Papers	O
&	O
informed	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
that	O
I	O
had	O
appointed	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
&	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
add	O
the	O
Dividends	O
to	O
the	O
Stock	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
increased	O
to	O
£36	O
,	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
since	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Frank	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
I	O
believe	O
he	O
goes	O
in	O
June	O
therefore	O
write	O
soon	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
&	O
our	O
Servant	O
shall	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
as	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
obliging	O
attention	O
had	O
he	O
called	O
on	O
us	O
oftener	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
regret	O
his	O
absence	O
from	O
England	B-place
the	O
leſs	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
estimable	O
&	O
distinguished	O
character	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
respect	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
CompteCf	B-pers
.	I-pers
the	I-pers
homophonous	I-pers
verb	I-pers
meaning	I-pers
‘	I-pers
enumerate	I-pers
’	I-pers
,	I-pers
for	I-pers
which	I-pers
the	I-pers
spelling	I-pers
compt	I-pers
was	I-pers
normal	I-pers
at	I-pers
the	I-pers
time	I-pers
.	I-pers
Soderini	I-pers
neither	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Colle	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
engaged	O
with	O
some	O
Ladies	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
leave	O
England	B-place
he	O
believed	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
might	O
remain	O
here	O
so	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
is	O
some	O
entanglement	O
du	O
Coeur	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
conjecture	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
lately	O
from	O
Italy	B-place
my	O
dear	O
old	O
Friend	O
is	O
well	O
he	O
desires	O
his	O
respectful	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
thus	O
,	O
Italians	O
have	O
a	O
respectful	O
phrase	O
which	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
translate	O
Oſsequiare	O
&	O
in	O
this	O
the	O
Chevalier	O
expreſses	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
answer	O
his	O
Letters	O
in	O
such	O
Italian	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
&	O
he	O
desires	O
I	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
perfect	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
He	O
ssays	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
reminded	O
Compte	B-pers
S	I-pers
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tour	O
in	O
Puglia	B-place
.	O
my	O
Letter	O
bears	O
date	O
the	O
14	O
April	O
--	O
Dear	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
breakfasted	O
with	O
us	O
this	O
morning	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
I	O
delivered	O
your	O
meſsage	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
goes	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
but	O
seldom	O
compared	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
wished	O
but	O
considering	O
the	O
melancholy	O
alteration	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
's	O
,	O
pretty	O
often	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
before	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
will	O
I	O
hope	O
meet	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Rothes	I-pers
is	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
friend	O
she	O
interests	O
herself	O
for	O
us	O
&	O
speaks	O
to	O
me	O
quite	O
affectionately	O
--	O
she	O
advises	O
me	O
strongly	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
not	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
she	O
says	O
much	O
better	O
this	O
year	O
which	O
I	O
impute	O
in	O
great	O
measure	O
to	O
Sea	O
Air	O
&	O
bathing	O
at	O
Ramsgate	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
scarcely	O
any	O
bilious	O
Symptoms	O
since	O
&	O
hardly	O
anything	O
of	O
that	O
languor	O
&	O
dejection	O
which	O
always	O
attended	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
Town	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
shows	O
me	O
great	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
attention	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
esteem	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
love	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
also	O
been	O
very	O
attentive	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
much	O
improved	O
&	O
agreeable	O
&	O
sensible	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
grown	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
pity	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
has	O
so	O
much	O
affectation	O
in	O
his	O
manners	O
.	O
Do	O
I	O
write	O
comfortably	O
now	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
answered	O
yours	O
almost	O
verbatim	O
--	O
Poor	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
&	O
well	O
in	O
health	O
I	O
go	O
continually	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
are	O
indeed	O
her	O
true	O
&	O
invaluable	O
friends	O
just	O
such	O
as	O
she	O
deserved	O
to	O
find	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
they	O
do	O
,	O
We	O
see	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
bestowing	O
friends	O
on	O
Us	O
even	O
when	O
friendship	O
itself	O
is	O
over	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
justly	O
may	O
we	O
say	O
,	O
his	O
Mercy	O
is	O
over	O
all	O
his	O
works	O
&	O
justly	O
may	O
we	O
rely	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
says	O
she	O
shall	O
leave	O
London	B-place
without	O
anxiety	O
for	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
you	O
know	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
better	O
--	O
Poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Foote	I-pers
is	O
confined	O
by	O
the	O
Gout	O
I	O
sent	O
this	O
Evening	O
he	O
is	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Taxal	B-place
has	O
a	O
thousand	O
beauties	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
is	O
among	O
its	O
fairest	O
ornaments	O
I	O
regret	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
&	O
Taxal	B-place
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
amiable	O
Partner	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
you	O
say	O
are	O
absent	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
receive	O
derive	O
both	O
health	O
&	O
pleasure	O
from	O
their	O
intended	O
excursion	O
--	O
Tell	O
my	O
Brother	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
I	O
am	O
dull	O
without	O
you	O
.	O
--	O
How	O
agreeable	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
last	O
Summer	O
most	O
affectionately	O
I	O
say	O
Adieu	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
the	O
Needles	O
next	O
time	O
We	O
are	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
:	O
Paul	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
the	O
7000	O
Children	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
then	O
buy	O
them	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
now	O
delay	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
News	O
of	O
the	O
dear	O
Children	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenſons	I-pers
--	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
took	O
advantage	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
cool	O
day	O
yesterday	O
&	O
called	O
on	O
A	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
but	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
apparently	O
recovered	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
attack	O
was	O
of	O
an	O
alarming	O
kind	O
a	O
fit	O
--	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
my	B-pers
Aunt	I-pers
Hardy	I-pers
who	O
is	O
her	O
Physician	O
--	O
.	O
Restrain	O
your	O
wrath	O
my	O
dear	O
Dr.	B-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
if	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
walked	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Lambeth	B-place
to	O
see	O
my	O
good	O
friend	O
Miranda	B-pers
&	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Hanover	B-place
Square	I-place
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
attempted	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
&	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
but	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
how	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
more	O
tired	O
with	O
walking	O
a	O
mile	O
in	O
the	O
extreme	O
hot	O
weather	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
again	O
so	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
scold	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
your	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Heberden	I-pers
I	O
knew	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
she	O
was	O
surprised	O
surprised	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
you	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
again	O
a	O
Mother	O
--	O
she	O
asked	O
kindly	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
advocate	O
for	O
cold	O
bathing	O
for	O
young	O
Children	O
I	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
I	O
met	O
Louisa	B-pers
en	O
paſsant	O
--	O
I	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Consultation	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackſon	I-pers
Fanny	B-pers
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
she	O
has	O
just	O
called	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
will	O
breakfast	O
here	O
on	O
Monday	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
