TOKEN	NE
Accept	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
your	O
obliging	O
letter	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
and	O
I	O
join	O
in	O
begging	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
be	O
aſsured	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
&	O
congratulations	O
on	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
our	O
Daughter	O
The	O
news	O
papers	O
have	O
however	O
been	O
before	O
us	O
in	O
their	O
intelligence	O
Lord	B-pers
Clonmell	I-pers
is	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
and	O
as	O
it	O
his	O
intention	O
to	O
settle	O
in	O
England	B-place
it	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
towards	O
the	O
spring	O
before	O
the	O
marriage	O
takes	O
place	O
we	O
look	O
forward	O
with	O
much	O
comfort	O
to	O
the	O
thought	O
of	O
seeing	O
our	O
Daughter	O
happily	O
settled	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
her	O
health	O
reèstablishd	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
partaking	O
of	O
the	O
amusemen	O
ts	O
in	O
the	O
neighborhood	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
tolerable	O
health	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
my	O
Eldest	O
Daughter	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
unwell	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
--	O
we	O
join	O
in	O
Compts	O
.	O
for	O
your	O
Daughter	O
&	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
very	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
Octr	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
1804	O
--	O
