TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
ye	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
1776	O
.	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
The	O
inexpreſsible	O
entertainment	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
your	O
letters	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
regularly	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
sometimes	O
by	O
Catherina	B-pers
sometimes	O
by	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
raiſ	O
'd	O
in	O
me	O
some	O
emulation	O
,	O
nay	O
an	O
immediate	O
deſire	O
to	O
succeed	O
in	O
the	O
epiſtolary	O
channel	O
of	O
converſing	O
with	O
a	O
diſtant	O
friend	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
feel	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
unjuſtifiable	O
diſlike	O
of	O
writing	O
letters	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
eraſ	O
'd	O
:	O
how	O
comes	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
now	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
,	O
without	O
its	O
uſual	O
reluctance	O
,	O
and	O
conceive	O
in	O
its	O
preſent	O
employment	O
a	O
moſt	O
senſible	O
pleaſure	O
?	O
This	O
,	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
becauſe	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
either	O
from	O
gratitude	O
for	O
the	O
pleaſure	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
frequent	O
commerce	O
with	O
Romiſh	O
temples	O
and	O
convents	O
have	O
learn	O
'd	O
the	O
art	O
of	O
working	O
miracles	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
the	O
latter	O
;	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
sweet	O
saint	O
,	O
surpaſs	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
living	O
inſtance	O
of	O
your	O
power	O
.	O
Laſt	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
your	O
good	O
mother	O
and	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Clarkes	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
peruſal	O
of	O
your	O
laſt	O
letters	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
an	O
air	O
of	O
sovereignty	O
aſk	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
Miranda	B-pers
;	O
I	O
meekly	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
rather	O
go	O
to	O
Spaa	B-place
,	O
and	O
make	O
my	O
excuſes	O
:	O
but	O
what	O
with	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
reflection	O
,	O
while	O
awake	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
dreams	O
,	O
while	O
aſleep	O
,	O
I	O
roſe	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
poſseſs	O
'd	O
with	O
something	O
so	O
like	O
inspiration	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
pauſe	O
of	O
wonder	O
at	O
my	O
sudden	O
change	O
,	O
I	O
seiſ	O
'd	O
my	O
pen	O
with	O
tranſport	O
,	O
&	O
instantly	O
diſcover	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
firſt	O
words	O
dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
contain	O
'd	O
a	O
spel	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
weaken	O
'd	O
by	O
diſtance	O
,	O
or	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
be	O
reſiſted	O
by	O
any	O
habitual	O
antipathy	O
to	O
a	O
mode	O
of	O
authorſhip	O
,	O
whoſe	O
excellence	O
is	O
render	O
'd	O
so	O
demonſtrable	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
proceed	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
society	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
sharing	O
in	O
your	O
preſent	O
felicity	O
,	O
and	O
improving	O
with	O
every	O
new	O
diſcovery	O
by	O
the	O
dove	O
sent	O
out	O
from	O
our	O
own	O
ark	O
.	O
Your	O
tour	O
in	O
itſelf	O
is	O
moſt	O
agreeable	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
more	O
so	O
to	O
your	O
senſibility	O
under	O
such	O
a	O
guidance	O
&	O
protection	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
forever	O
worſhip	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
for	O
their	O
parental	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
tender	O
attention	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
.	O
Reſpecting	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
long	O
been	O
appriſ	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
sentiments	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
founded	O
on	O
perſonal	O
knowledge	O
:	O
of	O
her	O
Ladyſhip	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
amiable	O
at	O
sight	O
;	O
but	O
through	O
you	O
I	O
quickly	O
learn	O
'd	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
merit	O
is	O
equal	O
to	O
his	O
:	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
,	O
will	O
content	O
her	O
.	O
Pray	O
kiſs	O
her	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
behalf	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
kiſs	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
pleaſe	O
:	O
whatever	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
you	O
beſtow	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
place	O
to	O
my	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
promiſe	O
to	O
repay	O
you	O
with	O
intereſt	O
upon	O
intereſt	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
probably	O
expect	O
from	O
me	O
some	O
news	O
from	O
America	B-place
.	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
none	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
at	O
Spaa	B-place
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
conſummate	O
doctor	O
on	O
that	O
subject	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
horridly	O
conceited	O
,	O
nor	O
sly	O
,	O
but	O
senſible	O
,	O
very	O
senſible	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
no	O
French	O
petit	O
maitre	O
,	O
nor	O
Engliſh	O
macaroni	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
ſtrange	O
sort	O
of	O
being	O
,	O
who	O
writes	O
knowledge	O
,	O
honour	O
&	O
probity	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
fortune	O
.	O
Pray	O
accoſt	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
moſt	O
reſpectful	O
compliments	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
harſh	O
in	O
my	O
examination	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
commons	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
gratefully	O
admit	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
profuſe	O
attonement	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
thouſand	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
accurate	O
and	O
satiſfactory	O
anſwer	O
to	O
my	O
queſtion	O
in	O
Flemiſh	O
huſbandry	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
unalterable	O
truth	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
Your	O
Moſt	O
Faithful	O
&	O
devoted	O
Servt	O
R	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
with	O
her	O
compliments	O
lets	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
day	O
will	O
exceed	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
return	O
.	O
Esqr	B-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
author	O
of	O
Leonidas	O
Hosiers	O
Ghost	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
1776	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Spa	B-place
15	O
Madamoiſelle	O
Madamoiſelle	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Spaa	B-place
Allemagne	B-place
3	O
Post	O
pd	O
-12	O
d	O
-	O
Poſte	O
reſtant	O
