TOKEN	NE
July	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
these	O
letters	O
of	O
mine	O
remain	O
unanswer	O
'd	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
?	O
!	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
write	O
every	O
post	O
?	O
The	O
letters	O
come	O
in	O
here	O
but	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
when	O
you	O
miſs	O
two	O
posts	O
--	O
think	O
what	O
a	O
long	O
long	O
time	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
anxious	O
&	O
impatient	O
I	O
grow	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
how	O
mortified	O
&	O
disappointed	O
to	O
find	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
just	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
the	O
letters	O
are	O
deliver	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
--	O
not	O
quite	O
happy	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
D	B-pers
--	O
I	O
fear	O
that	O
young	O
Man	O
suffers	O
from	O
much	O
from	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
attachment	O
--	O
the	O
Father	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
a	O
sensible	O
genteel	O
,	O
well	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
letter	O
--	O
very	O
flattering	O
to	O
your	O
friend	O
--	O
it	O
throws	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
dreadful	O
embarrassment	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
wt-	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
wd-	O
.	O
wish	O
to	O
act	O
wth-	O
discretion	O
,	O
yet	O
Honor	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
guide	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
be	O
base	O
enough	O
from	O
prudential	O
motives	O
alone	O
to	O
retract	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
once	O
said	O
--	O
Adieu	O
July	O
20	O
th	O
1780	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
London	B-place
Free	O
Wake	O
