TOKEN	NE
From	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
s	O
Old	O
faithful	O
Servt	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
7	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
Dear	O
madam	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
Concernd	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
miſs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
s	O
Illneſs	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
night	O
I	O
have	O
Sent	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
I	O
Could	O
think	O
of	O
to	O
night	O
which	O
was	O
our	O
Dear	O
angels	O
Cradle	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
I	O
Can	O
get	O
tomorrow	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
a	O
little	O
Bed	O
Compleat	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
alſo	O
Sent	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
Currant	O
Jelly	O
as	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
Service	O
and	O
any	O
thing	O
elſe	O
that	O
this	O
house	O
afford	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
madam	O
your	O
obedient	O
Hum	O
ble	O
Sert	O
E	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
