TOKEN	NE
23	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
|	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
25	O
returnd	O
home	O
|	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Eſsex	B-place
29	O
th	O
.	O
Septr	O
.	O
--	O
returnd	O
Home	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
9	O
--	O
Octbr-	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr-	O
Went	O
to	O
Eſsex	B-place
29	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
.	O
May	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
20	O
went	O
to	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
8	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
returnd	O
home	O
9	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
.	O
10	O
Return	O
'd	O
home	O
28	O
Went	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
7	O
th	O
July	O
Return	O
'd	O
home	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
18	O
Decbr	O
.	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
home	O
when	O
I	O
too	O
was	O
out	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
here	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
prob	O
able	O
he	O
would	O
--	O
Sunday	O
22	O
d	O
June	O
1783	O
/	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Knosely	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
Queens	O
House	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
.	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Prince	O
on	O
horseback	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
ill	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
stop	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	O
Jeweller	O
(	O
Denny	B-pers
)	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
examine	O
ye	O
.	O
Jewels	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schewellenberg	I-pers
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
Room	O
--	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
Jebb	I-pers
,	O
ye	O
Prince	O
,	O
Sr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Elliot	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
K	I-pers
Q	B-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
Mrs.	B-pers
E	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
sent	O
Charles	B-pers
back	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Stratton	O
Street	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s.	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Couch	O
just	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
bad	O
fever	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
at	O
home	O
went	O
to	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
after	O
dinner	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
garden	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
King	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Picture	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ma	O
d	O
g	O
dalen	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
7	O
oClock	O
there	O
Sert	O
.	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
.	O
met	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Bell	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
Spendlove	I-pers
walking	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
&	O
Master	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
whilst	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
the	I-pers
three	I-pers
young	I-pers
people	I-pers
amused	O
themselves	O
wth	O
.	O
looking	O
over	O
Seals	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
9	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
conversd	O
abt	O
.	O
friendship	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
,	I-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
not	O
of	O
ye	O
same	O
opinion	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
been	O
out	O
&	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
After	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
read	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
conversation	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
relative	O
to	O
Mrg	O
.	O
friendship	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
had	O
calld	O
in	O
ye	O
morng	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
was	O
indisposed	O
&	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Monday	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
--	O
My	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
&	O
read	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
ye	O
Book	O
Mr	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
lent	O
me	O
on	O
Charity	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
came	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
and	O
hour	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
:	O
of	O
H	O
.	O
Coach	O
wth	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
visits	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
C	O
.	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Houses	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
visit	O
at	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
(	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
(	O
at	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
ancaster	I-pers
s	O
&	O
for	O
Ldy	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Bertie	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Hill	O
Street	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Bayford	B-place
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
--	O
where	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
drove	O
me	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
after	O
tea	O
we	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
min	O
.	O
to	O
settle	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
disposal	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Jewels	O
--	O
Denny	B-pers
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
1	O
half	O
leſs	O
than	O
Jones	B-pers
--	O
we	O
drove	O
through	O
ye	O
Kings	O
roads	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
went	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
look	O
over	O
prints	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
agate	O
ball	O
to	O
hang	O
to	O
my	O
netting	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
my	O
gate	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
read	O
till	O
their	O
return	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
read	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
upon	O
friendship	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1783	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
to	O
Breakfast	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
below	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
11	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
to	O
See	O
S	O
t	O
Pauls	O
Church	O
--	O
met	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hotham	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
conversation	O
--	O
sent	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Street	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
ye	O
Water	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Strand	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
Hungerford	O
Stairs	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
boat	O
&	O
row	O
'd	O
down	O
ye	O
River	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Pauls	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
whispering	O
Gallery	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
dome	O
calld	O
ye	O
.	O
golden	O
Galery	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
530	O
steps	O
to	O
ye	O
top	O
--	O
ye	O
Church	O
exceeded	O
my	O
ideas	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
grand	O
ure	O
eur	O
&	O
beauty	O
of	O
ye	O
Architectu	O
re	O
&	O
proportions	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
was	O
40	O
years	O
building	O
cost	O
fifteen	O
Hundred	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Wren	I-pers
built	O
it	O
--	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
by	O
Water	O
&	O
landed	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
Stairs	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
uncommonly	O
Hot	O
--	O
an	O
East	O
wind	O
wch	O
..	O
prevented	O
our	O
having	O
so	O
distinct	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Objects	O
from	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
as	O
it	O
blew	O
ye	O
Smoke	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Park	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
remaind	O
on	O
with	O
us	O
ye	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
ye	O
.	O
Morrel	O
's	O
came	O
for	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
go	O
into	O
Kensington	O
Garden	O
--	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
Tea	O
also	O
--	O
they	O
went	O
at	O
7	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
left	O
me	O
abt	O
.	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
of	O
Hanover	O
Street	O
--	O
(	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
)	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
ladies	O
at	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
she	O
expects	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
Every	O
day	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
in	O
Conduit	O
Street	O
No	O
56.	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
they	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
sent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
by	O
Bell	B-pers
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
for	O
not	O
going	O
there	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
nt	O
over	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
..	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
to	O
work	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1783	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
back	O
ye	O
.	O
Jewels	O
Jeffries	B-pers
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
purchase	O
them	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
to	O
Catle	B-pers
Franc	I-pers
's	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
invite	O
us	O
to	O
eat	O
fruit	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
Bell	B-pers
read	O
to	O
us	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
began	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
's	O
Poem	O
Maid	O
of	O
Aragon	O
went	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
wth-	O
Little	O
Kitty	B-pers
whom	O
she	O
left	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
we	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
her	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
(	O
Manor	O
Row	O
Chelsea	B-place
)	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
Shells	O
Curiosities	O
from	O
Otahitie	B-place
--	O
foſsils	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
home	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
was	O
alone	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
soon	O
came	O
in	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
she	O
wrote	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
finish	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Poem	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
past	O
12	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
all	O
day	O
26	O
--	O
June	O
1783	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
Castle	B-pers
Franc	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Pall	O
Mall	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	O
Jewels	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
just	O
bought	O
some	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
purchasing	O
more	O
--	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
home	O
again	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
me	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
--	O
&	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
then	O
took	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
invite	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
ye	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
.	O
we	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
home	O
--	O
went	O
on	O
wth	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
shops	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
North	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
Coach	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
&	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
at	O
4	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
--	O
where	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
--	O
&	O
sup	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
anniversary	O
day	O
of	O
their	O
Marriage	O
at	O
dinner	O
we	O
had	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
afternoon	O
My	O
uncle	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
to	O
Tea	O
--	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
whist	O
table	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Edmond	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
--	O
at	O
supper	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
--	O
2	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
E.	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
--	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1783	O
Friday	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
came	O
&	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
me	O
in	O
y	O
B	O
.	O
upstairs	O
After	O
Breakfast	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
B	B-pers
went	O
out	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
wth	O
me	O
till	O
an	O
hour	O
read	O
Johnsons	O
beautiful	O
poem	O
ye	O
.	O
Vanity	O
of	O
Human	O
Wishes	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
City	O
on	O
busineſs	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
very	O
pleasant	O
agreeable	O
conversation	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
we	O
aſsembled	O
before	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
he	O
came	O
upstairs	O
he	O
read	O
whilst	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
Leonidas	O
--	O
Mason	O
's	O
Poem	O
Isis	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
came	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
U	O
&	O
Cousin	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
left	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
there	O
my	O
U——	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
20	O
Min	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
ye	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Beauclerc	I-pers
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
at	O
Bulstrode	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Autumn	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
to	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
with	O
my	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Dover	O
Street	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
c	O
we	O
supd	O
in	O
ye	O
D	O
Room	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
went	O
over	O
she	O
soon	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
28	O
Jun	O
e	O
1783	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
Breakfasted	O
together	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dr	O
eſs	O
for	O
ye	O
day	O
in	O
my	O
Habit	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
in	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
M	B-pers
&	O
B	B-pers
&	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garricks	I-pers
at	O
Hampton	B-place
we	O
had	O
much	O
pleasant	O
converse	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Satry	O
June	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
in	O
my	O
riding	O
Habit	O
at	O
11	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
my	O
little	O
habitation	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Parlour	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
then	O
went	O
over	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Coach	O
was	O
ready	O
&	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
wth	O
..	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Hampton	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
party	O
there	O
to	O
dinner	O
)	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
2	O
hours	O
&	O
half	O
going	O
&	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
was	O
animated	O
,	O
sensible	O
&	O
agreeable	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
aware	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
ye	O
..	O
Coach	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
she	O
received	O
us	O
with	O
her	O
usual	O
hospitality	O
--	O
(	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
)	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
garden	O
till	O
past	O
3	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
&	O
conversed	O
together	O
chiefly	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
at	O
Table	O
--	O
after	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
we	O
went	O
upstairs	O
&	O
drank	O
Coffee	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
gave	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W—	I-pers
&	O
me	O
high	O
entertainment	O
by	O
showing	O
us	O
Lord	B-pers
Monboddo	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
with	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
stile	O
&	O
proposal	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
forget	O
,	O
we	O
join	O
'd	O
y	O
e	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
tea	O
time	O
in	O
Shakespeares	O
Temple	O
--	O
this	O
Temple	O
is	O
an	O
Octagan	O
--	O
a	O
simple	O
elegant	O
Building	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Statue	O
in	O
a	O
Niche	O
s	O
opposite	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
of	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
--	O
by	O
Roubilliac	B-pers
--	O
there	O
is	O
like	O
wise	O
in	O
this	O
Temple	O
--	O
a	O
high	O
Chair	O
with	O
a	O
foot	O
stool	O
the	O
decorations	O
design	O
'd	O
by	O
Hogarth	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
consist	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
emblems	O
of	O
Tragedy	O
&	O
Comedy	O
--	O
carv	O
'd	O
&	O
going	O
round	O
ye	O
.	O
back	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Chair	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
high	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
dark	O
Oak	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Centre	O
of	O
ye	O
back	O
is	O
a	O
Medallion	O
of	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
s	O
head	O
carv	O
'd	O
by	O
Hogarth	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Oak	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Tree	O
under	O
which	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
shot	O
ye	O
.	O
Deer	O
.	O
we	O
seperated	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
obligingly	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Villa	O
that	O
day	O
Week	O
.	O
&	O
invited	O
the	O
party	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
.	O
upon	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
prolong	O
my	O
Visit	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
accompanied	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
Spent	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Eveg	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
conversed	O
after	O
Supper	O
till	O
12.	O
when	O
she	O
very	O
politely	O
conducted	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
saw	O
Ldy	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
paſs	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
when	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
near	O
Thurston	B-place
upon	I-place
Thames	I-place
Sunday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1783	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
dreſs	O
myself	O
&	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
weather	O
was	O
heavenly	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
together	O
.	O
at	O
9	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell	O
ring	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
after	O
B.	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
ye	O
pleasure	O
ground	O
--	O
&	O
seperated	O
for	O
a	O
hour	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
11	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
Parish	O
Church	O
a	O
neat	O
pretty	O
Church	O
very	O
near	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
decent	O
congregation	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
whos	O
appearance	O
was	O
amiable	O
--	O
an	O
Elderly	O
Man	O
wth	O
.	O
Silver	O
Hair	O
who	O
read	O
prayers	O
devoutly	O
&	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
pious	O
good	O
discourse	O
.	O
the	O
Manner	O
in	O
wch	O
they	O
sung	O
ye	O
.	O
psalms	O
was	O
very	O
pleasing	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
Church	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
grounds	O
.	O
Medallion	O
seat	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
conversing	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
alter	O
her	O
dreſs	O
for	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Water	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Book	O
&	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Garden	O
.	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Terrace	O
up	O
by	O
ye	O
Side	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
River	O
at	O
7.	O
went	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Water	O
&	O
was	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Thames	O
for	O
near	O
two	O
Hours	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
till	O
within	O
12	O
11	O
of	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
up	O
'd	O
&	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Marlborough	I-pers
's	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Conduct	O
--	O
we	O
sup	O
at	O
10.	O
after	O
supper	O
had	O
interesting	O
converse	O
.	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
pays	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Compt	O
.	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
conversation	O
agreeable	O
for	O
she	O
always	O
goes	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
or	O
In	O
by	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Monday	O
.	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
30	O
June	O
1783	O
.	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Garden	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
Book	O
.	O
read	O
some	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
'	O
poem	O
of	O
Judah	O
Restored	O
.	O
saw	O
Robert	B-pers
&	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
we	O
were	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
.	O
together	O
only	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
when	O
ye	O
.	O
Bell	O
rung	O
at	O
9.	O
for	O
B	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
then	O
parted	O
till	O
20	O
Min	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
&	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Phaeton	O
to	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
Palace	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
ye	O
.	O
complaisance	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
h	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
intelligent	O
Man	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
Pictures	O
&	O
c.	O
very	O
far	O
superior	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
generallity	O
of	O
People	O
who	O
shew	O
fine	O
Houses	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Pictures	O
&	O
rooms	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
admired	O
extremely	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
a	O
memorandum	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Maid	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
Hair	O
--	O
a	O
modest	O
pretty	O
Young	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
at	O
20	O
Min	O
before	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
came	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
dine	O
till	O
near	O
4.	O
before	O
dinner	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
entertain	O
'd	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Manner	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
daughter	O
Lady	B-pers
Burlington	I-pers
up	O
ye	O
Number	O
of	O
meals	O
they	O
ate	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
Coffee	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
largest	O
drawing	O
room	O
Lady	B-pers
Hartington	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
ye	O
China	O
Closet	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
adjoining	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
curiosities	O
wch	O
are	O
kept	O
there	O
from	O
Othietie	B-place
&	O
c	O
we	O
drank	O
tea	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
8	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Medallion	O
Seat	O
wch	O
.	O
looks	O
upon	O
ye	O
Thames	O
we	O
there	O
consulted	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
best	O
manner	O
of	O
cutting	O
ye	O
Seat	O
to	O
preserve	O
ye	O
.	O
Medallion	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
left	O
us	O
full	O
of	O
admiration	O
of	O
her	O
manner	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
strolld	O
abt	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
eat	O
her	O
little	O
supper	O
--	O
we	O
spent	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
much	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
&	O
very	O
agreeably	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
Son	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
July	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
7	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
myself	O
&	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
&	O
read	O
.	O
&	O
wrote	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
read	O
ye	O
psalms	O
&	O
Chapters	O
--	O
she	O
reads	O
a	O
Chapter	O
in	O
ye	O
Old	O
&	O
one	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
New	O
Testament	O
but	O
does	O
not	O
read	O
those	O
appointed	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Church	O
--	O
but	O
reads	O
ym	O
..	O
regularly	O
through	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
parted	O
till	O
Breakfast	O
time	O
--	O
Sat	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
10	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
in	O
a	O
Tent	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
&	O
wrote	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
arrange	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
ye	O
China	O
Closet	O
wch	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
opinion	O
abt	O
.	O
placing	O
furniture	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Salloon	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
read	O
till	O
past	O
2	O
--	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Maid	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
dreſs	O
my	O
Hair	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
3	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
Mrs	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
us	O
after	O
dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
letters	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
Lord	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Phaeton	O
to	O
Otelands	O
or	O
Oatlands	O
abt	O
.	O
7	O
Miles	O
from	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
ye	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
s	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
Grotto	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
finest	O
thing	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Kind	O
in	O
England	B-place
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
L	O
10-000	O
--	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
finish	O
'd	O
above	O
4	O
years	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
now	O
attempt	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
took	O
me	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
Garden	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
--	O
after	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
9	O
we	O
had	O
fruit	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
eat	O
her	O
Supper	O
.	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
retired	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Organ	O
&	O
harpsicord	O
to	O
me	O
till	O
10	O
oClock	O
.	O
after	O
Supper	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11.	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
new	O
Work	O
of	O
ye	O
Belles	O
Lettres	O
.	O
Blair	B-pers
netted	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
July	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1783	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
&	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
garden	O
with	O
my	O
book	O
Hugh	B-pers
Blair	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
seat	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Psalms	O
&	O
&	O
Chapters	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Head	O
ach	O
.	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Medallion	O
Seat	O
to	O
see	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Table	O
&	O
c	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
B	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
Painter	O
to	O
consult	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Painting	O
ye	O
Table	O
,	O
I	O
walkd	O
down	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
to	O
match	O
ye	O
.	O
Color	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
aſsist	O
at	O
her	O
leſson	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Celestial	O
Globe	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
instructed	O
her	O
.	O
it	O
lasted	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
abt	O
1	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
&	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
head	O
wd	O
not	O
allow	O
of	O
her	O
writing	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
her	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
I	O
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
we	O
were	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
stile	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
her	O
Maid	O
came	O
&	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
read	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Salloon	O
fed	O
ye	O
Pidgeons	O
&	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
after	O
dinner	O
Blair	B-pers
was	O
better	O
(	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
¼	O
before	O
3	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
attention	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
hurried	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
c	O
)	O
we	O
had	O
Coffee	O
&	O
sat	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
Sal	O
l	O
oon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
wrote	O
to	O
invite	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
¼	O
before	O
6.	O
we	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
ye	O
River	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Ferry	O
boat	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
Ser	O
t	O
.	O
attended	O
me	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Ferry	O
Boat	O
is	O
row	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
has	O
no	O
other	O
mark	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sex	O
but	O
wearing	O
a	O
Petycoat	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
Mans	O
Hat	O
--	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Jacket	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
follow	O
'd	O
this	O
emploment	O
for	O
her	O
livelihood	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
9	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
40	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
most	O
truly	O
masculine	O
figure	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
had	O
an	O
agreeable	O
ride	O
to	O
Town	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Dr	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
her	O
Conduct	O
Character	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Garden	O
Burchels	O
at	O
fulham	B-place
he	O
said	O
ye	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
poor	O
for	O
15	O
Yrs	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
consulted	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
disposal	O
of	O
my	O
Jewels	O
.	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
(	O
my	O
Old	O
Sert	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
went	O
with	O
me	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
2	O
of	O
her	O
Sons	O
&	O
another	O
Lady	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
took	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
afft	O
.	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
before	O
I	O
should	O
again	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
invited	O
,	O
&	O
kindly	O
Preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
a	O
Visit	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Autumn	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Door	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
Park	O
as	O
ye	O
lock	O
of	O
ye	O
gate	O
had	O
been	O
spoilt	O
by	O
some	O
one	O
putting	O
a	O
wrong	O
Key	O
in	O
ye	O
lock	O
.	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Young	O
Woman	O
at	O
ye	O
lodge	O
a	O
pretty	O
&	O
even	O
elegant	O
girl	O
.	O
her	O
mother	O
Nursed	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
.	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
ye	O
Lodge	O
civilly	O
open	O
'd	O
another	O
door	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
for	O
wh	O
all	O
ye	O
people	O
who	O
preſs	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
were	O
indebted	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Black	O
politely	O
handed	O
me	O
up	O
ye	O
step	O
&	O
made	O
way	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
get	O
out	O
first	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
came	O
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
they	O
all	O
staid	O
supper	O
except	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
who	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Our	O
friends	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
o'clock	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
London	B-place
July	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1783	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
in	O
ye	O
drawing	O
room	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8.	O
we	O
related	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
what	O
has	O
paſs	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
during	O
our	O
separation	O
(	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
seldom	O
comes	O
down	O
before	O
we	O
have	O
done	O
B	O
.	O
)	O
at	O
10	O
Maria	B-pers
went	O
up	O
to	O
dreſs	O
(	O
I	O
wrote	O
till	O
past	O
11.	O
at	O
12	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
went	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
to	O
hear	O
Maria	B-pers
play	O
&	O
sing	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
ask	O
My	O
Uncle	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
call	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
was	O
very	O
hot	O
&	O
I	O
dreaded	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
Walk	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
neither	O
see	O
him	O
or	O
be	O
set	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
she	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
airing	O
--	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Porter	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
to	O
rest	O
myself	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
civil	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
meſsage	O
for	O
my	O
Aunt	O
.	O
in	O
returning	O
home	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
people	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Lodgings	O
Conduit	O
Street	O
No	O
.	O
56	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
wa	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
where	O
just	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Yorkshire	B-place
--	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
Clerk	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
mention	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
Letter	O
.	O
Call	O
'd	O
at	O
Faulders	O
ye	O
Bookseller	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
&	O
settled	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Reviews	O
&	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
as	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
lately	O
dead	O
&	O
I	O
only	O
meant	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
s	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
only	O
left	O
a	O
meſsage	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Town	B-place
&	O
c	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
2	O
--	O
wrote	O
&	O
settled	O
my	O
accounts	O
--	O
My	O
Aunt	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
came	O
¼	O
before	O
3	O
.	O
her	O
Porter	O
having	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
visit	O
she	O
politely	O
came	O
immediately	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
her	O
return	O
from	O
airing	O
.	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
home	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
w	O
h	O
ere	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
son	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
on	O
Sunday	O
if	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glovers	I-pers
who	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
was	O
better	O
or	O
if	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
an	O
odd	O
circumstance	O
of	O
Letters	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
through	O
ye	O
.	O
careleſsneſs	O
of	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
--	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
2	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
3	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
3	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
meet	O
some	O
people	O
upon	O
busineſs	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
oClock	O
.	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Epigram	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
he	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
an	O
engagement	O
&	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
6	O
oClock	O
C.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	I-pers
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
paid	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
leave	O
London	B-place
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
ride	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
communicated	O
several	O
interesting	O
circumstances	O
relative	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
generosity	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
many	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
feel	O
myself	O
at	O
Liberty	O
to	O
put	O
down	O
upon	O
paper	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	O
Wilmots	O
--	O
their	O
conduct	O
towards	O
their	O
Daughter	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
..	O
when	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
day	O
packing	O
up	O
furniture	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
resign	O
'd	O
the	O
appartments	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
ye	O
Castle	O
for	O
15	O
Years	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Burlington	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
entreaty	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
seem	O
'd	O
delighted	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
Bow	O
window	O
Room	O
till	O
10	O
supper	O
time	O
.	O
she	O
read	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Character	O
she	O
had	O
written	O
of	O
ye	O
late	O
Provost	O
&	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
after	O
Supper	O
we	O
conversd	O
much	O
abt	O
..	O
ye-	O
Royal	O
family	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
retire	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
July	O
4	O
th	O
-	O
1783	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
found	O
Lady	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Bow	O
Window	O
Room	O
(	O
or	O
Salloon	O
)	O
where	O
we	O
always	O
breakfast	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
reading	O
her	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
arrive	O
at	O
this	O
hour	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
one	O
from	O
Derby	B-pers
with	O
flattering	O
complements	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
painted	O
ye	O
.	O
Table	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
directions	O
in	O
ye	O
Medallion	O
Seat	O
.	O
then	O
joind	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
who	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
us	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Green	O
bench	O
she	O
read	O
ye	O
Psalms	O
&	O
Chapters	O
.	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
wrote	O
&	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepy	I-pers
's	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
had	O
ye	O
complaisance	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
another	O
writing	O
box	O
wth	O
Paper	O
&	O
a	O
--	O
little	O
blank	O
leaf	O
book	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
wth-	O
her	O
to	O
aſsist	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Globe	O
lecture	O
--	O
at	O
wch	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
Astronomy	O
I	O
made	O
I	O
fear	O
a	O
contempt	O
a	O
i	O
ble	O
figure	O
.	O
at	O
¼	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
Maid	O
came	O
to	O
dreſs	O
my	O
Hair	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
&	O
do	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
Problems	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
clearly	O
understood	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
desired	O
her	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
&	O
we	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
Library	O
till	O
3	O
oClock	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
&	O
calld	O
us	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
after	O
Dinner	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
Haydens	O
leſsons	O
on	O
ye	O
Harpsicord	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
bow	O
window	O
Room	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
work	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
began	O
a	O
Box	O
for	O
ye	O
Ivory	O
Brush	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
ye	O
China	O
Closet	O
--	O
when	O
Miſs	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
her	O
busineſs	O
she	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
&	O
read	O
some	O
articles	O
in	O
ye	O
Papers	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
boat	O
&	O
was	O
row	O
'd	O
by	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
Servts-	O
we	O
went	O
landed	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Meadow	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
she	O
has	O
above	O
42	O
acres	O
of	O
Land	O
ye	O
.	O
Pleasure	O
Ground	O
stand	O
is	O
16	O
for	O
wch	O
.	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
Offices	O
furniture	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
gave	O
5,000	O
)	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
very	O
fine	O
&	O
we	O
sat	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Hay	O
Cocks	O
.	O
&	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
ye	O
ourselves	O
prodigeously	O
Mrs	B-pers
W	I-pers
read	O
some	O
Verses	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
.	O
a	O
Simile	O
comparing	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Moon	O
.	O
we	O
r	O
repeated	O
some	O
Verses	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Homer	B-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
our	O
boat	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
getting	O
home	O
again	O
--	O
we	O
strold	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
Garden	O
till	O
near	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
repeated	O
Milton	B-pers
s	O
Elegy	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
progreſs	O
ye	O
.	O
people	O
had	O
made	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Hay	O
Rick	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
Pope	B-pers
play	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
Handles	O
Musick	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Organ	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Supper	O
Room	O
after	O
Supper	O
Gray	B-pers
work	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
&	O
read	O
some	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Criticisms	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
different	O
Reviews	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Month	O
--	O
particularly	O
that	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
last	O
new	O
Work	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
till	O
12	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
retired	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
our	O
Conversation	O
after	O
Supper	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Blair	B-pers
&	O
c	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
July	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1783	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
till	O
near	O
8	O
oClock	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Garden	O
&	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
green	O
bench	O
wth	O
.	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Packet	O
of	O
letters	O
wch	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
with	O
hers	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
them	O
.	O
my	O
letters	O
were	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
9	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
as	O
usual	O
read	O
ye	O
.	O
Psalms	O
&	O
Chapters	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
till	O
ye	O
Bell	O
rang	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
our	O
Conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
ye	O
family	O
of	O
ye	O
Gunning	O
's	O
--	O
ye	O
Royal	O
family	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
had	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
maid	O
to	O
dreſs	O
my	O
Hair	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
came	O
whilst	O
my	O
Hair	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
Ears	O
&	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
opinion	O
abt	O
.	O
chusing	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
quickly	O
to	O
write	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
summoned	O
to	O
accompany	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
to	O
Twickenham	B-place
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
oClock	O
--	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
in	O
abt	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
5	O
miles	O
from	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
receive	O
us	O
--	O
reproach	O
'd	O
us	O
for	O
being	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
beyond	O
our	O
time	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Son	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
famous	O
Burke	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
--	O
Pictures	O
--	O
Busts	O
--	O
Drawings	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burke	I-pers
not	O
to	O
forget	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
all	O
Gothic	O
--	O
every	O
Window	O
decorated	O
wth	O
.	O
Painted	O
Glaſs	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
Rooms	O
built	O
on	O
purpose	O
for	O
Drawing	O
's	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
his	O
Play	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mysterious	O
Mother	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
make	O
memorandums	O
of	O
ye	O
things	O
I	O
saw	O
from	O
ye	O
great	O
Variety	O
besides	O
too	O
we	O
could	O
only	O
take	O
a	O
trasient	O
View	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
many	O
Cabinets	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
rare	O
&	O
curious	O
things	O
--	O
some	O
wch	O
.	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
famous	O
People	O
others	O
executed	O
by	O
ye	O
first	O
artists	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Beauclerc	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
D.	I-pers
Beauclerc	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
ye	O
table	O
extremely	O
well	O
serv	O
'd	O
.	O
ye	O
Conversation	O
perfectly	O
pleasant	O
numbers	O
of	O
entertaining	O
anecdotes	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
fine	O
China	O
Closet	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Ground	O
floor	O
ye	O
.	O
Library	O
--	O
other	O
Rooms	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
after	O
tea	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
ye	O
Pictures	O
in	O
ye	O
Galery	O
&	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
adjoining	O
--	O
made	O
mem	O
:	O
of	O
some	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
we	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
who	O
told	O
us	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
I	O
left	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
with	O
regret	O
as	O
my	O
curiosity	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
satisfied	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
told	O
me	O
at	O
parting	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
should	O
frequently	O
visit	O
his	O
Villa	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
regret	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
all	O
yt	O
.	O
pleased	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
came	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
T.	B-place
D	I-place
.	I-place
we	O
came	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
Garden	O
--	O
had	O
tea	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Medallion	O
Seat	O
walk	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
repeated	O
some	O
of	O
Mr-	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
c	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
got	O
ye	O
.	O
Manuscript	O
Collection	O
of	O
Milton	B-pers
Verses	O
--	O
read	O
many	O
clever	O
Poems	O
&	O
Letters	O
--	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Line	O
in	O
Sr	B-pers
Sr.	I-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
--	O
on	O
Dodsley	B-pers
being	O
as	O
slow	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
Sun	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
she	O
read	O
more	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
Anecdotes	O
&	O
c.	O
till	O
12	O
oClock	O
.	O
Young	B-pers
told	O
us	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
purg	O
'd	O
destroy	O
'd	O
those	O
writings	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
indeticate	O
Sunday	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	I-place
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
till	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
found	O
Lord	B-pers
Willmington	I-pers
in	O
Robe	O
de	O
Chambre	O
reading	O
ye	O
.	O
Anecdote	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
whos	O
Picture	O
Mr	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
had	O
shewn	O
us	O
.	O
in	O
ye	O
life	O
of	O
James	O
ye	O
1	O
by	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
a	O
few	O
Mom	O
.	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Seat	O
in	O
ye	O
Garden	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
another	O
week	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
--	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
&	O
sat	O
till	O
10	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
Church	O
time	O
Wilson	B-pers
shew	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
ye	O
House	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
--	O
Kiſs	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
so	O
like	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
politely	O
rectified	O
my	O
miſstake	O
.	O
after	O
Church	O
we	O
walk	O
&	O
sat	O
&	O
conversed	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
gardens	O
till	O
near	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
my	O
own	O
hair	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
an	O
Anthem	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Organ	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
at	O
6	O
by	O
Water	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vanbrugh	I-pers
--	O
got	O
there	O
in	O
40	O
Min	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garricks	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
drank	O
tea	O
in	O
Shakespeares	O
Temple	O
--	O
an	O
Octagon	O
21	O
feet	O
Diameter	O
21	O
feet	O
high	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
telling	O
me	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Hampton	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Flasby	I-pers
.	I-pers
returnd	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
November	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
met	O
wth	O
.	O
some	O
diſstreſs	O
's	O
in	O
returning	O
has	O
it	O
had	O
&	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
rain	O
--	O
we	O
got	O
however	O
into	O
ye	O
boat	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
through	O
Hampton	O
Bridge	O
got	O
into	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Coach	O
--	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
Servant	O
in	O
ye	O
boat	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
to	O
open	O
ye	O
.	O
Gates	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
drawing	O
room	O
--	O
sat	O
then	O
till	O
supper	O
time	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
brought	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
books	O
of	O
Manuscripts	O
--	O
read	O
many	O
things	O
particularly	O
a	O
severe	O
poem	O
of	O
Grays	O
upon	O
ye	O
Late	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
ridiculing	O
his	O
new	O
Made	O
Ruins	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
(	O
at	O
Kingsgate	B-place
)	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
read	O
us	O
after	O
supper	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
--	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
to	O
copy	O
&	O
Keep	O
lively	O
Conversation	O
--	O
did	O
not	O
separate	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
oClock	O
.	O
Monday	O
7	O
th	O
..	O
1783	O
--	O
we	O
Breakfasted	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Sat	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
things	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
to	O
bid	O
me	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Chaise	O
abt	O
.	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
.	O
preſs	O
'd	O
me	O
extremely	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
--	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
settled	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
11	O
of	O
Septr	O
till	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
november	O
--	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Carriage	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
my	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
at	O
home	O
&	O
happy	O
to	O
receive	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
to	O
invite	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
to	O
Supper	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
Sons	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
into	O
Suſsex	B-place
Yesterday	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
had	O
been	O
up	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
operation	O
of	O
h	O
aving	O
his	O
tooth	O
drawn	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
Peachey	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
she	O
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooke	I-pers
dind	O
out	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
alone	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
after	O
dinner	O
of	O
8	O
7	O
sides	O
of	O
ye	O
largest	O
uncut	O
folio	O
Paper	O
--	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
Butler	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
her	O
&	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Silver	O
Inkhorn	O
.	O
&	O
a	O
Fields	O
Bible	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
wth	O
.	O
ym	O
.	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
I	O
sent	O
my	O
excuse	O
having	O
letters	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
sudden	O
Death	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
home	O
at	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
..	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
&	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
plate	O
of	O
fruit	O
Pine	O
apple	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
8th	O
July	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Maria	B-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
--	O
I	O
amused	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
&	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
Books	O
&	O
c	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
we	O
amused	O
ourselves	O
in	O
laying	O
a	O
scheme	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Italy	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
6	O
we	O
came	O
went	O
upstairs	O
&	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
.	O
we	O
stopd	O
at	O
Pitts	O
Box	O
Maker	O
in	O
Mount	O
Street	O
where	O
I	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Box	O
wch	O
ye	O
.	O
Man	O
promised	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Sloane	O
Street	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
where	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
ye	O
Man	O
by	O
Mistake	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
--	O
till	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
wch	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
abt	O
..	O
ten	O
Min	O
.	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
s	O
Villa	O
--	O
met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
upon	O
a	O
Coach	O
Box	O
--	O
stop	O
'd	O
&	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
amusing	O
himself	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
as	O
ye	O
sert	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
sight	O
&	O
merely	O
a	O
Carriage	O
to	O
Break	O
Horses	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
I	O
merely	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
Lucius	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
at	O
Windsor	B-place
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
came	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
ye	O
Children	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
We	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
B	O
House	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
for	O
little	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
Met	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
in	O
Chelsea	B-place
walking	O
wth-	O
2	O
Ladies	O
--	O
just	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
we	O
Stop	O
'd	O
in	O
Vere	O
Street	O
to	O
give	O
orders	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Shoemaker	O
abt	O
.	O
our	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
brought	O
me	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Sr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Letters	O
to	O
give	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
was	O
remarkably	O
Cold	O
for	O
ye	O
Season	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
out	O
--	O
when	O
they	O
in	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
they	O
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
past	O
12	O
read	O
some	O
of	O
Youngs	O
Satires	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
x	O
9	O
th	O
July	O
1783	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
9	O
--	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
sat	O
&	O
wrote	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
till	O
1	O
oClock	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
came	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ranelagh	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
Maria	B-pers
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
wrote	O
letters	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
--	O
dind	O
at	O
home	O
wrote	O
after	O
dinner	O
till	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
s	O
(	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Porter	O
call	O
'd	O
&	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
ye	O
Manuscript	O
Verses	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
)	O
--	O
met	O
at	O
My	O
Uncle	O
s	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
her	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
--	O
her	O
Son	O
ye	O
Clergyman	O
a	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
acted	O
Isabella	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tating	I-pers
brought	O
us	O
home	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
where	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
got	O
there	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
&	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
only	O
ourselves	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
after	O
Supper	O
some	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tating	I-pers
Verses	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
July	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
8	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
sat	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
leſson	O
in	O
Italian	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
&	O
had	O
my	O
Hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
half	O
.	O
talkd	O
of	O
ye	O
Late	O
Maria	B-pers
my	O
great	O
Uncle	O
--	O
his	O
Patent	O
&	O
c	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
wrote	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Orkney	I-pers
&	O
c	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
King	B-pers
William	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
together	O
I	O
read	O
ym	O
.	O
some	O
Manuscript	O
Poetry	O
.	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
to	O
Bell	B-pers
s	O
--	O
met	O
there	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
(	O
who	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
Place	O
at	O
Farnbourough	B-place
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
--	O
2	O
of	O
her	O
Sons	O
The	O
y	O
were	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
Mrs	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s.	O
went	O
in	O
ye	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
where	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
was	O
laying	O
on	O
a	O
Sophy	O
.	O
--	O
Violent	O
Lightning	O
some	O
Thunder	O
&	O
a	O
Shower	O
of	O
Rain	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
from	O
Colmans	O
Theatre	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
prevaild	O
on	O
to	O
stay	O
supper	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jenny	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
P.	I-pers
B	I-pers
&	O
me	O
sup	O
'd	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
I	O
at	O
12.	O
came	O
home	O
wh	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
their	O
R	O
:	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
:	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
.	O
July	O
11	O
Saturday	O
--	O
M	O
r	O
Stan	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
before	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Maria	B-pers
's	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
Painters	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
sorting	O
Papers	O
--	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
franks	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
c	O
ye	B-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
every	O
Requisite	O
question	O
relative	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
Governeſs	O
to	O
Miſs	O
Wakes	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
capable	O
of	O
acting	O
in	O
that	O
capacity	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
French	O
Woman	O
--	O
a	O
Protestant	O
speaks	O
pure	O
French	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
She	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hereford	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
put	O
all	O
my	O
papers	O
to	O
Anglets	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
dinner	O
with	O
Madame	B-pers
Renaud	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Maria	B-pers
gave	O
me	O
ye	O
Character	O
of	O
Poor	O
Bell	B-pers
who	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
y	O
e	O
overturn	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
last	O
Year	O
.	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
Young	O
Woman	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
upstairs	O
wrote	O
my	O
Journal	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Gown	O
--	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
&	O
Maria	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Abthorpe	I-pers
H	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
tea	O
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
my	O
Uncle	O
came	O
also	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
went	O
to	O
Master	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
abt	O
.	O
12	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
came	O
&	O
conversed	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
Saturday	O
12	O
July	O
1783	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
read	O
till	O
near	O
10.	O
then	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
Little	O
Dſs	B-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
after	O
dinner	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
read	O
Katherine	B-pers
jackson	I-pers
Morals	O
till	O
7	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
&	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
gown	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
drank	O
tea	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
--	O
Epicurus	B-pers
came	O
at	O
8	O
for	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
&	O
took	O
little	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
home	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
9	O
--	O
sorting	O
my	O
Belles	O
edition	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Old	O
ser	O
vt	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
after	O
dinner	O
&	O
conversed	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
his	O
Place	O
in	O
ye	O
Customs	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
left	O
me	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
tete	O
a	O
tete	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
we	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Boudoir	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
for	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Ramsgate	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
read	O
her	O
last	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Handcock	I-pers
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
dreſsing	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Min	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Sunday	O
13	O
July	O
1783	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
after	O
8	O
to	O
B	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
nearly	O
finish	O
'd	O
--	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
Book	O
of	O
Anecdotes	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
.	O
was	O
disappointed	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Church	O
as	O
my	O
Uncle	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
lost	O
my	O
the	O
little	O
Canary	O
Bird	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Maria	B-pers
it	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Cage	O
.	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
read	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
came	O
frm	O
.	O
Church	O
she	O
sat	O
wt	O
.	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
came	O
--	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
--	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
s	O
--	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
her	O
&	O
Dr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
went	O
to	O
Dowg	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
W.	I-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
just	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
&	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Visits	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
drove	O
over	O
West	O
:	O
Bridge	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
for	O
her	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
in	O
Queen	O
Square	O
.	O
staid	O
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
.	O
she	O
then	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
for	O
ye	O
whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
wrote	O
till	O
9	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
--	O
met	O
there	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
hardly	O
set	O
down	O
before	O
Mr	B-pers
sent	O
to	O
beg	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
&	O
sup	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
wh	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
.	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
Monday	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1783	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
together	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
after	O
B	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
Maria	B-pers
came	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
gown	O
.	O
sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
for	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
went	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
went	O
away	O
abt	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
came	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
on	O
my	O
Gown	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
as	O
much	O
time	O
dine	O
&	O
c	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
during	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
absence	O
from	O
home	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
3	O
Weeks	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
hill	I-place
to	O
my	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
s.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
back	O
had	O
her	O
hair	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
at	O
2	O
Betty	B-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
her	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
in	O
seeing	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
only	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
in	O
daily	O
expectation	O
of	O
Lucius	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
from	O
Ireland	B-place
she	O
told	O
me	O
Lady	B-pers
D	I-pers
had	O
enquired	O
after	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
last	O
week	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
6	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
P	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
in	O
ye	O
Coach	O
wth	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Kelly	O
's	O
Vapour	O
Bath	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
&	O
c.	O
we	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
at	O
my	O
House	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Eſsex	B-place
&	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Servt	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Coach	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
Old	O
B	O
.	O
Street	O
--	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
going	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
&	O
c	O
:	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
tea	O
I	O
saw	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
sitting	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
bedroom	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
a	O
melancholy	O
object	O
wch	O
aflicted	O
me	O
deeply	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
little	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Phaeton	O
came	O
to	O
Player	O
Street	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Katherine	B-pers
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
they	O
find	O
a	O
Sert	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
all	O
set	O
out	O
together	O
they	O
for	O
Eſsex	B-place
&	O
Lady	B-pers
W——	I-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Queen	O
Sqr	O
.	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
to	O
enquire	O
wt	O
.	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Road	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Hart	O
Street	O
--	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
&	O
explain	O
'd	O
ye	O
Reasons	O
why	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
waited	O
upon	O
Mdm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Renaud	I-pers
--	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
10	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
M.R	B-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
I	O
sup	O
'd	O
there	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Jacksons	I-pers
told	O
me	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
away	O
before	O
5	O
oClock	O
June	O
22	O
d	O
to	O
July	O
14	O
th	O
--	O
a	O
gap	O
On	O
Aug.	O
7	O
th	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Essex	B-place
place	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
.	O
See	O
little	O
red	O
book	O
called	O
No	O
2	O
to	O
Sep	O
22	O
.	O
