TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
29	O
th	O
Novbr	O
1783	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
,	O
as	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
her	O
breast	O
is	O
still	O
very	O
painful	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
nother	O
bleeding	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
two	O
blisters	O
already	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
beleive	O
two	O
bleedings	O
--	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
her	O
worse	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
her	O
on	O
former	O
occasions	O
--	O
and	O
hope	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
alteration	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
momentous	O
busineſs	O
,	O
dreſsing	O
my	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
the	O
minute	O
--	O
therefore	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
half	O
what	O
I	O
wish	O
--	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Cot	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
to	O
receive	O
You	O
--	O
as	O
these	O
Walls	O
are	O
too	O
large	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
cruel	O
fates	O
decree	O
otherwise	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
this	O
grievance	O
will	O
be	O
removed	O
--	O
till	O
when	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
sincerly	O
Yours	O
L	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
past	O
one	O
oclock	O
