TOKEN	NE
My	O
dr	O
Madm	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
few	O
Days	O
that	O
remain	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
England	B-place
I	O
sent	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
last	O
Night	O
&	O
this	O
--	O
but	O
no	O
answer	O
coming	O
I	O
doubt	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
received	O
it	O
but	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
lose	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
Company	O
to	O
a	O
scramble	O
Supper	O
with	O
our	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
friends	O
this	O
Evening	O
--	O
most	O
affectionly	O
y-	O
Hmle	O
Sv	O
E	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
fryday	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
