TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1804	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
It	O
is	O
certainly	O
very	O
abominable	O
in	O
your	O
precious	O
Rib	O
to	O
agitate	O
your	O
Nerves	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
Tantrum	O
's	O
as	O
You	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Medical	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
may	O
punish	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
deserves	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
permit	O
her	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
force	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
promise	O
to	O
desist	O
from	O
such	O
Pranks	O
in	O
future	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
still	O
bear	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
Christian	O
affection	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
hope	O
,	O
the	O
Cheltenham	B-place
Waters	O
may	O
repair	O
the	O
mischief	O
She	O
has	O
done	O
herself	O
by	O
pretending	O
to	O
vomit	O
black	O
bile	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
not	O
known	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
my	O
personal	O
rebukes	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
have	O
tormented	O
You	O
so	O
.	O
Caution	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
avoid	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
bad	O
example	O
,	O
and	O
aſsure	O
her	O
Mother	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
ever	O
ventures	O
to	O
give	O
herself	O
such	O
airs	O
again	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Yours	O
very	O
Sincerely	O
Napier	B-pers
Madam	O
,	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
That	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
written	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
surprise	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
Naughtineſs	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
should	O
presume	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
,	O
without	O
asking	O
my	O
Leave	O
,	O
is	O
quite	O
intolerable	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
therefore	O
my	O
positive	O
commands	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
regain	O
your	O
health	O
with	O
all	O
poſsible	O
expedition	O
,	O
as	O
You	O
value	O
my	O
future	O
good	O
will	O
.	O
You	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
any	O
communication	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
difficult	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
history	O
,	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
commence	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
my	O
eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
this	O
time	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
announced	O
to	O
me	O
his	O
disinclination	O
to	O
becoming	O
a	O
Nabob	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
sure	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
his	O
sentiments	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
violently	O
attached	O
to	O
the	O
Indian	O
Tribe	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
creditably	O
raise	O
himself	O
to	O
independance	O
,	O
and	O
restore	O
the	O
broken	O
fortune	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
desireable	O
circumstance	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
feel	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
acquiesced	O
in	O
his	O
wishes	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
Writership	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
question	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
The	O
Dragoons	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Navy	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
pleased	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Dragoons	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
many	O
objections	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
purchase	O
promotion	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
line	O
,	O
&	O
secondly	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
consider	O
that	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
Military	O
Line	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
mere	O
nest	O
for	O
idleneſs	O
&	O
diſsipation	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
Infantry	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
early	O
had	O
an	O
inclination	O
for	O
the	O
Navy	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
resolved	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Tar	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
last	O
October	O
I	O
shipped	O
him	O
at	O
Leith	B-place
in	O
La	O
Chiffonne	O
Frigate	O
,	O
going	O
on	O
a	O
Cruize	O
to	O
the	B-place
Orkneys	I-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
conducted	O
to	O
Yarmouth	B-place
,	O
and	O
re=shipped	O
there	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Defence	O
of	O
74	O
Guns	O
,	O
Captn-	B-pers
George	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
off	O
the	B-place
Texel	I-place
.	O
The	O
latter	O
ship	O
he	O
reached	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
blockading	O
the	O
Dutch	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Captain	O
sent	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
air	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
remove	O
a	O
periodical	O
headache	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
considered	O
to	O
be	O
agueish	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
no	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
complaint	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
preparing	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	B-place
Texel	I-place
.	O
For	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
tall	O
,	O
lank	O
figure	O
of	O
six	O
feet	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
eighteen	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
compleat	O
his	O
beauty	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
light	O
red	O
curling	O
hair	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Mop	O
.	O
He	O
&	O
my	O
Nephew	O
Sedley	B-pers
are	O
just	O
gone	O
to	O
fish	O
for	O
Pike	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Loch	O
(	O
anglice	O
,	O
Lake	O
)	O
seven	O
miles	O
off	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
exactly	O
know	O
who	O
my	O
Nephew	O
Sedley	B-pers
is	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
Son	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sedley	I-pers
of	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
Bedchamber	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
brother	O
and	O
next	O
heir	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
Young	O
Sedley	B-pers
is	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
only	O
child	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
B.	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
Wife	O
is	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
youngest	O
Sister	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
sufficiently	O
instruct	O
You	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
Pedigree	O
)	O
.	O
Sedley	B-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Young	O
Son	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
lose	O
them	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
like	O
them	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
brilliant	O
Court	O
at	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
last	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
£100	O
more	O
expensive	O
,	O
than	O
last	O
Year	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
Government	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
contemplation	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
Salary	O
,	O
as	O
Commiſsioner	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
£1500	O
,	O
the	O
expence	O
this	O
Year	O
cost	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
£990	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Appointment	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
clear	O
from	O
7	O
to	O
800	O
pr	O
Ann	O
:	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
everything	O
kind	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
My	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
