TOKEN	NE
Colny	B-place
Hatch	I-place
ye	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
July	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
You	O
must	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
Sense	O
of	O
your	O
Friendship	O
&	O
Favour	O
in	O
the	O
Com̄unication	O
You	O
have	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
make	O
me	O
:	O
&	O
certainly	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
thought	O
too	O
highly	O
of	O
the	O
Sincerity	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
form	O
every	O
good	O
Wish	O
towards	O
You	O
.	O
Such	O
an	O
important	O
Occasion	O
calls	O
them	O
All	O
forth	O
,	O
Accept	O
them	O
;	O
&	O
be	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
more	O
hearty	O
for	O
the	O
perfect	O
Succeſs	O
of	O
your	O
approaching	O
Union	O
.	O
Long	O
may	O
You	O
enjoy	O
the	O
Happineſs	O
You	O
deserve	O
!	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
leave	O
You	O
to	O
decide	O
how	O
much	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Extent	O
of	O
my	O
Wish	O
,	O
I	O
appeal	O
;	O
&	O
venture	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
great	O
Truth	O
Dear	O
Miss	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
sincere	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Friend	O
&	O
Servant	O
FBoscawen	B-pers
You	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
our	O
good	O
Friend	O
seems	O
well	O
&	O
chearfull	O
this	O
Morning	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
July	O
--	O
84	O
