TOKEN	NE
Royal	O
hotel	O
Pall	O
Mall	O
Friday	O
13	O
th	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
confined	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
three	O
weeks	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
cold	O
and	O
fever	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
about	O
my	O
Marriage	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
Vain	O
enough	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
after	O
our	O
very	O
long	O
acquaintance	O
you	O
are	O
kind	O
enough	O
as	O
to	O
interest	O
yourself	O
about	O
every	O
One	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
My	O
wedding	O
took	O
place	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
for	O
nothing	O
or	O
else	O
believe	O
me	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
intentions	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
connection	O
between	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
family	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
so	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
made	O
out	O
one	O
day	O
at	O
Swanburne	B-place
if	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
indeed	O
greatly	O
flattered	O
at	O
the	O
chance	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
claim	O
a	O
relationship	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
poſsible	O
I	O
now	O
feel	O
more	O
warmly	O
then	O
ever	O
the	O
friendship	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
had	O
for	O
each	O
individual	O
of	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
Swanburne	B-place
,	O
I	O
gave	O
Justine	B-pers
Strict	O
orders	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
favours	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
so	O
few	O
were	O
sent	O
from	O
London	B-place
that	O
the	O
people	O
present	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
Stock	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
however	O
take	O
the	O
will	O
for	O
the	O
deed	O
and	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
You	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
so	O
little	O
of	O
you	O
for	O
some	O
Year	O
's	O
past	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
forget	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
shewed	O
us	O
when	O
at	O
Linslade	B-place
.	O
Justine	B-pers
joins	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
our	O
Old	O
friend	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
begs	O
me	O
to	O
add	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
Anxious	O
to	O
be	O
introduced	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
Most	O
Proud	O
at	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
related	O
to	O
One	O
who	O
he	O
knows	O
has	O
always	O
proved	O
such	O
a	O
Sincere	O
friend	O
to	O
his	O
little	O
Wife	O
Ever	O
believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
's	O
Very	O
Sincerely	O
Harriet	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
James	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Answered	O
Janry	O
1809	O
