TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
Decr-	O
1809	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
condole	O
with	O
You	O
on	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Your	B-pers
Uncle	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
Event	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
situation	O
he	O
had	O
placed	O
himself	O
in	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
much	O
regretted	O
,	O
further	O
than	O
what	O
must	O
be	O
felt	O
for	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
misconducts	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Children	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fortunate	O
circumstance	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
your	O
Uncle	O
will	O
do	O
something	O
proper	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
poor	O
Danish	O
Woman	O
from	O
being	O
driven	O
to	O
act	O
improperly	O
.	O
My	O
old	O
fashioned	O
Notions	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
conceive	O
the	O
Marriage	O
binding	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
strictly	O
so	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
married	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Country	O
,	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
destitute	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
observe	O
that	O
your	O
Cousin	O
the	O
Viscount	O
's	O
family	O
have	O
put	O
on	O
Mourning	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
their	O
dismals	O
.	O
How	O
thankful	O
ought	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
a	O
merciful	O
Providence	O
!	O
My	O
Son	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
is	O
a	O
Midshipman	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Huſsar	O
Frigate	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
conceive	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
our	O
Suffering	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
falsity	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Report	O
relative	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
ascertained	O
.	O
For	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
hopes	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
now	O
our	O
Minds	O
are	O
set	O
at	O
rest	O
.	O
A	O
friend	O
at	O
Guernsey	B-place
,	O
the	O
moment	O
the	O
Report	O
reached	O
that	O
Island	O
,	O
wrote	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Huſsar	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
at	O
Anchor	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Son	O
was	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
likewise	O
accounts	O
from	O
the	O
Admiral	O
ty	O
which	O
quieted	O
our	O
Apprehensions	O
.	O
My	O
eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
now	O
a	O
Lieutenant	O
in	O
the	O
Navy	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
Us	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
He	O
leaves	O
us	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
having	O
received	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Kent	O
at	O
Portsmouth	B-place
,	O
without	O
delay	O
.	O
He	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
blank	O
in	O
our	O
Society	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
between	O
five	O
&	O
six	O
Years	O
.	O
We	O
may	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
be	O
satisfied	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
amongst	O
us	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
Miſs	O
Children	O
.	O
They	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
their	O
old	O
Parents	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
become	O
old	O
themselves	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
awake	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
sinking	O
into	O
Dotage	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
amiable	O
Clack	O
of	O
my	O
four	O
Virgins	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
usually	O
gabble	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
sleep	O
after	O
Supper	O
.	O
Your	O
Louisa	B-pers
is	O
a	O
quiet	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
inclined	O
to	O
be	O
over	O
Garrulous	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
something	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
considering	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
allow	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
infin	O
ite	O
propriety	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
&	O
improved	O
the	O
Hamilton	O
Breed	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
My	O
Rib	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
kind	O
wish	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Best	O
Complements	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Tell	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
shines	O
bright	O
here	O
today	O
,	O
&	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Snow	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
,	O
the	O
Apples	O
may	O
ripen	O
next	O
Year	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Eighth	O
December	O
1809	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
49	O
,	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
