TOKEN	NE
I	O
take	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
informing	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
deliverd	O
your	O
kind	O
Invitation	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thinks	O
herself	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
with	O
great	O
Pleasure	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
Town	B-place
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Christening	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
altogether	O
certain	O
;	O
she	O
hopes	O
,	O
and	O
requests	O
therefore	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
disappoint	O
any	O
one	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
.	O
--	O
Do	O
you	O
ever	O
now	O
take	O
a	O
Trip	O
to	O
Eastbourne	B-place
?	O
or	O
are	O
you	O
totally	O
engroſs	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
gayer	O
scenes	O
of	O
Windsor	B-place
?	O
Mr	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
read	O
me	O
a	O
Paſsage	O
from	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
this	O
morning	O
:	O
as	O
if	O
by	O
magical	O
Enchantment	O
I	O
was	O
transported	O
to	O
Beachey	B-place
Head	I-place
,	O
the	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
much	O
more	O
delightful	O
Object	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
tire	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
my	O
Reveries	O
;	O
weak	O
minds	O
alone	O
delight	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
however	O
they	O
make	O
me	O
happy	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
permitted	O
sometimes	O
to	O
indulge	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
describe	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
own	O
,	O
is	O
unpardonable	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
left	O
E.Bourne	B-place
the	O
weather	O
no	O
doubt	O
must	O
have	O
cast	O
a	O
Gloom	O
on	O
our	O
minds	O
.	O
Fisher	B-pers
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
arrivd	O
at	O
Herstmonceaux	B-place
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
myself	O
at	O
all	O
disposd	O
to	O
disturb	O
his	O
contemplations	O
;	O
so	O
on	O
we	O
went	O
sad	O
,	O
and	O
silent	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
folk	O
at	O
Battle	B-place
gave	O
us	O
an	O
hearty	O
welcome	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dance	O
on	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
.	O
Such	O
Belles	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
Beaux	O
!	O
Oh	O
Guardian	O
Angels	O
!	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Traveller	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Peppermint	O
water	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
at	O
present	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
well	O
;	O
so	O
very	O
delicate	O
a	O
Constitution	O
requires	O
more	O
care	O
than	O
he	O
gives	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
preachd	O
on	O
that	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
hears	O
me	O
very	O
politely	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
way	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
Patience	O
however	O
is	O
requird	O
in	O
a	O
Work	O
of	O
Reformation	O
:	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
preach	O
again	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
your	O
Powers	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
says	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
t	O
s	O
o	O
great	O
an	O
Improvement	O
as	O
in	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
:	O
That	O
your	O
every	O
wish	O
,	O
and	O
Endeavour	O
may	O
be	O
crownd	O
with	O
an	O
equal	O
succeſs	O
is	O
the	O
ardent	O
Prayer	O
of	O
your	O
sincerely	O
aff	O
.	O
Friend	O
and	O
obl	O
humble	O
Servt	O
John	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
Kew	B-place
Octr	O
.	O
18	O
th	O
My	O
respectful	O
Compts	O
wait	O
on	O
Lady	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
