TOKEN	NE
Welwyn	B-place
,	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1781	O
.	O
This	O
days	O
Post	O
made	O
me	O
extremely	O
happy	O
--	O
It	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
s	O
letter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
want	O
of	O
friendship	O
for	O
not	O
accepting	O
her	O
very	O
generous	O
proposal	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Accounts	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
having	O
upon	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
presented	O
me	O
with	O
A	O
Nephew	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
may	O
now	O
salute	O
me	O
,	O
Uncle	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
You	O
please	O
.	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
proud	O
of	O
my	O
new	O
Dignity	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
more	O
saucy	O
(	O
if	O
poſsible	O
)	O
than	O
ever	O
.	O
Accept	O
of	O
my	O
Gratitude	O
for	O
your	O
good	O
wishes	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
perhaps	O
some	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
enjoy	O
a	O
competent	O
fortune	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
an	O
Affluent	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
however	O
determined	O
to	O
enjoy	O
&	O
be	O
thankful	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
viz	O
.	O
Content	O
--	O
Happy	O
in	O
the	O
esteem	O
&	O
confidence	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
sincere	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
e'en	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
bargain	O
,	O
&	O
comfort	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
re	O
c	O
ollection	O
that	O
All	O
things	O
under	O
the	O
Sun	O
are	O
Vanity	O
&	O
Vexation	O
of	O
Spirit	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
Mr-	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
promise	O
him	O
amusement	O
in	O
this	O
barbarous	O
Village	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
promise	O
him	O
a	O
hearty	O
welcome	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
disposed	O
of	O
my	O
Ensigncy	O
I	O
may	O
perhaps	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
visit	O
Town	B-place
to	O
receive	O
the	O
payment	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
case	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
personal	O
invitation	O
.	O
This	O
intended	O
Trip	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
perhaps	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
continues	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
--	O
wonderful	O
--	O
and	O
looks	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
hope	O
that	O
She	O
will	O
do	O
well	O
.	O
She	O
seems	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
herself	O
having	O
just	O
ordered	O
a	O
new	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
to	O
be	O
built	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
God	O
grant	O
she	O
may	O
live	O
to	O
order	O
another	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
Valuable	O
Life	O
.	O
Her	O
best	O
wishes	O
ever	O
attend	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
write	O
about	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
situation	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hoped	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
see	O
his	O
folly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
his	O
intimacy	O
with	O
his	O
R	O
.	O
Uncle	O
will	O
do	O
him	O
much	O
good	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
As	O
you	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
matters	O
stand	O
between	O
Ld-	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
I	O
have	O
subjoined	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
correspondence	O
which	O
has	O
paſsed	O
--	O
Conscious	O
of	O
having	O
acted	O
with	O
all	O
proper	O
Attention	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
&	O
the	O
whole	O
Set	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
leſs	O
concerned	O
at	O
their	O
behaviour	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
'till	O
They	O
shew	O
Attention	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
Yours	O
very	O
sincerely	O
&	O
affectionately	O
N——	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ld-	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
C——	I-pers
London	B-place
9	O
th	O
.	O
Febry-	O
1781	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Lord	O
,	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
Town	B-place
I	O
recd-	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
enclosing	O
Copies	O
of	O
his	O
letter	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
of	O
your	O
answer	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
your	O
Lop/	O
seems	O
to	O
wish	O
the	O
points	O
in	O
dispute	O
should	O
be	O
settled	O
by	O
yourself	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Sisters	O
have	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
state	O
some	O
facts	O
which	O
you	O
at	O
present	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
unaquainted	O
with	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
&	O
desire	O
to	O
have	O
conversed	O
with	O
You	O
in	O
person	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
my	O
Mother	O
s	O
portion	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
your	O
Lop/	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
taking	O
this	O
method	O
of	O
communicating	O
my	O
Sentiments	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
Your	O
Lop/	O
may	O
recollect	O
that	O
Mr-	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
who	O
had	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
s	O
busineſs	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
1774	O
.	O
The	O
decease	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
in	O
Janry-	O
1775	O
before	O
his	O
papers	O
were	O
recovered	O
from	O
Mr-	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
's	O
heirs	O
threw	O
all	O
my	O
Affairs	O
into	O
the	O
utmost	O
confusion	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
'till	O
a	O
Year	O
after	O
Mr-	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
s	O
death	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Vouchers	O
came	O
into	O
Mr-	B-pers
Buchan	I-pers
s	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
Upon	O
an	O
application	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
your	O
father	O
to	O
settle	O
the	O
Accompts	O
due	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Sisters	O
,	O
he	O
directed	O
that	O
Mr-	B-pers
Buchan	I-pers
should	O
make	O
out	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
my	O
Mother	O
s	O
portion	O
still	O
unpaid	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
&	O
was	O
aſsisted	O
in	O
it	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chas-	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
unneceſsary	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
remind	O
your	O
Lop/	O
that	O
a	O
stop	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
that	O
settlement	O
by	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
your	O
father	O
whose	O
friendship	O
&	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
&	O
myself	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
most	O
gratefully	O
recollect	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
America	B-place
,	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
all	O
Money	O
matters	O
settled	O
with	O
my	O
Sisters	O
,	O
I	O
repeatedly	O
applied	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
to	O
ascertain	O
the	O
Sum	O
due	O
from	O
your	O
Lop/	O
to	O
my	O
Sisters	O
&	O
as	O
often	O
received	O
his	O
promises	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Wearied	O
with	O
numberleſs	O
delays	O
,	O
I	O
one	O
morning	O
waited	O
upon	O
Mr-	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
with	O
my	O
Vouchers	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
'till	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
Accompts	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
adjusted	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
considerable	O
difference	O
appeared	O
between	O
the	O
State	O
given	O
in	O
by	O
Mr-	B-pers
Buchan	I-pers
&	O
that	O
exhibited	O
by	O
Mr-	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
as	O
your	O
Lop/	O
arrival	O
in	O
England	B-place
was	O
daily	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
consent	O
to	O
stop	O
all	O
proceedings	O
'till	O
your	O
return	O
&	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
the	O
Guardians	O
to	O
approve	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
supposition	O
that	O
You	O
would	O
yourself	O
either	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
diligent	O
search	O
amongst	O
your	O
Papers	O
or	O
have	O
impowered	O
some	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
that	O
search	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
now	O
to	O
request	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
directions	O
to	O
your	O
Agents	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
to	O
make	O
such	O
enquiries	O
as	O
will	O
enable	O
them	O
speedily	O
to	O
settle	O
this	O
Busineſs	O
to	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
all	O
Parties	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
your	O
answer	O
at	O
Welwyn	B-place
for	O
which	O
place	O
I	O
shall	O
set	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
Servant	O
returns	O
from	O
delivering	O
this	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ld-	B-pers
C——	I-pers
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
N——	I-pers
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
your	O
letter	O
on	O
my	O
Table	O
at	O
my	O
Return	O
from	O
Portsmouth	B-place
last	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
an	O
early	O
opportunity	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
your	O
Lop/	O
fully	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
it	O
contains	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
seize	O
the	O
first	O
Moment	O
to	O
aſsure	O
your	O
Lop/	O
of	O
the	O
Mortification	O
it	O
gives	O
me	O
that	O
some	O
Public	O
&	O
much	O
Private	O
Busineſs	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
allow	O
me	O
leisure	O
to	O
seek	O
an	O
interview	O
.	O
with	O
you	O
during	O
your	O
stay	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
the	O
more	O
so	O
as	O
that	O
hurry	O
has	O
now	O
ceased	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Honor	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Regard	O
ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Lord	B-pers
N——	I-pers
most	O
faithful	O
and	O
attached	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
.	O
C——	B-pers
Albemarle	O
Street	O
13	O
Febry-	O
1781	O
.	O
Since	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
letter	O
my	O
most	O
faithfull	O
&	O
attached	O
humble	O
Sert-	O
has	O
taken	O
no	O
further	O
Notice	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
N——	B-pers
