TOKEN	NE
Sudbro	B-place
'	I-place
June	O
29	O
th	O
permit	O
me	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
to	O
return	O
you	O
the	O
best	O
thanks	O
of	O
a	O
heart	O
that	O
is	O
most	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
marks	O
of	O
friendship	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
Congratulations	O
you	O
now	O
offer	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
expect	O
happineſs	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
married	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
attach	O
'd	O
and	O
whose	O
heart	O
&	O
Character	O
are	O
perfectly	O
known	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
whose	O
merit	O
and	O
Sincere	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
made	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
except	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
overlook	O
his	O
want	O
of	O
fortune	O
and	O
become	O
not	O
only	O
reconciled	O
to	O
the	O
match	O
but	O
extremely	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
happen	O
to	O
have	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
an	O
idle	O
half	O
hour	O
to	O
throw	O
away	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
it	O
will	O
be	O
received	O
with	O
most	O
Sincere	O
pleasure	O
&	O
gratitude	O
if	O
bestowed	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
