TOKEN	NE
Harleyford	B-place
.	O
Wednesday	O
March	O
29	O
th	O
1780	O
--	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Besides	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
Letter	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
ye	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
unexpected	O
Honour	O
of	O
a	O
Visit	O
from	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
so	O
gracious	O
&	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
they	O
charm	O
'd	O
away	O
all	O
my	O
Complaints	O
,	O
(	O
almost	O
my	O
Deafneſs	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
I	O
felt	O
nothing	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
happy	O
&	O
delighted	O
to	O
ſee	O
them	O
;	O
P.	B-pers
William	I-pers
I	O
think	O
looks	O
charmingly	O
,	O
&	O
much	O
improved	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
acquaint	O
my	O
dear	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
with	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
talk	O
with	O
much	O
tenderneſs	O
&	O
affection	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
patient	O
pretty	O
behaviour	O
during	O
her	O
illneſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
shockt	O
to	O
find	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
severer	O
&	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
hope	O
I	O
mend	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
deafneſs	O
,	O
thō	O
't	O
is	O
but	O
slowly	O
,	O
Yesterday	O
having	O
happen	O
'd	O
fortunately	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
day	O
I	O
have	O
yet	O
had	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
the	O
inceſsant	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
thō	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
deafen	O
me	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
pretty	O
Supper	O
you	O
had	O
had	O
on	O
little	O
Mr	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
,	O
birth-day	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
pleas	O
'd	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
End	O
Room	O
,	O
without	O
which	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
dined	O
here	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
Norfolk	B-place
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
poor	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
wth	O
.	O
great	O
concern	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
spoke	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
much	O
liked	O
&	O
approv	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
places	O
.	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
,	O
&	O
alas	O
how	O
Mr	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
is	O
,	O
&	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
Com̄ps	O
to	O
them	O
when	O
you	O
ſee	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
my	O
dear	O
the	B-pers
Smelts	I-pers
you	O
will	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
you	O
ought	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
dear	O
Children	O
during	O
my	O
Absence	O
,	O
&	O
dare	O
say	O
they	O
will	O
want	O
for	O
no	O
Amusement	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Care	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
procure	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schwellemberg	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
find	O
Madelle	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moula	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chevely	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
.	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
I	O
find	O
was	O
very	O
Serious	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
recovering	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Spring	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
set	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
Invalids	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
detain	O
you	O
longer	O
than	O
to	O
beg	O
my	O
Love	O
&	O
Duty	O
to	O
the	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
the	O
Sincerest	O
Affection	O
Most	O
faithfully	O
Yrs	O
.	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
P.	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
's	O
best	O
Com̄ps	O
attend	O
you	O
.	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
to	O
what	O
amount	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
Loſs	O
is	O
computed	O
To	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Governeſs	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Pſs	O
's	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
