TOKEN	NE
Deal	O
Castle	O
.	O
July	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
The	O
Difference	O
of	O
my	O
Account	O
of	O
dear	O
Little	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
from	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
yesterday	O
is	O
rather	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
Fever	O
is	O
leſs	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
unwillingneſs	O
to	O
walk	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wan	O
,	O
drooping	O
,	O
look	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
has	O
by	O
my	O
desire	O
been	O
writing	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
day	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
expreſsing	O
a	O
wish	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
drawn	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Chaise	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
beginger	O
being	O
so	O
constantly	O
in	O
Arms	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
walk	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
bad	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
in	O
consequence	O
wrote	O
by	O
my	O
desire	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Chaises	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
Deal	B-place
,	O
&	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
could	O
make	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
much	O
longer	O
before	O
we	O
cd	O
.	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
sending	O
it	O
for	O
it	O
from	O
London	B-place
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
safest	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
might	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
&	O
so	O
time	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
in	O
getting	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
free	O
enough	O
of	O
Fever	O
,	O
to	O
begin	O
the	O
Sea	O
bathing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
concern	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
by	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
London	B-place
yesterday	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
Mr	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
has	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
had	O
good	O
Aſsistance	O
at	O
New	B-place
York	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
Practice	O
for	O
Fractures	O
or	O
any	O
Accidents	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
my	O
Account	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
that	O
no	O
ill	O
Consequences	O
were	O
apprehended	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Distreſs	O
of	O
the	O
Asgill	O
family	O
I	O
pity	O
from	O
my	O
Heart	O
&	O
shall	O
think	O
poor	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
happy	O
if	O
as	O
the	O
Papers	O
say	O
is	O
likely	O
he	O
dies	O
without	O
it	O
having	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
every	O
hour	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
the	O
Ganges	O
(	O
Sr	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
s	O
Ship	O
)	O
coming	O
into	O
the	B-place
Downs	I-place
,	O
&	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Week	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
&	O
her	O
family	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Juliana	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
having	O
obliged	O
both	O
her	O
&	O
Me	O
much	O
,	O
by	O
lending	O
her	O
Walmer	O
Castle	O
,	O
Sea	O
bathing	O
being	O
advised	O
her	O
after	O
her	O
same	O
illneſs	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
likely	O
method	O
to	O
restore	O
her	O
Strength	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
as	O
prosperous	O
Accounts	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
Prince	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
humble	O
Duty	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Com̄ps	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
from	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
sincerely	O
Affcte	O
.	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
Charlotte	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
