TOKEN	NE
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
7	O
th	O
.	O
Febry-	O
1780	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
been	O
formed	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
obdurate	O
Composition	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
humanity	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
enquired	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
hanged	O
myself	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Another	O
Weeks	O
continuance	O
at	O
Marlow	B-place
,	O
would	O
probably	O
have	O
had	O
that	O
a	O
e	O
ffect	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
Creature	O
to	O
converse	O
with	O
--	O
No	O
Booksellers	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
--	O
No	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
lounging	O
place	O
to	O
divert	O
my	O
melancholy	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
thank	O
my	O
Stars	O
,	O
these	O
Evils	O
are	O
at	O
length	O
terminated	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
removed	O
Bag	O
&	O
Baggage	O
,	O
Company	O
&	O
all	O
to	O
Hertford	B-place
,	O
from	O
which	O
this	O
place	O
is	O
only	O
five	O
Miles	O
distant	O
.	O
Old	O
Ly-	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
says	O
,	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
Head	O
Quarters	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
command	O
of	O
Her	O
Horses	O
&	O
Carriages	O
.	O
'Till	O
my	O
Officers	O
join	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
kind	O
offer	O
&	O
therefore	O
this	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
Notice	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
near	O
Welwyn	B-place
Herts	B-place
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Your	O
Affec	O
.	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
I	O
see	O
some	O
Irish	O
Bishopricks	O
are	O
given	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
to	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
.	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
saved	O
himself	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Levee	O
--	O
