TOKEN	NE
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
tells	O
me	O
my	O
drst	O
that	O
Lay	B-pers
C	I-pers
has	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
I	O
feel	O
very	O
sensibly	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
too	O
well	O
know	O
what	O
yr-	O
Situation	O
is	O
,	O
keep	O
yr-	O
self	O
up	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
yr-	O
Mama	O
better	O
than	O
you	O
expect	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
convinced	O
,	O
that	O
Providence	O
knows	O
better	O
than	O
we	O
do	O
what	O
is	O
proper	O
for	O
us	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
,	O
try	O
to	O
sleep	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
affly	O
Y	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Satry	O
Night	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
