TOKEN	NE
Novbr	O
.	O
19	O
th	O
-	O
1782	O
windsor	B-place
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
gracious	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
advise	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
this	O
Raw	O
Cold	O
day	O
,	O
will	O
it	O
be	O
very	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dr	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
waiting	O
this	O
Evg	O
.	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
I	O
really	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Days	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
quite	O
bonny	O
,	O
sick	O
or	O
well	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
MCG	B-pers
--	I-pers
pt	O
one	O
--	O
do	O
n't	O
imagine	O
I	O
am	O
worse	O
by	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
&	O
fully	O
intended	O
coming	O
&	O
only	O
am	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
gracious	O
Meſsage	O
