TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
it	O
is	O
literally	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
above	O
two	O
words	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
instant	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
intend	O
writing	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
allowed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
will	O
require	O
--	O
but	O
my	O
Friends	O
here	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
left	O
a	O
moment	O
alone	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
received	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
my	O
return	O
here	O
i.e	O
.	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
--	O
you	O
dated	O
it	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
of	O
August	O
but	O
I	O
gueſsed	O
you	O
meant	O
October	O
--	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
you	O
with	O
some	O
prospect	O
nay	O
certainty	O
of	O
Comfort	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
most	O
happy	O
to	O
receive	O
you	O
both	O
then	O
&	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
&	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
since	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
very	O
happy	O
--	O
enjoyi	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
heavenly	O
weather	O
&	O
the	O
beautiful	O
country	O
&	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
family	O
&	O
my	O
kind	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
shocked	O
&	O
am	O
extremely	O
distreſsed	O
by	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Coll	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
its	O
influence	O
on	O
the	O
happineſs	O
&	O
prospects	O
of	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
lost	O
in	O
him	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
was	O
dear	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
value	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
!	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
am	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
day	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
's	O
Drawingroom	O
&	O
return	O
here	O
on	O
Friday	O
--	O
&	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
29	O
th	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Ly	I-pers
Binning	I-pers
desire	O
their	O
best	O
Compts	O
--	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
adieu	O
adieu	O
--	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
!	O
thank	O
God	O
!	O
most	O
affecly	O
:	O
&	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
C.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Ham	B-place
October	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
1788	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Oct	O
br	O
1788	O
