TOKEN	NE
Friday	O
morn	O
6	O
th	O
July	O
1781	O
Notwithstanding	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
under	O
your	O
displeasure	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
enquiring	O
after	O
your	O
health	O
.	O
And	O
is	O
it	O
poſsible	O
then	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
a	O
slight	O
omiſsion	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
apologizd	O
for	O
,	O
shoud	O
be	O
punish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Forfeiture	O
of	O
yr	O
Friendship	O
?	O
When	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
returnd	O
from	O
W	B-place
.	I-place
he	O
informd	O
me	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
wishd	O
to	O
make	O
many	O
enquiries	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
coud	O
not	O
be	O
answerd	O
--	O
I	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
here	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
also	O
I	O
was	O
disappointed	O
.	O
If	O
therefore	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
longer	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
write	O
to	O
Fisher	B-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
offended	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
yr	O
Health	O
.	O
Ever	O
yrs	O
J.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
