TOKEN	NE
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1802	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
most	O
saucy	O
Letter	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
made	O
my	O
blood	O
boil	O
so	O
violently	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
persuade	O
myself	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
give	O
my	O
Venom	O
vent	O
without	O
delay	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
You	O
presume	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
insult	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
imagine	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
sick	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
evident	O
signs	O
of	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
Ruddy	O
Health	O
in	O
a	O
Countenance	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
commend	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
too	O
much	O
resemble	O
Yours	O
.	O
For	O
her	O
own	O
sake	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
comfort	O
,	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
thinks	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
about	O
her	O
Cough	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
whatever	O
gives	O
You	O
pleasure	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
almost	O
detest	O
.	O
How	O
durst	O
You	O
affront	O
my	O
Consequence	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
direct	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
Portugal	O
Street	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
London	B-place
was	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Addreſs	O
f	O
f	O
o	O
r	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Sixteen	O
Representatives	O
of	O
The	O
most	O
Illustrious	O
Peerage	O
in	O
The	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
insult	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
tolerated	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
punishment	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
determined	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
reside	O
at	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
,	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
.	O
My	O
best	O
affections	O
ever	O
attend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
Wrath	O
,	O
hatred	O
,	O
and	O
abhorrence	O
are	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
portion	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affecte	O
.	O
Brothe	O
r	O
Napier	B-pers
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Wooburn	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
at	O
Eight	O
O'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
neither	O
knew	O
how	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
did	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
had	O
been	O
sent	O
for	O
--	O
London	B-place
,	O
Fifth	O
March	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Northampton	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
