TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
provoked	O
to	O
have	O
miſsed	O
you	O
this	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
I	O
stayed	O
at	O
home	O
expecti	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
all	O
yesterday	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
diſsappointment	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
is	O
not	O
well	O
--	O
if	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
rain	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
tomorrow	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
breakfas	O
t	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
expecti	O
n	O
g	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
him	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
naturally	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
between	O
from	O
8	O
to	O
ten	O
oclock	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
dine	O
out	O
)	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
uncertain	O
about	O
my	O
Father	O
--	O
adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
--	O
affec	O
:	O
yours	O
C.M.G	B-pers
Saturday	O
--	O
10	O
th	O
May	O
1788	O
London	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
