TOKEN	NE
Cumberland	O
Str	O
eet	O
1798	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
daily	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
kind	O
promise	O
,	O
as	O
your	O
favor	O
is	O
not	O
arrived	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
at	O
this	O
season	O
,	O
refrain	O
from	O
writing	O
to	O
wish	O
yourself	O
and	O
Family	O
all	O
happineſs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
each	O
succeeding	O
year	O
may	O
bring	O
you	O
those	O
blessing	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
store	O
for	O
those	O
so	O
worthy	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
satisfaction	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
corresponding	O
with	O
our	O
Friends	O
when	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
perfectly	O
convinced	O
of	O
your	O
--	O
levity	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
without	O
fear	O
of	O
criticism	O
spoil	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
in	O
covering	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
silly	O
prose	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
abundance	O
of	O
news	O
to	O
communicate	O
you	O
must	O
therefore	O
suppose	O
my	O
curiosity	O
is	O
agog	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
hopes	O
keep	O
pace	O
with	O
my	O
wishes	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
soon	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
this	O
very	O
cold	O
weather	O
agrees	O
with	O
yourself	O
and	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
it	O
came	O
on	O
so	O
suddenly	O
with	O
us	O
that	O
yesterday	O
that	O
very	O
few	O
hackney	B-place
Coaches	O
were	O
to	O
had	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Coachmen	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
horses	O
properlier	O
shod	O
for	O
the	O
frost	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
by	O
mere	O
chance	O
we	O
got	O
one	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
's	O
(	O
where	O
we	O
dined	O
)	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
one	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
were	O
therefore	O
obliged	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
them	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
very	O
agreable	O
party	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
an	O
intimate	O
friend	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
's	O
has	O
invited	O
us	O
to	O
spend	O
Twelfth	O
night	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
all	O
others	O
paid	O
us	O
a	O
visit	O
last	O
week	O
?	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Peckwell	I-pers
Who	O
came	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
dear	I-pers
J	I-pers
Kidd	I-pers
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
'	O
s	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Croasdale	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
have	O
called	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
C	I-pers
has	O
given	O
us	O
an	O
invitation	O
For	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
rather	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
accept	O
it	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
Sisters	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remembered	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
with	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
your	O
agreable	O
fireside	O
Believe	O
me	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yours	O
most	O
affectionately	O
M.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Blosset	I-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
and	O
Miss	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
and	O
all	O
enquiring	O
Friends	O
decbr	O
26	O
98	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedforshire	B-place
