TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
this	O
Evening	O
in	O
Kensington	B-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
at	O
any	O
place	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
&	O
set	O
you	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
at	O
any	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
Engag	O
'd	O
--	O
yrs	O
.	O
very	O
Affecly	O
.	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
