TOKEN	NE
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
note	O
and	O
little	O
journal	O
--	O
your	O
time	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
compleatly	O
employed	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
mine	O
tho	O
'	O
rather	O
more	O
agreeably	O
--	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
name	O
Thursday	O
&	O
Friday	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Days	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
always	O
must	O
be	O
engaged	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
when	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
all	O
this	O
Week	O
--	O
will	O
you	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
&	O
stay	O
till	O
¼	O
after	O
7	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
--	O
pray	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
the	O
Busineſs	O
on	O
which	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
is	O
not	O
forward	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
patience	O
with	O
this	O
foolish	O
Estate	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
violent	O
headache	O
today	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
&	O
increase	O
at	O
the	O
Drawingrooms	O
&	O
Play	O
.	O
yours	O
&	O
c	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
