TOKEN	NE
July	O
--	O
1789	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
it	O
never	O
ceased	O
to	O
rain	O
except	O
at	O
2	O
OClock	O
for	O
10	O
minutes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
till	O
4	O
when	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sawille	I-pers
came	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
dinner	O
&	O
I	O
provided	O
a	O
desert	O
of	O
Fruit	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
liked	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
7	O
&	O
after	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
I	O
accompanied	O
them	O
into	O
Gay	O
Street	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
's	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
cd	O
.	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
commiſsion	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
--	O
“	O
&	O
pray	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
your	O
Wife	O
&	O
Daughter	O
safe	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Vanbrugh	B-pers
s	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Blair	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
countenance	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
so	O
large	O
&	O
fat	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Neck	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
young	O
Womans	O
of	O
16	O
--	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Poulter	I-pers
who	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
a	O
likneſs	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
De	I-pers
Vesci	I-pers
,	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
married	O
8	O
Years	O
&	O
has	O
only	O
10	O
Children	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
croſsed	O
my	O
self	O
at	O
the	O
Idea	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
--	O
sister	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Kinnoul	I-pers
)	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
L	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Villiers	I-pers
.	O
Groom	O
of	O
the	O
B.C	O
.	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
a	O
young	O
man	O
&	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
--	O
we	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Evg	O
.	O
which	O
paſsed	O
in	O
lively	O
conversation	O
--	O
&	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Supper	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
conclude	O
was	O
elegant	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Fruits	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
forgot	O
a	O
Mr-	B-pers
Berg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
&	O
is	O
an	O
agent	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Opera	O
busineſs	O
--	O
he	O
talked	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
&	O
made	O
it	O
very	O
clear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
&	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hesitate	O
to	O
say	O
by	O
whom	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
positive	O
presumptive	O
proof	O
but	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
yet	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
after	O
Supper	O
the	O
word	O
Anthem	O
was	O
mentioned	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
's	O
manner	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
,	O
begged	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
would	O
favor	O
us	O
with	O
an	O
Anthem	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
due	O
preparation	O
of	O
hemming	O
and	O
coughing	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
serious	O
Anthem	O
--	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
drollest	O
Medley	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
&	O
kept	O
us	O
on	O
a	O
roar	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
at	O
Opera	O
has	O
clarified	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Van	I-pers
's	O
Ears	O
&	O
entirely	O
cured	O
her	O
Deafneſs	O
--	O
They	O
dont	O
expect	O
to	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
before	O
12	O
--	O
/	O
13	O
/	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
set	O
out	O
this	O
morning	O
for	O
London	B-place
--	O
This	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
day	O
of	O
rain	O
which	O
has	O
fallen	O
in	O
torrents	O
with	O
very	O
little	O
intermiſsion	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
s	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
who	O
made	O
many	O
enquiries	O
after	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
civil	O
things	O
--	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Dr-	O
s	O
-	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
&	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
figure	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
6	O
foot	O
high	O
&	O
thin	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
ruddy	O
complexion	O
,	O
grey	O
Eyes	O
with	O
large	O
Eye	O
brows	O
of	O
the	O
deepest	O
red	O
,	O
his	O
Wig	O
perfectly	O
white	O
to	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
off	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
mouth	O
distended	O
nearly	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
large	O
,	O
shapeleſs	O
,	O
dirty	O
Teeth	O
placed	O
zig	O
zag	O
acroſs	O
this	O
monstrous	O
Fiſsure	O
--	O
This	O
person	O
talked	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
with	O
wonderful	O
&	O
profound	O
deliberation	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
decided	O
in	O
his	O
Opinions	O
--	O
the	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
smiled	O
&	O
seemed	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
my	O
Visit	O
--	O
The	O
rain	O
,	O
which	O
never	O
ceased	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
detained	O
me	O
till	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
venture	O
thro	O
it	O
--	O
14/	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
at	O
the	O
pump	O
Room	O
&	O
he	O
introduced	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
&	O
he	O
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
The	O
post	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
Letters	O
this	O
morning	O
one	O
from	O
Grandpapa	O
at	O
Manr	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
Note	O
inclosed	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
return	O
him	O
my	O
thanks	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
pray	O
inform	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
anxious	O
about	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
3	O
days	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
the	O
only	O
draw	O
back	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
Rash	O
upon	O
my	O
left	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
itches	O
most	O
intolerably	O
--	O
every	O
person	O
compliments	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
clarification	O
of	O
my	O
Complexion	O
&	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
better	O
--	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
much	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
complain	O
,	O
when	O
thousands	O
suffer	O
infinitely	O
more	O
from	O
it	O
than	O
myself	O
--	O
The	O
other	O
Letter	O
came	O
from	O
your	O
Uncle	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
now	O
I	O
may	O
stile	O
him	O
Mine	O
--	O
“	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
--	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
Opera	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
found	O
your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
otherwise	O
have	O
been	O
answered	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
my	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
should	O
have	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Idea	O
that	O
by	O
your	O
continuing	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
had	O
fixed	O
for	O
so	O
material	O
an	O
object	O
as	O
your	O
health	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
a	O
disappointment	O
in	O
the	O
busineſs	O
of	O
raising	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
my	O
Son	O
's	O
Use	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
certainly	O
imagined	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Bond	O
or	O
Deed	O
was	O
executed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
for	O
your	O
return	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
come	O
soon	O
enough	O
.	O
In	O
Scotland	B-place
Money	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
only	O
at	O
certain	O
periods	O
,	O
for	O
instance	O
Lammas	O
or	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
August	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
that	O
paſses	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
which	O
is	O
Martin	O
mas	O
or	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
uncertain	O
when	O
a	O
Vacancy	O
may	O
happen	O
in	O
the	O
Regt	O
.	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
till	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
perfectly	O
convenient	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
of	O
a	O
punctual	O
disposition	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
prepared	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
offer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
favor	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
difficulty	O
find	O
words	O
to	O
expreſs	O
th	O
e	O
Sense	O
of	O
the	O
obligation	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
under	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
generous	O
confidence	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
me	O
such	O
an	O
Offer	O
without	O
the	O
smallest	O
par	O
ade	O
;	O
the	O
favor	O
done	O
me	O
on	O
your	O
part	O
is	O
most	O
complete	O
;	O
&	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
mine	O
will	O
I	O
trust	O
be	O
corresponding	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Agent	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
supply	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
your	O
diverting	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
from	O
the	O
purpose	O
you	O
have	O
allotted	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
even	O
a	O
small	O
period	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
might	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
aware	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
material	O
inconvenience	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
found	O
you	O
so	O
zealous	O
in	O
my	O
Interest	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
scrupulous	O
in	O
my	O
Attention	O
to	O
yours	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
therefore	O
with	O
a	O
thousand	O
Thanks	O
to	O
you	O
decline	O
putting	O
so	O
heavy	O
a	O
Tax	O
upon	O
your	O
friendship	O
.	O
I	O
every	O
day	O
expect	O
my	O
Son	O
home	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
Kind	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
interest	O
yourself	O
in	O
this	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
how	O
it	O
proceeds	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
always	O
happy	O
in	O
every	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
with	O
how	O
much	O
truth	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obliged	O
hble	O
Servant	O
F.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
July	O
13.1789	O
P.S	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
is	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
having	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
house	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
any	O
more	O
Letters	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
”	O
I	O
see	O
great	O
pleasure	O
from	O
this	O
letter	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
very	O
happy	O
--	O
it	O
appears	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
astonished	O
at	O
the	O
confidence	O
which	O
I	O
placed	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
find	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
Act	O
of	O
friendship	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
profeſsions	O
,	O
was	O
what	O
the	O
natural	O
coldneſs	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
probab	O
i	O
ly	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
his	O
doing	O
in	O
a	O
similar	O
situation	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
it	O
gives	O
me	O
v	O
ery	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pow	O
er	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
agreeably	O
flattered	O
by	O
the	O
warmth	O
of	O
his	O
Acknowledgments	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
very	O
soon	O
for	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
ye-	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
--	O
The	O
Major	O
&	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
Sacville	B-pers
who	O
sets	O
out	O
to	O
day	O
for	O
Teignmouth	B-place
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
meets	O
him	O
there	O
&	O
goes	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
proposed	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
accompany	O
him	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
but	O
h	O
e	O
di	O
d	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
If	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Milton	I-pers
shd	O
.	O
luckily	O
be	O
a	O
t	O
Weymouth	B-place
--	O
Sacville	B-pers
promised	O
to	O
return	O
here	O
and	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
otherwise	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
him	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
fair	O
morning	O
&	O
rather	O
warm	O
--	O
at	O
1	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
the	O
Major	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
--	O
which	O
continued	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
home	O
till	O
his	O
Servant	O
broke	O
in	O
upon	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
4	O
OClock	O
--	O
I	O
discovered	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
Son	O
of	O
Secretary	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
--	O
a	O
certain	O
Subject	O
.	O
was	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
,	O
not	O
paſsed	O
over	O
in	O
Silence	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
we	O
compared	O
Notes	O
At	O
8	O
OClock	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
by	O
appointment	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
came	O
there	O
soon	O
af	O
ter	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
sta	O
te	O
of	O
health	O
--	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
quarrel	O
--	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
encouragement	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Supper	O
&	O
we	O
took	O
our	O
leave	O
before	O
eleven	O
--	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
method	O
of	O
coloring	O
,	O
&	O
recommended	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
this	O
town	O
who	O
draws	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
masterly	O
stile	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
leſsons	O
as	O
you	O
expreſsed	O
a	O
wish	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
take	O
care	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
how	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
expreſs	O
yr-	O
wishes	O
as	O
they	O
shall	O
always	O
be	O
gratified	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
lays	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
rain	O
this	O
afternoon	O
--	O
14	O
15	O
th	O
/	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
5	O
OClock	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
finished	O
yr-	O
U	O
's	O
letter	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
breakfast	O
called	O
upon	O
The	O
drawing	O
Master	O
and	O
have	O
fixed	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
leſsons	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
endeavor	O
to	O
find	O
time	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
called	O
upon	O
me	O
yesterday	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
,	O
I	O
luckily	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
busy	O
to	O
admit	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Rundells	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
from	O
my	O
looks	O
there	O
was	O
now	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
yr-	O
being	O
a	O
Widow	O
soon	O
--	O
She	O
desired	O
her	O
Love	O
--	O
Another	O
wet	O
day	O
--	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
expences	O
this	O
year	O
&	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
purse	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
gratification	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Garside	B-pers
of	O
Stockport	B-place
to	O
procure	O
me	O
a	O
License	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
entirely	O
my	O
old	O
amusement	O
--	O
tho	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
lay	O
a	O
wager	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
fiddle	O
ten	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
shoot	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
listening	O
for	O
the	O
Postman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
cant	O
make	O
him	O
come	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
News	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Mama	O
--	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
delightful	O
walk	O
just	O
finished	O
from	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
parade	O
behind	O
Gay	O
Street	O
&	O
Brock	O
Street	O
to	O
the	O
Crescent	O
.	O
The	O
walk	O
is	O
16	O
feet	O
wide	O
of	O
excellent	O
Gravel	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
become	O
the	O
fashionable	O
promenade	O
&	O
how	O
delighted	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
to	O
amuse	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
Louisa	B-pers
on	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
visit	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
&	O
c	O
till	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
better	O
as	O
I	O
'm	O
obliged	O
to	O
use	O
every	O
precaution	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
taking	O
cold	O
--	O
The	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lieutenant	O
is	O
our	O
next	O
Neighbor	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
heartily	O
tired	O
of	O
reading	O
all	O
this	O
Nonsense	O
&	O
to	O
oblige	O
you	O
will	O
subscribe	O
my	O
self	O
Your	O
affectionate	O
Husband	O
--	O
J.D	B-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
selling	O
the	O
most	O
unpleasant	O
horse	O
I	O
ever	O
poſseſsed	O
--	O
A	O
die	O
u	O
Dieu	O
vous	O
garde	O
ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
femme	O
et	O
notre	O
fille	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
Post	O
