TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
.	O
1802	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Inst-	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
utmost	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Yourself	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
long	O
a	O
Father	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
feel	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
anxieties	O
of	O
Parents	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
very	O
impoſsible	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
write	O
comfort	O
.	O
That	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
derived	O
from	O
trust	O
,	O
and	O
confidence	O
in	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
and	O
mercy	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
afforded	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
whatever	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
event	O
of	O
the	O
Dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
sincere	O
Prayer	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
however	O
alarming	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
You	O
despair	O
of	O
the	O
iſsue	O
being	O
fortunate	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
from	O
experience	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
recovery	O
of	O
Children	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
dangerous	O
and	O
alarming	O
complaints	O
,	O
is	O
truly	O
wonderful	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Nursery	O
,	O
and	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Most	O
anxious	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
again	O
from	O
You	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
write	O
,	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Stapleford	O
Hall	O
,	O
Nottingham	B-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
propose	O
leaving	O
this	O
for	O
the	O
South	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
expect	O
to	O
reach	O
Stapleford	O
Hall	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
But	O
my	O
motions	O
must	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
Weather	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
accompanies	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Aunt	O
Lady	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
and	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
You	O
at	O
NorthHampton	B-place
.	O
After	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
Winter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
respite	O
from	O
frost	O
,	O
the	O
Snow	O
has	O
returned	O
again	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
weather	O
continues	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
thaw	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
intentions	O
of	O
leaving	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
should	O
there	O
be	O
another	O
fall	O
of	O
Snow	O
,	O
my	O
journey	O
may	O
be	O
delayed	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
You	O
again	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
aſsure	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
enters	O
into	O
all	O
your	O
fears	O
.	O
Be	O
aſsured	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
attached	O
than	O
We	O
both	O
are	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
Yours	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
unneceſsary	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Give	O
our	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
sweet	O
Girl	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
,	O
and	O
relieve	O
You	O
all	O
from	O
your	O
distreſs	O
.	O
Ever	O
,	O
with	O
sincere	O
regard	O
and	O
affection	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
much	O
attached	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
Febry-	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Northampton	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
