TOKEN	NE
It	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
want	O
of	O
Affection	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
has	O
kept	O
me	O
so	O
long	O
silent	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
I	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
make	O
excuses	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
real	O
truth	O
which	O
is	O
that	O
having	O
suffer	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
my	O
health	O
upon	O
our	O
journey	O
here	O
,	O
my	O
Nerves	O
remain	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
so	O
weak	O
a	O
state	O
as	O
made	O
writing	O
very	O
irksome	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
stronger	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
publick	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
got	O
such	O
a	O
habit	O
of	O
lazineſs	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
behav	O
'd	O
most	O
shamefully	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
correspondents	O
,	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
as	O
my	O
hand	O
&	O
not	O
my	O
heart	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
blame	O
.	O
Our	O
Summer	O
here	O
has	O
been	O
hitherto	O
very	O
favourable	O
to	O
our	O
Northern	O
constitutions	O
--	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
seldom	O
more	O
than	O
agreably	O
hot	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
often	O
had	O
very	O
refreshing	O
rains	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
Society	O
here	O
,	O
particularly	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Ambaſsadors	O
family	O
,	O
whose	O
daughter	O
the	B-pers
Comteſs	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chatignon	I-pers
is	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
young	O
Woman	O
we	O
make	O
parties	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
together	O
every	O
day	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
Society	O
,	O
a	O
comfort	O
one	O
can	O
seldom	O
enjoy	O
in	O
England	B-place
where	O
if	O
you	O
enjoy	O
the	O
com	O
fort	O
pany	O
you	O
like	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
most	O
likely	O
dispers	O
'd	O
diverse	O
different	O
ways	O
the	O
next	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
continues	O
to	O
enjoy	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
recover	O
'd	O
her	O
spirits	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
for	O
she	O
realy	O
made	O
me	O
quite	O
uneasy	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
regard	O
for	O
her	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
uneasineſs	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
prey	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
(	O
naturally	O
good	O
)	O
constitution	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
likewise	O
how	O
you	O
suffer	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
render	O
'd	O
you	O
still	O
more	O
amiable	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
prospect	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
well	O
settled	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
good	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
heart	O
is	O
wrapd	O
up	O
in	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
My	O
kind	O
Love	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
joins	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yr	O
Most	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
&	O
Sincere	O
friend	O
CHamilton	B-pers
Naples	B-place
Augst	O
.	O
ye	O
17	O
th	O
by	O
London	O
To	O
&	O
only	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
Northampton	O
Inghilterra	B-place
