TOKEN	NE
12	O
August	O
--	O
1789	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
have	O
time	O
only	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
-	O
and	O
7	O
th	O
-	O
with	O
the	O
gentle	O
jobation	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
to	O
give	O
me	O
credit	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
might	O
draw	O
upon	O
him	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
ascertain	O
till	O
I	O
wound	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
on	O
monday	O
for	O
15£	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
short	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
thrown	O
away	O
upon	O
my	O
poor	O
body	O
--	O
I	O
blush	O
--	O
Yours	O
of	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
which	O
is	O
just	O
arrived	O
with	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
inclosed	O
for	O
20£	O
I	O
like	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
any	O
letter	O
I	O
ever	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
shortest	O
how	O
happens	O
it	O
I	O
wonder	O
that	O
yr-	O
Letters	O
come	O
so	O
quick	O
--	O
before	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
always	O
been	O
5	O
days	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
12	O
days	O
at	O
least	O
must	O
elapse	O
before	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
receive	O
a	O
remittance	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
likes	O
to	O
find	O
fault	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
too	O
good	O
an	O
humour	O
and	O
too	O
high	O
spirits	O
at	O
the	O
thought	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
again	O
soon	O
,	O
to	O
pout	O
or	O
let	O
that	O
or	O
thing	O
else	O
vex	O
me	O
wh	O
.	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
thing	O
for	O
my	O
stomack	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
journalize	O
upon	O
this	O
Scrap	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
or	O
,	O
like	O
the	O
Scotsman	O
,	O
bring	O
this	O
Letter	O
myself	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
security	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
an	O
intended	O
Conspiracy	O
against	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
our	O
King	B-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
foundation	O
for	O
it	O
whatever	O
--	O
by	O
a	O
private	O
Letter	O
--	O
the	O
Swedes	O
have	O
beat	O
the	O
Ruſsians	O
at	O
Sea	O
--	O
The	O
bells	O
are	O
ringing	O
Colors	O
flying	O
from	O
every	O
Steeple	O
&	O
cannons	O
roaring	O
,	O
--	O
on	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
s	O
Birthday	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
same	O
will	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
honor	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
personage	O
with	O
a	O
cloven	O
foot	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
say	O
ten	O
thousand	O
things	O
the	O
most	O
affce	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
most	O
kind	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
journal	O
--	O
Pray	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
fourfooted	O
Creature	O
i	O
o	O
f	O
some	O
sort	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
place	O
for	O
monday	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
grumble	O
at	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Conveyance	O
that	O
will	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
arms	O
of	O
my	O
dearly	O
beloved	O
Mary	B-pers
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
&	O
Your	O
clever	O
J.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
post	O
