TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
safe	O
arrival	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
&	O
of	O
your	O
having	O
had	O
so	O
agreeable	O
a	O
meeting	O
of	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
are	O
more	O
composed	O
than	O
when	O
you	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
you	O
any	O
proposition	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
such	O
a	O
companion	O
wou	O
'd	O
break	O
in	O
upon	O
your	O
domestic	O
quiet	O
;	O
you	O
perceive	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
unfair	O
in	O
my	O
representations	O
of	O
him	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
too	O
candid	O
to	O
flatter	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
any	O
speedy	O
amendment	O
in	O
him	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
mind	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
bias	O
is	O
to	O
falsehood	O
in	O
preference	O
of	O
truth	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
matters	O
of	O
indifference	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
well	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
past	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
stock	O
of	O
merit	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
trust	O
to	O
!	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bring	O
myself	O
to	O
offer	O
a	O
single	O
argument	O
to	O
persuade	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
take	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Guest	O
;	O
if	O
however	O
from	O
affection	O
to	O
me	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
sacrifice	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
happineſs	O
I	O
will	O
leave	O
him	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
accede	O
to	O
the	O
Terms	O
you	O
have	O
proposed	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
shall	O
be	O
kept	O
secret	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
;	O
you	O
must	O
therefore	O
contrive	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
immediately	O
for	O
my	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
accept	O
your	O
invitation	O
of	O
continuing	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
for	O
a	O
longer	O
period	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
very	O
ill	O
provided	O
with	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
every	O
sort	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
ascertain	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
you	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
supplied	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
neceſsary	O
.	O
I	O
prefer	O
ordering	O
every	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
myself	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
bad	O
encouragement	O
to	O
trust	O
to	O
his	O
discretion	O
.	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
glad	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
direction	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
send	O
Things	O
to	O
Taxal	B-place
;	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
one	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Daughter	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
September	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
1791	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
Orchard	O
St	O
.	O
Portman	O
Sqr	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
.	O
Chapel	B-place
in	I-place
Frith	I-place
DerbyShire	B-place
