TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
unhappy	O
situation	O
I	O
ha	O
v	O
e	O
been	O
in	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
illnes	O
h	O
as	O
confused	O
my	O
memory	O
so	O
much	O
I	O
ha	O
v	O
e	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
much	O
leſs	O
select	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
,	O
those	O
fine	O
one	O
s	O
I	O
mention	O
'd	O
are	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Strong	O
Box	O
left	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
particularly	O
that	O
wrote	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
s	O
funeral	O
which	O
will	O
one	O
day	O
touch	O
the	O
Heart	O
&	O
improve	O
the	O
religious	O
feelings	O
of	O
Posterity	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
your	O
friendship	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
shew	O
them	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
please	O
one	O
for	O
whom	O
the	O
author	O
has	O
the	O
highest	O
veneration	O
&	O
whose	O
ta	O
s	O
te	O
&	O
discernment	O
are	O
so	O
decisi	O
v	O
e	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
soo	O
n	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
Home	O
every	O
Evening	O
--	O
Thu	O
rs	O
day	O
next	O
we	O
dine	O
with	O
Ms	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
nobody	O
can	O
say	O
what	O
time	O
they	O
will	O
l	O
e	O
ave	O
her	O
ever	O
y	O
our	O
most	O
affectiot	O
Vesey	B-pers
23	O
jan	O
These	O
letters	O
wrote	O
under	O
in	O
pain	O
are	O
the	O
least	O
worthy	O
of	O
yr	O
curiosity	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Sundries	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
look	O
