TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
The	O
remembrance	O
of	O
the	O
misunderstanding	O
you	O
allude	O
to	O
is	O
very	O
distreſsing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
acted	O
with	O
more	O
coolneſs	O
;	O
the	O
past	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
recall	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
aſsure	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
equally	O
desirous	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
subject	O
shou	O
'd	O
hereafter	O
be	O
buried	O
in	O
oblivion	O
;	O
&	O
consequently	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
touch	O
'd	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
now	O
considerably	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
enjoy	O
much	O
comfort	O
from	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mind	O
is	O
as	O
yet	O
too	O
much	O
distracted	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
visiting	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
in	O
deed	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
busineſs	O
upon	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
with	O
p	O
r	O
opriety	O
be	O
absent	O
from	O
my	O
present	O
residence	O
even	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
misfortune	O
that	O
has	O
lately	O
befallen	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
surrounded	O
by	O
various	O
domestic	O
grievances	O
,	O
&	O
these	O
bearing	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
advanced	O
period	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
occupy	O
my	O
mind	O
with	O
unpleasing	O
reflexions	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
poſseſs	O
sufficient	O
strength	O
to	O
exclude	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
will	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
leaving	O
me	O
soon	O
,	O
unleſs	O
upon	O
better	O
prospects	O
;	O
she	O
poſseſses	O
a	O
strong	O
mind	O
&	O
much	O
patience	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
has	O
great	O
occasion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
consider	O
'd	O
that	O
every	O
distreſs	O
that	O
may	O
aſsail	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
must	O
fall	O
equally	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
consult	O
her	O
interest	O
in	O
all	O
future	O
occurrences	O
respecting	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
for	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
subject	O
to	O
his	O
control	O
.	O
Having	O
sufficiently	O
tried	O
your	O
patience	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
favor	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
my	O
God	O
Daughter	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
and	O
affectionate	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
n	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
Feby	O
.	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1807	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
cousin	O
,	O
I	O
conclude	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
not	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
suspected	O
my	O
stay	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
would	O
be	O
prolonged	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
extreme	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
have	O
shown	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
inclined	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
conveniently	O
can	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
believe	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
,	O
how	O
happ	O
y	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
degree	O
,	O
to	O
alleviate	O
his	O
sad	O
situation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
perceiving	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
certainly	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
arrival	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
to-day	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
postscript	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
by	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
write	O
the	O
former	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
rejoice	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
perhaps	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
forwarded	O
from	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
gueſsed	O
that	O
matters	O
would	O
turn	O
out	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
respecting	O
my	O
stay	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
most	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
;	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
ever	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
highest	O
obligation	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
truest	O
regard	O
and	O
esteem	O
,	O
your	O
very	O
affectionate	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
daily	O
expectation	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
