TOKEN	NE
7	O
July	O
1789	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
Bath	B-place
7/	O
This	O
day	O
I	O
spent	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
8	O
/	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
left	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
&	O
dined	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
&	O
2	O
Miſs	B-pers
Kirkpatrick	I-pers
s	O
with	O
whom	O
they	O
lodge	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
was	O
ill	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
ye-	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
s	O
&	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
aſsemblee	O
consisting	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Blair	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vanbrugh	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
Brother	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
&	O
his	O
young	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	B-pers
George	I-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
introduc	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
always	O
says	O
when	O
I	O
leave	O
her	O
,	O
“	O
and	O
must	O
you	O
go	O
so	O
soon	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
in	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
stopped	O
for	O
½	O
hour	O
at	O
the	O
Earle	O
's	O
who	O
returned	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Spa	B-place
in	O
a	O
Week	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
the	B-pers
Earles	I-pers
I	O
went	O
into	O
ye-	O
Bath	O
Today	O
&	O
yesterday	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
heavy	O
Showers	O
9/	O
at	O
one	O
oClock	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Milne	I-pers
's	I-pers
who	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
--	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Cold	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
sorry	O
if	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
fancy	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
She	O
seemed	O
so	O
good	O
humoured	O
&	O
so	O
happy	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
my	O
Walk	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
here	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
to	O
introduce	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
polished	O
well	O
bred	O
Man	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
speaks	O
very	O
highly	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
poſsibly	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
recommendation	O
--	O
the	O
Major	O
is	O
fixed	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
pleasant	O
circumstance	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ingles	B-pers
who	O
has	O
spent	O
a	O
week	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
--	O
he	O
begins	O
his	O
Letter	O
with	O
“	O
Lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
going	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
polite	O
reception	O
awaits	O
you	O
”	O
&	O
concludes	O
with	O
a	O
description	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
croſsroads	O
to	O
the	O
mansion	O
--	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
at	O
Dr.	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
s	O
--	O
a	O
Comte	B-pers
Neuville	I-pers
his	O
Lady	O
&	O
Daughter	O
came	O
there	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
we	O
returned	O
at	O
ten	O
--	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
settg	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
heart	O
beat	O
at	O
the	O
postman	O
's	O
rap	O
&	O
calling	O
my	O
Name	O
--	O
I	O
flew	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
found	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
Love	O
10/	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
make	O
the	O
mistake	O
of	O
the	O
Parade	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
vouch	O
for	O
the	O
correctneſs	O
of	O
the	O
direction	O
youll	O
find	O
in	O
this	O
--	O
before	O
I	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
ye-	O
Letter	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
to	O
days	O
journal	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
my	O
company	O
to	O
dinner	O
to	O
day	O
instead	O
of	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Isteds	I-pers
I	O
promised	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
one	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
however	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Herschell	B-pers
s	O
&	O
made	O
her	O
look	O
grave	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
this	O
morng	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
improper	O
degree	O
of	O
delicacy	O
on	O
some	O
occasions	O
,	O
&	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
Cold	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Medicine	O
--	O
on	O
wednesday	O
Evg	O
I	O
bathed	O
which	O
brought	O
out	O
all	O
my	O
Rhumatick	O
pains	O
&	O
the	O
Castor	O
Oil	O
havg	O
had	O
too	O
strong	O
an	O
effect	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
might	O
all	O
together	O
affect	O
my	O
nerves	O
--	O
with	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
as	O
bad	O
weather	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
further	O
digreſsion	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
havg	O
compared	O
yr-	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
with	O
mine	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
when	O
a	O
general	O
rain	O
has	O
commenced	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
nearly	O
if	O
not	O
exactly	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
&	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
5	O
minutes	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
but	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Herschell	B-pers
s	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
played	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
amused	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Spirits	O
raised	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
of	O
my	O
learning	O
to	O
play	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
undoubtedly	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
all	O
thoughts	O
o	O
f	O
r	O
expectations	O
of	O
succeeding	O
on	O
that	O
instrument	O
--	O
I	O
began	O
seriously	O
to	O
despair	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
cald	O
to	O
mind	O
how	O
often	O
you	O
had	O
expreſsed	O
a	O
wish	O
that	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
play	O
upon	O
some	O
instrument	O
I	O
resolved	O
to	O
persevere	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
now	O
happy	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
greatest	O
difficulty	O
is	O
conquered	O
--	O
I	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
base	O
of	O
a	O
common	O
tune	O
now	O
nearly	O
at	O
sight	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
begun	O
to	O
play	O
Duetts	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
tolerably	O
good	O
violoncello	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
ruined	O
&	O
undone	O
&	O
I	O
imagine	O
will	O
not	O
trust	O
me	O
alone	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bull	O
's	O
Library	O
for	O
½	O
hour	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
dismal	O
Accts	O
.	O
from	O
France	B-place
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dreſs	O
&	O
at	O
3	O
went	O
to	O
ye-	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
--	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dining	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
met	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
face	O
to	O
make	O
enquiries	O
about	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
made	O
him	O
uneasy	O
--	O
he	O
recommended	O
some	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
aſsist	O
the	O
operation	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
due	O
formalities	O
with	O
an	O
R/	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
&	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
fee	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
laughed	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
squalling	O
Brats	O
at	O
dinner	O
--	O
&	O
dined	O
comfortably	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
relation	O
with	O
them	O
who	O
is	O
wife	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
Ruſsian	O
Fleet	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
profession	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
au	O
fait	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
overheard	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
conversation	O
&	O
charged	O
me	O
wth-	O
secrecy	O
,	O
which	O
diverted	O
me	O
inwardly	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
's	I-pers
with	O
a	O
promise	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Rundells	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Musick	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
civilly	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
whole	O
family	O
--	O
little	O
hopping	O
Rose	B-pers
enquired	O
after	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
the	O
sickly	O
one	O
was	O
tolerably	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
very	O
agreeable	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fraser	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
woman	O
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
wish	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
exterior	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
very	O
pretty	O
features	O
,	O
a	O
sweet	O
countenance	O
,	O
fine	O
blue	O
Eyes	O
&	O
a	O
delicate	O
figure	O
--	O
The	O
younger	O
Mr.	B-pers
Throgmorton	I-pers
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
me	O
--	O
Happening	O
to	O
mention	O
your	O
name	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
as	O
seldom	O
as	O
poſsible	O
)	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
to	O
enquire	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
&	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
&	O
seated	O
him	O
self	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
about	O
Bell	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
's	O
match	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
these	O
Lascelles	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
fortune	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
only	O
19	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
but	O
they	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
the	O
Harewood	O
estate	O
--	O
dont	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Hoptoun	I-pers
's	O
masked	O
ball	O
that	O
I	O
pointed	O
out	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
to	O
you	O
whose	O
manner	O
&	O
general	O
appearance	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
--	O
He	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
called	O
Prince	O
L——	O
from	O
his	O
aping	O
the	O
Prince	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
very	O
gay	O
young	O
Men	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
said	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Gents	O
.	O
name	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
place	O
under	O
Government	O
not	O
Digby	B-pers
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Throgm	I-pers
.	I-pers
spoke	O
of	O
George	B-pers
's	O
manners	O
and	O
his	O
turning	O
his	O
B——	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
as	O
great	O
impertinence	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
perceive	O
that	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
Charles	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
was	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
Cards	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
--	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Dr.	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
playing	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
Clavicello	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
curious	O
instrument	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
violoncello	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
3	O
strings	O
--	O
&	O
is	O
played	O
upon	O
with	O
Keys	O
for	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
right	O
uses	O
the	O
Bow	O
nearly	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
upon	O
a	O
violo	O
.	O
only	O
this	O
lies	O
flat	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Henry	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
I	O
ought	O
here	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
when	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
called	O
upon	O
me	O
he	O
expreſsed	O
his	O
anxiety	O
about	O
Sackville	B-pers
's	O
taking	O
his	O
wife	O
&	O
Child	O
into	O
a	O
country	O
where	O
civil	O
contests	O
are	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
inevitable	O
&	O
wished	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
an	O
opporty	O
of	O
of	O
mentioning	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
my	O
fears	O
for	O
their	O
safety	O
--	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
tho	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
disagreeable	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Fr	O
ance	O
,	O
yet	O
if	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
Idea	O
of	O
taking	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
with	O
him	O
&	O
wishes	O
for	O
C	O
ompany	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
set	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
”	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
generous	O
good	O
Crea	O
ture	O
--	O
Now	O
for	O
yr-	O
Letter	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
this	O
morng	O
.	O
after	O
I	O
again	O
r	O
ead	O
your	O
Letter	O
my	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
&	O
immediately	O
wrote	O
the	O
following	O
short	O
Epistle	O
to	O
your	O
Uncle	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
yr-	O
relation	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Wi	O
f	O
v	O
es	O
--	O
when	O
a	O
person	O
wishes	O
to	O
serve	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
friendly	O
&	O
delicate	O
way	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
point	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
heart	O
is	O
interested	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
approve	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
wrote	O
“	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sir	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Letter	O
by	O
this	O
days	O
post	O
from	O
“	O
Ly	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
which	O
she	O
informs	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
inconvenience	O
you	O
are	O
likely	O
to	O
sustain	O
“	O
from	O
the	O
unavoidable	O
delay	O
of	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
;	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
concern	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
waters	O
,	O
&	O
dont	O
find	O
myself	O
well	O
enough	O
at	O
present	O
to	O
return	O
into	O
Cheshire	B-place
or	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
out	O
immediately	O
--	O
If	O
it	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
a	O
cornetcy	O
for	O
yr-	O
Son	O
before	O
the	O
Bond	O
can	O
be	O
executed	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
1000£	O
of	O
mine	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
procure	O
for	O
you	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
notice	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Comps	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Dr	O
.	O
Sir	O
yr-	O
obliged	O
&	O
faithful	O
&	O
c	O
”	O
11	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
10	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
&	O
invited	O
them	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
is	O
right	O
--	O
this	O
morng	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
determination	O
to	O
finish	O
this	O
L	O
.	O
&	O
send	O
it	O
off	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
thrō	O
10	O
lines	O
it	O
brot-	O
on	O
a	O
headache	O
which	O
has	O
continued	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
thō	O
through	O
my	O
Italian	O
leſson	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
understand	O
tolerably	O
well	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
weather	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
unlucky	O
circumstance	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
almost	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
self	O
entirely	O
free	O
from	O
Colds	O
--	O
this	O
day	O
has	O
bee	O
rather	O
pleasant	O
,	O
thō	O
with	O
several	O
showers	O
--	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
(	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
simpleton	O
you	O
make	O
of	O
me	O
)	O
--	O
&	O
attempted	O
to	O
sing	O
for	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
at	O
one	O
Rauzzini	B-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
even	O
time	O
if	O
the	O
inclination	O
was	O
strong	O
,	O
to	O
admit	O
of	O
my	O
wandering	O
thoughts	O
--	O
but	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
inestimable	O
treasure	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
could	O
ever	O
forget	O
his	O
Wife	O
even	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
--	O
therefore	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
merit	O
in	O
being	O
faithful	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mary	O
--	O
I	O
paid	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Herschel	B-pers
this	O
morng	O
&	O
was	O
graciously	O
recd	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
C.m	B-place
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Isted	I-pers
was	O
there	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Water	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
injury	O
“	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
mad	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
”	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
always	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Acct	O
.	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Millnes	I-pers
s	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
there	O
a	O
favourite	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
s	O
The	O
rain	O
prevented	O
my	O
leaving	O
them	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Charlwood	B-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
intended	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
disappointment	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
The	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
which	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
better	O
than	O
usual	O
as	O
his	O
face	O
is	O
quite	O
clear	O
from	O
pimples	O
--	O
12	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
cold	O
last	O
night	O
in	O
returng	O
thrō	O
the	O
rain	O
,	O
but	O
otherwise	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
called	O
upon	O
me	O
yesterday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
afterwards	O
met	O
him	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
“	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
tomorrow	O
as	O
their	O
stay	O
was	O
very	O
short	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
excuses	O
&	O
thanked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
friendly	O
attentions	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
my	O
new	O
acquaintance	O
Mrs.	B-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pleasantest	O
men	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
lively	O
good	O
humored	O
,	O
sensible	O
,	O
well	O
informed	O
&	O
extremely	O
well	O
bred	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
amongst	O
French	O
Women	O
,	O
which	O
creates	O
a	O
pliability	O
of	O
manners	O
&	O
attentions	O
which	O
become	O
habitual	O
--	O
where	O
those	O
charming	O
qualities	O
are	O
not	O
natural	O
--	O
It	O
has	O
never	O
ceased	O
raining	O
all	O
morng	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
only	O
once	O
to	O
the	O
pump	O
&	O
the	O
air	O
is	O
so	O
damp	O
that	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
instant	O
at	O
dinner	O
&	O
the	O
natural	O
Vanity	O
of	O
my	O
Sex	O
induces	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
heave	O
a	O
Sigh	O
&	O
whisper	O
to	O
yr-	O
affectionate	O
Heart	O
“	O
How	O
wouldst	O
thou	O
palpitate	O
were	O
my	O
dear	O
Husband	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
thee	O
.	O
”	O
Major	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
'not	O
one	O
word	O
about	O
Louisa	B-pers
'	O
--	O
is	O
it	O
poſsible	O
?	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
&	O
preserve	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
&	O
her	O
charming	O
Mother	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
femme	O
,	O
toujours	O
Votre	O
Louisa	B-pers
Tell	O
J.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
the	O
Corn	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hay	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
shockg	O
condition	O
;	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
uncut	O
--	O
I	O
heard	O
yesterday	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
complaints	O
had	O
terminated	O
in	O
a	O
Drops	O
y	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
swolen	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
be	O
e	O
moved	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
must	O
now	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Mosley	B-pers
Taxal	O
Chapel	O
le	O
frith	O
Derbyshire	O
x	O
post	O
