TOKEN	NE
Greencroft	B-place
7	O
th	O
.	O
Septr-	O
1787	O
.	O
Baby	O
Gazette	O
Extraordinary	O
We	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
inform	O
our	O
correspondents	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
two	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
Walks	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
says	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
can	O
say	O
&	O
holds	O
a	O
conversation	O
with	O
regularity	O
&	O
spirit	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
Napier	O
is	O
a	O
prodigy	O
--	O
Ten	O
Months	O
old	O
--	O
poſseſses	O
Six	O
Teeth	O
,	O
--	O
stands	O
&	O
has	O
walked	O
alone	O
&	O
promises	O
to	O
unite	O
in	O
himself	O
all	O
the	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
of	O
Napier	O
&	O
Clavering	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
purposes	O
taking	O
her	O
departure	O
from	O
Axwell	O
Park	O
the	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
She	O
goes	O
to	O
Edinr	B-place
.	I-place
to	O
collect	O
Feathers	O
&	O
pick	O
Straws	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
form	O
her	O
nest	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
readineſs	O
for	O
the	O
Hatching	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
in	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
's	O
family	O
next	O
Decr-	O
or	O
January	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Right	I-pers
Honble	I-pers
The	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
talks	O
of	O
keeping	O
his	O
Gander	O
Month	O
in	O
the	O
Antient	O
Capital	O
of	O
the	O
Antient	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Caledonia	O
--	O
The	O
production	O
expected	O
soon	O
to	O
appear	O
as	O
an	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Merchiston	O
,	O
is	O
confidently	O
aſserted	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Feminine	O
Gender	O
.	O
The	O
Sponsors	O
in	O
contemplation	O
are	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
of	O
Greencroft	O
Esq	O
r	O
George	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
of	O
Taxal	B-place
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
of	O
Stratford	O
Place	O
.	O
Finis	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Having	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
given	O
you	O
a	O
full	O
detail	O
of	O
the	O
Infantry	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
pleased	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
the	O
good	O
accounts	O
you	O
send	O
me	O
of	O
your	O
little	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Pechell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
happy	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
Us	O
,	O
could	O
You	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
straggle	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
genteel	O
word	O
)	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
You	O
may	O
beleive	O
,	O
were	O
we	O
to	O
penetrate	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
London	B-place
,	O
we	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
visit	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
.	O
I	O
should	O
very	O
much	O
enjoy	O
the	O
countenances	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Mothers	O
,	O
viewing	O
each	O
others	O
productions	O
,	O
seeking	O
for	O
the	O
blemishes	O
&	O
paſsing	O
over	O
the	O
beauties	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
Infants	O
,	O
submitted	O
to	O
their	O
inspection	O
.	O
But	O
alas	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
probability	O
of	O
our	O
meeting	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
cruel	O
Lawsuit	O
still	O
exists	O
&	O
has	O
caused	O
me	O
much	O
vexation	O
&	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
Seven	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
my	O
Journey	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
&	O
the	O
purchase	O
&	O
furnishing	O
of	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
entirely	O
pennyleſs	O
.	O
My	O
Lawyers	O
flatter	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
next	O
term	O
may	O
conclude	O
the	O
busineſs	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
no	O
faith	O
in	O
their	O
expectations	O
having	O
been	O
already	O
so	O
frequently	O
disappointed	O
.	O
I	O
beleive	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
I	O
shall	O
receive	O
about	O
Three	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
which	O
will	O
do	O
more	O
than	O
pay	O
off	O
my	O
personal	O
Debts	O
contracted	O
by	O
Military	O
Purchases	O
before	O
Marriage	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
entailed	O
Debts	O
,	O
I	O
beleive	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
he	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
say	O
whether	O
William	B-pers
is	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
you	O
mention	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Dr.	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
title	O
page	O
will	O
perhaps	O
point	O
out	O
to	O
You	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
Reverence	O
or	O
not	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
Andrew	B-pers
when	O
we	O
meet	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
ever	O
You	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
You	O
a	O
full	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
confusion	O
which	O
arose	O
in	O
My	O
Sister	O
s	O
brain	O
on	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
's	O
being	O
originally	O
announced	O
to	O
her	O
She	O
&	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
regretted	O
his	O
departure	O
from	O
th	O
r	O
-	O
The	O
Doctor	O
has	O
lately	O
discovered	O
a	O
Lime	O
Rock	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Estates	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Tenant	O
s	O
already	O
pays	O
£250	O
pr	O
.	O
Ann	O
.	O
A	O
comfortable	O
addition	O
to	O
their	O
Income	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
left	O
her	O
Sister	O
with	O
every	O
proper	O
decency	O
.	O
We	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
approved	O
of	O
her	O
living	O
with	O
Harriot	B-pers
as	O
it	O
prevented	O
her	O
mixing	O
with	O
such	O
company	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
visiting	O
nobody	O
.	O
Her	O
health	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
has	O
been	O
precarious	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
habit	O
of	O
indolence	O
&	O
indulgence	O
which	O
has	O
not	O
made	O
her	O
better	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
three	O
Children	O
alive	O
.	O
One	O
Boy	O
&	O
two	O
Miſses	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tell	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
You	O
must	O
all	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
recovery	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
for	O
this	O
Month	O
past	O
had	O
the	O
entire	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Rib	O
having	O
taken	O
herself	O
to	O
Harrowgate	B-place
.	O
She	O
returns	O
about	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
-	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Thos	I-pers
.	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
has	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
confine	O
herself	O
at	O
Axwell	O
Park	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
had	O
hints	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
adopt	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
fine	O
Speeches	O
&	O
have	O
hitherto	O
declined	O
the	O
offer	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
begs	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
sincere	O
love	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
your	O
faithfull	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Maria	B-pers
Durham	B-place
September	O
eighth	O
1787	O
N—	B-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derby	B-place
Free	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
