TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
Street	O
15	O
July	O
1783	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
--	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
return	O
you	O
ten	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Verses	O
which	O
make	O
me	O
flush	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
Idle	O
as	O
to	O
mislay	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
prevail	O
'd	O
on	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
into	O
Eſsex	B-place
til	O
they	O
go	O
into	O
NorthamptonShire	B-place
--	O
I	O
think	O
yr	O
friend	O
can	O
hardly	O
ever	O
be	O
so	O
tasteleſs	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
tired	O
of	O
yr	O
company	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
judge	O
of	O
others	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
feelings	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
that	O
a	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
will	O
meet	O
you	O
at	O
Fenny	B-place
Stratford	I-place
,	O
whenever	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
yr	O
commands	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
Tring	B-place
Beds	B-place
Hemel	B-place
Hemsted	I-place
Bag	O
--	O
Adieu	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
all	O
confusion	O
but	O
always	O
yrs	O
very	O
affecly	O
DBloſset	B-pers
.	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
Cheap	O
&	O
most	O
Aimable	O
Milliner	O
you	O
will	O
oblige	O
me	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
apply	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
s	O
in	O
South	O
Molton	O
Street	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
poor	O
Gentlewomen	O
;	O
&	O
vastly	O
well	O
behav	O
'd	O
--	O
