TOKEN	NE
Kew	O
House	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
rejoice	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
hear	O
you	O
gain	O
strength	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
soon	O
be	O
ing	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
daresay	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
lucky	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
Courage	O
to	O
ride	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
of	O
London	B-place
.	O
Prſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
is	O
thank	O
God	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
quite	O
as	O
strong	O
,	O
&	O
more	O
ami	O
ab	O
le	O
then	O
ever	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
I	O
loved	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
more	O
then	O
ever	O
,	O
A	B-pers
R	I-pers
has	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
she	O
wishes	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
her	O
Apartments	O
which	O
are	O
full	O
of	O
Roses	O
,	O
Minionett	O
Violets	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
our	O
Airings	O
are	O
at	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
distance	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
meet	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
out	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
&	O
between	O
both	O
these	O
,	O
&	O
walk	O
Morg	O
&	O
Afternoon	O
besides	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
we	O
find	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
our	O
busineſs	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
very	O
qui	O
et	O
ly	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
,	O
once	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
your	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
afterwards	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
met	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
going	O
to	O
you	O
Adieu	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
finish	O
&	O
am	O
Sincerly	O
Yr	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
--	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
yourself	O
with	O
this	O
Cold	O
weather	O
--	O
