TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
March	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
1786	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
?	O
Why	O
have	O
you	O
never	O
answered	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
?	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
well	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
beleive	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
enough	O
so	O
to	O
prevent	O
you	O
writing	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
said	O
all	O
this	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
constantly	O
intended	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
continual	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
tormented	O
wth	O
a	O
cough	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
quite	O
in	O
despair	O
at	O
your	O
silence	O
had	O
not	O
I	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
who	O
aſsured	O
me	O
both	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
multitude	O
of	O
your	O
epistolary	O
engagements	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
know	O
by	O
experience	O
what	O
allowances	O
to	O
make	O
for	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
except	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
home	O
&	O
am	O
not	O
too	O
much	O
fatigued	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
anything	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
open	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
spare	O
from	O
visiting	O
I	O
give	O
to	O
musick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
exercise	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
weather	O
permits	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
my	O
Health	O
--	O
as	O
for	O
Evenings	O
the	O
few	O
that	O
remain	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
disposal	O
,	O
my	O
Friends	O
seize	O
upon	O
,	O
often	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
stay	O
quietly	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
but	O
how	O
can	O
I	O
shew	O
my	O
gratitude	O
for	O
their	O
attachment	O
&	O
friendships	O
&	O
my	O
sense	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
complying	O
with	O
requests	O
so	O
flatteri	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
so	O
warmly	O
urged	O
--	O
some	O
indeed	O
are	O
affronted	O
if	O
I	O
paſs	O
4	O
days	O
without	O
coming	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
to	O
those	O
indeed	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
leſs	O
pleasure	O
tho	O
'	O
their	O
motive	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
flatter	O
me	O
.	O
inshort	O
perfect	O
liberty	O
is	O
the	O
summum	O
bonum	O
&	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
least	O
restraint	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
obligation	O
of	O
doing	O
the	O
thing	O
even	O
that	O
we	O
like	O
,	O
the	O
charm	O
is	O
fled	O
--	O
you	O
indeed	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
are	O
happy	O
,	O
if	O
happineſs	O
exists	O
for	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
may	O
you	O
long	O
continue	O
so	O
!	O
may	O
bleſsings	O
be	O
poured	O
down	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
circumstance	O
that	O
can	O
enhance	O
their	O
value	O
,	O
or	O
add	O
to	O
them	O
a	O
charm	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
better	O
within	O
these	O
ten	O
Days	O
--	O
some	O
very	O
warm	O
,	O
delightful	O
weather	O
had	O
almost	O
cured	O
my	O
cough	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
snowing	O
violently	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
so	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
expect	O
that	O
tomorrows	O
ancient	O
musick	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
fresh	O
cold	O
--	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
indifferent	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
exceſsively	O
distreſsed	O
about	O
Mrs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
&	O
is	O
still	O
ill	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
better	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
vexed	O
at	O
this	O
most	O
cruel	O
circumstance	O
we	O
have	O
often	O
agreed	O
that	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
Mrs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
's	O
visit	O
is	O
rather	O
a	O
bad	O
&	O
hurryi	O
n	O
g	O
thing	O
for	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
but	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
is	O
too	O
provoking	O
,	O
especially	O
at	O
a	O
moment	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
wanted	O
no	O
additional	O
circumstance	O
of	O
distreſs	O
to	O
overcome	O
her	O
spirits	O
&	O
resolution	O
--	O
My	O
F	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
are	O
at	O
length	O
arrived	O
at	O
Bruſsels	B-place
--	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
from	O
thence	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
who	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
without	O
sayi	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
syllable	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
their	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
--	O
The	O
sensation	O
of	O
being	O
but	O
4	O
Days	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
that	O
of	O
19	O
--	O
is	O
quite	O
delight	O
ful	O
&	O
prepares	O
me	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
for	O
the	O
joy	O
of	O
that	O
moment	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
myself	O
in	O
their	O
arms	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
night	O
at	O
a	O
Ball	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
's	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
gay	O
thing	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
since	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
danced	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
crowd	O
went	O
away	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
became	O
cool	O
&	O
pleasant	O
--	O
I	O
beleive	O
it	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
&	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
with	O
pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
Ball	O
next	O
Thursday	O
at	O
the	O
french	O
Embaſsadors	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
long	O
Drawingroom	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
does	O
not	O
quite	O
fatigue	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
day	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
&	O
spend	O
the	O
Evening	O
wh	O
M	O
rs	O
Wilmot	B-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
night	O
&	O
of	O
cour	O
se	O
the	O
entertainment	O
will	O
be	O
delightful	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
preferable	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
to	O
all	O
other	O
amusem	O
ents	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
like	O
musick	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
Mrs	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
conclude	O
this	O
uninteresti	O
n	O
g	O
stupid	O
scrawl	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
no	O
merit	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
&	O
tender	O
attachme	O
nt	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
paſs	O
another	O
day	O
without	O
sending	O
my	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
in	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
perceive	O
by	O
the	O
date	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
Tuesday	O
28	O
th	O
--	O
adieu	O
,	O
ever	O
your	O
affec	O
:	O
CMG	B-pers
.	I-pers
Remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
you	O
now	O
owe	O
me	O
two	O
letters	O
--	O
died	O
at	O
Paris	O
To	O
Ld	B-pers
A	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
Northamton	B-place
I	O
hear	O
two	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
hear	O
to	O
that	O
