TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
13	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1797	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
my	O
punctuality	O
&	O
dispatch	O
,	O
I	O
now	O
(	O
¼	O
before	O
twelve	O
)	O
return	O
the	O
Poetry	O
received	O
from	O
You	O
at	O
Ten	O
O'Clock	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
Affairs	O
keep	O
Me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Alert	O
,	O
my	O
Regiment	O
having	O
received	O
orders	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
readineſs	O
to	O
move	O
from	O
Aberdeen	B-place
,	O
at	O
a	O
Moments	O
warning	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
notified	O
to	O
Our	O
Commander	O
Lord	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
that	O
(	O
disdaining	O
my	O
Privilege	O
of	O
Parliament	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Corps	O
,	O
whenever	O
he	O
may	O
think	O
my	O
presence	O
may	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
least	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
driven	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
forage	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
and	O
penetrate	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
your	O
Valuable	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
their	O
falling	O
into	O
such	O
unhallowed	O
hands	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
post	O
departs	O
at	O
One	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
write	O
short	O
.	O
Tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Teviot	O
,	O
running	O
past	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
abounds	O
with	O
Par	O
,	O
Small	O
Trout	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Salmon	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
a	O
few	O
Sea	O
Trout	O
,	O
find	O
their	O
way	O
up	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
remain	O
unmolested	O
by	O
Me	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Fishing	O
Rod	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
above	O
once	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
here	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
Pointer	O
,	O
two	O
Greyhounds	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Lady	O
has	O
a	O
Spaniel	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
ever	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
strays	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
He	O
may	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
thinks	O
fit	O
.	O
Partridges	O
&	O
Hares	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
they	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
&	O
Grouse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
sporting	O
intelligence	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
for	O
domestic	O
news	O
,	O
My	O
Wife	O
&	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
,	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
younger	O
Sons	O
,	O
&	O
two	O
Younger	O
Daughters	O
,	O
Colded	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
dont	O
understand	O
the	O
Expression	O
,	O
apply	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
fat	O
Uncle	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
confined	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
Myself	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Ordinar	O
,	O
(	O
apply	O
again	O
to	O
Countrywoman	O
)	O
,	O
&	O
doomed	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
forenoon	O
in	O
my	O
Library	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Sleet	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Westward	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
this	O
account	O
is	O
sufficiently	O
in	O
Detail	O
,	O
to	O
please	O
You	O
.	O
The	O
8	O
th	O
-	O
Vol	O
.	O
of	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
's	O
Natural	O
Histy-	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
and	O
a	O
Vixen	O
.	O
Happy	O
will	O
that	O
Man	O
be	O
,	O
whose	O
fate	O
may	O
join	O
him	O
to	O
so	O
much	O
Wisdom	O
.	O
Commend	O
me	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Being	O
an	O
ignorant	O
Blockhead	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
hate	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
savours	O
of	O
too	O
much	O
Learning	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
rather	O
see	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caroline	I-pers
running	O
about	O
,	O
laying	O
in	O
a	O
Stock	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
than	O
hear	O
one	O
enter	O
into	O
scientific	O
conversations	O
.	O
So	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Commend	O
me	O
most	O
Graciously	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
;	O
Give	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Kiſs	O
;	O
and	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
civil	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
My	O
Rib	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brothe	O
r	O
&	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
Thirteenth	O
Janry-	O
1797	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
HAWICK	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
