TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
Oct	O
r	O
-	O
1810	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
The	O
death	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
though	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
surprise	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Time	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
a	O
Parent	O
must	O
be	O
felt	O
,	O
happen	O
when	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
most	O
natural	O
that	O
Louisa	B-pers
should	O
be	O
distreſsed	O
at	O
the	O
Event	O
.	O
This	O
occurrence	O
may	O
probably	O
make	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
your	O
Arrangements	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
You	O
never	O
would	O
live	O
at	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
become	O
your	O
Summer	O
Residence	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
till	O
You	O
have	O
fixed	O
on	O
a	O
more	O
agreeable	O
situation	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
last	O
wrote	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
setting	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Tour	O
with	O
my	O
Daughters	O
Anne	B-pers
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
,	O
during	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
round	O
a	O
Circle	O
of	O
above	O
two	O
hundred	O
&	O
seventy	O
Miles	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Country	O
,	O
made	O
more	O
so	O
by	O
the	O
richneſs	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
abundant	O
harvest	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
p	O
erformed	O
in	O
the	O
finest	O
weather	O
,	O
I	O
ever	O
remember	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
Rain	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Evening	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
safely	O
housed	O
at	O
Carlisle	B-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Peebles	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
neat	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
Tweed	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
followed	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
traced	O
up	O
the	O
Banks	O
of	O
that	O
beautiful	O
River	O
to	O
its	O
source	O
;	O
then	O
descended	O
into	O
the	O
Vale	O
of	O
Moffat	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
well	O
built	O
Town	O
,	O
resorted	O
to	O
by	O
Invalids	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
two	O
medicinal	O
Waters	O
,	O
of	O
different	O
qualities	O
.	O
Eight	O
miles	O
from	O
Moffat	B-place
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
has	O
a	O
fine	O
Seat	O
called	O
Raehills	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
succeeded	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
heir	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Annandale	I-pers
.	O
We	O
spent	O
three	O
days	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
my	O
Nephew	O
Hunter	O
's	O
at	O
Barjarg	O
on	O
the	O
Nith	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Dumfries	B-place
;	O
then	O
to	O
Annan	B-place
;	O
then	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Amilius	I-pers
Irving	I-pers
s	O
,	O
Robgill	O
Tower	O
;	O
then	O
through	O
Gretna	B-place
Green	I-place
&	O
Longtown	B-place
to	O
Carlisle	B-place
;	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
Robgill	O
;	O
then	O
to	O
Langholm	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Buccleuch	I-pers
has	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
place	O
;	O
then	O
to	O
Hawick	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
explored	O
every	O
inch	O
of	O
our	O
former	O
Residence	O
at	O
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Cavers	B-place
;	O
then	O
,	O
through	O
Jedburgh	B-place
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rutherfurd	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Edgerston	O
,	O
within	O
three	O
Miles	O
of	O
the	O
Cheviot	O
Hills	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Mountains	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Chesters	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Teviot	O
;	O
then	O
to	O
Dryburgh	O
Abbey	O
(	O
Ruins	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Tweed	O
;	O
then	O
to	O
Melrose	O
Abbey	O
(	O
Ruins	O
on	O
the	O
Tweed	O
)	O
then	O
to	O
Selkirk	B-place
;	O
then	O
,	O
croſsed	O
the	O
Ettrick	O
,	O
reached	O
the	O
Tweed	O
at	O
Yair	B-place
,	O
mounted	O
up	O
the	O
Banks	O
of	O
that	O
River	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
again	O
reached	O
got	O
to	O
Peebles	B-place
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
.	O
Now	O
,	O
if	O
You	O
have	O
good	O
Maps	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
ingenuity	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
travel	O
all	O
this	O
over	O
,	O
in	O
leſs	O
time	O
than	O
we	O
took	O
.	O
The	O
spirit	O
of	O
motion	O
did	O
not	O
cease	O
,	O
on	O
our	O
reaching	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
two	O
travelling	O
Companions	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Haddington	I-pers
s	O
,	O
at	O
Tynninghame	O
,	O
in	O
East	B-place
Lothian	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
still	O
remain	O
.	O
Being	O
in	O
a	O
gracious	O
mood	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
,	O
at	O
Saltoun	O
Hall	O
,	O
fourteen	O
Miles	O
from	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
permitted	O
them	O
to	O
remain	O
unmolested	O
,	O
for	O
nearly	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
we	O
then	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
Lordship	O
wrote	O
expreſsly	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
visit	O
proved	O
pleasant	O
enough	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
laid	O
aside	O
their	O
fiddle	O
faddles	O
.	O
Since	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
at	O
Melville	O
Castle	O
,	O
&	O
tomorrow	O
Rib	B-pers
&	O
I	O
,	O
propose	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Buccleuch	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Dalkeith	O
House	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
expeditions	O
are	O
performed	O
,	O
with	O
Nightcaps	O
.	O
This	O
days	O
post	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
,	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
dated	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
well	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Kent	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
first	O
Cousins	O
Napier	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
action	O
in	O
Portugal	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
wounded	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Sarah	I-pers
's	O
eldest	O
Son	O
Major	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	O
severely	O
;	O
her	O
second	O
Son	O
Captain	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
slightly	O
;	O
her	O
third	O
Son	O
Captain	B-pers
William	I-pers
escaped	O
unhurt	O
;	O
but	O
Captain	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
(	O
my	O
uncle	O
Charles	O
's	O
eldest	O
Son	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
as	O
a	O
Volunteer	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
slight	O
knock	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
Major	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
had	O
arrived	O
at	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
when	O
William	B-pers
wrote	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wounds	O
were	O
doing	O
well	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
another	O
Battle	O
,	O
or	O
Maſsena	B-pers
must	O
have	O
retreated	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
yourself	O
,	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Fifth	O
October	O
1810	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Carill	I-pers
Worsley	I-pers
's	O
Derby	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
