TOKEN	NE
Saturday	O
Oakford	B-place
4	O
Sepr	O
13	O
Miſs	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
looking	O
very	O
blooming	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
health	O
James	B-pers
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
the	O
Clergyman	O
of	O
Bampton	B-place
a	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
much	O
esteemed	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
--	O
he	O
has	O
obligingly	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
old	O
Pointer	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
a	O
great	O
Fisherman	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Evg	O
when	O
it	O
rained	O
very	O
hard	O
--	O
Thursday	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
shooting	O
--	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
pronounced	O
commonly	O
Bear	O
--	O
joined	O
us	O
wh-	O
two	O
indifferent	O
Dogs	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
for	O
whom	O
James	B-pers
holds	O
a	O
Living	O
--	O
We	O
only	O
found	O
4	O
Birds	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Shot	O
&	O
miſsed	O
--	O
The	O
Corn	O
is	O
not	O
ripe	O
upon	O
these	O
hills	O
&	O
is	O
uncommonly	O
late	O
this	O
Year	O
--	O
So	O
that	O
Shooting	O
here	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
hot	O
walk	O
&	O
rather	O
tiresome	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
&	O
half	O
from	O
here	O
&	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
sport	O
in	O
fishing	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
beautiful	O
River	O
meandering	O
there	O
a	O
most	O
enchanting	O
Vale	O
&	O
the	O
Sides	O
of	O
the	O
hills	O
covered	O
to	O
their	O
Summit	O
with	O
wood	O
--	O
James	B-pers
laments	O
grievously	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
here	O
on	O
Friday	O
when	O
their	O
was	O
a	O
Stag	O
Chase	O
&	O
the	O
Stag	O
was	O
found	O
within	O
a	O
Mile	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
wild	O
Deer	O
in	O
this	O
immense	O
chain	O
of	O
Woods	O
that	O
are	O
hunted	O
at	O
this	O
Season	O
&	O
the	O
Chase	O
is	O
commonly	O
attended	O
by	O
100	O
or	O
150	O
Horsemen	O
&	O
the	O
hills	O
covered	O
wh-	O
Infantry	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
hear	O
the	O
Sport	O
for	O
the	O
Echo	O
from	O
the	O
Concert	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
pack	O
of	O
Hounds	O
is	O
very	O
exhilarating	O
--	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
the	O
Stag	O
before	O
he	O
leaves	O
Cover	O
himself	O
endeavours	O
to	O
drive	O
out	O
the	O
Ladies	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Harem	O
&	O
selfishly	O
tries	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
lordly	O
majority	O
--	O
at	O
this	O
Season	O
the	O
Hinds	O
are	O
not	O
hunted	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
young	O
ones	O
--	O
On	O
monday	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
this	O
Sport	O
as	O
the	O
Hunt	O
meet	O
7	O
miles	O
off	O
very	O
luckily	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pecularity	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
After	O
breakfast	O
James	B-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Tiverton	B-place
9	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
--	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
called	O
&	O
good	O
humordly	O
went	O
wh-	O
us	O
&	O
aſsisted	O
James	B-pers
in	O
pointing	O
out	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Skylarks	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
We	O
rode	O
thro	O
the	O
Woods	O
&	O
in	O
many	O
places	O
the	O
Vistas	O
are	O
like	O
Enchantment	O
--	O
Nothing	O
can	O
be	O
be	O
more	O
beautiful	O
.	O
A	O
Road	O
is	O
now	O
making	O
along	O
this	O
Valley	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
nearly	O
flat	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
here	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
up	O
the	O
vale	O
to	O
--	O
two	O
miles	O
--	O
commanding	O
this	O
beautiful	O
Scenery	O
--	O
the	O
Hill	O
from	O
the	O
river	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
will	O
be	O
mended	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
rather	O
steep	O
&	O
so	O
&	O
the	O
road	O
covered	O
wh-	O
leaf	O
stems	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Tiverton	B-place
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
this	O
valley	O
&	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
--	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
Church	O
at	O
T	B-place
.	I-place
There	O
is	O
an	O
Altarpiece	O
by	O
Cosway	B-pers
--	O
the	O
Angel	O
appearing	O
to	O
Peter	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
picture	O
--	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
is	O
ornamented	O
wh-	O
carved	O
work	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Ships	O
with	O
Coats	O
of	O
Arms	O
--	O
Adjoining	O
the	O
Church	O
Yard	O
is	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Castle	O
&	O
the	O
family	O
Seat	O
of	O
the	O
Carews	B-pers
&	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
town	O
I	O
was	O
shown	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
More	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
joined	O
the	O
Gypsies	O
--	O
The	O
school	O
at	O
T	B-place
.	I-place
is	O
upon	O
a	O
large	O
Establishmt	O
.	O
there	O
are	O
180	O
Boys	O
all	O
boarded	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
--	O
Whilst	O
our	O
Horses	O
were	O
feeding	O
we	O
walked	O
--	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Hays	B-pers
at	O
Collinpriest	O
½	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
Town	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
were	O
out	O
--	O
At	O
Collinpriest	B-place
I	O
had	O
a	O
specimen	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
Honesty	O
--	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Gunpowder	O
&	O
tendered	O
a	O
two	O
pound	O
Note	O
--	O
the	O
Shopkeeper	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Mayor	O
&	O
a	O
temporary	O
dispenser	O
of	O
Justice	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
notes	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
picked	O
out	O
one	O
&	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
had	O
seen	O
service	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
&	O
torn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
selected	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
Note	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
Banks	O
wch-	O
paſs	O
here	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
chip	O
Hat	O
&	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Note	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
change	O
--	O
however	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
procure	O
it	O
&	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
requested	O
I	O
would	O
change	O
the	O
Note	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forged	O
one	O
--	O
So	O
James	B-pers
&	O
I	O
packed	O
off	O
to	O
his	O
approaching	O
Worship	O
s	O
&	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Note	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
&	O
said	O
--	O
“	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
before	O
where	O
you	O
got	O
this	O
Note	O
”	O
which	O
shewed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
paſsing	O
a	O
bad	O
Note	O
&	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
forgery	O
in	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Stranger	O
--	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
reached	O
home	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bere	I-pers
joined	O
us	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
James	B-pers
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
a	O
fishing	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
&	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
walked	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
I	O
only	O
caught	O
3	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
humour	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
fly	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
ride	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
as	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
it	O
seems	O
odd	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
ride	O
of	O
20	O
miles	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Dog	O
.	O
Oh	O
how	O
Louisa	B-pers
wd-	O
have	O
exclaimed	O
what	O
a	O
beauty	O
--	O
Moses	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compared	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
At	O
T	B-place
.	I-place
there	O
is	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
Dickinsons	B-pers
who	O
are	O
rich	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
--	I-pers
Duntze	I-pers
I	O
found	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
my	O
Rod	O
&	O
paid	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Town	O
(	O
the	O
greatest	O
coxcomical	O
puppy	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
Mazin	O
Esqr	O
)	O
too	O
much	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
repair	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
me	O
for	O
doing	O
Nothing	O
to	O
it	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
two	O
Rods	O
for	O
my	O
loss	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
humored	O
man	O
a	O
good	O
Edition	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lord	O
--	O
the	O
very	O
worst	O
preacher	O
in	O
England	O
--	O
uses	O
z	O
for	O
s	O
on	O
all	O
occasions	O
&	O
what	O
is	O
very	O
singular	O
he	O
can	O
read	O
any	O
book	O
but	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
Saturday	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Rain	O
last	O
Night	O
--	O
Whilst	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
the	O
two	O
rods	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
They	O
are	O
made	O
on	O
a	O
better	O
principle	O
than	O
mine	O
&	O
have	O
skrews	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
joints	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
a	O
fishing	O
by	O
&	O
by	O
but	O
shall	O
wait	O
first	O
till	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
comes	O
from	O
Tiverton	B-place
as	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
You	O
--	O
The	O
great	O
exercise	O
this	O
week	O
agrees	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
better	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
just	O
shown	O
me	O
a	O
fine	O
Collection	O
of	O
useful	O
&	O
ornamental	O
China	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
House	O
--	O
a	O
good	O
Drawing	O
&	O
Dining	O
Room	O
a	O
large	O
paſsage	O
&	O
large	O
Servts	O
.	O
Hall	O
another	O
Sitting	O
Room	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Garden	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
settled	O
that	O
James	B-pers
&	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
poney	O
,	O
&	O
go	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
&	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
--	O
Exmouth	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
can	O
see	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
wind	O
&	O
weather	O
permitting	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
kind	O
fm-	O
hence	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
seems	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
here	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
suffered	O
greatly	O
in	O
Mind	O
&	O
Body	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
12	O
Months	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
lost	O
one	O
Eye	O
&	O
has	O
a	O
tumour	O
settled	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Man	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
picture	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
Opie	B-pers
&	O
another	O
extraordinary	O
likeness	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
by	O
him	O
&	O
a	O
fine	O
picture	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Beggar	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
gave	O
Opie	B-pers
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
&	O
refused	O
1	O
00	O
--	O
Cosway	B-pers
was	O
a	O
Native	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
&	O
means	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
here	O
--	O
James	B-pers
says	O
he	O
James	O
says	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
bury	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
present	O
the	O
Church	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
christened	O
with	O
an	O
Altarpiece	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
12	O
Yr	O
.	O
Welcome	O
letter	O
is	O
arrived	O
It	O
rains	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
fear	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
broke	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Dawlish	B-place
--	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
go	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
Boy	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
arrive	O
--	O
J.D	B-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
Exeter	B-place
