TOKEN	NE
Blackheath	B-place
May	O
21	O
st	O
,	O
1773	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
got	O
yours	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
&	O
propose	O
setting	O
off	O
from	O
London	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
ye	O
23	O
d	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
&	O
being	O
wt	O
you	O
to	O
dinner	O
on	O
ye	O
Monday	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
riding	O
but	O
wont	O
give	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
coming	O
a	O
stage	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
early	O
man	O
&	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
ſure	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
wt	O
you	O
to	O
breakfast	O
so	O
adieu	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
believe	O
me	O
yrs	O
most	O
affctly	O
Napier	B-pers
To	O
William	B-pers
Maule	I-pers
near	O
Forfarshire	B-place
Free	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
