TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
14	O
th	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1779	O
My	O
Frd	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
better	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
reasonably	O
expect	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Cough	O
is	O
at	O
times	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
&	O
nothing	O
but	O
Patience	O
that	O
Sovereign	O
remedy	O
to	O
all	O
Human	O
ills	O
can	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
my	O
Bed	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ordered	O
to	O
stay	O
this	O
Morg	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dearest	O
&	O
keep	O
you	O
form	O
these	O
Colds	O
&	O
every	O
other	O
complaint	O
of	O
Mind	O
&	O
Body	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Chi	B-pers
Chi	I-pers
Affly	O
Yours	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
¼	O
before	O
9	O
Sunday	O
Morg	O
kiſs	O
the	O
dear	O
Children	O
--	O
