TOKEN	NE
In	O
Uncle	O
Archie	B-pers
s	O
Memoirs	O
Naples	B-place
Augt	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
Your	O
tender	O
heart	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
,	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
take	O
a	O
part	O
in	O
my	O
present	O
affliction	O
,	O
your	O
poor	O
friend	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Dear	O
companion	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
24	O
years	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
Alas	O
!	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
siezed	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
fever	O
of	O
the	O
putrid	O
kind	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
expired	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Augt	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
44	O
year	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
but	O
health	O
Lovd	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
to	O
have	O
renderd	O
her	O
perfection	O
itself	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
her	O
patience	O
was	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
never	O
soured	O
her	O
temper	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
suffering	O
s	O
without	O
taking	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
God	O
knows	O
hers	O
were	O
but	O
too	O
frequent	O
,	O
from	O
almost	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
our	O
Union	O
--	O
if	O
ever	O
purity	O
,	O
chastity	O
,	O
humanity	O
,	O
benevolence	O
,	O
charity	O
,	O
occupied	O
a	O
human	O
breast	O
more	O
completely	O
than	O
they	O
did	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
respectable	O
deceaced	O
Katherine	B-pers
I	O
am	O
much	O
mistaken	O
,	O
inshort	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
perfect	O
Christian	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
7	O
years	O
paſsed	O
in	O
this	O
Corrupt	O
Country	O
Country	O
made	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
her	O
Morals	O
,	O
or	O
Sentiments	O
,	O
unleſs	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
increase	O
her	O
admiration	O
for	O
true	O
Virtue	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
Vice	O
with	O
greater	O
abhorrence	O
.	O
Even	O
the	O
late	O
Cardinal	B-pers
Arch	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
always	O
quoted	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
Example	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
never	O
visit	O
another	O
Lady	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
as	O
he	O
thought	O
her	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
that	O
lead	O
a	O
decent	O
and	O
proper	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Cardinal	B-pers
Sersale	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
prayer	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
daily	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
at	O
last	O
become	O
a	O
Catholick	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
Thank	O
God	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
suffer	O
much	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
fatal	O
illneſs	O
which	O
affected	O
her	O
brain	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
lethargick	O
--	O
My	O
only	O
consolation	O
is	O
that	O
death	O
has	O
put	O
a	O
period	O
to	O
her	O
sufferings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
horrid	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
her	O
whole	O
inside	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
cou	O
'd	O
never	O
have	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
a	O
moments	O
ease	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
recoverd	O
from	O
the	O
fever	O
--	O
She	O
requested	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
in	O
her	O
family	O
Vault	O
at	O
Slebech	B-place
in	O
Wales	B-place
&	O
that	O
when	O
my	O
hour	O
shall	O
come	O
that	O
my	O
remains	O
be	O
laid	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
be	O
complied	O
with	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
natural	O
sentiments	O
and	O
inclination	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
that	O
my	O
clay	O
shou	O
'd	O
mix	O
with	O
the	O
Ea	O
r	O
th	O
nearest	O
at	O
hand	O
at	O
The	O
moment	O
of	O
my	O
diſsolution	O
.	O
what	O
a	O
dream	O
is	O
this	O
life	O
?	O
it	O
seems	O
but	O
yesterday	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
yet	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
occurrences	O
in	O
the	O
24	O
years	O
We	O
have	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
more	O
Union	O
,	O
than	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
the	O
marriage	O
State	O
--	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
reflect	O
upon	O
a	O
Turkish	O
tale	O
in	O
the	O
Spectator	O
where	O
Mirza	B-pers
's	O
head	O
is	O
dipped	O
into	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
Water	O
by	O
a	O
Magician	O
&	O
paſses	O
an	O
imaginary	O
life	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
between	O
the	O
plunging	O
&	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
--	O
Life	O
is	O
a	O
dream	O
indeed	O
!	O
may	O
yours	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Niece	O
be	O
a	O
pleasant	O
one	O
--	O
W	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
via	O
Mantua	B-place
To	O
The	B-pers
Honourable	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
St	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
Windsor	O
Palace	O
Inghilterra	B-place
London	B-place
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
