TOKEN	NE
Grosvenor	O
Square	O
Decr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1800	O
My	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
Beleive	O
me	O
my	O
sincere	O
affection	O
towards	O
you	O
is	O
ever	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
once	O
receive	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
We	O
were	O
driven	O
from	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
line	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
any	O
mention	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Cavr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Palombo	I-pers
however	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
Palermo	B-place
without	O
having	O
had	O
from	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Acton	I-pers
the	O
most	O
solemn	O
promise	O
that	O
Palombo	B-pers
shoud	O
have	O
immediately	O
an	O
Employment	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
sufficient	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
family	O
a	O
competent	O
Subsistance	O
Subsistance	O
--	O
We	O
once	O
got	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
generosity	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
a	O
pecuniary	O
aſsistance	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
We	O
will	O
not	O
abandon	O
him	O
&	O
if	O
his	O
busineſs	O
is	O
not	O
done	O
already	O
Emma	B-pers
who	O
is	O
in	O
Constant	O
correspondence	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
will	O
engage	O
Her	B-pers
majesty	I-pers
to	O
induce	O
Acton	B-pers
to	O
fullfill	O
his	O
promise	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
so	O
little	O
time	O
that	O
let	O
these	O
few	O
words	O
suffice	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
untill	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
meeting	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
quit	O
London	B-place
untill	O
my	O
own	O
confused	O
affairs	O
are	O
Settled	O
as	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
ignorant	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
to	O
become	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
certainly	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
return	O
ro	O
Naples	B-place
at	O
least	O
in	O
a	O
Public	O
Character	O
--	O
my	O
Native	O
air	O
seems	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
untill	O
my	O
mind	O
is	O
at	O
rest	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
Emma	B-pers
s	O
kind	O
love	O
has	O
never	O
faild	O
towards	O
you	O
&	O
yrs	O
.	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
you	O
will	O
even	O
find	O
us	O
the	O
same	O
notwithstanding	O
strange	O
appearances	O
of	O
neglect	O
on	O
our	O
Side	O
--	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
our	O
Post	O
was	O
never	O
sure	O
&	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
Letters	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
distreſsfull	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
with	O
our	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
all	O
your	O
family	O
I	O
remain	O
yr	O
most	O
sincere	O
&	O
affectionate	O
uncle	O
Wm	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
