TOKEN	NE
Margate	B-place
August	O
26	O
.	O
1773	O
Once	O
more	O
My	O
Dear	O
Ward	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
write	O
you	O
&	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
mending	O
a	O
pace	O
;	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
really	O
a	O
terrible	O
time	O
ſince	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Edinburgh	B-place
&	O
ſome	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
two	O
Phiſicians	O
constantly	O
attending	O
me	O
with	O
Surgeons	O
Nurses	O
and	O
the	O
D——l	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
well	O
recovered	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
thank	O
My	O
Dear	O
Ward	O
for	O
hers	O
of	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
July	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
her	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
first	O
letter	O
(	O
but	O
one	O
on	O
buſineſs	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
Goodneſs	O
will	O
excuse	O
the	O
shortneſs	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
&	O
am	O
very	O
impatient	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
Killarney	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
the	O
binding	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
do	O
always	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
&	O
get	O
round	O
the	O
Spiral	O
Circle	O
with	O
yr	O
Mama	O
&	O
Guardian	O
just	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
so	O
nothing	O
more	O
can	O
be	O
ſaid	O
but	O
that	O
its	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
pleasure	O
so	O
of	O
course	O
we	O
must	O
subscribe	O
yr	O
mama	O
wont	O
own	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
dont	O
ſignify	O
&	O
its	O
not	O
the	O
leſs	O
true	O
remember	O
the	O
Picture	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
dining	O
Parlour	O
,	O
pray	O
how	O
does	O
it	O
look	O
now	O
?	O
I	O
really	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
deſire	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
Book	O
&	O
Ring	O
unleſs	O
you	O
could	O
send	O
them	O
derected	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ruſsell	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Naſsau	O
Street	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
he	O
will	O
send	O
them	O
by	O
ſome	O
ſafe	O
hand	O
that	O
is	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
St	B-place
Annes	I-place
&	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
him	O
that	O
ſuch	O
a	O
parcell	O
will	O
be	O
sent	O
him	O
&	O
beg	O
he	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Ward	O
&	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
two	O
sincerer	O
friends	O
than	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
who	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
Compts-	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
affctly	O
yours	O
Napier	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
wrote	O
you	O
very	O
lately	O
.	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
Recd	O
:	O
at	O
Edinburgh	B-place
Septr	O
.	O
5	O
th	O
1773	O
