TOKEN	NE
July	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
3	O
Letters	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
so	O
can	O
not	O
satisfy	O
myself	O
without	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
how	O
much	O
pleasure	O
they	O
afford	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
so	O
sure	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
hardly	O
excusable	O
for	O
troubling	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
really	O
feels	O
such	O
a	O
burden	O
on	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
acknowledgements	O
where	O
I	O
feel	O
they	O
are	O
due	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
indulgence	O
to	O
myself	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
these	O
public	O
Charges	O
will	O
again	O
embarraſs	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
&	O
disturb	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
s	O
Quiet	O
,	O
pray	O
send	O
me	O
word	O
how	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
&	O
whether	O
his	O
good	O
Spirits	O
keep	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Parliament	O
will	O
set	O
for	O
ever	O
for	O
whilst	O
Administration	O
is	O
so	O
unsettled	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
rise	O
.	O
I	O
shd	O
think	O
the	O
remaining	O
at	O
W	B-place
.	I-place
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
a	O
more	O
Comfortable	O
Scheme	O
&	O
better	O
for	O
the	O
Pſs	O
s	O
than	O
going	O
backwards	O
&	O
forwards	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
they	O
think	O
abt	O
.	O
that	O
?	O
Pſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Letters	O
are	O
wrote	O
quite	O
in	O
Spirits	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
pretty	O
.	O
The	O
Acct	O
Hawkins	B-pers
will	O
have	O
given	O
from	O
hence	O
I	O
fancy	O
will	O
fix	O
her	O
here	O
sometime	O
longer	O
,	O
indeed	O
it	O
ought	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
s	O
sake	O
with	O
whom	O
it	O
certainly	O
agrees	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
by	O
My	O
Family	O
contriving	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
me	O
't	O
is	O
made	O
really	O
very	O
comfortable	O
.	O
I	O
aim	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dont	O
aim	O
to	O
all	O
particulars	O
in	O
yours	O
,	O
but	O
notice	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
much	O
interested	O
&	O
amused	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
that	O
Dutcheſs	O
keep	O
her	O
Post	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
on	O
the	O
Terrace	O
)	O
so	O
constantly	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
seeking	O
Mortification	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
P	O
.	O
does	O
not	O
notice	O
them	O
particularly	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
one	O
can	O
Acct	O
.	O
for	O
their	O
coming	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Chapel	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
add	O
any	O
more	O
now	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Event	O
here	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
tis	O
at	O
Cdr	B-pers
Dickes	I-pers
whose	O
Wife	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
good	O
Sort	O
of	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
to	O
meet	O
us	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Ever	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
