TOKEN	NE
Light-foot	B-pers
will	O
be	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
Collection	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
inclose	O
the	O
Advertisment	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
She	O
commanded	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
She	O
takes	O
great	O
Care	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
wished	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
was	O
too	O
early	O
--	O
Then	O
your	O
D——	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
s	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
and	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
buys	O
her	O
garden	O
Seeds	O
--	O
She	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
L——	O
from	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
as	O
She	O
read	O
it	O
--	O
exclaimed	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
every	O
Sentence	O
“	O
Impudence	O
--	O
Flattery	O
--	O
Deceit	O
--	O
Hypocrite	O
--	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
kick	O
him	O
”	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
laughs	O
at	O
his	O
cajoling	O
you	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
returned	O
from	O
Cambrid	B-place
day	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
dearly	O
--	O
best	O
of	O
Women	O
--	O
best	O
of	O
Wives	O
&	O
best	O
of	O
friends	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
and	O
preserve	O
You	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
yr-	O
happy	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
again	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
shall	O
do	O
next	O
week	O
--	O
--	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Respects	O
&	O
Love	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
