TOKEN	NE
Boston	B-place
Decr	O
:	O
20	O
th	O
1768	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
Sorry	O
for	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Sillence	O
--	O
we	O
heartily	O
wish	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
the	O
entire	O
Recovery	O
of	O
their	O
Healths	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
make	O
Liffe	O
agreeable	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
them	O
.	O
Accept	O
&	O
offer	O
them	O
from	O
us	O
all	O
our	O
best	O
Wishes	O
for	O
many	O
Happy	O
returns	O
of	O
the	O
Saison	O
:	O
as	O
its	O
generaly	O
a	O
Merry	O
makeing	O
time	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
all	O
able	O
to	O
enjoy	O
it	O
as	O
Such	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
us	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
Well	O
indeed	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
our	O
Share	O
of	O
Sickneſs	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
'm	O
so	O
Unweildy	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
sorry	O
when	O
the	O
time	O
comes	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
confine	O
me	O
altogether	O
I	O
might	O
now	O
return	O
Mrs	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
Isted	I-pers
s	O
Card	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
were	O
I	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
&	O
Say	O
I	O
am	O
too	O
big	O
to	O
go	O
Visitting	O
--	O
however	O
like	O
her	O
I	O
still	O
contrive	O
to	O
crawll	O
about	O
amongst	O
my	O
friends	O
people	O
here	O
are	O
much	O
leſs	O
Babylonians	O
than	O
with	O
you	O
they	O
are	O
an	O
Honest	O
kind	O
good	O
Sort	O
of	O
People	O
--	O
live	O
well	O
&	O
are	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
friends	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
their	O
good	O
things	O
No	O
Election	O
disputes	O
&	O
but	O
litle	O
party	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
amongst	O
people	O
of	O
any	O
fashion	O
though	O
the	O
Division	O
of	O
the	O
Fens	O
bred	O
horrid	O
Riots	O
but	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
all	O
goes	O
Smooth	O
--	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
do	O
us	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
bellieve	O
we	O
heartily	O
regreate	O
the	O
present	O
Interuption	O
of	O
the	O
pleasures	O
we	O
proposed	O
ourselves	O
in	O
yr	O
Neighbourhood	O
&	O
Society	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
ever	O
Esteem	O
ourselves	O
Happy	O
in	O
any	O
Oportunity	O
to	O
Renew	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
otherwise	O
we	O
have	O
changed	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
especialy	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
s	O
House	O
extravagantly	O
dear	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
would	O
have	O
proved	O
too	O
Small	O
for	O
the	O
Augmentation	O
we	O
hope	O
for	O
to	O
our	O
familly	O
--	O
here	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
Excellent	O
House	O
,	O
room	O
enough	O
&	O
plenty	O
of	O
good	O
Furniture	O
--	O
.	O
I	O
agree	O
wt	O
yr	O
Pappa	O
in	O
thinking	O
the	O
Ruſsian	O
dispatch	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Second	O
hand	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
Hurry	O
they	O
are	O
were	O
in	O
I	O
fansy	O
made	O
them	O
not	O
send	O
above	O
one	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
familly	O
to	O
be	O
transmitted	O
through	O
the	O
different	O
Branches	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
:	O
I	O
imagine	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
more	O
at	O
Leisure	O
haveing	O
received	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
Yesterday	O
from	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
--	O
my	O
Br	O
:	O
is	O
remarkably	O
well	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
very	O
much	O
so	O
;	O
their	O
own	O
House	O
not	O
yet	O
fitted	O
up	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
good	O
Spiritts	O
&	O
she	O
infinatly	O
pleas	O
'd	O
wt	O
their	O
Situation	O
&	O
the	O
Usage	O
they	O
meet	O
with	O
--	O
so	O
its	O
to	O
be	O
hoped	O
all	O
will	O
go	O
well	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
wt	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
schocking	O
affair	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Arden	I-pers
s	O
:	O
Im	O
sorry	O
Mrs	B-pers
Isted	I-pers
trains	O
her	O
Eleve	O
's	O
no	O
better	O
&	O
hope	O
the	O
Widow	O
will	O
alwise	O
remain	O
so	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
pray	O
write	O
soon	O
&	O
bellieve	O
me	O
Ever	O
most	O
Sincearly	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Enclose	O
my	O
Letter	O
under	O
Covers	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	O
M	O
:	O
P	O
:	O
at	O
His	O
House	O
Broad	O
Street	O
London	B-place
&	O
send	O
me	O
all	O
yr	O
News	O
&	O
wt	O
yr	O
Elections	O
are	O
doing	O
for	O
its	O
not	O
over	O
yet	O
.	O
To	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
:	I-pers
Ch	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
free	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
M	O
:	O
P	O
:	O
