TOKEN	NE
Saturday	O
--	O
4	O
Sepr	O
.	O
13	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
off	O
my	O
letter	O
by	O
the	O
old	O
Post	O
Woman	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Fishing	O
Rod	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
&	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
Shower	O
of	O
Rain	O
&	O
very	O
good	O
Sport	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Adept	O
my	O
Bag	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
distended	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Dish	O
of	O
Trouts	O
which	O
were	O
acceptable	O
as	O
Two	O
Gentlemen	O
dined	O
here	O
Revd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
Bere	I-pers
a	O
sensible	O
Clergyman	O
&	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
who	O
made	O
his	O
fortune	O
in	O
America	B-place
&	O
is	O
settled	O
in	O
this	O
Neighborhood	O
--	O
In	O
my	O
sport	O
I	O
forgot	O
the	O
perpendicular	O
hill	O
I	O
went	O
around	O
before	O
dinner	O
&	O
had	O
hard	O
work	O
to	O
return	O
in	O
time	O
as	O
it	O
requires	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
bridge	O
which	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
mile	O
--	O
Sunday	O
--	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
decent	O
Congregation	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
gratified	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
yr-	O
Knight	O
discharged	O
his	O
Duty	O
as	O
a	O
Parish	O
priest	O
--	O
his	O
Voice	O
is	O
loud	O
&	O
clear	O
&	O
he	O
reads	O
extremely	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
Clergymen	O
were	O
paid	O
by	O
the	O
Tenor	O
of	O
the	O
Voice	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
proportion	O
as	O
fine	O
Ladies	O
pay	O
their	O
Footman	O
wages	O
by	O
their	O
Heigth	O
,	O
his	O
Salary	O
would	O
be	O
immense	O
--	O
his	O
Voice	O
would	O
fill	O
Westminster	B-place
Abbey	I-place
--	O
without	O
an	O
effort	O
--	O
After	O
service	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
poney	O
&	O
rode	O
to	O
the	O
Bridge	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Sketch	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
tho	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
rude	O
Attempt	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
she	O
will	O
understand	O
it	O
is	O
meant	O
for	O
a	O
Bridge	O
without	O
much	O
explanation	O
--	O
The	O
Scenery	O
about	O
it	O
is	O
beautiful	O
--	O
The	O
afternoon	O
Service	O
was	O
well	O
attended	O
--	O
the	O
Church	O
was	O
crammed	O
full	O
--	O
James	B-pers
had	O
a	O
Christening	O
&	O
a	O
Churching	O
--	O
and	O
the	O
Children	O
sang	O
their	O
Catechism	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
excellent	O
Sermon	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Catechism	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Orchestra	O
--	O
3	O
Ladies	O
sing	O
who	O
are	O
much	O
superior	O
to	O
Catalani	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
have	O
3	O
Violins	O
&	O
2	O
Players	O
on	O
the	O
Violoncello	O
--	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Band	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
one	O
Performer	O
--	O
I	O
observed	O
when	O
these	O
Operators	O
wish	O
to	O
shew	O
their	O
Talents	O
&	O
give	O
a	O
Shake	O
wch	O
.	O
frequently	O
occurs	O
--	O
they	O
give	O
the	O
Inſtrument	O
a	O
good	O
hearty	O
Shake	O
--	O
&	O
once	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
the	O
performer	O
drew	O
his	O
Bow	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
over	O
the	O
same	O
Note	O
rapidly	O
which	O
produces	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
Melody	O
that	O
Nothing	O
can	O
exceed	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
proves	O
his	O
taste	O
&	O
fine	O
Ears	O
--	O
After	O
evening	O
Service	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
rode	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
returned	O
the	O
Rain	O
began	O
&	O
has	O
seldom	O
ceased	O
for	O
many	O
minutes	O
--	O
Monday	O
--	O
Constant	O
Rain	O
has	O
prevented	O
our	O
going	O
a	O
hunting	O
or	O
rather	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Hunt	O
--	O
if	O
the	O
y	O
Sportsmen	O
really	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
find	O
a	O
Deer	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
wet	O
as	O
wet	O
--	O
We	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
but	O
unleſs	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
probability	O
of	O
better	O
weather	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
advisable	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P——	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
fine	O
Collection	O
of	O
China	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
some	O
beauties	O
&	O
one	O
handsome	O
set	O
with	O
the	O
Arms	O
--	O
In	O
examining	O
my	O
fishing	O
apparatus	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
small	O
fish	O
that	O
were	O
overlooked	O
for	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
dinner	O
was	O
ready	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
fishing	O
but	O
as	O
twelve	O
fish	O
were	O
produced	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
dreſsed	O
&	O
very	O
delicious	O
they	O
were	O
&	O
the	O
Visitors	O
&	O
all	O
had	O
a	O
feast	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Custom	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
teazed	O
me	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Clocks	O
on	O
the	O
Stair	O
Case	O
or	O
rather	O
Landing	O
--	O
one	O
strikes	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
&	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
kept	O
exact	O
--	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
liked	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Alarm	O
Clock	O
for	O
the	O
Servants	O
to	O
let	O
thm	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
real	O
time	O
of	O
Day	O
was	O
approaching	O
Phoebe	B-pers
would	O
fall	O
asleep	O
in	O
listening	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
which	O
keeps	O
the	O
Cook	O
's	O
time	O
&	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
delightful	O
to	O
hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
speak	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Husband	O
,	O
She	O
describes	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
of	O
human	O
beings	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
Deepest	O
Mourning	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dreſs	O
--	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brickdale	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
&	O
lives	O
two	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
has	O
made	O
some	O
thatched	O
Huts	O
in	O
his	O
Woods	O
in	O
places	O
that	O
command	O
the	O
most	O
interesting	O
Scenes	O
&	O
here	O
the	O
families	O
in	O
the	O
Neighborhood	O
often	O
resort	O
in	O
summer	O
time	O
&	O
carry	O
a	O
cold	O
dinner	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
these	O
excursions	O
&	O
on	O
these	O
Occasions	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brickdale	I-pers
would	O
let	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Water	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
those	O
Woods	O
which	O
came	O
foaming	O
&	O
dashing	O
down	O
the	O
Wood	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
torrent	O
&	O
he	O
would	O
fish	O
off	O
a	O
Corner	O
when	O
the	O
Reverberations	O
were	O
magnificently	O
sublime	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
fond	O
of	O
a	O
Garden	O
&	O
takes	O
as	O
much	O
pains	O
as	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Sarah	B-pers
--	O
At	O
this	O
moment	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
heavy	O
shower	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
--	O
She	O
wont	O
hear	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
News	O
paper	O
that	O
comes	O
here	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
a	O
country	O
paper	O
--	O
one	O
may	O
get	O
used	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
that	O
has	O
paſsed	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
Town	B-place
&	O
am	O
very	O
content	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
sorry	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
discovered	O
the	O
grand	O
Secret	O
but	O
She	O
may	O
thank	O
herself	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
felt	O
offended	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
&	O
walked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
mad	O
to	O
be	O
talked	O
to	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
my	O
Countenance	O
&	O
manner	O
were	O
legible	O
enough	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
own	O
she	O
teazes	O
me	O
exceſsively	O
&	O
She	O
so	O
frequently	O
makes	O
you	O
nervous	O
&	O
fatigued	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
no	O
particular	O
anxiety	O
for	O
her	O
Company	O
--	O
Independently	O
of	O
our	O
affection	O
for	O
Nanny	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
Mad	O
as	O
She	O
is	O
--	O
She	O
can	O
command	O
herself	O
&	O
be	O
very	O
agreeable	O
&	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
Sweetneſs	O
of	O
disposition	O
naturally	O
that	O
one	O
can	O
bear	O
wh	O
.	O
her	O
Oddities	O
--	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
are	O
perversities	O
--	O
quite	O
a	O
different	O
thing	O
--	O
A	O
fine	O
Peacock	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
James	B-pers
contends	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
finer	O
Bird	O
than	O
at	O
Bullock	B-pers
s	O
Museum	O
The	O
tai	O
l	O
of	O
this	O
Bird	O
is	O
absent	O
at	O
present	O
therefore	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
judge	O
of	O
natural	O
dimensions	O
--	O
If	O
Louisa	B-pers
was	O
here	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
fine	O
Subjects	O
for	O
her	O
pencil	O
as	O
Memorandums	O
--	O
The	O
Clouds	O
are	O
magnifique	O
--	O
&	O
paſsing	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
wh-	O
great	O
Rapidity	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Madam	B-pers
de	I-pers
S.	I-pers
H	I-pers
will	O
recover	O
her	O
Spirits	O
to	O
the	O
Tone	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
when	O
she	O
sketched	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
Likeneſs	O
or	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
perfect	O
the	O
Character	O
which	O
she	O
has	O
so	O
well	O
conceived	O
--	O
Poor	O
Robert	B-pers
is	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
tall	O
&	O
well	O
looking	O
very	O
like	O
Miſs	B-pers
P——	I-pers
his	O
effort	O
in	O
speaking	O
seems	O
very	O
laborious	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
use	O
his	O
Tongue	O
--	O
I	O
understand	O
him	O
tolerably	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
humored	O
--	O
his	O
legs	O
are	O
very	O
weak	O
--	O
his	O
feet	O
not	O
straight	O
&	O
he	O
walks	O
with	O
difficulty	O
--	O
&	O
has	O
little	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
--	O
he	O
can	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
&	O
unlock	O
a	O
padlock	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
effort	O
--	O
His	O
Amusement	O
is	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
some	O
Rabits	O
&	O
his	O
exercise	O
going	O
to	O
visit	O
them	O
frequently	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
proper	O
Pens	O
as	O
the	O
poor	O
Creatures	O
are	O
kept	O
without	O
light	O
&	O
air	O
&	O
he	O
seems	O
much	O
pleased	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
understands	O
my	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
management	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Object	O
for	O
a	O
tenderhearted	O
Mother	O
to	O
have	O
constantly	O
under	O
her	O
Observation	O
--	O
.	O
12	O
Oclock	O
--	O
have	O
just	O
recd	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
of	O
Friday	O
the	O
second	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
presented	O
you	O
wh	O
.	O
a	O
Bullfinch	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Keadges	B-pers
as	O
I	O
thought	O
their	O
invitation	O
a	O
shuffling	O
one	O
like	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
preſsing	O
--	O
Birds	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
scarce	O
here	O
--	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Shooting	O
--	O
The	O
Corn	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
cut	O
in	O
my	O
time	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
fatality	O
about	O
my	O
Shooting	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
Fishing	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
hospitable	O
Benning	B-place
brough	I-place
so	O
the	O
comparison	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
as	O
Fishing	O
is	O
a	O
Nuelty	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
not	O
like	O
high	O
prices	O
at	O
Brighton	B-place
--	O
Staying	O
a	O
week	O
leſs	O
makes	O
the	O
difference	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
if	O
you	O
&	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
approve	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
agree	O
wh-	O
Mor	B-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
face	O
in	O
the	O
picture	O
seems	O
larger	O
than	O
Nature	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
different	O
when	O
properly	O
shaded	O
--	O
by	O
giving	O
the	O
Head	O
a	O
twist	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
as	O
thank	O
God	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
within	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
shewn	O
a	O
double	O
Chin	O
which	O
increases	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
face	O
&	O
tho	O
natural	O
to	O
the	O
Creation	O
in	O
that	O
position	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
fond	O
of	O
is	O
not	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
chosen	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
content	O
--	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Resemblance	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
Girl	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
Mind	O
is	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
pretty	O
little	O
Pea	O
Chick	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Accept	O
Love	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
every	O
Body	O
--	O
most	O
Affy-	O
Yr	O
.	O
own	O
JD	B-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
