TOKEN	NE
KenWood	O
Janry	O
:	O
6	O
th	O
:	O
1789	O
I	O
have	O
waited	O
for	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
a	O
Frank	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Madam	O
,	O
or	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
many	O
Days	O
in	O
returning	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Letter	O
,	O
&	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
Joy	O
at	O
the	O
good	O
account	O
it	O
contained	O
of	O
those	O
most	O
dear	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
exceeding	O
glad	O
that	O
Miss	B-pers
A	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
has	O
found	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
his	O
troublesome	O
complaint	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
the	O
Soap	O
Pills	O
will	O
keep	O
off	O
any	O
return	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
conceive	O
your	O
little	O
Girl	O
grows	O
every	O
Day	O
more	O
&	O
more	O
amusing	O
&	O
engaging	O
,	O
Children	O
of	O
understanding	O
,	O
are	O
at	O
her	O
Age	O
delightful	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
more	O
to	O
their	O
affectionate	O
Parents	O
!	O
who	O
besides	O
the	O
Love	O
&	O
regard	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
have	O
constant	O
opportunities	O
of	O
observing	O
all	O
their	O
little	O
enchanting	O
ways	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
wonderfully	O
their	O
young	O
Minds	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
Obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
congratulations	O
on	O
our	O
dearest	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
recovery	O
,	O
which	O
thank	O
God	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
all	O
who	O
attended	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
wished	O
,	O
Elizth	B-pers
:	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
youngest	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
thrives	O
fast	O
,	O
sweet	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
chatters	O
away	O
like	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
Towards	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Octor	O
:	O
our	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
was	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
disorder	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
which	O
pulled	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
dread	O
the	O
consequences	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
our	O
unspeakable	O
Joy	O
&	O
amazement	O
he	O
is	O
better	O
now	O
than	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
Constitution	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
turn	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
off	O
Laudanum	O
,	O
&	O
Sleeps	O
well	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
takes	O
no	O
Medicines	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
,	O
except	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
of	O
Rhubarb	O
,	O
Eats	O
very	O
tolerably	O
,	O
has	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
of	O
those	O
dreadful	O
irritations	O
,	O
can	O
enter	O
into	O
conversation	O
,	O
&	O
listen	O
to	O
reading	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
difference	O
for	O
the	O
worse	O
is	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
weakneſs	O
in	O
the	O
Limbs	O
which	O
prevents	O
his	O
rising	O
from	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
or	O
walking	O
when	O
up	O
,	O
without	O
some	O
aſsistance	O
he	O
Dines	O
alone	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
help	O
'd	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
stiffneſs	O
of	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
constantly	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
an	O
apartment	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
,	O
&	O
really	O
has	O
suffered	O
as	O
little	O
from	O
the	O
intense	O
cold	O
of	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
far	O
leſs	O
than	O
my	O
poor	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
never	O
goes	O
out	O
,	O
is	O
seldom	O
without	O
pain	O
in	O
Head	O
or	O
Stomach	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
hitherto	O
brave	O
all	O
Weather	O
,	O
&	O
unleſs	O
when	O
Snow	O
is	O
falling	O
,	O
never	O
miſs	O
a	O
charming	O
Walk	O
in	O
Wood	O
or	O
Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Publick	O
Calamity	O
is	O
too	O
dreadful	O
a	O
Subject	O
to	O
dwell	O
upon	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
any	O
one	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
private	O
distreſs	O
it	O
also	O
occasions	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
greatest	O
commiseration	O
for	O
the	O
unhappy	O
sufferers	O
,	O
the	O
Politicks	O
are	O
too	O
intricate	O
for	O
my	O
discernment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heartily	O
joyn	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
wishing	O
the	O
steps	O
taken	O
,	O
may	O
tend	O
to	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
parties	O
concerned	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
Ld	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
would	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
her	O
dear	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Measles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
most	O
favourably	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Boys	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
enjoying	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
her	O
beloved	O
William	B-pers
at	O
Little	B-place
Grove	I-place
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
distreſs	O
at	O
present	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
youngest	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
Obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
inclosed	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
curious	O
Manuscript	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
place	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
must	O
by	O
your	O
description	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
extensive	O
a	O
Forrest	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
many	O
beautiful	O
Ridings	O
can	O
not	O
fail	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
effect	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Sister	O
to	O
offer	O
their	O
best	O
&	O
kindest	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
accept	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
most	O
sincerely	O
,	O
&	O
Affectionately	O
Your	O
's	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
PS	O
Twenty	O
kiſses	O
to	O
your	O
sweet	O
Girl	O
.	O
