TOKEN	NE
James	O
street	O
.	O
Weſtminſter	B-place
.	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1778	O
My	O
deareſt	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
that	O
thurſday	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
of	O
reſigning	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
upon	O
his	O
recovery	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
five	O
mornings	O
to	O
viſit	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
regularly	O
diſappointed	O
by	O
some	O
notice	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
requiring	O
my	O
attendance	O
in	O
another	O
quarter	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
depriv	O
'd	O
of	O
yeſterday	O
morning	O
,	O
much	O
leſs	O
of	O
this	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
inauſpicious	O
demons	O
interpoſ	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
irreſiſtible	O
obſtruction	O
,	O
&	O
compell	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pour	O
out	O
my	O
affection	O
upon	O
paper	O
,	O
never	O
with	O
reluctance	O
before	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
earneſt	O
deſire	O
of	O
addreſsing	O
Miranda	B-pers
with	O
my	O
perſon	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
with	O
my	O
pen	O
after	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
abſence	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
friends	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
knowing	O
,	O
as	O
eye	O
witneſses	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
conſolation	O
,	O
moſt	O
kindly	O
gave	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ſuggeſted	O
my	O
full	O
juſtification	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pilgrim	O
's	O
progreſs	O
from	O
that	O
paſsage	O
,	O
where	O
Chriſtian	B-pers
's	O
companion	O
after	O
many	O
disappointments	O
,	O
difficulties	O
&	O
delays	O
arriv	O
'd	O
at	O
laſt	O
to	O
his	O
long	O
wiſh	O
'd	O
-for	O
object	O
,	O
still	O
Faithf	O
ul	O
as	O
ever	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
compare	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
to	O
Chriſtian	B-pers
himſelf	O
in	O
a	O
ſtate	O
of	O
deſpondency	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
cold	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
with	O
relaxation	O
from	O
ye	O
late	O
intenſe	O
heat	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
,	O
nor	O
wanting	O
her	O
share	O
of	O
buſineſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
leave	O
her	O
to	O
explain	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
meets	O
you	O
again	O
with	O
more	O
ardour	O
,	O
than	O
can	O
be	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
salutation	O
by	O
letter	O
.	O
Though	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
expected	O
succeſs	O
of	O
my	O
apology	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
vex	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
soul	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
inſtead	O
of	O
writing	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
Miranda	B-pers
's	O
Moſt	O
faithful	O
&	O
affectionate	O
R	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
