TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
presents	O
his	O
Complements	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
begs	O
her	O
to	O
accept	O
his	O
sincerest	O
thanks	O
for	O
her	O
kind	O
note	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
obliging	O
enquiries	O
about	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
felt	O
himself	O
much	O
distreſsed	O
to	O
know	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
should	O
expreſs	O
his	O
gratitude	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
for	O
being	O
so	O
gracious	O
as	O
to	O
prescribe	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
this	O
morning	O
releived	O
from	O
his	O
anxiety	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
fortune	O
to	O
be	O
honoured	O
with	O
a	O
q	O
uarter	O
of	O
an	O
hours	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
at	O
Kew	B-place
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
breakfasting	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
last	O
week	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
friend	O
&	O
Collegue	O
begs	O
his	O
Comps	O
:	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Kew	B-place
.	O
Oct	O
:	O
22	O
.	O
1781	O
