TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
How	O
agreeably	O
did	O
you	O
deceive	O
me	O
with	O
your	O
welcome	O
Billet	O
--	O
others	O
deceive	O
to	O
injure	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
to	O
please	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
indebted	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Book	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
troublesome	O
for	O
--	O
besides	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
you	O
only	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
indulged	O
by	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
consequence	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
read	O
your	O
disjoined	O
Paper	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
offer	O
of	O
Rollin	O
from	O
our	O
Leonidas	B-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
his	O
Poem	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Heroes	O
of	O
the	O
Athenaid	O
--	O
when	O
shall	O
we	O
enjoy	O
That	O
together	O
?	O
Caterina	B-pers
says	O
Miranda	B-pers
expects	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
motive	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
this	O
--	O
shall	O
it	O
be	O
such	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
excuse	O
its	O
dullneſs	O
--	O
in	O
wha	O
t	O
new	O
Words	O
shall	O
I	O
expreſs	O
--	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
how	O
greatly	O
I	O
esteem	O
Miranda	B-pers
Miss	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
James	O
Street	O
Westminster	B-place
