TOKEN	NE
Holbrooke	B-place
Wed	O
:	O
Morg	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
April	O
1795	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
came	O
here	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
four	O
yesterday	O
&	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
friendly	O
reception	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
quite	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
her	O
fine	O
Boy	O
--	O
On	O
Monday	O
we	O
walked	O
out	O
at	O
ten	O
OClock	O
Mr	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Lathkill	B-place
&	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
Bakewell	B-place
Meadows	I-place
where	O
I	O
fished	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
--	O
the	O
old	O
pract	O
it	O
ioner	O
shewed	O
me	O
how	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
line	O
&	O
I	O
very	O
soon	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
at	O
which	O
I	O
g	O
i	O
ve	O
a	O
strong	O
pluck	O
--	O
the	O
man	O
rubbed	O
his	O
hands	O
&	O
laughed	O
heartily	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
fool	O
&	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
fish	O
had	O
kept	O
his	O
hold	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
thrown	O
him	O
as	O
high	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
as	O
Bakewell	B-place
Steeple	O
--	O
I	O
improved	O
upon	O
the	O
hint	O
&	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
short	O
of	O
my	O
story	O
)	O
,	O
caught	O
in	O
a	O
capital	O
Style	O
fifteen	O
fish	O
--	O
ten	O
Graylings	O
--	O
two	O
trouts	O
&	O
three	O
Salmon	O
trouts	O
--	O
9	O
were	O
takable	O
fish	O
&	O
6	O
were	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Stream	O
.	O
with	O
proper	O
admonitions	O
&	O
friendly	O
advice	O
not	O
to	O
trust	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
appear	O
ance	O
,	O
We	O
dined	O
at	O
4	O
--	O
6	O
were	O
invited	O
,	O
5	O
red	O
hot	O
Democrats	O
&	O
we	O
played	O
at	O
Cards	O
till	O
past	O
eleven	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
breakfast	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
yesterdays	O
party	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
small	O
collection	O
of	O
Medals	O
&	O
Coins	O
--	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
an	O
Antiquary	O
--	O
unluckily	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
upon	O
busineſs	O
&	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
minutes	O
but	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
his	O
collection	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
as	O
Birch	B-pers
had	O
promised	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
to	O
Rowter	B-place
at	O
a	O
certain	O
hour	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
returned	O
&	O
we	O
set	O
off	O
but	O
unluckily	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Haddon	B-place
the	O
rain	O
came	O
on	O
--	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
Bakewell	B-place
&	O
I	O
jogged	O
on	O
to	O
Matlock	B-place
--	O
I	O
gave	O
up	O
seeing	O
the	O
druidical	O
temple	O
till	O
another	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
affronted	O
that	O
no	O
credit	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
my	O
Succeſs	O
in	O
fishing	O
as	O
every	O
body	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
many	O
Whi	B-pers
had	O
hooked	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
how	O
many	O
the	O
Baby	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
flattered	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
a	O
general	O
Acknowledgment	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
succeſsful	O
a	O
Coup	O
d'eſsai	O
known	O
th	O
ere	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
Kershaw	B-pers
fishing	O
there	O
--	O
this	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
mind	O
that	O
my	O
Arm	O
aches	O
grievously	O
still	O
--	O
Miſs	O
Pretty	O
face	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Derby	B-place
at	O
9	O
OClock	O
&	O
will	O
take	O
this	O
letter	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
Bradshaw	B-pers
tells	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
p	O
air	O
of	O
hawks	O
sold	O
in	O
this	O
Neighborhood	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
since	O
tha	O
t	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
suited	O
my	O
father	O
exactly	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
dreſs	O
&	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
Therefore	O
good	O
morrow	O
to	O
yr	O
night	O
Cap	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
ma	O
tres	O
chere	O
Votre	O
J.D——	B-pers
--	O
Love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
c	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchester	B-place
