TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
26	O
th	O
.	O
Sept	O
.	O
1782	O
Highly	O
grateful	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
my	O
Dear	O
Uncle	O
for	O
the	O
Affectionate	O
proof	O
of	O
your	O
regard	O
on	O
your	O
recollection	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
so	O
melancholy	O
a	O
Season	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
shock	O
'd	O
and	O
afflicted	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
immediate	O
acknowledgment	O
to	O
your	O
letter	O
--	O
I	O
mourn	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
with	O
ye	O
.	O
sincerest	O
sorrow	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
liveliest	O
gratitude	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
consideration	O
she	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
even	O
from	O
my	O
earliest	O
days	O
of	O
recollection	O
,	O
I	O
weep	O
also	O
for	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
I	O
loved	O
from	O
inclination	O
,	O
&	O
whom	O
I	O
admired	O
&	O
esteem	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Virtues	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Sir	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
judge	O
what	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
fully	O
sensible	O
how	O
irreparable	O
is	O
the	O
loſs	O
You	O
have	O
Sustain	O
'd	O
.	O
“	O
The	O
Death	O
of	O
real	O
and	O
Virtuous	O
friends	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
heaviest	O
trials	O
of	O
this	O
Uncertain	O
World	O
,	O
But	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
delightful	O
consolation	O
when	O
they	O
leave	O
us	O
poſseſs	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
our	O
Esteem	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
our	O
thoughts	O
can	O
follow	O
them	O
with	O
joyful	O
hopes	O
of	O
their	O
complete	O
happineſs	O
.	O
”	O
Source	O
not	O
yet	O
traced	O
.	O
This	O
consolation	O
is	O
Yours	O
--	O
this	O
comfort	O
You	O
have	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
support	O
you	O
to	O
bear	O
properly	O
the	O
deprivation	O
of	O
a	O
happineſs	O
in	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
deservedly	O
dear	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
have	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
upon	O
this	O
Melancholy	O
Subject	O
,	O
they	O
spoke	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
highest	O
terms	O
of	O
Commendation	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
letters	O
You	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
read	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
how	O
much	O
they	O
felt	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
May	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
hint	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
me	O
happy	O
by	O
answering	O
this	O
)	O
that	O
You	O
will	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
interested	O
themselves	O
in	O
Your	O
Affliction	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
request	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
refuse	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
any	O
persons	O
coming	O
to	O
England	B-place
something	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
valued	O
friend	O
--	O
indulge	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
Weakneſs	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Weakneſs	O
,	O
An	O
old	O
letter	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
drawing	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
will	O
content	O
me	O
--	O
never	O
shall	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
reminded	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
poſseſs	O
something	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Sir	O
,	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
entreat	O
the	O
continuance	O
of	O
your	O
affection	O
I	O
will	O
ever	O
endeavour	O
to	O
deserve	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
Esteem	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
Respect	O
&	O
true	O
Affection	O
Your	O
Neice	O
&	O
Friend	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
If	O
you	O
write	O
soon	O
,	O
direct	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
otherwise	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
I	O
imagine	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
their	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
have	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Affliction	O
of	O
losing	O
their	O
last	O
Child	O
--	O
