TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Nobody	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
Sensible	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
kind	O
Attentions	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
set	O
a	O
higher	O
Value	O
on	O
the	O
Motive	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
the	O
Goodneſs	O
of	O
yr	O
heart	O
;	O
the	O
greatest	O
mark	O
of	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
can	O
shew	O
me	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
yourself	O
,	O
by	O
wch	O
.	O
means	O
I	O
shall	O
the	O
sooner	O
have	O
an	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
renewing	O
the	O
happy	O
Connexion	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
are	O
engaged	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Majesties	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
yr	O
Regret	O
about	O
being	O
deprived	O
so	O
long	O
from	O
attending	O
yr	O
Duty	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
exprest	O
great	O
Concern	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
&	O
hopes	O
that	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
re-establish	O
yr	O
health	O
that	O
was	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
&	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
a	O
very	O
proper	O
Step	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Princeſses	O
all	O
send	O
their	O
Love	O
.	O
&	O
now	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
must	O
repeat	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
you	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
uneasy	O
abt	O
.	O
my	O
Attendance	O
;	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
,	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
is	O
above	O
Stairs	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
future	O
Ones	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
flatter	O
myself	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
many	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
two	O
weekly	O
pay	O
to	O
lose	O
,	O
as	O
very	O
probably	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
's	O
Stay	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
vastly	O
well	O
&	O
Sets	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Pſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
make	O
the	O
Partie	O
quarrée	O
.	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
C.Finch	B-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
