TOKEN	NE
St.	B-place
Petersb	I-place
:	I-place
g	I-place
1	O
n	O
.	O
s	O
.	O
Janry	O
177	O
0	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
a	O
Meſsenger	O
going	O
to	O
London	B-place
to	O
wish	O
you	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Daughter	O
,	O
a	O
happy	O
New	O
year	O
and	O
better	O
health	O
than	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
I	O
wont	O
reproach	O
you	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
wont	O
allow	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
unmindful	O
of	O
my	O
Eldest	O
Brother	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
unjust	O
to	O
myself	O
did	O
I	O
give	O
room	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
appearance	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
yourself	O
forgot	O
.	O
This	O
Country	O
particularly	O
often	O
puts	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
thoughts	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
much	O
improved	O
in	O
its	O
buildgs	O
since	O
that	O
date	O
,	O
another	O
difference	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
refined	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
french	O
taste	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
;	O
drinking	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
fashion	O
but	O
E	O
ating	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
truth	O
has	O
tak	O
en	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
great	O
plenty	O
of	O
fish	O
flesh	O
&	O
fowl	O
(	O
All	O
froze	O
at	O
prest	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
every	O
thing	O
has	O
a	O
better	O
taste	O
in	O
Engd	B-place
than	O
here	O
.	O
Mutton	O
I	O
never	O
taste	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
like	O
any	O
one	O
Ruſsian	O
dainty	O
such	O
as	O
Caviar	O
Sterlit	O
are	O
but	O
witht	O
:	O
these	O
there	O
are	O
plenty	O
&	O
variety	O
sufficient	O
,	O
&	O
now	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
settled	O
&	O
have	O
all	O
our	O
Poultry	O
fatted	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
approve	O
of	O
our	O
Table	O
in	O
all	O
re	O
sp	O
ects	O
,	O
&	O
otherwise	O
of	O
our	O
House	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
streets	O
called	O
La	O
Grande	O
Mosckaie	O
.	O
Our	O
Summer	O
residence	O
is	O
lent	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
the	B-pers
G.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
it	O
was	O
built	O
&	O
laid	O
out	O
by	O
Chancellor	B-pers
Bestuchett	I-pers
&	O
is	O
in	O
an	O
Island	O
a	O
few	O
Wersts	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Petersb	I-place
:	I-place
g	I-place
Called	O
Kaminoj	B-place
Ostroff	I-place
,	O
we	O
like	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
given	O
to	O
us	O
again	O
for	O
next	O
Summer	O
.	O
The	O
Cold	O
dry	O
air	O
here	O
proves	O
specifick	O
for	O
My	O
Dear	O
Lord	O
thank	O
God	O
his	O
health	O
is	O
perfectly	O
restored	O
.	O
he	O
offers	O
you	O
his	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Complimts	O
:	O
as	O
does	O
your	O
Three	O
Nephews	O
&	O
three	B-pers
Nieces	I-pers
who	O
are	O
all	O
prodigeously	O
grown	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
so	O
far	O
forget	O
for	O
a	O
momt	O
.	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Children	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
you	O
will	O
h	O
ear	O
with	O
pleasure	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
universally	O
reckoned	O
here	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
fine	O
family	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
good	O
natured	O
Children	O
&	O
nothing	O
is	O
spared	O
for	O
their	O
Education	O
.	O
I	O
heartily	O
wiſh	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
at	O
their	O
return	O
that	O
they	O
desarve	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
Ld	B-pers
e	O
njoy	O
perfect	O
health	O
The	O
Court	O
has	O
I	O
believe	O
always	O
been	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
the	O
Empreſs	O
's	O
very	O
brilliant	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
now	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Reigning	O
Sovereign	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
finest	O
Woman	O
in	O
Every	O
distinguishing	O
quality	O
&	O
perfection	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
K	O
ingdom	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
extraordinarily	O
fortunate	O
in	O
the	O
Succeſs	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Campaign	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
probably	O
will	O
be	O
decicive	O
.	O
They	O
speak	O
here	O
upon	O
these	O
victories	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
moderation	O
.	O
I	O
sometimes	O
see	O
Genl	B-pers
Fullarton	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
your	O
Compliments	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
would	O
please	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Command	O
in	O
Petersbg	B-place
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fowel	I-pers
remembers	O
you	O
&	O
Consul	B-pers
Swallow	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
long	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
much	O
&	O
justly	O
Esteemed	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Marischal	I-pers
is	O
settled	O
with	O
the	O
K	O
of	O
Prusia	B-place
he	O
writes	O
to	O
me	O
sometimes	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Charmg	O
Old	O
man	O
&	O
as	O
lively	O
as	O
at	O
forty	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
once	O
more	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
yourself	O
&	O
family	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
your	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Sister	O
&	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
.	O
J.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
