TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
June	O
16	O
th	O
:	O
1775	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
always	O
in	O
my	O
Penitentials	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
worst	O
Correspondent	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deserve	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
this	O
makes	O
me	O
quite	O
asham	O
'd	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
whenever	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
favour	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
you	O
'	O
l	O
say	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ought	O
immediatly	O
to	O
set	O
about	O
answering	O
it	O
.	O
very	O
true	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
added	O
ingratitude	O
to	O
neglect	O
in	O
not	O
returning	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
yourself	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
great	O
Civilities	O
to	O
Jack	B-pers
,	O
&	O
the	O
good	O
Opinion	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
entertain	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
a	O
Dutiful	O
good	O
Lad	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
continue	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
a	O
comfort	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
the	O
Notice	O
you	O
took	O
of	O
him	O
made	O
full	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
Mortifications	O
he	O
sufferd	O
from	O
other	O
circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
Visit	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
.	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
length	O
return	O
'd	O
full	O
of	O
Acknowledgements	O
for	O
your	O
Politeneſs	O
&	O
Hospitality	O
.	O
&	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
his	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
in	O
this	O
Frank	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
inclose	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
has	O
happend	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
uneasineſs	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
tenderneſs	O
in	O
your	O
disposition	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
thought	O
on	O
this	O
occation	O
that	O
the	O
lot	O
of	O
human	O
Happineſs	O
is	O
more	O
equally	O
dispens	O
'd	O
than	O
People	O
generally	O
I	O
m	O
agine	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
dull	O
&	O
insensible	O
tho	O
'	O
incapable	O
of	O
the	O
refined	O
pleasures	O
of	O
friendship	O
do	O
at	O
least	O
paſs	O
through	O
the	O
World	O
with	O
more	O
ease	O
to	O
themselves	O
,	O
than	O
they	O
whose	O
delicate	O
sensibilities	O
make	O
them	O
so	O
deeply	O
affected	O
with	O
the	O
loſs	O
o	O
r	O
distreſs	O
of	O
every	O
Friend	O
in	O
a	O
World	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
opportunities	O
to	O
grieve	O
than	O
to	O
rejoyce	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
look	O
'd	O
among	O
my	O
old	O
Friend	O
s	O
Letters	O
since	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
send	O
you	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
utterly	O
incapable	O
of	O
drawing	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
tho	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
always	O
wishd	O
I	O
coud	O
have	O
been	O
Mrs	O
:	O
of	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Talent	O
that	O
way	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
exert	O
&	O
improve	O
it	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
both	O
entertaining	O
&	O
useful	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
very	O
sultry	O
hot	O
Weather	O
which	O
disagrees	O
with	O
me	O
exceſsively	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
very	O
lame	O
&	O
poorly	O
at	O
prest	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
moderate	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
better	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
joynes	O
me	O
in	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
good	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
yourself	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
me	O
Your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
are	O
removing	O
so	O
fa	O
r	O
off	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
give	O
me	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
had	O
fixd	O
yourselves	O
agreeably	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Lawton	I-pers
be	O
returnd	O
from	O
London	B-place
I	O
shoud	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
favour	O
(	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
)	O
that	O
you	O
give	O
leave	O
for	O
your	O
Servt	O
:	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
inclos	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
