TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dst	O
I	O
am	O
hurt	O
to	O
find	O
by	O
your	O
Letter	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
hurt	O
by	O
the	O
little	O
you	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
is	O
but	O
too	O
t	O
rue	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
my	O
Own	O
appearances	O
very	O
often	O
are	O
deceitful	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
it	O
will	O
prove	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
forgive	O
me	O
if	O
unasked	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
Advice	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
by	O
any	O
method	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
wound	O
your	O
delicacy	O
,	O
bring	O
on	O
an	O
Eclairſsiment	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
Friend	O
sufficiently	O
acquainted	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
beleive	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
kn	O
ew	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
would	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
by	O
experience	O
,	O
what	O
misery	O
is	O
undergone	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
explanation	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
done	O
at	O
first	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
meet	O
do	O
not	O
look	O
displeased	O
,	O
for	O
conscious	O
himself	O
of	O
having	O
acted	O
unkindly	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
him	O
fear	O
to	O
aproach	O
when	O
perhaps	O
if	O
you	O
lay	O
aside	O
the	O
Female	O
Pride	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
on	O
these	O
ocaſsions	O
are	O
is	O
always	O
misplaced	O
)	O
he	O
will	O
venture	O
to	O
speak	O
&	O
own	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
wrong	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
I	O
again	O
my	O
Dst	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
pardon	O
this	O
Liberty	O
,	O
it	O
proceeds	O
from	O
a	O
Heart	O
that	O
knows	O
the	O
feelings	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
knows	O
its	O
worth	O
,	O
&	O
wishes	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
--	O
Indeed	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
conscious	O
of	O
shewing	O
a	O
preference	O
by	O
having	O
given	O
my	O
Picture	O
to	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
take	O
care	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
too	O
vain	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
kind	O
reproaches	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
Amour	O
propre	O
enough	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Picture	O
unasked	O
,	O
&	O
last	O
Summer	O
(	O
or	O
rather	O
Autumn	O
)	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Profile	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
time	O
to	O
sit	O
for	O
,	O
&	O
upon	O
her	O
liking	O
my	O
Picture	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
has	O
,	O
&	O
expreſs	O
ing	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
a	O
Copy	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
now	O
my	O
Dear	O
if	O
you	O
wish	O
such	O
a	O
Phiz	O
as	O
mine	O
should	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
yr	O
Apartment	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
desire	O
Mrs	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
to	O
have	O
it	O
copied	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
present	O
in	O
g	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
thinks	O
P	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
fractious	O
&	O
spoilt	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
bel	O
ie	O
ve	O
Monday	O
Afternoon	O
in	O
the	O
Phaet	O
on	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
opinion	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
more	O
then	O
once	O
what	O
a	O
reasonable	O
little	O
Creature	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
this	O
Morg	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Cowper	I-pers
s	O
every	O
thing	O
one	O
could	O
wish	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
she	O
would	O
ever	O
be	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
unmixed	O
,	O
&	O
seen	O
what	O
she	O
really	O
is	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dst	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
for	O
yr	O
kind	O
intentions	O
of	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
unreasonable	O
as	O
to	O
expect	O
it	O
often	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
with	O
the	B-pers
Dartrys	I-pers
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
certainly	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
kind	O
Compts	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
beg	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
wont	O
be	O
many	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
Embrace	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Q	O
House	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
now	O
cordially	O
in	O
Idea	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Wednes	O
day	O
Night	O
--	O
