TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
21	O
st	O
Octr	O
1771	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
As	O
Mr	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
&	O
very	O
buſsie	O
since	O
his	O
return	O
till	O
this	O
day	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
procure	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
dellivred	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
was	O
agreeably	O
surprized	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
no	O
time	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
as	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
&	O
answer	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
dated	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
(	O
a	O
day	O
beffore	O
yours	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
wrote	O
)	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
Annual	O
Rent	O
due	O
from	O
the	O
Estate	O
here	O
&	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Pappers	O
nor	O
Coppy	O
's	O
of	O
Pappers	O
bellongeing	O
either	O
to	O
yourself	O
or	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Original	O
Pappers	O
haveing	O
been	O
transmitted	O
by	O
my	O
Br	O
:	O
&	O
Sister	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
to	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
at	O
least	O
given	O
to	O
your	O
Father	O
or	O
Mother	O
by	O
them	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
likewise	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
since	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
further	O
remains	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
soon	O
how	O
you	O
all	O
both	O
do	O
:	O
&	O
should	O
most	O
sincearly	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
ev'ry	O
thing	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
aimacably	O
setled	O
&	O
evry	O
thing	O
fixed	O
to	O
yr	O
wishes	O
.	O
in	O
all	O
events	O
be	O
asured	O
that	O
both	O
you	O
and	O
her	O
have	O
our	O
kindest	O
good	O
Wishes	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
yr	O
Young	O
Cousins	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectly	O
remembred	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
bellieve	O
me	O
ever	O
Sincearly	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
I	O
'm	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Frank	O
to	O
send	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
whenever	O
I	O
can	O
procure	O
any	O
--	O
