TOKEN	NE
Bedford	O
Row	O
Augst	O
:	O
14	O
th	O
:	O
1801	O
It	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
since	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
to	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
that	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
ashamed	O
of	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
now	O
&	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
very	O
shabby	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
now	O
get	O
any	O
other	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
now	O
this	O
day	O
than	O
delay	O
it	O
any	O
longer	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
lately	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
has	O
.	O
I	O
rec	O
'd	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
affecte	O
.	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
when	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
at	O
Bromley	B-place
&	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
Leighton	O
Hse	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
very	O
very	O
happy	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
to	O
accept	O
it	O
&	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
much	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
time	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
en	I-pers
has	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
visit	O
you	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
down	O
:	O
to	O
morrow	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
:	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
fixed	O
for	O
my	O
marriage	O
.	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
present	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
remember	O
with	O
pleasure	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
such	O
an	O
awful	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
very	O
anxious	O
&	O
uncomfortable	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
indeed	O
am	O
certain	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
your	O
good	O
wishes	O
:	O
indeed	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
most	O
gratefully	O
remember	O
the	O
many	O
kindneſses	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
pray	O
give	O
my	O
best	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
:	O
I	O
quite	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
most	O
affecte	O
.	O
&	O
sincerely	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Fanny	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
kind	O
love	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
begs	O
I	O
will	O
remember	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
I	O
leave	O
Bedford	O
Row	O
this	O
evening	O
:	O
tomorrow	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Trowbridge	B-place
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
disappointed	O
in	O
the	O
wish	O
I	O
have	O
formed	O
of	O
finding	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
some	O
one	O
of	O
yr	O
:	O
family	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
Bromley	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
hardly	O
merit	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
soon	O
again	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
imag	O
ine	O
the	O
hurry	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
&	O
there	O
fore	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
is	O
needleſs	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
apology	O
for	O
suc	O
h	O
a	O
scrawl	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
's	O
kind	O
Compts	O
.	O
&	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morriſon	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
single	O
