TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
of	O
yr-	O
kind	O
enquiries	O
yesterdy	O
&	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
any	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
fear	O
it	O
is	O
lost	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
forwarded	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Malvern	B-place
&	O
Worcester	B-place
since	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
better	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
free	O
from	O
Pain	O
or	O
shortneſs	O
of	O
Breath	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
so	O
gracious	O
as	O
to	O
allow	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Morg	O
before	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
fatigue	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
by	O
by	O
care	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
on	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
old	O
a	O
Complaint	O
as	O
mine	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
get	O
quite	O
rid	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
will	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
yr-	O
Friends	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
know	O
would	O
send	O
many	O
kind	O
wishes	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Sincerely	O
Yr-	O
M	B-pers
C	I-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Tuesdy	O
Morg	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bullstrode	B-place
