TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
Febry	O
5	O
th	O
1773	O
Indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
am	O
Coverd	O
with	O
Confusion	O
by	O
receiving	O
a	O
Second	O
Letter	O
beffore	O
I	O
had	O
thankt	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
:	O
but	O
am	O
Happy	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
has	O
explained	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
real	O
meaning	O
of	O
my	O
Sillence	O
--	O
be	O
asured	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
requisite	O
to	O
remind	O
me	O
of	O
those	O
whose	O
Ideas	O
so	O
often	O
&	O
so	O
agreeably	O
present	O
themselves	O
as	O
yours	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
do	O
to	O
my	O
Mind	O
but	O
realy	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
's	O
absence	O
I	O
have	O
scarce	O
one	O
Moment	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Command	O
;	O
when	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
devoted	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
Correspondant	O
but	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
presume	O
on	O
yr	O
Indulgence	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
content	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
all	O
my	O
failings	O
&	O
Modestly	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
indulge	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
Letters	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
a	O
Priveledge	O
we	O
Matrons	O
claim	O
from	O
our	O
Unmarried	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
Happy	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
Much	O
recovred	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
persuade	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
an	O
Aſsignation	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
wt	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
next	O
May	O
which	O
I	O
'm	O
certain	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
:	O
&	O
make	O
him	O
Happy	O
thank	O
God	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
yr	O
young	O
friends	O
are	O
all	O
Well	O
these	O
of	O
yr	O
Acquaintance	O
beg	O
me	O
to	O
asure	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
their	O
constant	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Remembrance	O
of	O
all	O
yr	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
them	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
but	O
realy	O
I	O
'm	O
jelous	O
the	O
only	O
comfort	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
admires	O
you	O
both	O
so	O
much	O
&	O
fills	O
his	O
letters	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
both	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
his	O
affections	O
are	O
Divided	O
&	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
my	O
third	O
share	O
were	O
it	O
all	O
Center	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Object	O
:	O
the	O
affair	O
would	O
realy	O
be	O
too	O
Serious	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
think	O
Mr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
an	O
agreeable	O
adition	O
to	O
yr	O
Society	O
&	O
that	O
his	O
Spiritts	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
improved	O
:	O
I	O
Envy	O
him	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
agreeably	O
Situated	O
as	O
to	O
enjoy	O
a	O
Society	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
so	O
often	O
wish	O
in	O
Vain	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
do	O
?	O
I	O
fear	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
enjoy	O
much	O
Health	O
or	O
Happineſs	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
!	O
if	O
our	O
next	O
accounts	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
are	O
not	O
better	O
than	O
those	O
received	O
Last	O
Post	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
make	O
both	O
his	O
Son	O
&	O
me	O
dilletory	O
Correspondants	O
but	O
if	O
so	O
impute	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
cause	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
any	O
failure	O
in	O
that	O
affectionate	O
Regard	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
be	O
My	O
Dear	O
Francis	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	I-pers
6th	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
s	O
Most	O
Sinceare	O
Friend	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Miss	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
most	O
Affect	O
respects	O
ever	O
attend	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
I	O
'm	O
quite	O
Vext	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
no	O
Franks	O
