TOKEN	NE
Wandsworth	O
hill	O
Augst	O
.	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
A	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Letter	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
goes	O
on	O
vastly	O
well	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
these	O
two	O
last	O
days	O
&	O
continues	O
nursing	O
her	O
Boy	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
she	O
begs	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
duty	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
for	O
so	O
graciously	O
enquiring	O
after	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
prudent	O
&	O
takes	O
great	O
care	O
of	O
herself	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
otherwise	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
any	O
check	O
upon	O
her	O
for	O
I	O
dont	O
believe	O
she	O
has	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
opinion	O
of	O
my	O
matronly	O
care	O
as	O
my	O
good	O
friends	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
highly	O
flattered	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
civil	O
things	O
contained	O
in	O
your	O
Letter	O
and	O
Postcript	O
concerning	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
only	O
wish	O
I	O
deserved	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
quite	O
easy	O
about	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
for	O
she	O
is	O
amazingly	O
well	O
&	O
so	O
tractable	O
that	O
she	O
readily	O
submits	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
Nurse	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
orders	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
accept	O
the	O
sincere	O
good	O
wishes	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
friends	O
at	O
Wandsworth	B-place
--	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yr	O
.	O
very	O
affecte	O
.	O
Elizath	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
Be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
and	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
yesterday	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
who	O
says	O
she	O
intends	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
--	O
