TOKEN	NE
Oakford	B-place
1	O
Sepr	O
.	O
13	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
9	O
from	O
Wellington	B-place
&	O
got	O
here	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
and	O
am	O
shook	O
almost	O
to	O
a	O
Jelly	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
Devonshire	B-place
Roads	O
but	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
Conception	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
&	O
felt	O
them	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
be	O
worse	O
&	O
so	O
narrow	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
sometimes	O
difficult	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Arrangement	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
single	O
horse	O
paſs	O
--	O
the	O
side	O
W	O
indows	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
down	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Boughs	O
from	O
breaking	O
them	O
&	O
in	O
hot	O
weather	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
particularly	O
pleasant	O
as	O
they	O
enter	O
the	O
Carriage	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
--	O
just	O
now	O
it	O
is	O
rather	O
amusing	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
gather	O
Nuts	O
without	O
any	O
trouble	O
--	O
On	O
one	O
Occasion	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
smiling	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Lady	O
on	O
Horseback	O
with	O
a	O
Gentn	O
.	O
behind	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
without	O
remarked	O
the	O
difficulty	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
without	O
a	O
constant	O
Res	O
traint	O
traint	O
must	O
natur	O
ally	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
Dame	O
's	O
Lap	O
--	O
I	O
merely	O
write	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
paſsed	O
17	O
Miles	O
of	O
the	O
Devonshire	B-place
X	O
Country	O
Roads	O
in	O
a	O
Chaise	O
and	O
am	O
alive	O
after	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
my	O
hand	O
shakes	O
but	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
remedied	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
me	O
wh-	O
great	O
Cordiality	O
--	O
James	B-pers
is	O
out	O
--	O
&	O
Margt	B-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
on	O
her	O
Way	O
from	O
The	O
Hays	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
no	O
Saturday	O
--	O
Friday	O
is	O
no	O
post	O
Most	O
Affy	O
Yrs	O
.	O
JD	B-pers
At	O
Wellington	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
neat	O
Town	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
Squirrel	O
where	O
I	O
sojourned	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Turnspit	O
They	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
old	O
Custom	O
--	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Terrier	O
is	O
the	O
Officiator	O
--	O
He	O
seemed	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
his	O
Abilities	O
&	O
is	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
when	O
his	O
Services	O
are	O
wanted	O
&	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
he	O
likes	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
catching	O
Rats	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
delightful	O
day	O
--	O
no	O
Sun	O
&	O
very	O
warm	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
seen	O
two	O
bad	O
crops	O
of	O
Wheat	O
all	O
the	O
journey	O
--	O
Barley	O
is	O
the	O
finest	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
known	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
--	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
