TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
unavoidably	O
detain	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
illneſs	O
of	O
my	O
Curate	O
till	O
yesterday	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
prevented	O
from	O
acquitting	O
myself	O
to	O
you	O
sooner	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
excuse	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
at	O
Stanton	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
my	O
Living	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
;	O
a	O
very	O
tolerable	O
House	O
,	O
now	O
well	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
excellent	O
Offices	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
a	O
charming	O
Country	O
with	O
very	O
good	O
Roads	O
,	O
&	O
Post	O
Coaches	O
from	O
London	B-place
daily	O
paſsing	O
by	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
well	O
with	O
your	O
Works	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
favorable	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
other	O
respects	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
is	O
well	O
as	O
also	O
my	O
little	O
God	O
Daughter	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
sincere	O
regard	O
&	O
esteem	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
--	O
249	O
April	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
.	O
Enclosing	O
a	O
Bank	O
Post	O
Bill	O
for	O
£25.0.0	O
from	O
Meſsrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ransom	I-pers
Morland	I-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
4950	O
dated	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1790	O
.	O
