TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
You	O
really	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
justice	O
in	O
supposing	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
gain	O
'd	O
ground	O
upon	O
my	O
affection	O
;	O
I	O
now	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
behavior	O
and	O
unreserved	O
confidence	O
have	O
completely	O
rivetted	O
my	O
regard	O
and	O
love	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
above	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
leaning	O
upon	O
your	O
interest	O
whatever	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
you	O
ever	O
receive	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
smallest	O
hint	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
any	O
views	O
from	O
that	O
quarter	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
noble	O
sentiments	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
your	O
heart	O
that	O
poſseſses	O
so	O
much	O
sensibility	O
and	O
so	O
thorough	O
a	O
contempt	O
for	O
all	O
sordid	O
considerations	O
;	O
if	O
my	O
own	O
will	O
not	O
bear	O
this	O
test	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
for	O
your	O
purpose	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
proud	O
enough	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
will	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
indisposition	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
;	O
your	O
undergoing	O
so	O
much	O
fatigue	O
on	O
their	O
accounts	O
,	O
will	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
be	O
esteem	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
return	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
for	O
their	O
affection	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
be	O
laying	O
up	O
a	O
a	O
further	O
stock	O
of	O
merit	O
where	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
properly	O
estimated	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
constitution	O
does	O
not	O
suffer	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
pity	O
you	O
for	O
these	O
fatigues	O
;	O
independency	O
obtained	O
by	O
your	O
your	O
own	O
labor	O
and	O
merit	O
will	O
be	O
vastly	O
more	O
satisfactory	O
than	O
a	O
philosophical	O
contentment	O
in	O
too	O
contracted	O
a	O
situation	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
check	O
that	O
sensibility	O
from	O
which	O
you	O
feel	O
so	O
much	O
pleasure	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
already	O
surmounted	O
many	O
difficulties	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
surrounded	O
by	O
respectable	O
Friends	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
acquiring	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
convinced	O
of	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
additional	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
perceive	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
inactive	O
one	O
and	O
such	O
as	O
will	O
easily	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
prospects	O
pointed	O
out	O
by	O
an	O
honorable	O
ambition	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
trite	O
observation	O
,	O
that	O
every	O
one	O
is	O
the	O
architect	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
fortune	O
;	O
your	O
plan	O
is	O
good	O
and	O
your	O
foundations	O
judiciously	O
laid	O
we	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
not	O
disappointing	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
superstructure	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
quit	O
this	O
stile	O
of	O
authority	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
good	O
advice	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
repaid	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
and	O
unask	O
'd	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
privilege	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
no	O
sooner	O
call	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
that	O
privilege	O
.	O
Captain	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
has	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
near	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
raising	O
men	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
Regiment	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Major	O
;	O
eighty	O
men	O
are	O
his	O
proportion	O
which	O
will	O
cost	O
a	O
considerable	O
sum	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
already	O
tolerably	O
succeſsful	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
supplies	O
the	O
means	O
,	O
his	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fullerton	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Col	O
.	O
Commandant	O
.	O
Captain	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
unaffected	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
fine	O
dispositions	O
--	O
we	O
make	O
no	O
comparisons	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
equally	O
disposed	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
merit	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
opportunities	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
that	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
introduce	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
to	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
W.k	I-pers
had	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
desire	O
of	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affection-te	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sackville	O
Street	O
March	O
14	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
till	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
May	O
next	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
Latour	O
.	O
