TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
Novr	O
:	O
17	O
th	O
1771	O
Yours	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
received	O
late	O
last	O
Night	O
gave	O
me	O
too	O
much	O
pleasure	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
oportunity	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
Anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
setled	O
to	O
yours	O
&	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
s	O
wishes	O
I	O
hope	O
from	O
yours	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
the	O
case	O
&	O
Sincearly	O
congratulate	O
you	O
both	O
upon	O
it	O
--	O
be	O
asured	O
it	O
gives	O
yr	O
friends	O
in	O
this	O
familly	O
the	O
sincearest	O
Pleasure	O
though	O
we	O
regreate	O
much	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Health	O
&	O
Spiritts	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
impaired	O
though	O
its	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
wonder	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
all	O
she	O
has	O
lately	O
suffer	O
'd	O
--	O
should	O
have	O
those	O
disagreeable	O
effects	O
.	O
the	O
affection	O
of	O
yr	O
Aunt	O
and	O
Uncle	B-pers
Wilm	I-pers
:	I-pers
will	O
I	O
hope	O
prove	O
as	O
Useful	O
as	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
--	O
&	O
shall	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
yr	O
saffe	O
return	O
home	O
&	O
total	O
ceſsation	O
of	O
ev'ry	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
Uneasineſs	O
!	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Eldest	O
Daughter	O
were	O
here	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
setling	O
their	O
affairs	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Edinburgh	B-place
they	O
called	O
here	O
one	O
Morning	O
beffore	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
:	O
we	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
afterwards	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
&	O
they	O
comeing	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
Act	O
:	O
of	O
his	O
Motions	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
both	O
much	O
indisposed	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
begin	O
both	O
to	O
be	O
better	O
:	O
yr	O
Cousins	O
are	O
all	O
Well	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
very	O
lately	O
from	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
our	O
best	O
compts	O
&	O
good	O
Wishes	O
ever	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
most	O
faithful	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Im	O
sorry	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
Frank	O
for	O
you	O
