TOKEN	NE
Mrs	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
Complements	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
is	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
takeing	O
the	O
trouble	O
about	O
the	O
tickets	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
lucky	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
equally	O
obliged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
wishes	O
her	O
much	O
joy	O
of	O
this	O
day	O
and	O
sorry	O
she	O
has	O
it	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
show	O
her	O
respect	O
and	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
affraid	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
wait	O
of	O
her	O
befor	O
she	O
sets	O
out	O
for	O
east	B-place
Bourn	I-place
,	O
she	O
goes	O
herself	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
to	O
Brighthelmeston	B-place
and	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
happen	O
to	O
come	O
then	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
Maddox	O
Street	O
Monday	O
