TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
Jany	O
:	O
26	O
1794	O
Dr	O
:	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Birthday	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
offered	O
up	O
my	O
prayers	O
for	O
your	O
dear	O
Child	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
(	O
if	O
it	O
please	O
God	O
)	O
She	O
may	O
see	O
your	O
many	O
happy	O
returns	O
of	O
this	O
Day	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
She	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Comfort	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
her	O
dear	O
Father	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
very	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
to	O
Day	O
for	O
the	O
Snow	O
frightens	O
us	O
away	O
lest	O
the	O
Roads	O
sd	O
:	O
be	O
blocked	O
up	O
as	O
they	O
sometimes	O
are	O
;	O
&	O
we	O
go	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
post	O
comes	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
the	O
Letters	O
are	O
given	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Pen	O
&	O
ink	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
finish	O
with	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
how	O
Affly	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
yrs	O
:	O
PC	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
sends	O
his	O
love	O
,	O
&	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
kind	O
Comps	O
.	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
beg	O
Comp	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
his	O
best	O
Respects	O
If	O
any	O
thing	O
is	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
Militia	O
in	O
our	O
Quarter	O
Ld-	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
certainly	O
subscribe	O
or	O
rather	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
--	O
but	O
pray	O
tell	O
dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H.	I-pers
M	I-pers
if	O
one	O
Guinea	O
is	O
wanted	O
&	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
given	O
Anonymous	O
--	O
if	O
she	O
will	O
give	O
one	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
punctually	O
repaid	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
very	O
dr	O
..	O
Friend	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
:	O
--	O
We	O
never	O
Travel	O
a	O
Sunday	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
I	O
hope	O
an	O
allowable	O
Neceſsity	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Alfred	O
Street	O
