TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Janry-	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
concerned	O
to	O
hear	O
read	O
so	O
bad	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Yourself	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
14	O
th	O
-	O
Instant	O
furnishes	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
accident	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
attending	O
Louisa	B-pers
in	O
her	O
dancing	O
parties	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
feel	O
much	O
inconvenience	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
an	O
Hospital	O
.	O
Five	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Measles	O
;	O
three	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
Convalescence	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
youngest	O
Boys	O
introduced	O
this	O
disorder	O
into	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
three	O
youngest	O
Girls	O
have	O
caught	O
it	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
has	O
been	O
confined	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
A	O
cold	O
&	O
Cough	O
of	O
an	O
obstinate	O
nature	O
,	O
which	O
refused	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
usual	O
remedies	O
,	O
has	O
at	O
length	O
been	O
succeeded	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
Eruption	O
over	O
her	O
Arms	O
&	O
Legs	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
entirely	O
removed	O
the	O
Cough	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
bestowing	O
a	O
new	O
skin	O
on	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
.	O
Though	O
She	O
is	O
well	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
yet	O
care	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
changeable	O
weather	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
return	O
of	O
her	O
Cold	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
permitted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
state	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
has	O
occasioned	O
my	O
remaining	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Meeting	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
had	O
Maria	B-pers
been	O
able	O
to	O
stump	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
the	O
Invalid	O
's	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
,	O
my	O
Boys	O
Tutor	O
is	O
confined	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
feverish	O
Complaint	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
increased	O
by	O
apprehension	O
.	O
Whenever	O
anything	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
grows	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
more	O
plague	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
his	O
Spirits	O
again	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
disorder	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
accounts	O
lately	O
from	O
my	O
eldest	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
cruizing	O
in	O
the	O
Mediterranean	O
.	O
My	O
second	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
cruizing	O
in	O
the	B-place
Channel	I-place
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drowned	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
conducting	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
with	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Prize	O
to	O
his	O
Frigate	O
,	O
when	O
(	O
probably	O
being	O
overloaded	O
)	O
the	O
Boat	O
sunk	O
,	O
&	O
left	O
the	O
contents	O
sprawling	O
in	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Providentially	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
the	O
Frigate	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
saved	O
.	O
My	O
Francis	B-pers
swam	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
&	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Sides	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
changed	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Boat	O
,	O
&	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Prize	O
for	O
more	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
aſsociate	O
with	O
the	O
diſsipated	O
&	O
gambling	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Community	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
Intelligence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
's	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
met	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Wynne	O
's	O
or	O
Campbell	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
party	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
.	O
His	O
character	O
was	O
notorious	O
here	O
,	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
robbed	O
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
s	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
accused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
resent	O
the	O
accusation	O
,	O
though	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
left	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
His	O
Marriage	O
did	O
not	O
induce	O
me	O
to	O
seek	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
,	O
after	O
You	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
your	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
as	O
their	O
Sister	O
in	O
Law	O
countenances	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
did	O
Lady	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
when	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
sufficient	O
reason	O
for	O
my	O
family	O
having	O
anything	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
quietly	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
happineſs	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
domestic	O
kind	O
,	O
not	O
depending	O
on	O
the	O
Gay	O
World	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
connexion	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
;	O
but	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
surprised	O
at	O
what	O
has	O
happened	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
everything	O
kind	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
and	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Lord	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
was	O
thought	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
lived	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
this	O
appearance	O
of	O
recovery	O
did	O
not	O
last	O
above	O
two	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
his	O
funeral	O
out	O
of	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
on	O
its	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
North	O
--	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Eighteenth	O
January	O
1808	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
