TOKEN	NE
To	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Birthday	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Lady	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
1807	O
I	O
use	O
the	O
Latin	O
Maria	B-pers
for	O
Mary	B-pers
Rejoice	O
;	O
my	O
Friend	O
Rejoice	O
the	O
Sun	O
appears	O
Which	O
marks	O
the	O
progreſs	O
of	O
Maria	B-pers
's	O
years	O
,	O
When	O
virtuous	O
minds	O
attain	O
an	O
age	O
mature	O
Sweet	O
is	O
the	O
pleasure	O
&	O
the	O
joy	O
is	O
pure	O
Should	O
we	O
look	O
backward	O
on	O
her	O
early	O
life	O
,	O
Great	O
is	O
the	O
merit	O
of	O
thy	O
charming	O
Wife	O
Endu	O
'd	O
with	O
powr	O
's	O
to	O
fascinate	O
mankind	O
Her	O
stedfast	O
aim	O
was	O
to	O
improve	O
her	O
mind	O
Virtue	O
&	O
Piety	O
adorn	O
'd	O
her	O
youth	O
--	O
And	O
led	O
her	O
safely	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
of	O
Truth	O
Each	O
duty	O
she	O
perform	O
'd	O
with	O
zeal	O
and	O
love	O
,	O
Her	O
Parents	O
bleſsings	O
did	O
her	O
acts	O
approve	O
,	O
Nor	O
yet	O
confin	O
d	O
within	O
a	O
circle	O
small	O
Her	O
warm	O
benevolence	O
extends	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
--	O
If	O
one	O
she	O
knows	O
is	O
wounded	O
by	O
distreſs	O
She	O
by	O
her	O
kindneſs	O
makes	O
the	O
sorrow	O
leſs	O
,	O
In	O
noble	O
friendship	O
none	O
can	O
her	O
excell	O
I	O
speak	O
who	O
feel	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
prov	O
'd	O
known	O
it	O
well	O
,	O
By	O
fire	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
gold	O
we	O
we	O
fully	O
prove	O
And	O
adverse	O
fortune	O
is	O
the	O
test	O
of	O
love	O
She	O
pour	O
'd	O
the	O
balm	O
of	O
comfort	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
And	O
chac	O
'd	O
misfortune	O
from	O
my	O
menae	O
'd	O
menac	O
'd	O
head	O
Happy	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
so	O
dear	O
a	O
Wife	O
Whose	O
smiles	O
can	O
diſsipate	O
the	O
clouds	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
Whose	O
cheerful	O
converse	O
cheats	O
the	O
tedious	O
hours	O
And	O
strews	O
the	O
thorny	O
way	O
with	O
fragrant	O
flow	O
e	O
rs	O
Oh	O
;	O
well-deserving	O
long	O
mayst	O
Thou	O
poſseſs	O
In	O
dear	O
Thy	O
Maria	B-pers
human	O
happineſs	O
--	O
Long	O
may	O
She	O
live	O
exempt	O
from	O
care	O
&	O
pain	O
And	O
in	O
Louisa	B-pers
may	O
you	O
live	O
again	O
Accept	O
the	O
cordial	O
wishes	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
whose	O
zeal	O
and	O
love	O
with	O
Life	O
alone	O
can	O
end	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenſon	I-pers
My	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
as	O
you	O
desire	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
criticize	O
your	O
elegant	O
&	O
most	O
acceptable	O
presents	O
so	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
for	O
my	O
inability	O
in	O
humbly	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
celebrate	O
your	O
Birth-day	O
but	O
my	O
desire	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
my	O
unfeigned	O
affection	O
&	O
esteem	O
dictated	O
the	O
Lines	O
on	O
this	O
sheet	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
the	O
agreeable	O
intelligence	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
&	O
invited	O
Isabella	B-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
the	O
Hare	O
in	O
honour	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
kind	O
attention	O
a-propos	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
asked	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
respecting	O
the	O
Letters	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledges	O
but	O
declines	O
all	O
writing	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
nor	O
could	O
I	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
an	O
ear	O
to	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
but	O
she	O
loves	O
&	O
esteems	O
you	O
&	O
speaks	O
of	O
you	O
with	O
pleasure	O
I	O
was	O
prevented	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
dining	O
with	O
her	O
by	O
an	O
appointment	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Leſson	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Moellor	I-pers
in	O
music	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
at	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
putting	O
him	O
off	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
Letter	O
anticipating	O
the	O
Box	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
almost	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
as	O
Cheney	B-pers
paſsed	O
through	O
&	O
came	O
in	O
perfect	O
safety	O
--	O
I	O
unpacked	O
it	O
with	O
great	O
delight	O
but	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
postpone	O
it	O
until	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
so	O
agitable	O
are	O
my	O
spirits	O
--	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
expreſs	O
the	O
sence	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
pleasing	O
instances	O
of	O
kindneſs	O
so	O
very	O
pretty	O
&	O
so	O
valuable	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
pleased	O
with	O
all	O
particularly	O
with	O
dear	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
exertions	O
to	O
please	O
Mamma	O
's	O
old	O
friend	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
Love	O
&	O
aſsure	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
inexpreſsible	O
&	O
gratitude	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
use	O
the	O
eligant	O
Gifts	O
--	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
admire	O
the	O
Gown	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prettiest	O
&	O
at	O
once	O
the	O
liveliest	O
and	O
gravest	O
thing	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
I	O
do	O
intend	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
&	O
to	O
spend	O
that	O
day	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
remember	O
you	O
all	O
return	O
my	O
sincere	O
thanks	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
thinking	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Gown	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
better	O
one	O
than	O
common	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
spending	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
learning	O
Handel	O
's	O
Concertoes	O
accompanied	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
M	I-pers
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
have	O
afforded	O
one	O
at	O
present	O
I	O
am	O
rich	O
in	O
Gowns	O
the	O
Bodyce	O
also	O
came	O
safe	O
the	O
2	O
Shirt	O
Hank	O
are	O
extremely	O
pretty	O
&	O
the	O
2	O
Frill	O
s	O
Stocks	O
--	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
these	O
the	O
stick	O
came	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
the	O
6	O
Pocket	O
Hank	O
are	O
remarkably	O
pretty	O
&	O
neat	O
--	O
the	O
2	O
Hand	O
Screws	O
are	O
beautifully	O
made	O
light	O
&	O
elegant	O
--	O
tell	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
shall	O
always	O
look	O
on	O
them	O
with	O
pleasure	O
the	O
Netting	O
Case	O
I	O
am	O
charmed	O
with	O
&	O
it	O
suits	O
me	O
so	O
well	O
because	O
my	O
Playwork	O
is	O
Netting	O
Garters	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
nett	O
two	O
pair	O
for	O
you	O
two	O
for	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
two	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
my	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
remembrance	O
--	O
tell	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
think	O
it	O
the	O
prettiest	O
Netting	O
Case	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
--	O
the	O
Pincushion	O
is	O
also	O
very	O
pretty	O
my	O
Sister	O
s	O
Comp	O
to	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Pincushion	O
which	O
she	O
thinks	O
extremely	O
pretty	O
in	O
general	O
for	O
all	O
accept	O
my	O
warmest	O
thanks	O
&	O
be	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
the	O
kind	O
intention	O
is	O
delightful	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
&	O
shocked	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
decease	O
I	O
esteemed	O
her	O
&	O
was	O
gratified	O
in	O
her	O
society	O
her	O
manner	O
was	O
attentive	O
agreeable	O
&	O
obliging	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Woman	O
What	O
is	O
Beauty	O
all	O
is	O
as	O
the	O
flower	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
an	O
echo	O
of	O
Alexander	O
Innes	O
,	O
Twelve	O
Sermons	O
Preach	O
'd	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
...	O
(	O
1726	O
:	O
177	O
)	O
,	O
who	O
asks	O
'What	O
is	O
Beauty	O
?	O
'	O
and	O
goes	O
on	O
to	O
cite	O
Isaiah	O
40.6	O
'alll	O
[	O
...	O
]	O
is	O
as	O
the	O
flower	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
'	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
&	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
You	O
will	O
I	O
know	O
be	O
truly	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
I	O
am	O
eſsentially	O
amended	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
nervous	O
dejection	O
&	O
disquietude	O
my	O
head	O
is	O
clearer	O
tho	O
though	O
at	O
times	O
confused	O
I	O
now	O
employ	O
at	O
my	O
Needle	O
my	O
Book	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
Piano	O
Forte	O
from	O
5	O
to	O
6	O
hours	O
every	O
day	O
&	O
last	O
year	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
compose	O
mysef	O
myself	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
on	O
Xmas	O
day	O
&	O
received	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
after	O
two	O
years	O
omiſsion	O
of	O
both	O
a	O
great	O
comfort	O
it	O
will	O
alway	O
s	O
ma	O
ke	O
me	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
y	O
ou	O
.	O
Your	O
s	O
most	O
affectly	O
:	O
A	B-pers
C	I-pers
Dear	O
Madam	O
--	O
My	O
Aunts	O
have	O
requested	O
me	O
just	O
to	O
add	O
their	O
Sincere	O
thanks	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
her	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
which	O
they	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
recieved	O
--	O
from	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
&	O
hopes	O
you	O
have	O
rec	O
'd	O
her	O
Letr	O
Mrs	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
also	O
adds	O
her	O
best	O
Compts	O
..	O
--	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
intention	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
present	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
..	O
Inst	O
.	O
to	O
drink	O
your	O
health	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
Obet	O
humble	O
Sert	O
.	O
Annabella	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
--	O
single	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
