TOKEN	NE
Decr	O
7	O
th	O
1814	O
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Canterbury	B-place
My	O
dear	O
friend	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
excused	O
my	O
not	O
answering	O
your	O
very	O
interesting	O
Letter	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
intended	O
marriage	O
of	O
your	O
most	O
amiable	O
Daughter	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
particularly	O
grateful	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
congratulate	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
herself	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Letters	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
Postcript	O
to	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
were	O
received	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
affectionately	O
to	O
both	O
&	O
mention	O
my	O
Letter	O
when	O
you	O
shall	O
write	O
I	O
was	O
inexpreſsibly	O
gratified	O
by	O
that	O
much	O
desired	O
reconciliation	O
&	O
I	O
anxiously	O
wish	O
that	O
two	O
friends	O
so	O
long	O
attached	O
may	O
be	O
always	O
united	O
by	O
that	O
tender	O
tie	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
shamefully	O
broken	O
I	O
rejoice	O
much	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
I	O
once	O
lost	O
the	O
favor	O
&	O
friendship	O
of	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
own	O
Sister	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Parent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
some	O
oblique	O
conduct	O
in	O
a	O
Person	O
&	O
some	O
property	O
was	O
depending	O
but	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
only	O
caused	O
me	O
vexation	O
--	O
I	O
imparted	O
the	O
agreeable	O
intelligence	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Inglis	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Inglis	I-pers
who	O
both	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
gratified	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
expreſs	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
with	O
very	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
called	O
to	O
thank	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
again	O
called	O
&	O
left	O
the	O
following	O
Lines	O
en	O
Auteur	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
expreſsed	O
in	O
confidence	O
to	O
myself	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
flatterd	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
him	O
this	O
proves	O
his	O
warm	O
attachment	O
to	O
you	O
so	O
pray	O
my	O
dear	O
Brother	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
effusion	O
&	O
restore	O
his	O
good	O
humour	O
--	O
suppreſsing	O
what	O
has	O
paſsed	O
Pray	O
inquire	O
&	O
inform	O
me	O
whether	O
Col	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
are	O
returned	O
to	O
Upper	O
Grosvenor	O
Street	O
I	O
am	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
or	O
written	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
respecting	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
a	O
Line	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
comfortable	O
in	O
our	O
Apartments	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
furnished	O
and	O
we	O
appear	O
very	O
smart	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
this	O
Eve	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Whist	O
perhaps	O
&	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prebendal	O
Parties	O
Dr.	B-pers
Whalesby	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
is	O
a	O
wellbred	O
&	O
pleasing	O
woman	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
make	O
room	O
for	O
Dr.	B-pers
Inglis	I-pers
&	O
with	O
kindest	O
friendship	O
say	O
farewell	O
ever	O
yours	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
C	I-pers
a	O
Thought	O
on	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
approaching	O
marriage	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
with	O
Major	B-pers
General	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
--	O
to	O
MGA	B-pers
When	O
from	O
their	O
Eastern	O
to	O
this	O
Western	O
Bed	O
Neptune	O
&	O
Phoebus	O
the	O
first	O
Anson	O
led	O
;	O
Of	O
all	O
that	O
met	O
the	O
Navigator	O
's	O
eye	O
No	O
blesd	O
Oasis	O
could	O
with	O
Tinian	O
vie	O
.	O
Thou	O
his	O
Descendant	O
tra	O
travelling	O
Life	O
's	O
wide	O
round	O
Hast	O
in	O
thy	O
search	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Louisa	B-pers
found	O
With	O
whom	O
united	O
in	O
the	O
Bands	O
of	O
Love	O
A	O
Desert	O
must	O
to	O
Thee	O
a	O
Tinian	O
prove	O
.	O
Dr	O
Inglis	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
identified	O
)	O
,	O
occasional	O
poem	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
sincere	O
friend	O
&	O
wellwisher	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
D	I-pers
NB	O
the	O
last	O
line	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
suggested	O
by	O
that	O
well-known	O
Couplet	O
Thou	O
from	O
all	O
dangers	O
darkneſs	O
canst	O
exclude	O
And	O
from	O
a	O
Desert	O
banish	O
solitude	O
Abraham	O
Cowley	O
,	O
Of	O
Solitude	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
