TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
May	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
minute	O
I	O
have	O
scarce	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
hold	O
a	O
Pen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
distracted	O
with	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
has	O
now	O
left	O
me	O
entirely	O
.	O
How	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
so	O
well	O
know	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
melancholy	O
accident	O
you	O
mention	O
&	O
by	O
its	O
still	O
more	O
melancholy	O
consequences	O
--	O
what	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
dread	O
to	O
ask	O
--	O
you	O
say	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
then	O
dangerously	O
ill.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
Event	O
--	O
has	O
God	O
spared	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
is	O
he	O
recovering	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
anxious	O
indeed	O
to	O
hear	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
one	O
word	O
from	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
.	O
should	O
you	O
be	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
consolation	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Religion	O
;	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
good	O
sens	O
e	O
in	O
your	O
strong	O
reason	O
,	O
in	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
affectio	O
n	O
&	O
regard	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
induce	O
&	O
enable	O
you	O
to	O
exert	O
yourselves	O
mutually	O
for	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
sakes	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
my	O
attempts	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
deeply	O
interested	O
in	O
your	O
situation	O
.	O
The	O
account	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
like	O
her	O
names	O
extremely	O
,	O
is	O
charming	O
indeed	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
happineſs	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
Being	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Angel	O
,	O
which	O
attaches	O
&	O
interests	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
&	O
which	O
already	O
must	O
prove	O
the	O
greatest	O
of	O
comfort	O
,	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
little	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
about	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
now	O
very	O
well	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
distracted	O
wth	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
winter	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
very	O
thin	O
,	O
look	O
pale	O
&	O
should	O
not	O
please	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
by	O
my	O
appearance	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
in	O
three	O
weeks	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
little	O
as	O
I	O
rake	O
&	O
sit	O
up	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
still	O
more	O
quiet	O
&	O
regular	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
even	O
more	O
fatigui	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
the	O
spirits	O
&	O
mind	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
noise	O
&	O
bustle	O
on	O
all	O
sides	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
it	O
yourself	O
than	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
foremost	O
in	O
the	O
riot	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
my	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
very	O
little	O
into	O
publick	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
God	O
knows	O
still	O
leſs	O
interest	O
in	O
what	O
is	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
etourdie	O
with	O
the	O
arrangements	O
plans	O
&	O
diſsappointments	O
of	O
others	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
intend	O
carryi	O
n	O
g	O
my	O
Sister	O
down	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
where	O
I	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Drawingroom	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
here	O
for	O
that	O
Day	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
go	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
tell	O
what	O
comfort	O
&	O
relief	O
I	O
feel	O
from	O
this	O
idea	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
enables	O
me	O
to	O
bear	O
the	O
short	O
time	O
I	O
must	O
remain	O
here	O
longer	O
,	O
with	O
patience	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
made	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
Books	O
&	O
musick	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
down	O
&	O
amuse	O
myself	O
with	O
formi	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
plan	O
of	O
reading	O
&	O
occupation	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
left	O
us	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
is	O
established	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
where	O
he	O
is	O
maki	O
n	O
g	O
great	O
alterations	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
&	O
Grounds	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
new	O
paper	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
white	O
&	O
next	O
year	O
shall	O
afford	O
new	O
curtains	O
&	O
chairs	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
whole	O
swarm	O
of	O
french	O
People	O
here	O
who	O
are	O
all	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
de	I-pers
Poligniac	I-pers
(	O
the	O
quondam	O
favourite	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Woman	O
,	O
very	O
short	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
pleasing	O
countenance	O
&	O
manners	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
de	I-pers
Guiche	I-pers
her	O
Daughter	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
married	O
but	O
two	O
years	O
&	O
is	O
but	O
15	O
--	O
is	O
still	O
shorter	O
but	O
pretty	O
tho	O
'	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
high	O
forehead	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
reckoned	O
the	O
prettie	O
st	O
woman	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
hundreds	O
here	O
who	O
excell	O
her	O
infinitly	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Ball	O
at	O
the	O
French	O
Ambaſsadors	O
on	O
Thursday	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
in	O
my	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
Saturday	O
)	O
at	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
gay	O
&	O
pretty	O
Ball	O
,	O
too	O
numerous	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
dancing	O
pleasant	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
early	O
--	O
what	O
I	O
expect	O
great	O
pleasure	O
from	O
is	O
the	O
Play	O
at	O
Richmond	O
House	O
to	O
which	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
go	O
on	O
Thursday	O
next	O
I	O
am	O
invited	O
by	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
so	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
attend	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
&	O
go	O
undreſsed	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Papers	O
full	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
acted	O
5	O
times	O
&	O
every	O
body	O
seems	O
delighted	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
you	O
for	O
my	O
Sister	O
calls	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
may	O
this	O
find	O
you	O
all	O
happy	O
&	O
comfortable	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
for	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
may	O
contribute	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
so	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
ever	O
yours	O
CMG	B-pers
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
June	O
1787	O
