TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
hearing	O
such	O
good	O
accounts	O
from	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
and	O
your	O
sweet	O
Babe	O
,	O
going	O
on	O
so	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
at	O
present	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
thought	O
in	O
leaving	O
Bath	B-place
till	O
April	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Dear	O
Child	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
the	O
shake	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
journey	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
both	O
;	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
always	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
k	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
circumstanc	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
neice	O
of	O
mine	O
is	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
leave	O
London	B-place
till	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
having	O
busineſs	O
to	O
settle	O
with	O
her	O
intended	O
Spouse	O
.	O
--	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
match	O
,	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
app	O
r	O
ove	O
of	O
,	O
He	O
being	O
a	O
sensiable	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
must	O
dread	O
my	O
Purse	O
strings	O
.	O
pray	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
time	O
suits	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Prattinton	I-pers
for	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
&	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
set	O
off	O
Post	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
your	O
saucy	O
husband	O
,	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
arrived	O
to	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
father	O
,	O
there	O
wil	O
be	O
no	O
bearing	O
him	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
.	O
yours	O
affectionately	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
my	O
love	O
to	O
your	O
good	O
Dickinson	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Feby	O
27	O
--	O
1787	O
