TOKEN	NE
Naples	B-place
,	O
May	O
1	O
st	O
:	O
1802	O
At	O
length	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
nearer	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
general	O
Peace	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
we	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
separated	O
more	O
by	O
the	O
unhappy	O
&	O
desolating	O
War	O
than	O
by	O
the	O
Alps	B-place
,	O
&	O
distant	O
tracts	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
are	O
plac	O
'd	O
between	O
this	O
country	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
Native	O
land	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
to	O
the	O
ever-lamentable	O
revolutions	O
which	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
pervaded	O
&	O
convuls	O
'd	O
all	O
Europe	B-place
but	O
almost	O
the	O
whole	O
World	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
attribute	O
any	O
seeming	O
negligence	O
of	O
mine	O
towards	O
such	O
good	O
Friends	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
without	O
doubt	O
,	O
suffer	O
'd	O
in	O
Engd	B-place
:	I-place
the	O
effects	O
of	O
this	O
general	O
vain	O
&	O
intollerable	O
confusion	O
,	O
yet	O
you	O
can	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
idea	O
of	O
what	O
weaker	O
&	O
more	O
defenceleſs	O
&	O
ill-	O
govern	O
'd	O
countries	O
have	O
undergone	O
&	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
regret	O
for	O
many	O
many	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
however	O
prolong	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
which	O
never	O
fails	O
to	O
recall	O
the	O
most	O
painful	O
ideas	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
only	O
touch	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
plead	O
my	O
excuse	O
,	O
for	O
never	O
having	O
written	O
immediately	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Bror	O
:	O
&	O
my	O
amiable	O
Niece	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
&	O
acceptable	O
present	O
I	O
recd	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
1801	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
render	O
more	O
secure	O
your	O
having	O
my	O
acknowledgements	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
proper	O
expreſsion	O
of	O
gratitude	O
,	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
our	O
Dear	O
Sarah	B-pers
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
very	O
particularly	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
;	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
memory	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
:	O
but	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
past	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
difficult	O
to	O
ascertain	O
any	O
point	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
uncertainty	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
actual	O
interruption	O
of	O
all	O
correspondence	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
to	O
redouble	O
my	O
thanks	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
recd	O
:	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
8	O
guineas	O
from	O
England	B-place
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
any	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
I	O
am	O
left	O
to	O
gueſs	O
the	O
generous	O
hand	O
it	O
comes	O
from	O
:	O
Be	O
aſsur	O
'd	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
very	O
sensible	O
to	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
;	O
who	O
have	O
still	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
remembrance	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
to	O
confer	O
benefits	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Now	O
that	O
Commerce	O
is	O
restor	O
'd	O
to	O
Europe	B-place
I	O
shall	O
frequently	O
have	O
opportunities	O
of	O
sending	O
to	O
Liverpool	B-place
,	O
wch	O
:	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
pleasing	O
to	O
me	O
indeed	O
,	O
cou	O
'd	O
I	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
hence	O
wch	O
:	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
agreeable	O
or	O
useful	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
again	O
I	O
am	O
limited	O
to	O
the	O
smallest	O
trifles	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
entred	O
into	O
Engd	B-place
:	I-place
by	O
the	O
aid	O
of	O
some	O
obliging	O
Captn	O
:	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
find	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
privately	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
without	O
causing	O
my	O
Freinds	O
to	O
pay	O
more	O
for	O
the	O
duties	O
than	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
been	O
anxious	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
little	O
token	O
of	O
remembrance	O
to	O
my	O
sweet	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Aunt	B-pers
Ippa	I-pers
,	O
for	O
whom	O
my	O
Sister	O
informs	O
me	O
she	O
still	O
retains	O
a	O
regard	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
several	O
curiosities	O
which	O
I	O
obtain	O
'd	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
lost	O
or	O
ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
change	O
of	O
place	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
hope	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
;	O
particularly	O
as	O
your	O
present	O
residence	O
is	O
now	O
remote	O
from	O
Manchester	B-place
.	O
It	O
luckily	O
happens	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
opporty	O
:	O
of	O
sending	O
to	O
Liverpool	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
sister	O
tells	O
me	O
you	O
are	O
expected	O
at	O
B	O
.	O
Hall	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
hastily	O
done	O
some	O
cuttings	O
out	O
,	O
wch	O
:	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
executed	O
had	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
stronger	O
eyes	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Bomboliera	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
Louisa	B-pers
may	O
serve	O
as	O
a	O
specimen	O
of	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
indeed	O
a	O
greater	O
proof	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
than	O
the	O
most	O
elegant	O
keep-sake	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
sent	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
weakneſs	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
almost	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
obtaining	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
quiet	O
moments	O
to	O
employ	O
myself	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
art	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
excuse	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
owe	O
so	O
much	O
gratitude	O
,	O
I	O
venture	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
so	O
simple	O
a	O
token	O
of	O
remembrance	O
as	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cold	O
marble	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
freezing	O
to	O
the	O
touch	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
told	O
that	O
this	O
comes	O
from	O
a	O
very	O
warm	O
heart	O
,	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
fam	O
'd	O
Mount	B-place
Vesuvius	I-place
,	O
whose	O
productions	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
disdain	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
lover	O
of	O
nature	O
&	O
natural	O
curiosities	O
.	O
These	O
specimens	O
of	O
lava	O
which	O
but	O
ill	O
reppresent	O
the	O
mountain	O
,	O
sea	O
,	O
&	O
light-house	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
were	O
actually	O
thrown	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
eruptions	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
dislike	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
also	O
some	O
ashes	O
found	O
in	O
our	O
garden	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
great	O
eruption	O
,	O
&	O
wch	O
:	O
threatend	O
Naples	B-place
with	O
destruction	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
were	O
found	O
200	O
miles	O
distant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
3	O
red	O
pearls	O
wch	O
:	O
are	O
formd	O
in	O
a	O
shell-fish	O
resembling	O
a	O
muscle	O
,	O
but	O
much	O
larger	O
,	O
from	O
wch	O
:	O
they	O
take	O
the	O
wool	O
from	O
wch	O
:	O
gloves	O
are	O
made	O
at	O
Taranto	B-place
,	O
specimens	O
of	O
wch	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	O
&	O
begg	O
'd	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
divide	O
them	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
beg	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Portrait	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
favorite	O
P	O
art	O
y	O
who	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
much	O
admiration	O
here	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
send	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
perhaps	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
better	O
preserv	O
'd	O
than	O
by	O
the	O
Sea	O
;	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
I	O
must	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
this	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
charming	O
accts	O
.	O
of	O
you	O
all	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
continue	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
consolation	O
to	O
find	O
,	O
that	O
age	O
or	O
infirmities	O
make	O
very	O
slow	O
progreſs	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
our	O
ever	O
reverd	O
&	O
beloved	O
Father	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
ever	O
yours	O
Pray	O
excuse	O
my	O
venturing	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
such	O
ridiculous	O
trifles	O
wch	O
:	O
indeed	O
are	O
laughable	O
but	O
the	O
time	O
was	O
so	O
limited	O
that	O
nothing	O
better	O
cou	O
'd	O
be	O
musterd	O
with	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
my	O
Bror	O
:	O
&	O
affectte	O
:	O
remembrance	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Morison	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
yours	O
Elizth	B-pers
.	I-pers
Palombi	I-pers
.	O
May	O
1	O
st	O
X	O
1802	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
