TOKEN	NE
Bath	B-place
ye	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1785	O
My	O
Deareſt	O
Miranda	B-pers
:	O
A	O
severe	O
,	O
though	O
salutary	O
return	O
of	O
inflammation	O
and	O
defluxion	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
hath	O
given	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
joyful	O
intelligence	O
imparted	O
this	O
day	O
by	O
my	O
attentive	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
and	O
permits	O
me	O
to	O
pour	O
upon	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
conſort	O
my	O
moſt	O
cordial	O
congratulations	O
and	O
benedictions	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
disorder	O
is	O
retreating	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
compound	O
for	O
its	O
reſidence	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
only	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
obſtruct	O
my	O
pen	O
for	O
the	O
preſent	O
in	O
deſcribing	O
so	O
fully	O
what	O
I	O
feel	O
on	O
the	O
joyful	O
occaſion	O
,	O
which	O
preſents	O
such	O
a	O
proſpect	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
happineſs	O
for	O
life	O
.	O
Excuſe	O
m	O
e	O
y	O
brevity	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
my	O
beſt	O
compliments	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
let	O
me	O
conclude	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miranda	B-pers
your	O
affectionate	O
father	O
R	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
June	O
24	O
1785	O
Mr	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
June	O
24	O
th	O
1785	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenſon	I-pers
