TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	B-place
--	O
Octr-	O
3	O
--	O
1789	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
perfect	O
charity	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
for	O
your	O
Packet	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
long	O
Letter	O
;	O
But	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
feared	O
I	O
had	O
unintentionally	O
given	O
some	O
offence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
most	O
unsatisfactorily	O
puzzled	O
my	O
Head	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
leſsen	O
the	O
Concern	O
I	O
gave	O
You	O
about	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
Alaſs	O
,	O
We	O
are	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
accident	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
apparently	O
gained	O
one	O
Step	O
in	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Leg	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
rather	O
more	O
freedom	O
from	O
Pain	O
,	O
(	O
whether	O
Rhumatic	O
,	O
or	O
Spasmodic	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
named	O
in	O
turn	O
,	O
)	O
sleeps	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
no	O
other	O
Complaint	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
He	O
is	O
greatly	O
fallen	O
away	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
Spirits	O
are	O
lower	O
than	O
You	O
can	O
have	O
any	O
idea	O
of	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
from	O
London	B-place
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
aſsures	O
us	O
that	O
even	O
if	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
moved	O
there	O
,	O
nothing	O
further	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
heat	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
length	O
of	O
Time	O
yet	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
chief	O
things	O
to	O
depend	O
upon	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Bone	O
is	O
any	O
way	O
affected	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Muscles	O
&	O
Ligaments	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
are	O
most	O
thoroughly	O
shook	O
&	O
relaxed	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
till	O
They	O
can	O
gain	O
Strength	O
,	O
an	O
amendment	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
trying	O
to	O
exert	O
it	O
as	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
recommended	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
advised	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
total	O
rest	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
He	O
continues	O
during	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
entirely	O
on	O
his	O
Couch	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
his	O
excellent	O
Constitution	O
&	O
Temperance	O
,	O
as	O
You	O
justly	O
observe	O
,	O
are	O
very	O
great	O
preservatives	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Melancholy	O
Prospect	O
for	O
Him	O
&	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Our	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
's	O
heart	O
is	O
heavy	O
,	O
as	O
You	O
may	O
imagine	O
,	O
under	O
such	O
an	O
Affliction	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
continued	O
,	O
yet	O
She	O
is	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
happy	O
Composure	O
in	O
general	O
sustains	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
flattered	O
by	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
friendly	O
design	O
to	O
visit	O
me	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
wish	O
He	O
had	O
put	O
earlier	O
in	O
execution	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
his	O
bad	O
Health	O
had	O
not	O
impeded	O
his	O
coming	O
on	O
to	O
Wherwell	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
the	O
Soap	O
Pills	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
estimation	O
that	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
deserve	O
when	O
He	O
was	O
here	O
;	O
&	O
pray	O
thank	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
remarkable	O
levity	O
&	O
politeneſs	O
in	O
overlooking	O
my	O
Blots	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
him	O
such	O
lasting	O
marks	O
of	O
his	O
goodneſs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
finding	O
out	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Chatterton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
could	O
not	O
learn	O
where	O
She	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
suspect	O
her	O
Demesne	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
compaſs	O
of	O
my	O
Walks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
particularly	O
pleased	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
's	O
answer	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
&	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
You	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
your	O
offer	O
of	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
Bishop	O
Bonner	O
's	O
Ghost	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
seeing	O
&	O
shall	O
most	O
gladly	O
accept	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
my	O
Collection	O
,	O
which	O
You	O
have	O
so	O
kindly	O
enriched	O
.	O
Mr-	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
's	O
ode	O
on	O
the	O
Grave	O
of	O
Arthur	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
poſseſs	O
'd	O
of	O
in	O
Print	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
Poems	O
.	O
The	O
Quipos	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
decypher	O
to	O
our	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
quite	O
hate	O
the	O
information	O
You	O
give	O
me	O
of	O
Dr-	B-pers
Darwin	I-pers
's	O
being	O
an	O
Infidel	O
in	O
Religion	O
;	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
poſsible	O
He	O
should	O
be	O
an	O
Atheist	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
very	O
Curious	O
Notes	O
,	O
He	O
must	O
be	O
convinced	O
of	O
the	O
exalted	O
order	O
,	O
(	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
extensive	O
minuteneſs	O
,	O
)	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
wise	O
regularity	O
,	O
of	O
every	O
Law	O
in	O
Nature	O
?	O
Would	O
not	O
one	O
naturally	O
conclude	O
that	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
anatomy	O
of	O
the	O
human	O
frame	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
anatomy	O
of	O
a	O
Plant	O
would	O
both	O
contribute	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
mind	O
to	O
a	O
creator	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
confirm	O
most	O
stedfastly	O
the	O
belief	O
;	O
&	O
yet	O
Physicians	O
to	O
a	O
Proverb	O
,	O
are	O
generally	O
reckoned	O
Free-thinkers	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Riddles	O
which	O
I	O
enclose	O
with	O
Your	O
's	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
I——	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
You	O
a	O
thousand	O
acknowlegements	O
for	O
the	O
receipts	O
for	O
the	O
Poor	O
which	O
You	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
begs	O
to	O
detane	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Copies	O
printed	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
restored	O
to	O
You	O
safely	O
.	O
--	O
Have	O
You	O
heard	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
is	O
going	O
by	O
a	O
Tontine	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
£200,000	O
?	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
means	O
He	O
is	O
recommended	O
to	O
procure	O
his	O
Estates	O
in	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
He	O
will	O
have	O
£10	O
,	O
or	O
12000	O
p	O
ann	O
.	O
left	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
Place	O
.	O
Proposals	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
are	O
at	O
his	O
Banker	O
's	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
tho't	O
it	O
will	O
succeed	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
sends	O
a	O
Re	O
-buſs	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
;	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
happineſs	O
&	O
animation	O
at	O
Park-gate	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
is	O
to	O
your	O
Heart	O
's	O
wish	O
.	O
Grandpapa	O
I	O
find	O
is	O
just	O
what	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
executed	O
his	O
intention	O
prosperously	O
,	O
of	O
riding	O
57	O
Miles	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
our	O
Grandpapa	O
here	O
could	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
With	O
regard	O
to	O
your	O
friendly	O
enquiries	O
after	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
&	O
c	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
well	O
&	O
stout	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
's	O
Health	O
has	O
been	O
recovered	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
indeed	O
as	O
You	O
imagine	O
,	O
engroſsed	O
in	O
fine	O
Acquaintances	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
She	O
quarrels	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Mother	O
&	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
I	O
am	O
sure	O
are	O
better	O
without	O
her	O
attentions	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
sounds	O
severe	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
tittle	O
more	O
than	O
She	O
deserves	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
never	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
Heart	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
on	O
a	O
Tour	O
to	O
fine	O
friends	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
;	O
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
is	O
about	O
to	O
miscarry	O
at	O
Berne	B-place
;	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
much	O
signify	O
what	O
becomes	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
Them	O
;	O
I	O
sometimes	O
think	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
's	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
Luttrell	O
Family	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
or	O
Two	O
good	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Flock	O
,	O
quite	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
If	O
You	O
knew	O
my	O
Louisa	B-pers
as	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
You	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
justneſs	O
of	O
my	O
Remarks	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
agree	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
is	O
made	O
up	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
obtrude	O
herself	O
like	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
her	O
Health	O
is	O
recovering	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
Nerves	O
are	O
shaken	O
is	O
no	O
wonder	O
;	O
She	O
is	O
just	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Weymouth	B-place
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefits	O
of	O
Mild	O
air	O
as	O
the	O
Winter	O
advances	O
.	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Twyford	B-place
in	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
is	O
only	O
3	O
Miles	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Winchester	B-place
from	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
touched	O
with	O
your	O
Expreſsions	O
of	O
Concern	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
feels	O
thoroughly	O
grateful	O
for	O
your	O
's	O
&	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
's	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
Regard	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
sincerely	O
that	O
the	O
air	O
of	O
Park-gate	B-place
has	O
been	O
so	O
salutary	O
to	O
your	O
good	O
Marito	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
He	O
has	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
made	O
himself	O
Master	O
of	O
Italian	O
;	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
rapidly	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
Acquaintance	O
Mr-	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
here	O
this	O
Summer	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
who	O
always	O
gives	O
me	O
some	O
instructions	O
.	O
Your	O
's	O
sincerely	O
&	O
much	O
Obliged	O
E——	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
