TOKEN	NE
Tunbridge	B-place
Wells	I-place
14	O
Aug	O
:	O
1782	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
if	O
you	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
rain	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
we	O
experience	O
here	O
,	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
we	O
are	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
yet	O
not	O
washed	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
floods	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
high	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
Mount	B-place
Ephraim	I-place
,	O
we	O
only	O
see	O
the	O
w	O
h	O
et	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
that	O
inconvenience	O
--	O
the	O
weather	O
however	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
mortifying	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
certainly	O
must	O
en	O
the	O
spring	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
,	O
the	O
water	O
can	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
service	O
.	O
my	O
Mother	O
is	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
much	O
better	O
;	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
atended	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Leeds	I-pers
's	O
invitation	O
to	O
the	O
Ball	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
an̄ualy	O
gives	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
's	O
Birthday	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
at	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
much	O
entertained	O
at	O
the	O
ceremony	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Bad	O
Weather	O
,	O
spoilt	O
the	O
gayest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
show	O
:	O
as	O
the	O
Walks	O
are	O
dreſst	O
with	O
Bows	O
&	O
Lights	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
with	O
company	O
,	O
all	O
dreſst	O
in	O
gayest	O
fancy	O
--	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
rooms	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
company	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
in	O
smartest	O
dreſs	O
,	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
pay	O
their	O
compts	O
:	O
Lady	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
Lady	O
here	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Queen	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
tea	O
Drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
handed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
seated	O
himself	O
,	O
next	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
staring	O
to	O
sit	O
alone	O
,	O
more	O
chairs	O
were	O
brought	O
Lady	B-pers
Brudenell	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Bligh	I-pers
,	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
Yr	O
.	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
next	O
the	O
Counteſs	O
;	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Bowlby	I-pers
,	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
(	O
Ly.Darnley	B-pers
's	O
mother	O
)	O
behind	O
;	O
the	O
minuets	O
then	O
began	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Bligh	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Beaufoy	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
a	O
Quaker	O
and	O
vinegar	O
merchant	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Beau	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Ball	O
;	O
making	O
their	O
compts	O
(	O
as	O
at	O
court	O
)	O
to	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
exhibition	O
of	O
Dreſses	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
dancers	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
few	O
kept	O
time	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
truly	O
amusing	O
:	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
ceremony	O
's	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
trouble	O
,	O
is	O
trying	O
to	O
introduce	O
long	O
Lappets	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
minuets	O
.	O
so	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
had	O
Lappets	O
long	O
enough	O
,	O
to	O
sit	O
upon	O
,	O
pin	O
'd	O
,	O
under	O
little	O
Dancers	O
hats	O
,	O
with	O
Short	O
peticoats	O
:	O
those	O
indeed	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
trains	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
manage	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
tumbles	O
:	O
the	O
minuets	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
over	O
;	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
ceremony	O
's	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Bow	O
,	O
to	O
notifye	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Duke	O
and	O
company	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
excuse	O
hoping	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
excused	O
as	O
an	O
invalid	O
,	O
for	O
going	O
home	O
so	O
early	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
.	O
country	O
dances	O
then	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
usual	O
entertainments	O
took	O
place	O
;	O
of	O
cards	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
the	O
company	O
very	O
brilliant	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
supose	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Quaker	O
dancing	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Sussex	I-pers
,	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Darnley	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
,	O
Sigr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pacchierotti	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
faces	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
again	O
!	O
made	O
a	O
sufficient	O
croud	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
at	O
your	O
partys	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
a	O
disconsolate	O
Widower	O
,	O
has	O
sold	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
summer	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
children	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
I	O
saw	O
on	O
the	O
walks	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
only	O
came	O
for	O
th	O
e	O
day	O
--	O
nobody	O
need	O
be	O
sick	O
here	O
,	O
if	O
Doctors	O
can	O
cure	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
two	O
Bishops	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ball	O
,	O
with	O
Lower	O
Clergy	O
in	O
abundance	O
!	O
and	O
Phisicians	O
,	O
without	O
end	O
.	O
Even	O
Doctor	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	O
Lowths	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
Eldest	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
Warren	B-pers
thought	O
her	O
better	O
.	O
the	O
Bishop	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
again	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
distressful	O
situation	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
sick	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
party	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
Stonelands	O
:	O
(	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sackville	I-pers
s	O
about	O
6	O
mile	O
off	O
)	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
place	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
wont	O
have	O
shown	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
Beyond	O
,	O
is	O
Withiam	B-place
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Burial	O
Place	O
of	O
the	O
familly	O
.	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
old	O
tomb	O
,	O
erected	O
to	O
a	O
Seventh	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
thirteenth	O
Child	O
of	O
a	O
Sackville	O
;	O
the	O
you	O
ng	O
man	O
Lays	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
the	O
father	O
&	O
mother	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
weeping	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
round	O
the	O
sides	O
,	O
are	O
the	O
other	O
children	O
;	O
the	O
dead	O
,	O
are	O
distinguished	O
by	O
Palm	O
Branches	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
living	O
,	O
by	O
full	O
bottom	O
'd	O
Wig	O
s	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
marble	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
executed	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Statuary	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
modest	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
his	O
work	O
deserves	O
admiration	O
.	O
we	O
also	O
v	O
w	O
ent	O
into	O
the	O
Burial	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
many	O
Coffins	O
,	O
Sir	B-pers
Ed	I-pers
:	I-pers
Sack	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
fought	O
the	O
famous	O
Duel	O
--	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
&	O
Parsonage	O
,	O
is	O
delightful	O
.	O
Buckhurst	O
Tower	O
,	O
forms	O
a	O
beautifull	O
object	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
Old	O
Gateway	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
remains	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
ancient	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
Sackville	O
Familly	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
sketch	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
give	O
some	O
idea	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
busy	O
with	O
my	O
Pencil	O
;	O
&	O
taken	O
another	O
view	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
mount	O
Misery	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
a	O
pleasing	O
object	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
name	O
shd	O
.	O
bespeak	O
the	O
reverse	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
mounts	O
,	O
remind	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pilgrims	O
progreſs	O
,	O
wish	O
You	O
could	O
come	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ramble	O
about	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rocks	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
w	O
:	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
seeing	O
,	O
but	O
fear	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
will	O
keep	O
her	O
at	O
Strood	B-place
.	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
seem	O
in	O
spirits	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
,	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
Camp	O
by	O
Yarmouth	B-place
,	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
fear	O
this	O
weather	O
in	O
so	O
unhealthy	O
a	O
country	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
make	O
them	O
very	O
stout	O
--	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
apologise	O
for	O
making	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
any	O
franks	O
:	O
and	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
follow	O
my	O
example	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
it	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
grudge	O
my	O
pence	O
;	O
&	O
think	O
me	O
not	O
public	O
spirited	O
enough	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
with	O
pleasure	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
like	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
sister	O
,	O
joyn	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
Sincerly	O
Yours	O
Wil	B-pers
:	I-pers
King	I-pers
how	O
does	O
Mad	B-pers
La	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
?	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pelham	I-pers
's	O
near	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
.	O
sad	O
Weather	O
for	O
her	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
single	O
sheet	O
