TOKEN	NE
Kew	O
House	O
Friday	O
Afternoon	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
my	O
Dearest	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
begin	O
to	O
feel	O
some	O
benefit	O
from	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
,	O
&	O
trust	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
sleep	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
Mrs	B-pers
Goodyer	I-pers
write	O
me	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
lines	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
good	O
tidings	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
situated	O
as	O
we	O
both	O
are	O
hear	O
as	O
frequently	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
anxiet	O
y	O
or	O
inclination	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
litteraly	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
either	O
the	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
we	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
or	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
we	O
are	O
quite	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
airings	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
the	O
uncertninty	O
of	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
coming	O
the	O
amusing	O
the	O
Dear	O
Child	O
&	O
the	O
nurse	O
leaving	O
her	O
,	O
fully	O
employs	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
mend	O
hourly	O
paſses	O
very	O
chearfully	O
&	O
quickly	O
,	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
my	O
Love	O
have	O
an	O
Idea	O
of	O
her	O
amendment	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
then	O
I	O
dared	O
hope	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
She	O
sleeps	O
perfectly	O
quiet	O
,	O
her	O
Apetite	O
is	O
perfectly	O
good	O
&	O
her	O
Strength	O
very	O
near	O
recovered	O
,	O
she	O
goes	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
out	O
any	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
daresay	O
in	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
days	O
will	O
run	O
,	O
She	O
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
&	O
freque	O
ntly	O
talks	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Prſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
says	O
Poor	O
Ham	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
Tick	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
more	O
delightful	O
then	O
Ever	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
entertainment	O
,	O
&	O
amusement	O
to	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mrs	B-pers
Schwellenburg	I-pers
s	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
s	O
Rooms	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
vary	O
the	O
Scene	O
we	O
drink	O
Tea	O
alternately	O
with	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
s	O
&	O
your	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
fe	O
lt	O
most	O
exceedingly	O
your	O
very	O
friendly	O
congratulations	O
a	O
s	O
did	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
&	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
comes	O
into	O
waiting	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
begining	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
may	O
you	O
recover	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
y	O
ou	O
to	O
believe	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Afftly	O
Yr	O
MC	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Comps	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
if	O
she	O
is	O
with	O
you	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cheveley	I-pers
begs	O
her	O
kind	O
ones	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
--	O
