TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
did	O
myself	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
acquainting	O
you	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Stratford	I-pers
second	O
Son	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Aldborough	I-pers
has	O
made	O
proposals	O
for	O
my	O
Daughter	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
accepted	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
marriage	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
is	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
character	O
&	O
disposition	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
estate	O
&	O
has	O
great	O
expectations	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
who	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
richest	O
men	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
in	O
his	O
86	O
th	O
.	O
year	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
on	O
all	O
hands	O
thought	O
a	O
most	O
advantageous	O
match	O
for	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Gardiner	O
's	O
Row	O
March	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1777	O
