TOKEN	NE
Wolverton	B-place
Friday	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Many	O
Thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
&	O
inquiries	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
any	O
good	O
accounts	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
except	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
tolerably	O
well	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
are	O
perfectly	O
so	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
present	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
course	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
&	O
indeed	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
past	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
escaped	O
some	O
thing	O
or	O
other	O
always	O
made	O
me	O
procrastinate	O
my	O
constant	O
intention	O
of	O
coming	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
happineſs	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
soon	O
have	O
.	O
What	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
expreſs	O
yourself	O
stout	O
&	O
well	O
&	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
ball	O
at	O
Woburn	B-place
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
most	O
kindly	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
in	O
meeting	O
her	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
little	O
requisite	O
is	O
an	O
invitation	O
,	O
an	O
article	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
rather	O
wonder	O
at	O
,	O
but	O
under	O
existing	O
circumstances	O
it	O
would	O
probably	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
Daughter	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Stowe	B-place
last	O
year	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
peculiar	O
sort	O
of	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
too	O
young	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
Correspondence	O
between	O
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
myself	O
is	O
rather	O
an	O
uncommon	O
event	O
as	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
silence	O
the	O
last	O
letter	O
went	O
from	O
hence	O
&	O
the	O
last	O
account	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
never	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
calls	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
beleive	O
very	O
much	O
averse	O
to	O
writing	O
which	O
can	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
silence	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
principal	O
anxiety	O
is	O
on	O
Colonel	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
s	O
account	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
recently	O
if	O
not	O
now	O
with	O
General	B-pers
Castanos	I-pers
.	O
The	O
aspect	O
of	O
affairs	O
in	O
Spain	B-place
is	O
dismal	O
beyond	O
imagination	O
&	O
holds	O
out	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
general	O
misfortune	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
escape	O
a	O
share	O
.	O
I	O
united	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
Wynne	I-pers
on	O
Monday	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Writer	O
to	O
the	O
Signet	O
,	O
brother	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
of	O
Gilchrist	B-place
near	O
Lanark	B-place
who	O
married	O
Miſs	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
of	O
Scha	B-place
He	O
is	O
of	O
good	O
repute	O
&	O
certainly	O
good	O
figure	O
but	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
consider	O
as	O
so	O
very	O
preeminent	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
my	O
Son	O
next	O
week	O
&	O
hope	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
suppose	O
Xmas	O
day	O
may	O
paſs	O
over	O
uninterrupted	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
with	O
kindest	O
remembrance	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
your	O
very	O
Affect	O
Cousin	O
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzard	I-place
