TOKEN	NE
Suppose	O
We	O
go	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Aufreres	I-pers
on	O
Saturday	O
if	O
you	O
approve	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
soon	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
they	O
wish	O
us	O
to	O
come	O
early	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
again	O
by	O
Twelve	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Most	O
affectly	O
.	O
W.H	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thursday	O
Morng	O
