TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
12	O
th	O
-	O
Decr-	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
puzzle	O
s	O
remains	O
unravelled	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
paper	O
uncut	O
into	O
four	O
equal	O
parts	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
,	O
I	O
attempted	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
after	O
counfounding	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
myself	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
aside	O
.	O
Though	O
descended	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
Mathematician	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
feel	O
myself	O
equal	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
Paper	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
directions	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
,	O
shall	O
now	O
deliver	O
over	O
both	O
the	O
Torments	O
to	O
my	O
Girls	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
their	O
ingenuity	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
it	O
occasioned	O
no	O
little	O
Astonishment	O
at	O
my	O
Breakfast	O
Table	O
,	O
when	O
these	O
puzzles	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
“	O
Dear	O
Mamma	O
,	O
“	O
(	O
said	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Anne	B-pers
)	O
,	O
how	O
differently	O
“	O
Papa	O
must	O
behave	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
from	O
“	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
ever	O
“	O
enter	O
into	O
anybody	O
's	O
head	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
“	O
puzzles	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
.	O
”	O
What	O
Idea	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
Moment	O
formed	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	O
you	O
had	O
taken	O
with	O
her	O
Papa	O
's	O
Dignity	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
You	O
to	O
judge	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
her	O
astonishment	O
shews	O
You	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
good	O
Discipline	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
Wife	O
&	O
Brats	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
for	O
some	O
folks	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
follow	O
my	O
Example	O
.	O
My	O
Boys	O
were	O
both	O
well	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
them	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
had	O
rejoined	O
his	O
Ship	O
(	O
the	O
Imperieuse	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
preparing	O
to	O
sail	O
after	O
the	O
Frigates	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
escaped	O
from	O
Toulon	B-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Corsican	O
Port	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
at	O
Portsmouth	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Resistance	O
is	O
undergoing	O
some	O
repair	O
,	O
having	O
suffered	O
from	O
the	O
Storms	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
six	O
Weeks	O
paſsage	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
.	O
My	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
these	O
some	O
weeks	O
past	O
in	O
Perthshire	B-place
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
comfort	O
Lady	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
MacGregor	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
lately	O
went	O
to	O
Spain	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
L	O
.	O
Dragoons	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
is	O
to	O
paſs	O
her	O
Christmas	O
,	O
at	O
Dunkeld	B-place
,	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
escorts	O
my	O
daughter	O
home	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
My	O
Carriage	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
halfway	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
Us	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
stationary	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Months	O
.	O
past	O
.	O
Of	O
my	O
own	O
intended	O
Motions	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
yet	O
speak	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
regulated	O
by	O
the	O
neceſsity	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
attending	O
Parliament	O
.	O
If	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
arrange	O
my	O
matters	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Wish	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
desirous	O
of	O
quitting	O
my	O
own	O
fireside	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
next	O
.	O
I	O
hate	O
travelling	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
anticipate	O
much	O
Debating	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
defeat	O
of	O
Castanos	B-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
consequent	O
alterations	O
which	O
must	O
take	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Operations	O
of	O
our	O
Forces	O
in	O
Spain	B-place
,	O
are	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
lamented	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Cintra	O
Convention	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Sir	B-pers
Hew	I-pers
is	O
to	O
blame	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
Sir	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
for	O
he	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
desirous	O
of	O
allowing	O
Juniot	B-pers
to	O
retire	O
with	O
the	O
French	O
Troops	O
,	O
as	O
Sir	B-pers
Hew	I-pers
was	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
the	O
Succeſs	O
at	O
Vimeira	B-place
was	O
not	O
followed	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
fought	O
,	O
Sir	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
Burrard	I-pers
must	O
explain	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
old	O
Soldier	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
convinced	O
that	O
our	O
Troops	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
advanced	O
on	O
the	O
Enemy	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
the	O
threshing	O
they	O
ha	O
ve	O
got	O
,	O
was	O
fresh	O
in	O
their	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
Convention	O
might	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
even	O
then	O
have	O
been	O
neceſsary	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
different	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
or	O
her	O
Letters	O
form	O
the	O
Mountains	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
dont	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
smallest	O
particle	O
of	O
Indigo	O
pollutes	O
our	O
little	O
domestick	O
Circle	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
too	O
,	O
is	O
unknown	O
to	O
Us	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
all	O
read	O
Faber	O
.	O
Much	O
have	O
I	O
yawned	O
,	O
much	O
have	O
I	O
slept	O
over	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
too	O
deep	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
much	O
have	O
I	O
admired	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
firm	O
Believer	O
in	O
the	O
fulfilment	O
of	O
Prophecy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
conceived	O
that	O
the	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
Succeſs	O
of	O
the	O
infamous	O
Buonaparte	B-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
astonishing	O
Events	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
all	O
witneſsed	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
accounted	O
for	O
,	O
on	O
any	O
other	O
Ground	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
literal	O
accomplishment	O
of	O
those	O
predictions	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
Daniel	O
,	O
the	O
Apocalypse	O
&	O
c.	O
This	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
superstitious	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
Man	O
to	O
act	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
soundest	O
dictates	O
of	O
human	O
Wisdom	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Iſsue	O
to	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Universe	O
.	O
The	O
Inventor	O
of	O
the	O
Logarithms	O
,	O
published	O
a	O
Treatise	O
on	O
the	O
Revelation	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
Anno	O
1593	O
.	O
He	O
conceived	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
World	O
would	O
not	O
last	O
longer	O
than	O
to	O
the	O
Year	O
1786	O
--	O
All	O
here	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
Love	O
&	O
best	O
Wishes	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
&	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
Napier	B-pers
Best	O
wishes	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
December	O
1808	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
