TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
1	O
Jan	O
.	O
1787	O
My	O
Dear	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
under	O
Your	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
land	O
of	O
the	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
settled	O
so	O
comfortably	O
for	O
the	O
Winter	O
Season	O
:	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
I	O
found	O
on	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
at	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
find	O
You	O
as	O
myself	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
oweing	O
to	O
her	O
silence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
I	O
known	O
where	O
to	O
direct	O
shd	O
.	O
certainly	O
have	O
sent	O
You	O
notice	O
of	O
our	O
arrival	O
in	O
the	O
regions	O
of	O
smoke	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
joyns	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
self	O
in	O
presenting	O
Yourself	O
and	O
Captain	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
with	O
the	O
compts	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
,	O
sincerely	O
wishing	O
You	O
very	O
many	O
happy	O
returns	O
--	O
it	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
You	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
hope	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
of	O
hearing	O
the	O
great	O
event	O
is	O
happily	O
over	O
and	O
of	O
an	O
aditional	O
Happineſs	O
to	O
You	O
and	O
the	O
Familly	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
glad	O
at	O
Your	O
situation	O
and	O
think	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
was	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
it	O
happened	O
very	O
lucky	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
You	O
could	O
remove	O
with	O
Him	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
settled	O
for	O
Yourself	O
have	O
You	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
crouded	O
as	O
poſsible	O
East	O
Indian	O
Nabobs	O
and	O
Irish	O
Fortunes	O
or	O
,	O
fortune	O
hunters	O
in	O
plenty	O
.	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
supose	O
You	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bustles	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
very	O
severe	O
Weather	O
frost	O
and	O
snow	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
bustle	O
(	O
being	O
You	O
know	O
a	O
good	O
Walker	O
)	O
to	O
get	O
sandals	O
to	O
convey	O
me	O
safely	O
over	O
the	O
ice	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
the	O
frost	O
broke	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
so	O
wet	O
and	O
dirty	O
that	O
I	O
want	O
Stilts	O
instead	O
of	O
cloggs	O
--	O
We	O
found	O
our	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
just	O
recover	O
ing	O
from	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
painfull	O
illneſs	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
the	O
Shingles	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
got	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
as	O
good	O
spirits	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
an	O
invalid	O
out	O
one	O
day	O
and	O
forced	O
to	O
keep	O
house	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
grown	O
much	O
older	O
considering	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
who	O
I	O
thought	O
looked	O
very	O
indifferrent	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
so	O
fond	O
of	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
her	O
continual	O
attacks	O
must	O
wear	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
Masquerade	O
as	O
to	O
dreſses	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
every	O
body	O
was	O
complaining	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
feathers	O
or	O
flowers	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
pulled	O
out	O
their	O
powder	O
&	O
hair	O
yet	O
every	O
Body	O
's	O
cap	O
was	O
equaly	O
troublesome	O
I	O
was	O
entertained	O
when	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
was	O
presented	O
(	O
as	O
a	O
bride	O
)	O
being	O
tall	O
and	O
dreſst	O
out	O
with	O
feathers	O
--	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Kiſs	O
the	O
hand	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
brushed	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
face	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
not	O
held	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
as	O
back	O
as	O
poſsible	O
&	O
her	O
hand	O
as	O
forward	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
gracefull	O
posture	O
or	O
,	O
a	O
Gracious	O
one	O
--	O
Your	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
but	O
has	O
got	O
an	O
inflamation	O
on	O
her	O
lungs	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
very	O
ill	O
--	O
it	O
generaly	O
attacks	O
her	O
on	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fresh	O
air	O
into	O
these	O
smoky	O
regions	O
by	O
what	O
You	O
say	O
there	O
seems	O
little	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
You	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
selfish	O
enough	O
to	O
repine	O
at	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
:	O
and	O
at	O
present	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
call	O
that	O
is	O
likly	O
to	O
draw	O
us	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
We	O
all	O
joyn	O
in	O
compts	O
to	O
Yourself	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Black	I-pers
who	O
we	O
hope	O
is	O
got	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
accept	O
the	O
Affectionate	O
compts	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
s	O
Yours	O
Affectionately	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Park	O
Str	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1787	O
