TOKEN	NE
Cork	B-place
21	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1785	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
You	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
your	O
Letter	O
giving	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Marriage	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
very	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
as	O
miserable	O
&	O
unhappy	O
in	O
his	O
new	O
Situation	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
surprised	O
at	O
not	O
having	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
your	O
Letter	O
'till	O
last	O
Night	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
having	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
Weeks	O
,	O
looking	O
after	O
a	O
Legacy	O
I	O
lately	O
succeeded	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
a	O
distant	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
(	O
a	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Naper	I-pers
)	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
who	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
an	O
Executor	O
&	O
Residuary	O
Legatee	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
pocket	O
about	O
Three	O
Thousand	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
her	O
relations	O
have	O
however	O
attacked	O
the	O
Will	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
good	O
ground	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
busineſs	O
will	O
be	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Prerogative	O
Court	O
next	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
administered	O
,	O
paid	O
the	O
Legacies	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
If	O
I	O
carry	O
my	O
cause	O
I	O
shall	O
directly	O
point	O
at	O
a	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
You	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
must	O
pray	O
fervently	O
for	O
my	O
Succeſs	O
,	O
if	O
You	O
have	O
any	O
desire	O
of	O
seeing	O
me	O
in	O
Britain	B-place
.	O
Maria	B-pers
grows	O
large	O
&	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
next	O
Month	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
event	O
happens	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
fail	O
to	O
communicate	O
it	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
She	O
begs	O
to	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
good	O
wish	O
for	O
the	O
happineſs	O
&	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
Yourself	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
ever	O
your	O
very	O
sincere	O
friend	O
&	O
affectie	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
