TOKEN	NE
7	O
th	O
May	O
1789	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
intendi	O
n	O
g	O
every	O
day	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
of	O
an	O
absolute	O
age	O
never	O
indeed	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
last	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
good	O
intentions	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
as	O
upon	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
detourne	O
ed	O
&	O
divertd	O
from	O
been	O
put	O
into	O
execution	O
by	O
the	O
various	O
constant	O
occurences	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
&	O
moment	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
or	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
occupied	O
--	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
accounting	O
for	O
my	O
time	O
and	O
silence	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
ashamed	O
of	O
--	O
no	O
what	O
one	O
does	O
from	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
night	O
here	O
deserves	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
dignified	O
with	O
by	O
the	O
na	O
me	O
of	O
occupation	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
hurry	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
something	O
that	O
carries	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
importance	O
,	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
neceſsity	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
is	O
vain	O
,	O
empty	O
&	O
unsatisfactory	O
--	O
such	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
however	O
it	O
demands	O
the	O
attention	O
&	O
fills	O
up	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
miserable	O
Beings	O
who	O
are	O
confined	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
;	O
&	O
must	O
account	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
not	O
doi	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
like	O
&	O
prefer	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
this	O
instance	O
particularly	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
besides	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
tormented	O
for	O
this	O
month	O
past	O
with	O
a	O
rheumat	O
ic	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Blyster	O
on	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
--	O
My	O
Father	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
these	O
6	O
weeks	O
past	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
duri	O
n	O
g	O
3	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
stirred	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
is	O
returned	O
,	O
is	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
to	O
Harrowgate	B-place
for	O
a	O
Month	O
which	O
will	O
bring	O
him	O
&	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
June	O
when	O
thanked	O
be	O
God	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
!	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
to	O
expreſs	O
the	O
disgust	O
the	O
abhorrence	O
I	O
have	O
conceived	O
for	O
this	O
place	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
growing	O
these	O
some	O
years	O
&	O
now	O
is	O
arrived	O
at	O
a	O
degree	O
that	O
makes	O
it	O
quite	O
insupp	O
ortable	O
Oh	O
!	O
that	O
something	O
would	O
happen	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
longing	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
interrupted	O
in	O
this	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
&	O
now	O
resume	O
it	O
&	O
mean	O
to	O
conclude	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Richmond	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
.	O
Never	O
was	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
so	O
heavenly	O
&	O
enchanting	O
as	O
the	O
weather	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sitti	O
n	O
g	O
with	O
my	O
window	O
open	O
hearing	O
the	O
Birds	O
sing	O
&	O
absolutely	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
leaves	O
burst	O
into	O
life	O
--	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
can	O
be	O
prettier	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
than	O
the	O
scene	O
before	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
however	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
description	O
,	O
but	O
tell	O
you	O
somethi	O
n	O
g	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
about	O
myself	O
or	O
rather	O
ourselves	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
gone	O
abroad	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
--	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
sev'night	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
already	O
heard	O
from	O
him	O
from	O
Paris	B-place
where	O
he	O
arrived	O
safe	O
after	O
a	O
good	O
paſsage	O
&	O
pleasant	O
journey	O
,	O
&	O
where	O
the	O
concourse	O
of	O
People	O
who	O
were	O
collected	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
aſsemblée	O
des	O
notables	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
wth	O
the	O
utmost	O
difficulty	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Lodgi	O
n	O
g	O
in	O
any	O
Hôtel	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
means	O
to	O
remain	O
there	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
depend	O
on	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
you	O
will	O
perhaps	O
often	O
hear	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
that	O
the	O
Ki	O
n	O
g	O
is	O
ill	O
--	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
God	O
be	O
thanked	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
&	O
all	O
such	O
sincere	O
Lovers	O
of	O
his	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
wish	O
him	O
he	O
feels	O
weak	O
and	O
exhausted	O
--	O
how	O
natural	O
,	O
how	O
inevitable	O
after	O
such	O
an	O
illneſs	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
--	O
a	O
day	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
forget	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Q	O
s	O
House	O
first	O
of	O
course	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
th	O
e	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
spoke	O
my	O
knees	O
trembled	O
my	O
tongue	O
faultered	O
&	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
utter	O
a	O
word	O
but	O
burst	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
fit	O
of	O
tears	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
beginni	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
so	O
grand	O
so	O
stupendous	O
so	O
imposant	O
as	O
the	O
Building	O
of	O
St	O
Pauls	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
affecti	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
Solemn	O
as	O
the	O
whole	O
Service	O
--	O
we	O
all	O
walked	O
in	O
proceſsion	O
thro	O
'	O
th	O
e	O
isle	O
amidst	O
the	O
songs	O
of	O
5000	O
Children	O
--	O
the	O
Sermon	O
was	O
preached	O
by	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
the	O
finest	O
I	O
d	O
ever	O
heard	O
I	O
did	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
but	O
cry	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
conceiv	O
e	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
so	O
affecti	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
the	O
Ki	O
n	O
g	O
was	O
devout	O
&	O
attentive	O
as	O
usual	O
Porteus	B-pers
much	O
affected	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
;	O
laughi	O
n	O
g	O
immoderatly	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
--	O
every	O
other	O
Person	O
impreſsed	O
with	O
the	O
awfulneſs	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
&	O
the	O
occasion	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
recovered	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
a	O
week	O
afterwa	O
rds	O
I	O
remember	O
promising	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Ball	O
at	O
Whites	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
magnificent	O
&	O
perfectly	O
well	O
conducted	O
--	O
the	O
Pantheon	O
was	O
lit	O
up	O
with	O
enclosed	O
Lamps	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
every	O
woman	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
in	O
white	O
&	O
gold	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarquably	O
good	O
one	O
--	O
Brook	O
s	O
Ball	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Opera	O
--	O
magnificent	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
pleasant	O
as	O
the	O
crowd	O
was	O
amazi	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
neither	O
D.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Y	I-pers
.	I-pers
nor	O
I	O
were	O
there	O
owi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
Bell	B-pers
's	O
objecti	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
her	O
Friend	O
's	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
there	O
--	O
this	O
original	O
one	O
was	O
altered	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
given	O
away	O
our	O
Tickets	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
--	O
the	O
Club	O
of	O
Boodles	O
give	O
a	O
Ball	O
at	O
Ranalaugh	B-place
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
--	O
the	O
French	O
&	O
Spanish	O
Ambaſsadors	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
magnif	O
ic	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
goes	O
&	O
we	O
attend	O
her	O
--	O
Good	O
God	O
how	O
sick	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
it	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
leaing	O
to	O
draw	O
flowers	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
s	O
Man	O
&	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
first	O
leſson	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
it	O
vastly	O
--	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
my	O
first	O
decent	O
production	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
yet	O
not	O
seen	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
but	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
she	O
rings	O
the	O
Bell	O
&	O
is	O
comi	O
n	O
g	O
up	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
called	O
on	O
each	O
other	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
London	O
succeſs	O
--	O
ie	O
never	O
meeti	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
well	O
--	O
that	O
dear	O
little	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
grows	O
&	O
speaks	O
&	O
is	O
not	O
spoilt	O
--	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
yourself	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
begs	O
her	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
talks	O
of	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
at	O
Courteenhall	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
June	O
--	O
happy	O
--	O
she	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
once	O
more	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
--	O
pray	O
write	O
soon	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
is	O
well	O
chès	O
vous	O
--	O
Saturday	O
9	O
th	O
May	O
.	O
To	O
Ly	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
