TOKEN	NE
June	O
25	O
--	O
89	O
--	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
Queen	O
's	O
Parade	O
This	O
day	O
my	O
dearest	O
Love	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
off	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Earles	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
this	O
morning	O
into	O
Hampse	B-place
.	I-place
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
&	O
then	O
return	O
here	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
left	O
Bath	B-place
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brownlow	I-pers
was	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Brownlow	I-pers
's	O
conduct	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
his	O
son	O
400£	O
Pr	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
addition	O
to	O
his	O
Income	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
fancy	O
they	O
were	O
distreſsed	O
--	O
Wed	O
.	O
Drank	O
the	O
Waters	O
--	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
happy	O
by	O
receiving	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
|	O
20	O
|	O
--	O
I	O
approve	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
yr-	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fred.k	I-pers
the	O
busineſs	O
he	O
writes	O
about	O
is	O
curious	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
title	O
sufft	O
.	O
for	O
a	O
morgage	O
without	O
your	O
relinquishing	O
all	O
claims	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
a	O
convincing	O
proof	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
claims	O
)	O
upon	O
that	O
Estate	O
--	O
otherwise	O
the	O
deed	O
we	O
signed	O
was	O
sufft	O
.	O
release	O
--	O
however	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
proper	O
shall	O
be	O
done	O
--	O
with	O
this	O
salvo	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
as	O
much	O
attention	O
to	O
this	O
busineſs	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
was	O
shewn	O
by	O
that	O
family	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
Town	O
as	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
equally	O
as	O
much	O
expence	O
&	O
no	O
more	O
--	O
Yr	O
.	O
Lr	O
.	O
to	O
him	O
is	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
wished	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
poſseſsing	O
finer	O
feelings	O
it	O
is	O
calculated	O
to	O
rouse	O
them	O
&	O
make	O
him	O
blush	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
spirit	O
of	O
independence	O
wh	O
.	O
gratifies	O
me	O
--	O
Dont	O
fancy	O
that	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
region	O
of	O
Clouds	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
if	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
Somersetshire	B-place
people	O
now	O
at	O
Buxton	B-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
impertinence	O
to	O
exclaim	O
against	O
Buxton	B-place
Weather	O
now	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
seldom	O
fair	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
24	O
hours	O
it	O
has	O
rained	O
more	O
than	O
15	O
&	O
exceſsively	O
hard	O
--	O
yesterday	O
&	O
today	O
every	O
body	O
complained	O
of	O
Cold	O
and	O
longed	O
for	O
a	O
fire	O
--	O
Thursday	O
--	O
This	O
morning	O
Capt	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
left	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
regret	O
his	O
absence	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
modest	O
sensible	O
man	O
,	O
has	O
seen	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
service	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
his	O
profession	O
when	O
our	O
Madcaps	O
return	O
from	O
Bristol	B-place
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
too	O
soon	O
--	O
they	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
3	O
guineas	O
a	O
day	O
--	O
drink	O
constantly	O
2	O
&	O
sometimes	O
3	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Claret	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
comes	O
from	O
Barbados	B-place
&	O
there	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
D——	B-pers
of	I-pers
C——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
complete	O
Blackguard	O
in	O
nature	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
talks	O
to	O
women	O
in	O
Sea	O
phrases	O
--	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
a	O
pamphlet	O
called	O
the	O
Royal	O
Interview	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
supposed	O
conversation	O
that	O
paſsed	O
between	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
&	O
the	O
P——	O
it	O
is	O
ye-	O
best	O
written	O
of	O
any	O
publication	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
in	O
strong	O
nervous	O
language	O
without	O
any	O
party	O
violence	O
--	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
then	O
points	O
out	O
the	O
Opporty	O
.	O
that	O
the	O
P	O
.	O
had	O
of	O
making	O
himself	O
idolized	O
by	O
His	O
Nation	O
--	O
respected	O
by	O
all	O
parties	O
,	O
admired	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
&	O
his	O
Name	O
&	O
conduct	O
handed	O
down	O
to	O
posterity	O
as	O
a	O
Model	O
for	O
future	O
Princes	O
--	O
he	O
then	O
points	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
--	O
&	O
what	O
would	O
probably	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
Conduct	O
--	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
lent	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
it	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
to	O
shew	O
to	O
his	O
Countrymen	O
--	O
who	O
's	O
conduct	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
with	O
patience	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
expect	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
something	O
about	O
my	O
self	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
been	O
here	O
a	O
Week	O
--	O
this	O
day	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
perfectly	O
well	O
--	O
the	O
Waters	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
excellent	O
Spirits	O
&	O
health	O
--	O
the	O
Sun	O
has	O
shone	O
for	O
3	O
hours	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Showers	O
,	O
which	O
enlivened	O
every	O
body	O
&	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
so	O
much	O
pleasure	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
improvement	O
I	O
make	O
in	O
playing	O
upon	O
the	O
violincello	O
which	O
I	O
feel	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
yr-	O
amusement	O
in	O
time	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
delighted	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
greatest	O
earthly	O
bliſs	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
's	O
power	O
to	O
please	O
&	O
make	O
those	O
happy	O
who	O
are	O
most	O
dear	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
surely	O
no	O
man	O
can	O
love	O
a	O
Woman	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
Husband	O
loves	O
you	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
about	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
so	O
calm	O
a	O
determination	O
of	O
conquering	O
every	O
difficulty	O
than	O
In	O
this	O
instance	O
--	O
My	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
no	O
flatterer	O
,	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
encouragement	O
,	O
by	O
aſsuring	O
me	O
that	O
no	O
person	O
can	O
improve	O
faster	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
--	O
the	O
great	O
difficulty	O
in	O
this	O
instrument	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
obtain	O
at	O
first	O
a	O
proper	O
position	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
without	O
which	O
there	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
great	O
execution	O
--	O
the	O
cramp	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
thumb	O
reduces	O
me	O
too	O
often	O
to	O
a	O
stand	O
still	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
to	O
conquer	O
all	O
impediments	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
learning	O
Italian	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Master	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
paſs	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
acquiring	O
a	O
knowledge	O
of	O
that	O
delicate	O
language	O
--	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
Tuscan	O
,	O
and	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
thorough	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Languages	O
--	O
he	O
resided	O
20	O
years	O
in	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
now	O
teaches	O
that	O
language	O
;	O
--	O
Now	O
you	O
shall	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
paſs	O
my	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
rise	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
wake	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
this	O
morning	O
20	O
minutes	O
before	O
4	O
--	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsd	O
I	O
made	O
myself	O
perfect	O
in	O
yesterdays	O
Italian	O
leſson	O
&	O
then	O
read	O
in	O
Ganganelle	O
's	O
Letters	O
(	O
in	O
Italian	O
)	O
till	O
6	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ye-	O
bath	O
and	O
returned	O
by	O
7	O
--	O
&	O
till	O
9	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
dont	O
bathe	O
,	O
that	O
time	O
is	O
employed	O
in	O
drinking	O
the	O
Waters	O
&	O
exercise	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dreſsed	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
done	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
by	O
an	O
excellent	O
Friſseur	O
for	O
5/	O
a	O
week	O
)	O
then	O
breakfasted	O
en	O
famille	O
with	O
Ct	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
read	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
every	O
morning	O
to	O
Madam	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
&	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Signior	B-pers
Borzacchini	I-pers
,	O
where	O
I	O
stay	O
till	O
one	O
--	O
then	O
to	O
Bull	O
's	O
library	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
papers	O
--	O
return	O
home	O
to	O
transcribe	O
my	O
Italian	O
Leſson	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
learn	O
from	O
a	O
manuscript	O
grammar	O
)	O
which	O
generally	O
occupies	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
steal	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
reading	O
,	O
dinner	O
,	O
tea	O
,	O
&	O
supper	O
employ	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
--	O
/	O
I	O
called	O
this	O
morning	O
Thursday	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
between	O
my	O
two	O
leſsons	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Herschell	I-pers
--	O
afterwards	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
's	O
&	O
was	O
again	O
unsucceſful	O
at	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
--	O
at	O
6	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
wth-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
stayed	O
only	O
½	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
jumbled	O
this	O
letter	O
abominably	O
--	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
have	O
bathed	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
has	O
been	O
fair	O
thō	O
cold	O
&	O
I	O
wear	O
greatcoat	O
--	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
my	O
leſsons	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
S.	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
had	O
called	O
&	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
a	O
Lady	O
had	O
ans	O
wered	O
it	O
pr	O
oved	O
to	O
be	O
Dr	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
--	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
returned	O
from	O
an	O
agreeable	O
vi	O
to	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
She	O
had	O
understood	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
was	O
just	O
gog	O
--	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
had	O
called	O
3	O
times	O
--	O
She	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
Bath	B-place
,	O
who	O
's	O
mother	O
now	O
lies	O
dead	O
&	O
who	O
's	O
son	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
dying	O
,	O
that	O
ord	O
's	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
a	O
note	O
this	O
afternoon	O
&	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
waiting	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
morrow	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
often	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
on	O
monday	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
to	O
a	O
small	O
party	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
on	O
the	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
's	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
--	O
Pray	O
let	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundel	I-pers
kno	O
w	O
how	O
highly	O
obliged	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
her	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
aſsuredly	O
wi	O
ll	O
not	O
fail	O
in	O
making	O
good	O
the	O
loſs	O
she	O
deplores	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
particular	O
obligation	O
for	O
the	O
care	O
She	O
took	O
in	O
fitting	O
me	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
smickets	O
adorned	O
with	O
demi	O
rouffles	O
--	O
You	O
delight	O
me	O
with	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
Child	O
--	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
engaging	O
little	O
creature	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Months	O
--	O
yesterday	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
3	O
years	O
old	O
at	O
ye-	O
pump	O
room	O
wh	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
like	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
only	O
taller	O
than	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
that	O
age	O
I	O
flirted	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
--	O
her	O
Father	O
who	O
is	O
unlike	O
any	O
other	O
Father	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
heard	O
takes	O
the	O
child	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
admired	O
--	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
foolish	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
could	O
repeat	O
200	O
lines	O
of	O
Gay	O
's	O
fables	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
all	O
those	O
early	O
acquisitions	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
ripening	O
of	O
the	O
understanding	O
&	O
is	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
ye-	O
strength	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
our	O
child	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
backward	O
now	O
,	O
may	O
know	O
ten	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
Years	O
old	O
--	O
Saturday	O
--	O
desire	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
kiſs	O
this	O
place	O
20	O
times	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
as	O
many	O
kiſses	O
--	O
how	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
&	O
our	O
little	O
Darling	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pity	O
our	O
finances	O
are	O
so	O
limited	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
such	O
an	O
excellent	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
fortune	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
too	O
happy	O
perhaps	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
rich	O
or	O
even	O
independant	O
--	O
this	O
subject	O
distreſses	O
therefore	O
will	O
take	O
another	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
&	O
was	O
settg	O
out	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
two	O
Notes	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
to	O
in	O
vite	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
join	O
her	O
party	O
in	O
a	O
country	O
tea	O
drinking	O
this	O
aftern	O
oon	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
right	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
every	O
civility	O
,	O
I	O
consented	O
--	O
the	O
other	O
no	O
te	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
yesterday	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
--	O
I	O
ansd	O
.	O
no	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
seen	O
her	O
fine	O
drawgs	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
said	O
“	O
O	O
She	O
is	O
infinitely	O
better	O
than	O
her	O
drawings	O
”	O
--	O
and	O
her	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
transcribe	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
She	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
compliment	O
yesterday	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
political	O
pamphlet	O
--	O
“	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
compts	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
She	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
naming	O
him	O
yesterday	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
wd	O
.	O
favor	O
her	O
wth-	O
his	O
company	O
tomorrow	O
Evg	O
at	O
7	O
to	O
meet	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
She	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
requires	O
some	O
apology	O
to	O
have	O
sent	O
a	O
pamphlet	O
made	O
so	O
very	O
dirty	O
by	O
the	O
numbers	O
it	O
was	O
lent	O
to	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
is	O
too	O
much	O
opposition	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
its	O
readers	O
”	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
delicate	O
manner	O
of	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
talk	O
politicks	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
She	O
was	O
in	O
excellent	O
Spirits	O
,	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
seemed	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
“	O
She	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Orde	I-pers
very	O
lately	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
truth	O
in	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
swelling	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
fat	O
enou	O
gh	O
--	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
say	O
,	O
his	O
understanding	O
is	O
actually	O
clearer	O
than	O
ever	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
may	O
arise	O
from	O
his	O
having	O
in	O
some	O
degree	O
left	O
off	O
his	O
unkingly	O
tricks	O
--	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
told	O
me	O
many	O
Anecdotes	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
room	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
O	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
&	O
will	O
put	O
this	O
into	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
's	O
servant	O
,	O
tho	O
often	O
called	O
to	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
answer	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
my	O
Sisters	O
are	O
at	O
Matlock	B-place
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
ever	O
dear	O
Wife	O
God	O
bleſs	O
&	O
preserve	O
You	O
&	O
our	O
lovely	O
Girl	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
affy	O
and	O
faithfully	O
Yr	O
.	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Say	O
everything	O
that	O
is	O
kind	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Sisters	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
J.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
X	O
post	O
