TOKEN	NE
Tunbridge	B-place
Wells	I-place
Friday	O
Augst	O
:	O
20	O
th	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
'till	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
Ly-	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
that	O
He	O
this	O
Morning	O
did	O
us	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
breakfasting	O
here	O
,	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
lively	O
&	O
agreable	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
ever	O
an	O
Invalid	O
--	O
Every	O
body	O
here	O
says	O
He	O
has	O
found	O
great	O
Benefit	O
by	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
&	O
Air	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
meets	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
upon	O
the	O
Pantiles	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
meeting	O
him	O
carried	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
waited	O
2	O
hours	O
,	O
--	O
in	O
vain	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
few	O
People	O
,	O
wd	O
:	O
tempt	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
so	O
disagreable	O
a	O
Walk	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
Europe	B-place
there	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
dirty	O
or	O
tiresome	O
a	O
One	O
--	O
He	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
much	O
better	O
Spirits	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
aſsure	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
that	O
I	O
should	O
feel	O
happy	O
in	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
shew	O
any	O
Civility	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sayse	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Rooms	O
,	O
Publick	O
Breakfasts	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
Things	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
would	O
very	O
naturally	O
feel	O
a	O
Civility	O
&	O
Attention	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
at	O
present	O
prefers	O
walking	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
,	O
&	O
skipping	O
over	O
Heath	O
like	O
a	O
Lambkin	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
foolish	O
enough	O
to	O
prefer	O
walking	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
walking	O
the	O
Pantiles	O
of	O
or	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
heated	O
Rooms	O
--	O
If	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sayse	I-pers
will	O
condescend	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
stupid	O
Old	O
Mother	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
vastly	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
(	O
rather	O
an	O
Intimacy	O
)	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Sheridan	I-pers
the	I-pers
Father	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
some	O
hopes	O
he	O
will	O
teach	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
without	O
Joking	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Reading	O
next	O
wedy	O
:	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
invited	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
Honor	O
of	O
calling	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
waited	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
(	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
also	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Little	O
One	O
are	O
going	O
on	O
well	O
.	O
Adieu	O
here	O
are	O
more	O
than	O
six	O
Lines	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
be	O
very	O
generous	O
in	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
six	O
pages	O
in	O
return	O
,	O
Yrs	O
:	O
sincerely	O
PD	B-pers
Sat	O
Morng	O
8	O
'	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
good	O
Accounts	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
J.	I-pers
Penn	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Vine	I-place
--	O
13	O
miles	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
inclose	O
you	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
returns	O
his	O
best	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
about	O
the	O
Calabrese	O
&	O
the	O
Drawing	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
trouble	O
him	O
with	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D——	I-pers
--	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
--	O
N.B	O
.	O
Dickenson	B-pers
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
advised	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
should	O
spend	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
the	B-place
Continent	I-place
after	O
we	O
were	O
married	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
August	O
1784	O
To	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
Clargis	O
Street	O
