TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
We	O
are	O
extremely	O
disappointed	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
have	O
determined	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
your	O
visit	O
to	O
your	O
Friends	O
in	O
London	B-place
to	O
so	O
distant	O
a	O
period	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
really	O
promised	O
myself	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
having	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
personally	O
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
my	O
obligations	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
attention	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
a	O
late	O
occasion	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
left	O
us	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
to	O
join	O
his	O
Regiment	O
at	O
Nottingham	B-place
,	O
his	O
equipment	O
with	O
his	O
Commiſsion	O
have	O
cost	O
me	O
at	O
least	O
£1500	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
add	O
an	O
Allowance	O
of	O
Two	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
his	O
pay	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
manage	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
answer	O
,	O
for	O
further	O
I	O
positively	O
can	O
not	O
aſsist	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
made	O
an	O
exchange	O
of	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
North	B-place
of	I-place
Ireland	I-place
for	O
a	O
very	O
moderate	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
Suffolk	B-place
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
loser	O
of	O
about	O
£	O
300	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
reside	O
upon	O
it	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
tolerable	O
House	O
with	O
good	O
accommodations	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
mean	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Country	O
retreat	O
which	O
will	O
not	O
only	O
defray	O
all	O
expences	O
attending	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
my	O
Son	O
s	O
allowance	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
must	O
stand	O
in	O
balance	O
for	O
my	O
loſs	O
of	O
income	O
.	O
The	O
Living	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Stanton	B-place
,	O
equally	O
distant	O
from	O
Thetford	B-place
&	O
St.	B-place
Edmund	I-place
,	I-place
Bury	I-place
,	O
a	O
very	O
beautiful	O
Country	O
,	O
with	O
excellent	O
roads	O
&	O
a	O
capital	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Enclosed	O
is	O
my	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
have	O
lent	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
executed	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
attested	O
by	O
a	O
Notary	O
Publick	O
&	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
years	O
Interest	O
will	O
be	O
due	O
upon	O
it	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
next	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
please	O
to	O
direct	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
receive	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
presents	O
to	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
£1500	O
for	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
by	O
law	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
Security	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
in	O
Two	O
Years	O
in	O
equal	O
yearly	O
payments	O
this	O
Security	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
hand	O
over	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
addition	O
to	O
my	O
Bond	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
conceive	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
any	O
collateral	O
Security	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
give	O
you	O
upon	O
my	O
Estate	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
At	O
all	O
events	O
when	O
you	O
find	O
occasion	O
for	O
your	O
money	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
forthcoming	O
after	O
Six	O
months	O
notice	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
you	O
may	O
rest	O
aſsured	O
that	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Bond	O
alone	O
is	O
security	O
sufficient	O
&	O
indubitable	O
for	O
God	O
forbid	O
that	O
I	O
shoud	O
trifle	O
with	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
matter	O
as	O
this	O
!	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
fully	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
transaction	O
&	O
of	O
your	O
conduct	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
the	O
Bond	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
convenient	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
safely	O
by	O
Post	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
you	O
proposed	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
preferr	O
'd	O
from	O
my	O
impatience	O
to	O
acquit	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
God	O
Daughter	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
sincerely	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
encreasing	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
conceive	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
happineſs	O
upon	O
her	O
acquisition	O
of	O
a	O
Daughter	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
indeed	O
a	O
very	O
beautiful	O
Child	O
,	O
&	O
perfectly	O
healthy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
being	O
her	O
God	O
Father	O
also	O
.	O
All	O
little	O
unfriendly	O
ideas	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S_t	I-pers
might	O
have	O
given	O
foundation	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
perfectly	O
obliterated	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
is	O
beginning	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Friends	O
a	O
little	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
in	O
a	O
very	O
private	O
way	O
next	O
Friday	O
evening	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
&	O
Dutcheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
with	O
their	O
whole	O
Family	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
formerly	O
inhabited	O
by	O
the	O
Imperial	O
Minister	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
me	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
our	O
not	O
seeing	O
you	O
the	O
next	O
spring	O
is	O
not	O
owing	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
œconomical	O
suggestions	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
however	O
I	O
confeſs	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
ridiculed	O
,	O
nor	O
am	O
I	O
disposed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
be	O
rememberd	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
say	O
nothing	O
from	O
my	O
Daughter	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
means	O
to	O
write	O
immediately	O
herself	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
,	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
--	O
249	O
February	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
.	O
