TOKEN	NE
My	O
dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
ye	O
Long	O
loan	O
of	O
ye	O
Picture	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
with	O
this	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
repeat	O
my	O
Apologies	O
for	O
having	O
kept	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
for	O
many	O
Months	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
to	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
Reap	O
'd	O
so	O
little	O
Advantage	O
from	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
consider	O
ye	O
having	O
had	O
so	O
pretty	O
a	O
Production	O
before	O
me	O
without	O
having	O
made	O
any	O
Use	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
an	O
Additional	O
melancholly	O
Proof	O
of	O
my	O
Capacity	O
of	O
throwing	O
away	O
many	O
Aſsistances	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
better	O
Purpose	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
Greek	O
Hebrew	O
to	O
You	O
who	O
never	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Such	O
thing	O
--	O
So	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
an	O
End	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
unintelligible	O
&	O
scrawl	O
'd	O
Epistle	O
--	O
only	O
flattering	O
myself	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
yr	O
oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
sincere	O
humble	O
Sert	O
H	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Kew	B-place
Sunday	O
Night	O
