TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
It	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
Note	O
when	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
both	O
there	O
&	O
here	O
unite	O
in	O
being	O
truly	O
concern	O
'd	O
for	O
your	O
Disorder	O
&	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
all	O
imaginable	O
care	O
of	O
yrself	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Sound	O
of	O
a	O
Sore	O
Throat	O
(	O
thō	O
I	O
hope	O
yrs	O
.	O
is	O
no	O
alarming	O
Sort	O
)	O
does	O
not	O
allow	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Princes	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
here	O
could	O
be	O
useful	O
to	O
you	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
particularly	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
Deal	B-place
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
a	O
little	O
proper	O
Care	O
will	O
restore	O
you	O
to	O
perfect	O
health	O
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affly	O
C.Finch	B-pers
St	O
James	O
's	O
Wednesday	O
½	O
past	O
3	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
