TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
It	O
is	O
allmost	O
presumptious	O
to	O
write	O
when	O
I	O
inclose	O
so	O
valuable	O
a	O
Letter	O
as	O
one	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
must	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
anxiety	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
so	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
aſsure	O
you	O
likewise	O
upon	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wish	O
to	O
create	O
my	O
friend	O
any	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
therefore	O
wished	O
to	O
conceal	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
really	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uncomfortable	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
low	O
the	O
latter	O
is	O
rather	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
thing	O
to	O
happen	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
over	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
equal	O
to	O
two	O
Hours	O
walking	O
upon	O
the	O
Terrace	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
uncomfortable	O
than	O
Ever	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
short	O
the	O
being	O
from	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morg	O
.	O
till	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
Duty	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Bathing	O
agrees	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
infinite	O
Service	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Drs	O
I	O
have	O
stole	O
this	O
moment	O
&	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Monday	O
17	O
th	O
