TOKEN	NE
Octbr	O
.	O
1786	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
It	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
pen	O
to	O
paper	O
,	O
except	O
on	O
busineſs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
rather	O
taken	O
a	O
dislike	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
now	O
can	O
not	O
refrain	O
from	O
wishing	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
joy	O
on	O
the	O
expectation	O
of	O
her	O
soon	O
being	O
a	O
Mother	O
;	O
Every	O
sincere	O
wish	O
for	O
your	O
safety	O
,	O
&	O
welfare	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
your	O
friends	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
anxious	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
than	O
my	O
Self	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
my	O
Summer	O
,	O
very	O
retired	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
chearful	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
doing	O
some	O
good	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
already	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
how	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
has	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
ill	O
treated	O
by	O
five	O
of	O
his	O
Children	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
youngest	O
girl	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
god-daughter	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
disposition	O
&	O
a	O
understanding	O
,	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
during	O
her	O
vacation	O
,	O
fearing	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
totally	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
hope	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sav	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
is	O
now	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Miſs	O
Duttons	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
good	O
example	O
,	O
&	O
kind	O
treatment	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
proper	O
impreſsion	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Young	O
&	O
tender	O
mind	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
pleasing	O
reflection	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
.	O
&	O
since	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
Anna-Marie	B-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Bruſsels	B-place
for	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
her	O
family	O
are	O
behaving	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
scandelous	O
manner	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
tried	O
all	O
means	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
with	O
themselves	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
nobly	O
withstood	O
,	O
both	O
their	O
intreaties	O
,	O
&	O
menaces	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
at	O
last	O
from	O
ill	O
treatment	O
to	O
fly	O
from	O
her	O
father	O
s	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chollet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
now	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
the	O
good	O
accounts	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
is	O
truly	O
a	O
most	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
&	O
amiable	O
Girl	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sweetneſs	O
of	O
temper	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
does	O
not	O
often	O
meet	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
quite	O
love	O
her	O
;	O
&	O
have	O
promis	O
'd	O
her	O
my	O
protection	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
house	O
shall	O
be	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
till	O
her	O
father	O
returns	O
from	O
Paris	B-place
;	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
fifteen	O
Months	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
busineſs	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
ten	O
thousand	O
pound	O
per	O
year	O
;	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
story	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
have	O
forgot	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
expected	O
home	O
these	O
six	O
Months	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
wild	O
project	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
unlike	O
himself	O
;	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
never	O
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
appears	O
a	O
just	O
plea	O
for	O
his	O
delay	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
real	O
sentiments	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
resolution	O
,	O
&	O
firmneſs	O
,	O
to	O
doe	O
himself	O
justice	O
,	O
&	O
those	O
that	O
deserve	O
his	O
future	O
favors	O
;	O
he	O
certainly	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
father	O
,	O
&	O
loved	O
all	O
his	O
Children	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
faulty	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
pitty	O
him	O
most	O
sincerely	O
in	O
his	O
present	O
situation	O
;	O
for	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
alternative	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
shut	O
his	O
Doors	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
task	O
for	O
a	O
Parent	O
to	O
perform	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
young	O
friend	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
Age	O
till	O
Febry	O
.	O
&	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Broad	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
prudence	O
,	O
&	O
gen	O
tle	O
manner	O
,	O
got	O
introduced	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
familys	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Court	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
inform	O
'd	O
left	O
a	O
great	O
character	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
many	O
Friends	O
;	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
some	O
stile	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
father	O
supported	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
pride	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
natural	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
greatly	O
admire	O
her	O
good	O
sense	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
set	O
up	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
account	O
of	O
R	B-pers
:	I-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
after	O
receiving	O
fourteen	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
since	O
his	O
father	O
s	O
Death	O
,	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
Man	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
upon	O
speaking	O
terms	O
,	O
since	O
our	O
busineſs	O
was	O
finish	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
he	O
has	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Old	O
Lodging	O
into	O
a	O
worse	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
a	O
wretch	O
.	O
--	O
how	O
perfectly	O
did	O
his	O
poor	O
Dear	O
Father	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
one	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
himself	O
!	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
kindly	O
rememberd	O
to	O
your	O
better	O
half	O
pray	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
lucky	O
in	O
recommending	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
quite	O
happy	O
that	O
she	O
suit	O
s	O
you	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
with	O
best	O
compliments	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
E	B-pers
G	I-pers
My	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
have	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
las	O
t	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sh	O
all	O
be	O
very	O
anxious	O
for	O
her	O
safety	O
,	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
witneſs	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
news	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
well	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
heard	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
,	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
very	O
poorly	O
indeed	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
is	O
just	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
being	O
married	O
to	O
Coln	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
their	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
Our	O
dear	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
returns	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
add	O
both	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
happineſs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
writing	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Luxmore	I-pers
room	O
Miſs	B-pers
E	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
that	O
was	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
is	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
looks	O
indifferently	O
&	O
I	O
suppose	O
has	O
not	O
got	O
up	O
her	O
spirits	O
.	O
--	O
With	O
best	O
compts	O
:	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
dear	O
Brother	O
yr	O
-	O
Affectionate	O
Sister	O
M——	B-pers
G——	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Octbr	O
1786	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Single	O
Sheet	O
