TOKEN	NE
Orchard	O
St	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Portman	O
Sqe-	O
May	O
4	O
th	O
1791	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
After	O
having	O
paſsed	O
four	O
months	O
at	O
Stanton	B-place
and	O
five	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
we	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
see	O
our	O
friends	O
and	O
partake	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
various	O
Amusements	O
which	O
this	O
Season	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
affords	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
Our	O
movements	O
have	O
I	O
fear	O
made	O
us	O
all	O
extremely	O
reprehensible	O
in	O
our	O
neglect	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
altho	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
intended	O
,	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
altho	O
yet	O
Jane	B-pers
endeavors	O
when	O
we	O
speak	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
to	O
exculpate	O
herself	O
by	O
observing	O
that	O
in	O
your	O
last	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
acknowledged	O
yourself	O
in	O
her	O
debt	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
,	O
however	O
be	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
we	O
really	O
feel	O
the	O
little	O
Intercourse	O
that	O
has	O
subsisted	O
between	O
us	O
of	O
late	O
with	O
very	O
great	O
regret	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
do	O
hope	O
in	O
future	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
long	O
without	O
hearing	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
health	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
and	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Girl	O
.	O
You	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
will	O
mind	O
for	O
yourself	O
your	O
being	O
Engaged	O
in	O
Building	O
and	O
in	O
neceſsary	O
Employments	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
experience	O
Engroſses	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
ones	O
time	O
;	O
So	O
indeed	O
does	O
continual	O
moving	O
and	O
change	O
of	O
situation	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
we	O
think	O
neither	O
profitable	O
nor	O
amusing	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
in	O
short	O
we	O
all	O
agree	O
is	O
very	O
tiresome	O
,	O
therefore	O
that	O
plan	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
End	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
will	O
be	O
finally	O
determined	O
upon	O
as	O
yet	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
House	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
wish	O
,	O
whether	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
Bath	B-place
or	O
London	B-place
I	O
know	O
not	O
but	O
shall	O
not	O
long	O
be	O
ignorant	O
as	O
I	O
expect	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
home	O
from	O
Stanton	B-place
the	O
End	O
of	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
aſsisting	O
in	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Flock	O
at	O
Easter	O
,	O
and	O
letting	O
his	O
Parsonage	O
.	O
This	O
Step	O
I	O
know	O
will	O
surprise	O
you	O
untill	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
that	O
were	O
the	O
Emolument	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
it	O
woud	O
only	O
keep	O
it	O
self	O
and	O
defray	O
the	O
Expenses	O
of	O
moving	O
a	O
family	O
twice	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
living	O
there	O
for	O
five	O
months	O
and	O
keeping	O
up	O
a	O
Dining	O
Neighborhood	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
thickly	O
inhabitted	O
Country	O
,	O
Entertaing	O
Servts-	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
all	O
,	O
no	O
pleasure	O
in	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
work	O
to	O
compensate	O
.	O
Therefore	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
the	O
family	O
shou	O
'd	O
go	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Man	O
can	O
go	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
and	O
be	O
his	O
Curates	O
Guest	O
without	O
inconvenience	O
.	O
If	O
our	O
future	O
settlement	O
shoud	O
be	O
London	B-place
which	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
Mr	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
wish	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
very	O
moderate	O
House	O
upon	O
a	O
Rent	O
no	O
purchasing	O
for	O
we	O
will	O
not	O
break	O
Bulk	O
and	O
then	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
shoud	O
offer	O
for	O
Jane	B-pers
that	O
was	O
worthy	O
of	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
so	O
charming	O
so	O
valuable	O
a	O
creature	O
there	O
will	O
then	O
be	O
a	O
pretty	O
little	O
sum	O
to	O
accompany	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
this	O
there	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
no	O
prospect	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
impatient	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
are	O
we	O
.	O
When	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
left	O
Town	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
His	O
Banker	O
Mr	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
had	O
been	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Interest	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
intention	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Principal	O
next	O
period	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
returned	O
before	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
writing	O
either	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
more	O
fully	O
upon	O
this	O
point	O
.	O
All	O
your	O
friends	O
here	O
are	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
expected	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
Our	O
Son	O
is	O
more	O
grown	O
and	O
improved	O
than	O
you	O
can	O
imagine	O
,	O
often	O
enquires	O
after	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
He	O
is	O
quite	O
happy	O
in	O
his	O
Military	O
Situation	O
and	O
is	O
most	O
lucky	O
in	O
being	O
already	O
Eldest	O
Cornet	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
scrawled	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
and	O
to	O
very	O
little	O
purpose	O
being	O
so	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
our	O
own	O
detail	O
which	O
one	O
is	O
too	O
apt	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
however	O
to	O
you	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
leſs	O
uninteresting	O
than	O
to	O
many	O
others	O
=as	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
kind	O
concern	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
relates	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
Pray	O
pray	O
write	O
soon	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
Charity	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
With	O
Jane	B-pers
s	O
best	O
love	O
I	O
remain	O
Yrs	O
.	O
R	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
