TOKEN	NE
Green	O
Street	O
Leicester	O
fields	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
much	O
flattered	O
with	O
your	O
Congratulations	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
just	O
returned	O
to	O
Town	B-place
&	O
dine	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
's	O
.	O
My	O
Chariot	O
&	O
Servant	O
shall	O
wait	O
your	O
Commands	O
about	O
½	O
past	O
Seven	O
&	O
Shall	O
carry	O
You	O
home	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
we	O
regret	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
the	O
Presentation	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
trouble	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Chair	O
.	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
Your	O
Affect	O
.	O
friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
this	O
is	O
wrote	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
