TOKEN	NE
Yours	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
ago	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
my	O
having	O
been	O
from	O
home	O
on	O
a	O
jaunt	O
to	O
Stirlingshire	B-place
and	O
Schaw	O
Park	O
/	O
Ld	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s/	O
otherwise	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
persuaded	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
anſwering	O
so	O
kind	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
one	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
regard	O
for	O
&	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
sensible	O
does	O
me	O
great	O
honor	O
by	O
her	O
friendship	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
will	O
still	O
continue	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
shall	O
ſay	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
yours	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
wrote	O
like	O
yourself	O
with	O
that	O
delicacy	O
,	O
friendship	O
,	O
&	O
good	O
ſense	O
particularly	O
the	O
Characteristic	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
few	O
or	O
none	O
could	O
can	O
come	O
up	O
too	O
,	O
Believe	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
that	O
kind	O
concern	O
you	O
both	O
shew	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
my	O
health	O
is	O
ſince	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
greatly	O
mended	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
&	O
so	O
is	O
my	O
spirits	O
tho	O
I	O
must	O
ſay	O
very	O
,	O
very	O
little	O
effects	O
both	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
do	O
everything	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
keep	O
both	O
as	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
&	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
this	O
Winter	O
over	O
I	O
shall	O
reestablish	O
my	O
health	O
entirely	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
long	O
letter	O
ſome	O
weeks	O
ago	O
with	O
your	O
most	O
entertaining	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
places	O
you	O
saw	O
with	O
L	O
in	O
yo	O
ur	O
jaunt	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
c	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
in	O
not	O
anſwering	O
that	O
letter	O
particularly	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
home	O
&	O
have	O
more	O
time	O
on	O
my	O
hands	O
than	O
I	O
poſsibly	O
can	O
have	O
abroad	O
tho	O
I	O
must	O
just	O
mention	O
one	O
thing	O
which	O
is	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
than	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
lately	O
by	O
your	O
own	O
account	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
ruin	O
your	O
constitution	O
entirely	O
,	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
scold	O
a	O
little	O
my	O
friendship	O
for	O
my	O
dear	O
Ward	O
entittles	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
you	O
are	O
too	O
sanguine	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
)	O
in	O
your	O
pursuits	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
like	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
reaſon	O
after	O
its	O
over	O
your	O
body	O
suffers	O
&	O
you	O
get	O
a	O
fever	O
which	O
brings	O
you	O
to	O
deaths	O
door	O
&	O
you	O
are	O
surprised	O
that	O
your	O
constitution	O
of	O
body	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
Ward	O
too	O
much	O
fatigue	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
thing	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
think	O
yourself	O
much	O
stronger	O
than	O
you	O
really	O
are	O
,	O
witneſs	O
you	O
r	O
meeting	O
with	O
your	O
mama	O
after	O
your	O
jaunt	O
,	O
those	O
fitts	O
will	O
become	O
more	O
frequent	O
if	O
great	O
care	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
to	O
prevent	O
ſuch	O
a	O
sensibility	O
getting	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
a	O
Constitution	O
not	O
the	O
strongest	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
ſaid	O
too	O
much	O
I	O
beg	O
pardon	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
any	O
ward	O
will	O
forgive	O
my	O
doing	O
my	O
duty	O
as	O
a	O
Guardian	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
ſure	O
I	O
shall	O
ſend	O
you	O
ſome	O
more	O
of	O
these	O
odes	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
author	O
is	O
not	O
always	O
in	O
a	O
humour	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
and	O
has	O
really	O
threatned	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
his	O
compoſition	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
rather	O
of	O
the	O
Mule	O
Kind	O
when	O
he	O
takes	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
head	O
&	O
is	O
not	O
fond	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
writing	O
however	O
I	O
shall	O
do	O
my	O
best	O
to	O
oblige	O
you	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
family	O
join	O
my	O
three	O
eldest	O
young	O
folks	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
forget	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
affct	O
manner	O
&	O
Compliments	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
Has	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
s	I-pers
made	O
it	O
up	O
yet	O
?	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
story	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
trust	O
me	O
with	O
however	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
wth	O
the	O
greatest	O
truth	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
Yrs	O
most	O
affctly	O
Shaw	O
Park	O
Sepr	O
,	O
6	O
th	O
-	O
1774	O
