TOKEN	NE
Piccadilly	B-place
June	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1787	O
My	O
dearest	O
friend	O
For	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
your	O
friend	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
addresses	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
her	O
dear	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
your	O
good	O
father	O
is	O
again	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
your	O
good	O
man	O
is	O
so	O
well	O
&	O
my	O
sweet	O
little	O
baby	O
my	O
lovely	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
though	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
engaged	O
&	O
my	O
thoughts	O
are	O
well	O
occupied	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
think	O
of	O
my	O
much	O
loved	O
friends	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
happy	O
how	O
happy	O
&	O
how	O
hurried	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
On	O
tuesday	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
united	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
love	O
,	O
&	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
doubt	O
will	O
ever	O
make	O
me	O
happy	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
amiable	O
polite	O
generous	O
man	O
,	O
belov	O
'd	O
by	O
every	O
one	O
who	O
knows	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
therefore	O
believe	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
say	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
entire	O
poſseſsion	O
of	O
your	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
heart	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
thankful	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
bleſsings	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
pray	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
deserving	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
love	O
him	O
my	O
dearest	O
Henry	B-pers
for	O
my	O
sake	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
how	O
happy	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
Henly	O
Park	O
&	O
my	O
dearest	O
Halsey	B-pers
likewise	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
how	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
All	O
the	O
muslins	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Henry	B-pers
gave	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
beautiful	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
hopes	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
next	O
year	O
to	O
our	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
bring	O
my	O
sweet	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Henly	O
Park	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
enclosed	O
&	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
meadow	O
lands	O
therefore	O
h	O
.	O
can	O
not	O
now	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
very	O
excellent	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
entice	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
A	B-pers
,	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
even	O
the	O
winter	O
to	O
be	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
will	O
have	O
charms	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
evening	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
spend	O
with	O
Miſs	O
Clarkes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
therefore	O
writing	O
here	O
,	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
friend	O
s	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
toast	O
after	O
dinner	O
for	O
my	O
Henry	B-pers
&	O
me	O
in	O
verse	O
May	O
all	O
yr	O
.	O
days	O
in	O
endleſs	O
pleasures	O
run	O
and	O
end	O
with	O
commence	O
in	O
Joy	O
&	O
end	O
as	O
they	O
begun	O
I	O
rank	O
with	O
three	O
times	O
three	O
.	O
you	O
must	O
forgive	O
this	O
scraw	O
l	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Henly	O
immediately	O
on	O
our	O
marriage	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
ever	O
dear	O
Brother	O
&	O
sister	O
dDickenson	B-pers
congratulations	O
addreſs	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
Henly	O
Park	O
near	O
Farnham	B-place
Surrey	B-place
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
desires	O
her	O
love	O
likewise	O
the	O
Clarkes	O
:	O
Ever	O
yr	O
.	O
unalterable	O
friend	O
pour	O
la	O
deniere	O
foi	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
June	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1787	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
