TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
friends	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
all	O
dearly	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
wished	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
imediate	O
answering	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
,	O
will	O
convince	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
was	O
gratify	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
towards	O
you	O
all	O
;	O
My	O
Scrawls	O
would	O
much	O
oftener	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
altho	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
think	O
them	O
worth	O
the	O
pos	O
tage	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
That	O
you	O
could	O
better	O
inform	O
me	O
what	O
paſses	O
in	O
London	B-place
then	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
Therefore	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
any	O
news	O
from	O
Thence	O
.	O
of	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
lamentation	O
could	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
Pen	O
;	O
for	O
from	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
may	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
were	O
nothing	O
Then	O
winter	O
Month	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
fine	O
fruit	O
was	O
distroy	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Summer	O
will	O
begin	O
at	O
Christmas	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
at	O
least	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
new	O
made	O
up	O
muslin	O
gowns	O
before	O
they	O
will	O
become	O
out	O
of	O
fashion	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
I	O
spend	O
my	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
retirement	O
;	O
now	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
time	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
!	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
is	O
well	O
at	O
Cowslip	B-place
.	O
Ever	O
Yours	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
.	O
Adelphi	O
Novr	O
.	O
the	O
23	O
:	O
1799	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Dickenson	O
Esqr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Leighton	B-place
Buſsard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
