TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
,	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
March	O
1793	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Some	O
Resolutions	O
paſsed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Committee	O
of	O
Privileges	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
give	O
Me	O
a	O
very	O
broad	O
hint	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Right	O
of	O
Franking	O
will	O
cease	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
your	O
Pence	O
,	O
not	O
from	O
a	O
Cacoethes	O
scribendi	O
;	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
not	O
very	O
partial	O
to	O
the	O
Amusement	O
of	O
Writing	O
)	O
I	O
hasten	O
to	O
answer	O
your	O
Letter	O
.	O
Their	O
Lordships	O
of	O
the	O
Committee	O
,	O
have	O
Unanimously	O
resolved	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
Napier	O
is	O
perfectly	O
good	O
.	O
Even	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
attack	O
my	O
Dignities	O
,	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
their	O
inability	O
to	O
sustain	O
their	O
objections	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
cost	O
Me	O
upwards	O
of	O
£170	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
back	O
from	O
my	O
Enemies	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
They	O
have	O
punished	O
Me	O
pretty	O
severely	O
,	O
for	O
presuming	O
to	O
differ	O
in	O
opinion	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
misfortunes	O
do	O
not	O
stop	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Committee	O
having	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Voters	O
had	O
no	O
claim	O
to	O
the	O
Title	O
he	O
had	O
aſsumed	O
,	O
and	O
repelled	O
some	O
objections	O
I	O
had	O
stated	O
to	O
the	O
Voting	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Kinnaird	I-pers
,	O
it	O
becomes	O
certain	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
lose	O
my	O
Election	O
,	O
for	O
Alas	O
!	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
of	O
my	O
Noble	O
Voters	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
will	O
likewise	O
be	O
turned	O
off	O
the	O
Roll	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
comes	O
the	O
worst	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Solicitors	O
Bill	O
(	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
General	O
Expenses	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
amount	O
to	O
some	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
in	O
groſs	O
,	O
&	O
consequently	O
will	O
cost	O
one	O
individually	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
£	O
P	O
ounds	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
more	O
)	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
Ambition	O
.	O
Had	O
matters	O
turned	O
out	O
more	O
to	O
my	O
wishes	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
making	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
.	O
We	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
next	O
May	O
,	O
or	O
whenever	O
it	O
is	O
convenient	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
says	O
,	O
she	O
rejoices	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
sooner	O
,	O
because	O
our	O
Trees	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
Leaf	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
has	O
now	O
lived	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
that	O
she	O
feels	O
an	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
appearing	O
well	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eyes	O
of	O
Strangers	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
may	O
have	O
read	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Women	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
a	O
Valiant	O
&	O
Sturdy	O
Knight	O
of	O
Nova	O
Scotia	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
still	O
equal	O
to	O
keeping	O
her	O
in	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
She	O
attempts	O
to	O
corrupt	O
the	O
Allegiance	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
Cascade	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
She	O
may	O
be	O
soused	O
,	O
till	O
She	O
cries	O
peccavi	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Yours	O
very	O
Sincerely	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
be	O
under	O
no	O
apprehensions	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Blue	O
Stocking	O
Tribe	O
in	O
this	O
habitation	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
downright	O
Country	O
Folks	O
,	O
staring	O
with	O
our	O
Eyes	O
&	O
gaping	O
with	O
our	O
Mouths	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
all	O
Puts	O
do	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
has	O
taught	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Mary	B-pers
to	O
read	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
performs	O
very	O
tolerably	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
beginning	O
to	O
dabble	O
in	O
French	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
very	O
quick	O
parts	O
&	O
a	O
good	O
Memory	O
.	O
Little	O
Anne	B-pers
,	O
has	O
likewise	O
begun	O
to	O
learn	O
her	O
Letters	O
under	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
tuition	O
,	O
but	O
She	O
,	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
,	O
takes	O
an	O
obstinate	O
fit	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
They	O
fight	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
comprehend	O
his	O
Letters	O
&	O
he	O
now	O
reads	O
Gay	B-pers
's	O
Fables	O
&	O
the	O
Bible	O
.	O
Taking	O
on	O
Me	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
Godfather	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
pains	O
and	O
labour	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taught	O
him	O
to	O
repeat	O
his	O
Catechism	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
Psalms	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Busy	O
Bee	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
Erudition	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
My	O
young	O
hopeful	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
other	O
accomplishments	O
,	O
has	O
added	O
a	O
happy	O
Stutter	O
,	O
arising	O
from	O
an	O
overeagerneſs	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Twist	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
will	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Charming	O
Young	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
Mischief	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
Boys	O
are	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
bid	O
thee	O
farewell	O
,	O
desiring	O
You	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
sincere	O
Wellwishers	O
of	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Hawick	B-place
Third	O
March	O
1793	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr=	I-pers
HAWICK	B-place
Taxal	B-place
Chapel-in-Frith	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
by	O
Derbyshire	B-place
49	O
5	O
24-¼	O
245	O
269	O
9/	O
269	O
29	O
