TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
25	O
th	O
:	O
March	O
1779	O
A	O
Caution	O
to	O
Miſses	O
.	O
Young	O
Lady	O
's	O
having	O
Franks	O
laying	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
ought	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
the	O
Member	O
who	O
directed	O
them	O
has	O
a	O
Seat	O
in	O
this	O
Parliament	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
their	O
Correspondents	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
double	O
Postage	O
.	O
Jas-	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
has	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
Parliament	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
From	O
your	O
long	O
silence	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
thoroughly	O
convinced	O
of	O
your	O
nonexistence	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
ordered	O
all	O
my	O
old	O
Blacks	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
brushed	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
Letter	O
by	O
last	O
Nights	O
Post	O
soon	O
convinced	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Error	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
begi	O
n	O
by	O
begging	O
you	O
may	O
write	O
no	O
more	O
joint	O
Letters	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
changing	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Hopetoun	O
House	O
this	O
day	O
with	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
the	O
Contract	O
of	O
Marriage	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
a	O
Dr-	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
&	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
mentioned	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
talked	O
of	O
for	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
saw	O
you	O
.	O
His	O
fortune	O
is	O
easy	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
affluent	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
contracted	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
so	O
narrow	O
a	O
sphere	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Godly	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
best	O
match	O
she	O
can	O
expect	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
worthy	O
,	O
religious	O
,	O
good	O
man	O
,	O
rather	O
enthusiastic	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Ideas	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
suits	O
with	O
her	O
temper	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
before	O
regretted	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
Line	O
of	O
Life	O
Mainie	B-pers
pursued	O
and	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
so	O
proper	O
a	O
choice	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
exactly	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
that	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
better	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
beleive	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
tolerable	O
bustle	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
the	O
Picture	O
pleased	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
lucky	O
in	O
leaving	O
London	B-place
so	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	O
The	O
good	O
man	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
tolerable	O
opinion	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
God	O
knows	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
lasted	O
.	O
Poor	O
Mr	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
Well	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
pity	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
sustained	O
by	O
his	O
Absence	O
.	O
That	O
Wit	O
,	O
that	O
Spirit	O
,	O
that	O
inexpreſsible	O
humour	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
was	O
irresistable	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
undergo	O
any	O
punishment	O
you	O
think	O
sufficient	O
to	O
expiate	O
&	O
atone	O
for	O
my	O
Offence	O
.	O
C.	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
glad	O
you	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
favourite	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
Her	O
Grace	O
of	O
Atholl	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
at	O
Caroline	O
Park	O
.	O
Affable	O
,	O
pleasing	O
,	O
dignified	O
yet	O
condescending	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
a	O
perfect	O
reformation	O
.	O
His	O
Grace	O
expected	O
daily	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
first	O
who	O
have	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Stormont	O
's	O
to	O
me	O
since	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
this	O
instant	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Caroline	O
Park	O
(	O
Sir	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Oughton	I-pers
s	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Contract	O
&	O
c	O
Yours	O
sincerely	O
&	O
Affecly-	O
N——	B-pers
I	O
hope	O
Miſs	B-pers
K.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
be	O
happy	O
in	O
her	O
matrimonial	O
schemes	O
--	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
.	O
