TOKEN	NE
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
oClock	O
he	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
recd	O
.	O
equal	O
pleasure	O
in	O
meeting	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
went	O
away	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
the	O
ladies	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
their	O
walk	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
Master	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
at	O
home	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
sup	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
wholly	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
character	O
and	O
improvements	O
--	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hours	O
converse	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
July	O
16	O
th	O
.	O
Friday	O
1784	O
AMaria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
together	O
parts	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
of	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
would	O
sit	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
--	O
She	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
clever	O
letter	O
she	O
recd	O
:	O
Yesterday	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
an	O
elegant	O
composition	O
--	O
the	O
thoughts	O
were	O
new	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
lamented	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Thrale	I-pers
s	O
having	O
so	O
lost	O
herself	O
in	O
marrying	O
Piozzi	B-pers
ye	O
.	O
Italian	O
Singer	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
After	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
left	O
me	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
both	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
8	O
quarto	O
pages	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
finish	O
'd	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
,	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
à	O
tête	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
debate	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
India	O
busineſs	O
.	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lefft	O
left	O
a	O
meſsage	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
proper	O
&	O
what	O
I	O
owed	O
myself	O
&	O
family	O
&	O
also	O
that	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
right	O
to	O
put	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
upon	O
a	O
proper	O
footing	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
presented	O
at	O
Court	O
soon	O
after	O
a	O
certain	O
event	O
might	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
wd	O
.	O
present	O
us	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
engage	O
my	O
other	O
friends	O
&	O
Relations	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Court	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
that	O
neither	O
I	O
or	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
need	O
apprehend	O
that	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
occasion	O
us	O
any	O
material	O
expence	O
--	O
nor	O
that	O
there	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
neceſsity	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
Court	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
all	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
world	O
wd	O
.	O
suppose	O
I	O
had	O
married	O
some	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
my	O
Relations	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
reply	O
to	O
this	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
detirmin	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
rul	O
'd	O
by	O
wht	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
agreeable	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
two	O
dear	O
Boys	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
usual	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
told	O
me	O
how	O
her	O
oldest	O
boy	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
)	O
behaved	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
&	O
how	O
properly	O
Mrs.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
reproved	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
pertneſs	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
our	O
Cousin	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
desired	O
her	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
intended	O
calling	O
on	O
me	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
prevented	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
Windsor	B-place
earlier	O
than	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
a	O
comfortable	O
afternoon	O
together	O
--	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
plan	O
'd	O
the	O
drawing	O
Box	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
gave	O
all	O
the	O
particular	O
directions	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Cabinet	O
maker	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
left	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
--	O
I	O
promised	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
town	B-place
till	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
.	O
home	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
were	O
out	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
w	O
as	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
an	O
introduction	O
to	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
also	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
--	O
enclosed	O
these	O
Notes	O
with	O
my	O
letter	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
chat	O
wth	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
.	O
found	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Ducheſs	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
at	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
July	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
Saturday	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
&	O
shock	O
'd	O
by	O
our	O
Housemaid	O
who	O
came	O
&	O
knelt	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
&	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
some	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
yt	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
liar	O
--	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Cambric	O
Handif	O
.	O
of	O
mine	O
of	O
wch	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
ye	O
.	O
Mark	O
.	O
she	O
implored	O
my	O
forgiveneſs	O
and	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
from	O
losing	O
her	O
character	O
--	O
the	O
motive	O
of	O
her	O
telling	O
me	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
that	O
Betty	B-pers
our	O
Maid	O
had	O
detected	O
&	O
threatren	O
'd	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
acquainting	O
us	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
&	O
so	O
pain	O
'd	O
by	O
finding	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
deceived	O
in	O
this	O
Girls	O
character	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
power	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
this	O
Morng	O
with	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
story	O
&	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
right	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
she	O
approved	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
a	O
t	O
ſ	O
sist	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
early	O
--	O
I	O
question	O
'd	O
Betty	B-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
many	O
things	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
Hannah	B-pers
had	O
stoln	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
acquainted	O
her	O
that	O
as	O
B	B-pers
:	I-pers
alledged	O
these	O
things	O
against	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
expect	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
let	O
B	B-pers
:	I-pers
see	O
ye	O
.	O
contents	O
of	O
her	O
Boxes	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
hesitate	O
in	O
complying	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
--	O
charging	O
to	O
prevent	O
B	B-pers
.	I-pers
not	O
to	O
say	O
ing	O
any	O
thing	O
harsh	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
reclaim	O
&	O
not	O
to	O
oppreſs	O
her	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
some	O
old	O
lace	O
edging	O
of	O
mine	O
--	O
besides	O
wht-	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
before	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
apron	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
solemn	O
manner	O
denied	O
&	O
then	O
bursting	O
into	O
an	O
agony	O
of	O
tears	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
relied	O
on	O
my	O
goodneſs	O
for	O
not	O
being	O
more	O
prejudiced	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
what	O
Betty	B-pers
said	O
for	O
that	O
Betty	B-pers
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
us	O
as	O
much	O
&	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
evidently	O
marks	O
of	O
confusion	O
in	O
Betty	B-pers
s	O
countenance	O
&	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
quarrel	O
between	O
these	O
women	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
what	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
B	B-pers
:	I-pers
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
ready	O
for	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
made	O
H——	B-pers
acquaint	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
accusing	O
B——	B-pers
in	O
that	O
indirect	O
manner	O
--	O
She	O
opened	O
such	O
a	O
scene	O
e	O
of	O
fraud	O
--	O
falseneſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
that	O
my	O
astonishment	O
was	O
great	O
indeed	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
confidence	O
in	O
B——	B-pers
&	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
perfectly	O
honest	O
&	O
good	O
young	O
Woman	O
I	O
had	O
imagined	O
her	O
principles	O
were	O
excellent	O
&	O
also	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Affection	O
for	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
and	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
thought	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
treated	O
her	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
came	O
home	O
at	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
--	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
Betty	B-pers
if	O
she	O
could	O
vindicate	O
herself	O
&	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
shock	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
take	O
ye	O
mildest	O
method	O
&	O
endeavour	O
if	O
poſsible	O
to	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
minds	O
of	O
these	O
Women	O
&	O
try	O
first	O
to	O
rec	O
t	O
l	O
aim	O
them	O
by	O
gentle	O
means	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
that	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
utterly	O
impossible	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
character	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
them	O
away	O
but	O
by	O
a	O
generous	O
forgiveneſs	O
&	O
good	O
advice	O
try	O
to	O
effect	O
a	O
reformation	O
in	O
their	O
minds	O
&	O
excite	O
their	O
gratitude	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
's	O
thoughts	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
mine	O
--	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
&	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
them	O
away	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
reproach	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
their	O
mutually	O
forgiving	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
promise	O
they	O
would	O
keep	O
this	O
affair	O
a	O
secret	O
from	O
their	O
acquaintances	O
--	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
this	O
promise	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
embrace	O
each	O
other	O
with	O
real	O
signs	O
of	O
forgiveneſs	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
advice	O
--	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
penitent	O
&	O
so	O
ended	O
this	O
disagreeable	O
affair	O
.	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
note	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
&	O
sent	O
the	O
pacquet	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
ready	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
at	O
2	O
oClock	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Stainforth	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
ye	O
.	O
liberty	O
of	O
short'ning	O
her	O
visit	O
,	O
she	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
's	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
their	O
House	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Summer	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
if	O
poſsible	O
.	O
Return	O
'd	O
home	O
immediately	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
dinnertime	O
.	O
rec	O
'd	O
a	O
charming	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
--	O
was	O
disappointed	O
in	O
not	O
receiving	O
one	O
from	O
D——shire	B-place
.	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
sat	O
by	O
whilst	O
we	O
dined	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Carmarthen	I-pers
s.	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
--	O
A.M	B-pers
:	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
leſson	O
--	O
we	O
separated	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7	O
--	O
I	O
begun	O
Madme	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
last	O
work	O
les	O
Veillées	O
du	O
Chateau	O
wch	O
.	O
Stephanie	B-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
lent	O
me	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
tea	O
.	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
from	O
Hampton	O
)	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
fine	O
flowers	O
&	O
fruit	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
interesting	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
join	O
'd	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Veseys	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
fruit	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
--	O
We	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Supper	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
--	O
y	O
spirits	O
were	O
quite	O
worn	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
retire	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
&	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
forbid	O
his	O
coming	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Sunday	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
A	O
Maria	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
disagreeable	O
affair	O
of	O
yesterday	O
&	O
were	O
satisfied	O
we	O
had	O
at	O
least	O
done	O
what	O
was	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
charitable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
May-fair	O
Chapel	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
Pulpit	O
who	O
preach	O
'd	O
the	O
most	O
extravagant	O
discourse	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
composition	O
of	O
loose	O
unconnected	O
sentences	O
in	O
Blank	O
Verse	O
or	O
rather	O
Prose	O
run	O
d	O
mad	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
immediately	O
after	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
quite	O
a	O
levée	O
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
--	O
Each	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
wish	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
gone	O
--	O
at	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
kept	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
dinner	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
service	O
--	O
from	O
3	O
till	O
4	O
I	O
was	O
quiet	O
,	O
&	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
myself	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
&	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
Extracts	O
from	O
Dear	O
my	B-pers
Cousin	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Church	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
together	O
above	O
10	O
Minutes	O
--	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servs	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
still	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
dumb	O
waiters	O
so	O
our	O
conversation	O
was	O
not	O
under	O
any	O
restraint	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
being	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
room	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
amused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
his	O
conversation	O
.	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
living	O
at	O
Vienna	B-place
wch	O
.	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
resided	O
there	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
polished	O
Court	O
in	O
Europe	B-place
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
great	O
difference	O
of	O
expence	O
in	O
every	O
article	O
between	O
living	O
abroad	O
&	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
Lord	O
S——	O
said	O
that	O
not	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
society	O
was	O
more	O
agreeable	O
but	O
that	O
what	O
an	O
income	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
one	O
could	O
live	O
on	O
with	O
difficulty	O
in	O
England	B-place
with	O
bare	O
comfort	O
was	O
in	O
Italy	B-place
,	O
France	B-place
Germany	B-place
&	O
c.	O
able	O
to	O
support	O
one	O
in	O
an	O
elegant	O
&	O
manner	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
staid	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
me	O
till	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Lord	O
S	O
:	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
conversation	O
that	O
had	O
paſs	O
'd	O
between	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
negōciation	O
between	O
ye	O
.	O
English	O
French	O
&	O
Ruſsians	O
--	O
when	O
through	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
prudence	O
in	O
conducting	O
that	O
affair	O
we	O
were	O
saved	O
from	O
a	O
War	O
with	O
Russia	B-place
.	O
When	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Paris	B-place
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
said	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
never	O
should	O
out	O
live	O
ye	O
.	O
rememberance	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
&	O
his	O
Country	O
owed	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
yt	O
.	O
he	O
might	O
depend	O
upon	O
his	O
eternal	O
gratitude	O
.	O
Yet	O
How	O
has	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
fulfilled	O
kept	O
up	O
to	O
these	O
professions	O
?	O
by	O
turning	O
out	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Ministry	O
--	O
Alas	O
!	O
ye	O
.	O
promises	O
of	O
Princes	O
are	O
little	O
to	O
be	O
relied	O
on	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
had	O
certainly	O
no	O
excuse	O
--	O
no	O
reason	O
for	O
behaving	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
to	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
enquired	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
Distreſs	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Street	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
young	O
children	O
&	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
--	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
d	O
6	O
&	O
made	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
do	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
&	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
enable	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Month	O
of	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
extracts	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
took	O
up	O
L'amie	O
des	O
femmes	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
this	O
book	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
about	O
our	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Pierre-Joseph	B-pers
Boudier	I-pers
de	I-pers
Villemert	I-pers
is	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
him	O
*	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
had	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
were	O
at	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S——	I-pers
--	O
they	O
went	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
.	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
..	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
Bedchamber	O
Women	O
)	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
in	O
ye	O
Morng	O
.	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
abt	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
Monday	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Breakfasted	O
alone	O
--	O
busy	O
writing	O
all	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
several	O
Visits	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
saw	O
Hannah	B-pers
--	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
my	O
Old	O
maid	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
her	O
husband	O
went	O
on	O
--	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
still	O
unsettled	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Wm	B-pers
..	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
to	O
intreat	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
return	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
to	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
&	O
stay	O
a	O
Week	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Busineſs	O
--	O
to	O
tempt	O
me	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
&	O
that	O
he	O
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
were	O
to	O
construct	O
an	O
Air	O
Balloon	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
off	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
Philosopher	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
to	O
spend	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
also	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
a	O
Week	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
.	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
wholly	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
affairs	O
in	O
Ireland	O
--	O
my	O
U	O
.	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
apprehend	O
a	O
Reb	O
el	O
lion	O
there	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
charming	O
letter	O
from	O
my	B-pers
Cousin	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
a	O
letter	O
also	O
from	O
Frederick	B-pers
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
payment	O
of	O
ye	O
rent	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
in	O
James	O
Street	O
.	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
D——shire	O
!	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
Coach	O
&	O
Serts	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
commons	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
.	O
debates	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
India	B-place
busineſs	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stor——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
a	O
comfortable	O
afternoon	O
together	O
she	O
humanely	O
relieved	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
mite	O
.	O
--	O
the	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
education	O
of	O
Children	O
particularly	O
Girls	O
--	O
we	O
agree	O
'd	O
in	O
most	O
points	O
--	O
&	O
both	O
condemn	O
'd	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
method	O
--	O
her	O
writings	O
are	O
ingenious	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
charming	O
things	O
in	O
them	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
hands	O
of	O
Young	O
people	O
on	O
many	O
accounts	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
now	O
leisure	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
all	O
the	O
reasons	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
ten	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
convey	O
'd	O
me	O
home	O
--	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
but	O
excused	O
myself	O
dining	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
engaged	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
6	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
very	O
happy	O
by	O
informing	O
her	O
how	O
well	O
her	O
Brother	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
had	O
acquitted	O
himself	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
spoke	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
affairs	O
in	O
India	B-place
,	O
--	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Speech	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
fine	O
manner	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
sent	O
us	O
an	O
excuse	O
for	O
not	O
jo	O
y	O
i	O
n	O
ing	O
us	O
again	O
h	O
a	O
s	O
he	O
had	O
letters	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
soon	O
left	O
me	O
being	O
engaged	O
to	O
sup	O
at	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
I	O
sent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
out	O
some	O
Verses	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
at	O
12	O
oClock	O
.	O
found	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
&	O
spend	O
a	O
day	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
week	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
20	O
th	O
-	O
July	O
1784	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
Maker	O
brought	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
s	O
Drawing	O
box	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
executed	O
my	O
directions	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
copied	O
ye	O
.	O
plan	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
&	O
answerd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	O
Stormont	O
--	O
Settled	O
some	O
busineſs	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Scott	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
linnen	O
&	O
gave	O
her	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
Lord	O
Stormont	O
came	O
he	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
proud	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
favorite	O
of	O
his	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Uncles	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
.	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Irish	O
affairs	O
--	O
Fredk	B-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
he	O
imagin	O
'd	O
things	O
wd-	O
come	O
to	O
extremities	O
there	O
.	O
he	O
laugh	O
'd	O
&	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
go	O
&	O
live	O
abroad	O
or	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
for	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
impoſsible	O
if	O
things	O
went	O
on	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
William	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
&	O
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
20	O
Min	O
:	O
.	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
S——	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
last	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
Eveg	O
.	O
this	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
nor	O
tomorrow	O
but	O
promised	O
them	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
.	O
this	O
dear	O
dear	O
Woman	O
was	O
charming	O
well	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
reading	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
working	O
&	O
sorting	O
letters	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
sent	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
informd	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
day	O
this	O
week	O
.	O
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Madme	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
--	O
No	O
letter	O
from	O
D——shire	B-place
!	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
playd	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Leſsons	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
's	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
from	O
6	O
till	O
7	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
Boudoir	O
arranging	O
Papers	O
--	O
AMaria	B-pers
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Sr	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
found	O
Vento	B-pers
very	O
well	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
was	O
delighted	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
box	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
Compts	O
.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Spent	O
a	O
pleasant	O
afternoon	O
--	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Chariot	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
--	O
finish	O
'd	O
sorting	O
my	O
letters	O
recd	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
after	O
.	O
Read	O
2	O
hours	O
in	O
Veillies	O
du	O
Chateau	O
.	O
arranged	O
all	O
my	O
loose	O
papers	O
--	O
wrote	O
some	O
extracts	O
.	O
several	O
agreeable	O
little	O
Visits	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
--	O
one	O
from	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
consult	O
me	O
about	O
dreſs	O
--	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
nor	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
I	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
appointed	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
poke	O
to	O
her	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
Stormont	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
succeed	O
in	O
making	O
up	O
the	O
quarrel	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
be	O
guided	O
by	O
my	O
advice	O
.	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
the	O
post	O
brought	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
D-shire	B-place
a	O
thousand	O
disagreeable	O
apprehensions	O
made	O
me	O
feel	O
quite	O
miserable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
French	O
Gentleman	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
a	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Secretaries	O
of	O
State	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
French	O
Ministry	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
Minister	O
to	O
Ruſsia	B-place
--	O
he	O
staid	O
on	O
till	O
5	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
left	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
dreſs	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
absent	O
Our	O
Cousin	O
Compte	B-pers
Segur	I-pers
dined	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
did	O
her	O
Brother	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
dumb	O
waiters	O
as	O
usual	O
&	O
an	O
agreeable	O
conversation	O
made	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
paſs	O
pleasantly	O
--	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
talk	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
family	O
&	O
its	O
attendants	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
yesterday	O
who	O
enquired	O
much	O
about	O
me	O
&	O
sent	O
his	O
Compliments	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
he	O
wonders	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
me	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
&	O
said	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
pleasure	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Ball	O
he	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
goin	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
s	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Vis	O
a	O
Vis	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Carriages	O
paſs	O
'd	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
hardly	O
time	O
to	O
bow	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
left	O
us	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
'd	O
together	O
(	O
whilst	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
)	O
abt-	O
our	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
he	O
vindicated	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
gentle	O
lecture	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
oClock	O
I	O
left	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Coll	O
.	O
staid	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
Uncle	B-pers
Fredk-	I-pers
was	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
he	O
din	O
'd	O
to	O
day	O
with	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
got	O
home	O
by	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
sat	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
till	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
Lord	B-pers
Thurlow	I-pers
&	O
I	O
wrote	O
&	O
chatted	O
.	O
I	O
copied	O
some	O
verses	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
W	O
ent	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
A	O
:	O
M	O
:	O
made	O
so	O
me	O
Italian	O
verses	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
&	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
uneasineſs	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
be	O
ing	O
revenged	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
see	O
some	O
day	O
as	O
anxious	O
upon	O
a	O
similair	O
occasion	O
Wednesday	O
Thursday	O
2	O
1	O
2	O
st	O
nd	O
:	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Dear	O
A	O
M	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
10	O
oClock	O
--	O
AM	B-pers
came	O
gave	O
orders	O
for	O
a	O
frame	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
picture	O
Read	O
2	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
Vielées	O
du	O
Chateau	O
,	O
very	O
busy	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
,	O
arranging	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
&	O
putting	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
perfect	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
reception	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Dſs	O
&	O
Kelly	B-pers
--	O
The	O
post	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
no	O
letter	O
from	O
Derbyshire	B-place
!	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
extremely	O
disappointed	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
check	O
the	O
falling	O
tear	O
,	O
I	O
reproach	O
'd	O
myself	O
for	O
the	O
weakneſs	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
harbour	O
any	O
doubts	O
of	O
the	O
affection	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
Leonidas	B-pers
&	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
them	O
till	O
6	O
oClock	O
we	O
then	O
separated	O
I	O
read	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
get	O
through	O
thise	O
3	O
large	O
Octv	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
has	O
promised	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
friend	O
--	O
at	O
7	O
oClock	O
my	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
came	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
the	O
time	O
paſs	O
'd	O
rapidly	O
--	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
tell	O
them	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
my	O
dearest	O
&	O
beloved	O
friend	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
highly	O
satisfied	O
,	O
charm	O
'd	O
wth-	O
his	O
Character	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
--	O
O	O
how	O
delightful	O
is	O
virtuous	O
praise	O
!	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
said	O
that	O
our	O
conduct	O
proved	O
that	O
we	O
poſseſsed	O
the	O
heigth	O
of	O
sentiment	O
without	O
being	O
romantic	O
She	O
&	O
two	B-pers
respectable	I-pers
friends	I-pers
touch	O
'd	O
my	O
heart	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
sensible	O
manner	O
by	O
the	O
tender	O
and	O
delicate	O
aſsurances	O
of	O
their	O
love	O
&	O
esteem	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
in	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
aſsured	O
me	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
should	O
have	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
impatient	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
depend	O
upon	O
his	O
spending	O
some	O
days	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
this	O
Autumn	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
my	O
other	O
friends	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
commission	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
Vici	O
de	O
poche	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
read	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
she	O
had	O
inclosed	O
to	O
to	O
her	O
Sert	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
J——	O
)	O
she	O
says	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
disappointment	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
family	O
at	O
my	O
not	O
coming	O
to	O
Horton	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
preſsing	O
meſsage	O
to	O
invite	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
supper	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
gave	O
us	O
some	O
picturesque	O
descriptions	O
of	O
places	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
--	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
Friday	O
23	O
d	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
abt	O
her	O
Italian	O
Friend	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
inquire	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
purchase	O
of	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
poor	O
Mrs	O
--	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
paid	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
visit	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
of	O
Our	O
Ldy	B-pers
..	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
..	O
S——	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
lamented	O
that	O
Robert	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
was	O
so	O
apt	O
to	O
see	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
prejudiced	O
light	O
--	O
however	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
all	O
our	O
failings	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
make	O
full	O
allowance	O
for	O
those	O
of	O
others	O
&	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
peculiarities	O
in	O
the	O
characters	O
of	O
our	O
friends	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
to	O
conceal	O
them	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
notice	O
of	O
others	O
if	O
poſsible	O
:	O
as	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
was	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
to	O
Windsor	B-place
I	O
gave	O
him	O
meſsages	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
in	O
my	B-pers
Cousin	I-pers
s	O
family	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
consult	O
him	O
abt	O
.	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
letter	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
immediately	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
advice	O
.	O
he	O
sat	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
,	O
related	O
some	O
curious	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
some	O
beautiful	O
branches	O
of	O
orange	O
tree	O
in	O
flower	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Swiſs	O
&	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
--	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Children	O
stay	O
'd	O
sometime	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
my	O
old	O
Torment	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
Mary	B-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
friendly	O
visit	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
purchase	O
ye	O
.	O
thing	O
for	O
poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
this	O
Aft	O
.	O
to	O
Portland	O
place	O
.	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
me	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
ran	O
upstairs	O
&	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
expected	O
letter	O
--	O
the	O
contents	O
made	O
me	O
ample	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
anxiety	O
I	O
suffer	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
x	I-pers
&	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
expected	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
due	O
for	O
ye	O
½	O
years	O
rent	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
owed	O
these	O
3	O
years	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
this	O
Money	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
who	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
not	O
doubting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
immediate	O
payment	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
finishd	O
writing	O
this	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
this	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Serts	O
.	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
--	O
Richard	B-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
we	O
sat	O
long	O
at	O
table	O
--	O
no	O
Servts-	O
waiting	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
open	O
&	O
communicative	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
particulars	O
relative	O
to	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
--	O
little	O
Ldy	B-pers
:	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
desert	O
George	B-pers
made	O
them	O
repeat	O
2	O
Greek	O
lines	O
he	O
had	O
taught	O
them	O
--	O
the	O
eldest	O
is	O
abt	O
4	O
ye	O
youngest	O
3	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
hours	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
D——shire	B-place
friend	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
outlines	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
letter	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
highly	O
entertained	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
reception	O
of	O
my	O
Picture	O
,	O
&	O
made	O
my	O
promise	O
to	O
tell	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
that	O
she	O
should	O
take	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
sit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
for	O
a	O
picture	O
for	O
him	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
saucy	O
&	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
better	O
order	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
join	O
'd	O
us	O
&	O
our	O
conversation	O
took	O
another	O
turn	O
--	O
Saunders	B-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Madme-	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
were	O
our	O
topics	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
Politics	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
no	O
opinion	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
as	O
a	O
Financier	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
promise	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
gave	O
directions	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
abt-	O
getting	O
the	O
things	O
--	O
At	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
wanted	O
to	O
detain	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
anxious	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
by	O
this	O
nights	O
post	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
.	O
had	O
my	O
Cousin	O
s	O
Coach	O
&	O
Servts	O
.	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Justi	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
the	O
fine	O
Edition	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
Quarto	O
&	O
also	O
the	O
large	O
Set	O
of	O
Prints	O
belonging	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
Had	O
just	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
to	O
scribble	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
this	O
nights	O
Post	O
inclos	O
'd	O
a	O
Packet	O
of	O
Diary	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
Cook	B-pers
waited	O
supper	O
for	O
me	O
join	O
'd	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
dispatches	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
staid	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
went	O
Mr-	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
we	O
sent	O
servts	O
.	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
&	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
chatted	O
over	O
my	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
my	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
some	O
parts	O
of	O
wch	O
..	O
I	O
communicated	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
the	O
subject	O
was	O
too	O
interesting	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
feel	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
rest	O
so	O
we	O
sat	O
talking	O
till	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morng	O
.	O
A	O
M	O
.	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
leſson	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
&	O
abt	O
.	O
½	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
retired	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
.	O
Saturday	O
24	O
th	O
:	O
July	O
1784	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
Dear	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
past	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
read	O
an	O
affecting	O
Story	O
in	O
les	O
Veillées	O
du	O
Chateau	O
whilst	O
my	O
Hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
--	O
as	O
Handel	B-pers
generally	O
is	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
&	O
sometimes	O
longer	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
read	O
always	O
,	O
I	O
get	O
through	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
Volumes	O
my	O
hair	O
dresſing	O
is	O
never	O
lost	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
commonly	O
also	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
scribble	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
.	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Friend	O
's	O
letter	O
of	O
yesterday	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
2	O
packets	O
of	O
Diary	O
under	O
two	O
covers	O
.	O
Read	O
&	O
wrote	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
--	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Betty	B-pers
--	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
ever	O
obliging	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
request	O
some	O
leſsons	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
we	O
separated	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Miſs	O
C	O
's	O
join	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
tea	O
early	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Grace	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
.	O
Dear	O
Madme	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
one	O
uninterrupted	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
two	O
dear	O
friends	O
very	O
happy	O
by	O
telling	O
ym	O
..	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
generous	O
aſsurance	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
separate	O
me	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
society	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Dſs	O
's	O
daughters	O
)	O
&	O
her	O
two	O
eldest	O
unmarried	O
daughters	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
came	O
¼	O
after	O
8	O
--	O
The	O
conversation	O
was	O
general	O
&	O
agreeable	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thynne	I-pers
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
the	O
Ducheſs	O
goes	O
to	O
Margate	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Thynne	I-pers
on	O
Monday	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
wth	O
her	O
to	O
supper	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
came	O
home	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
till	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V——	I-pers
came	O
&	O
chatted	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
undreſs	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
headach	O
&	O
did	O
not	O
set	O
up	O
to	O
read	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
generally	O
do	O
Mem	O
:	O
sent	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
Painter	O
4	O
L	O
:4	O
s	O
--	O
being	O
ye	O
remainder	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Money	O
for	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
Portrait	O
--	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
gives	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
Money	O
left	O
with	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Glover	O
for	O
ye	O
Picture	O
.	O
Sunday	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
.	O
Br	O
with	O
Opie	B-pers
we	O
had	O
a	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
aſsisted	O
her	O
in	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
buſineſs	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
not	O
being	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
when	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
from	O
C——	O
settled	O
some	O
accounts	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Answer	O
she	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
to	O
her	O
letter	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
one	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
--	O
extracts	O
from	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
wch	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
obliging	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
till	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
Stormont	B-pers
din	O
'd	O
&	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
heard	O
that	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
had	O
greatly	O
offended	O
his	O
friends	O
by	O
his	O
late	O
absence	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
--	O
They	O
wrote	O
to	O
remonstrate	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
folly	O
&	O
impropriety	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Answer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
&	O
quiet	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Anns	O
Hill	O
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
stay	O
sometime	O
longer	O
&	O
concluded	O
his	O
letter	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
wonder	O
'd	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
&	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
talk	O
'd	O
Politics	O
--	O
I	O
listen	O
'd	O
&	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
could	O
only	O
draw	O
ye	O
.	O
melancholy	O
conclusion	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
a	O
ruin	O
'd	O
People	O
&	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
Glory	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
was	O
set	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
before	O
10	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
to	O
meet	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
however	O
I	O
lost	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
her	O
Coach	O
when	O
I	O
drove	O
up	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
alone	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Dowgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Barrymore	I-pers
--	O
we	O
sup	O
'd	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
wickedly	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
a	O
blunder	O
I	O
made	O
by	O
calling	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
A	B-pers
M——	I-pers
&	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
toast	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
ye	O
.	O
Eveg	O
in	O
innocent	O
Mirth	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V——	I-pers
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
&	O
wishd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
before	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
.	O
Monday	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
Read	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
Madme	O
.	O
Genlis	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
breakfasted	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
upon	O
The	O
improvement	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Mind	O
--	O
the	O
characters	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
Children	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
method	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
in	O
bringing	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
condemn	O
'd	O
it	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
brought	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
over	O
to	O
my	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
.	O
at	O
10	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
sent	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
excuse	O
myself	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
so	O
hard	O
--	O
besides	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
A.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
execute	O
a	O
commiſsion	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
at	O
12	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
for	O
me	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
late	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Auction	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
ye	O
.	O
Japan	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
so	O
crouded	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
heat	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
after	O
suffering	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
detirmind	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
fainting	O
--	O
a	O
gentleman	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
politely	O
handed	O
me	O
through	O
ye	O
.	O
Croud	O
Dgr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Harrington	I-pers
&	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
wait	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
return	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
&	O
very	O
fair	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
This	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
Auction	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
at	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
I	O
think	O
will	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
&	O
c	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
's	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
good	O
Lady	B-pers
Mry.Churchill	I-pers
&	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
till	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
then	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
three	O
Letters	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
&	O
one	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
much	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
paſs	O
by	O
--	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
but	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
his	O
Horses	O
&	O
Grooms	O
were	O
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
s	O
door	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
--	O
by	O
this	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
I	O
suppose	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
cc	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
's	O
Carriage	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
well	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Brother	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
after	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
french	O
is	O
were	O
certainly	O
taking	O
infinite	O
pains	O
to	O
ad	O
d	O
o	O
pt	O
our	O
Manners	O
&	O
learn	O
our	O
language	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
astonishing	O
what	O
a	O
rapid	O
progreſs	O
they	O
made	O
in	O
both	O
.	O
he	O
entertained	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
describing	O
the	O
different	O
stiles	O
of	O
of	O
manners	O
in	O
foreign	O
Countries	O
&	O
particularly	O
the	O
bon	O
ton	O
etiquette	O
in	O
France	B-place
.	O
After	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
left	O
us	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
pretty	O
things	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
had	O
arranged	O
--	O
we	O
then	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
conversd	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
Justi	I-pers
Dſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
were	O
our	O
topics	O
--	O
not	O
forgetting	O
Lady	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
s	O
three	O
Sons	O
who	O
always	O
afford	O
her	O
ample	O
matter	O
for	O
converse	O
&	O
for	O
in	O
our	O
tête	O
à	O
têtes	O
.	O
got	O
home	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
ten	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Duncannon	I-pers
for	O
an	O
hour	O
read	O
&	O
wrote	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
A	O
M	O
--	O
Breakfasted	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
--	O
she	O
read	O
me	O
some	O
paſsages	O
she	O
had	O
selected	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
pleasures	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
imagination	O
,	O
what	O
genius	O
&	O
imagination	O
fancy	O
&	O
how	O
many	O
fine	O
images	O
of	O
Providence	O
&	O
Nature	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
beautiful	O
Poem	O
though	O
I	O
must	O
confeſs	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
parts	O
of	O
it	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
me	O
obscure	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
defect	O
owing	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
want	O
of	O
comprehension	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
among	O
my	O
favorite	O
lines	O
--	O
“	O
There	O
let	O
thy	O
Soul	O
acknowledge	O
its-	O
complaint	O
How	O
blind	O
,	O
how	O
impious	O
!	O
there	O
behold	O
ye-	O
ways	O
Of	O
Heav'n	O
's	O
eternal	O
destiny	O
to	O
Man	O
For	O
ever	O
just	O
,	O
benevolent	O
,	O
&	O
wise	O
,	O
That	O
Virtue	O
's	O
awful	O
steps	O
,	O
howe'er	O
pursu	O
e	O
'd	O
By	O
vexing	O
fortune	O
&	O
intrusive	O
pain	O
,	O
Should	O
never	O
be	O
divided	O
from	O
her	O
chaste	O
,	O
Her	O
fair	O
attendant	O
pleasure	O
,	O
need	O
I	O
urge	O
Thy	O
tardy	O
thought	O
thro	O
'	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
various	O
round	O
Of	O
this	O
existence	O
,	O
that	O
thy	O
soft'ning	O
soul	O
At	O
length	O
may	O
learn	O
what	O
energy	O
ye	O
hand	O
Of	O
Virtue	O
mingles	O
in	O
ye	O
bitter	O
tide	O
Of	O
Paſsion	O
swelling	O
wth	O
.	O
distreſs	O
&	O
pain	O
,	O
To	O
mitigate	O
ye	O
.	O
sharp	O
with	O
gracious	O
drops	O
Of	O
cordial	O
pleasure	O
?	O
“	O
Ask	O
ye	O
faithful	O
Youth	O
“	O
Why	O
ye	O
.	O
cold	O
Urn	O
of	O
her	O
whom	O
long	O
he	O
lov	O
'd	O
“	O
So	O
often	O
fills	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
so	O
often	O
draws	O
“	O
His	O
lonely	O
footsteps	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
silent	O
hour	O
“	O
To	O
pay	O
ye	O
.	O
mournful	O
tribute	O
of	O
his	O
tears	O
?	O
O	O
!	O
he	O
“	O
O	O
!	O
he	O
will	O
tell	O
thee	O
;	O
that	O
y	O
e	O
wealth	O
of	O
worlds	O
“	O
Should	O
ne'er	O
seduce	O
his	O
bosom	O
to	O
forego	O
“	O
That	O
sacred	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
noise	O
“	O
Of	O
care	O
&	O
envy	O
,	O
sweet	O
remembrance	O
sooths	O
“	O
With	O
Virtue	O
's	O
kindest	O
looks	O
his	O
aking	O
breast	O
,	O
“	O
And	O
turns	O
his	O
tears	O
to	O
rapture.	O
”	O
--	O
Mark	O
Akenside	O
,	O
The	O
Pleasures	O
of	O
the	O
Imagination	O
,	O
3	O
vols	O
.	O
(	O
London	O
:	O
R.	O
Dodsley	O
,	O
1744	O
)	O
,	O
ii.	O
,	O
ll	O
.	O
669-693	O
.	O
--	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
sat	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
read	O
,	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
conversed	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
letters	O
--	O
to	O
Akenside	B-pers
&	O
to	O
AMaria	B-pers
--	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
to	O
put	O
into	O
ye	O
post	O
.	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
(	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
this	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
being	O
engaged	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Stormonts	O
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
friend	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
as	O
did	O
Master	O
Mr	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
(	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
eldest	O
Son	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
as	O
usual	O
our	O
comfortable	O
dumb-waiters	O
&	O
no	O
Servts	O
.	O
to	O
restrain	O
conversation	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Scotch	O
were	O
much	O
discontented	O
with	O
the	O
Taxes	O
on	O
linnens	O
Gauses	O
&	O
Ribbons	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
quite	O
ruin	O
the	O
manufacturers	O
of	O
Perthshire	B-place
Glasſcow	B-place
&	O
Paisley	O
--	O
that	O
ye	O
..	O
Irish	O
grew	O
every	O
day	O
more	O
violent	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
a	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
had	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Theatre	O
at	O
Dublin	B-place
when	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
came	O
in	O
&	O
they	O
had	O
begun	O
playing	O
“	O
God	O
Save	O
ye	O
.	O
King	O
”	O
“	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
God	O
save	O
Mr-	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
King	O
of	O
France	B-place
&	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
oppreſsed	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Rutland	I-pers
told	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
Court	O
had	O
but	O
too	O
good	O
intelligence	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
paſs	O
'd	O
both	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
England	B-place
--	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
too	O
true	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
now	O
upon	O
an	O
equality	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
wth	O
..	O
respect	O
to	O
Navy	O
affairs	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
after	O
dinner	O
the	O
three	O
little	O
boys	O
engroſs	O
'd	O
attention	O
&	O
Politics	O
were	O
drop	O
'd	O
--	O
Louis	B-pers
ye	I-pers
16th	I-pers
returns	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
laugh	O
'd	O
a	O
news	O
paper	O
lie	O
wch	O
.	O
inform	O
'd	O
ye	O
Public	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
join	O
'd	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
&	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
as	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
--	O
this	O
arose	O
from	O
his	O
dining	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
Last	O
Week	O
--	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
in	O
Company	O
&	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
word	O
was	O
utter	O
'd	O
concerning	O
Politics	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
left	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
oClock	O
.	O
we	O
workd	O
&	O
conversed	O
till	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Thurlow	I-pers
told	O
me	O
how	O
ill	O
the	O
--	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
late	O
father	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
)	O
&	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
&	O
broken	O
promises	O
to	O
all	O
our	O
family	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
lay	O
under	O
great	O
obligations	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
our	O
deceased	O
Parents	O
--	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
behaviour	O
when	O
a	O
Volounnteer	O
in	O
ye	O
Ruſsian	O
Service	O
.	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
characters	O
of	O
my	B-pers
father	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
me	O
to	O
join	O
her	O
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
P——ſs	I-pers
at	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
went	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
supper	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
f	O
rom	O
or	O
Dear	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
to	O
beg	O
I	O
would	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
the	O
five	O
or	O
6	O
run	O
awat	O
Matches	O
&	O
the	O
several	O
imprudent	O
ones	O
lately	O
made	O
were	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
--	O
however	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
illnatured	O
censure	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
animadversions	O
on	O
the	O
folly	O
of	O
people	O
plunging	O
themselves	O
into	O
certain	O
misery	O
or	O
Unhappineſs	O
.	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
¾	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	O
rooms	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
s	O
Women	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
bedchamber	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
this	O
afternoon	O
.	O
July	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
1784	O
Wednesday	O
Read	O
in	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boughton	I-pers
from	O
6	O
till	O
8	O
--	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
--	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
drawers	O
gave	O
orders	O
abt-	O
notable	O
things	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
aſsure	O
myself	O
that	O
Madme	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
&	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
are	O
become	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
their	O
faults	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
conducted	O
themselves	O
extremely	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
advice	O
&	O
pardon	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
that	O
in	O
general	O
mild	O
reproof	O
&	O
good	O
advice	O
effects	O
a	O
more	O
lasting	O
reform	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
heart	O
is	O
not	O
utterly	O
depraved	O
tha	O
t	O
n	O
harsh	O
reproaches	O
&	O
severe	O
treatment	O
.	O
My	O
Old	O
Maid	O
Hannah	B-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
&	O
she	O
&	O
her	O
husband	O
were	O
now	O
settled	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
--	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
procure	O
her	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
custom	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
advice	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
she	O
took	O
very	O
gratefully	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
follow	O
--	O
had	O
several	O
visits	O
from	O
Betty	B-pers
--	O
wrote	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
--	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
gentle	O
Lecture	O
upon	O
his	O
general	O
conduct	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
as	O
AMaria	B-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
hint	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
letter	O
that	O
my	O
young	O
friend	O
had	O
forgot	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
admonitions	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
&	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
from	O
3	O
till	O
4	O
--	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
polite	O
,	O
&	O
friendly	O
letter	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
.	O
she	O
inform	O
s	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
dear	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
was	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
c	O
¼	O
before	O
5	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
hear	O
ye	O
:	O
debates	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
--	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
were	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
longer	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
than	O
usual	O
--	O
George	B-pers
gave	O
them	O
a	O
reading	O
leſson	O
--	O
her	O
method	O
is	O
very	O
proper	O
,	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
tire	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
makes	O
it	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
when	O
she	O
instructs	O
ym	O
.	O
.	O
--	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
conversed	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
when	O
Charles	B-pers
came	O
home	O
.	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
debates	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
told	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
News	O
papers	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
note	O
ym	O
.	O
down	O
.	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
Char̄iotCharriot	O
at	O
10	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
we	O
wrote	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
continued	O
my	O
employment	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
writing	O
Extracts	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
more	O
work	O
again	O
Thursday	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
B	O
:	O
with	O
A	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
10.	O
our	O
conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
learned	O
education	O
for	O
Women	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
of	O
different	O
opinions	O
I	O
was	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
however	O
we	O
left	O
our	O
argument	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
immediately	O
after	O
B.	O
sent	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
to	O
Church	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Thanksgiving	O
day	O
A	O
.	O
M	O
:	O
went	O
also	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
time	O
wth	O
.	O
reading	O
writing	O
&	O
working	O
--	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Scott	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
me	O
when	O
ye	O
Tax	O
on	O
franking	O
takes	O
place	O
--	O
wch	O
..	O
will	O
be	O
abt	O
.	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
date	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
came	O
from	O
her	O
Villa	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
she	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
honest	O
Heart	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
--	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
restore	O
tranquility	O
to	O
her	O
wounded	O
breast	O
&	O
clear	O
XXXX	O
from	O
appearances	O
wch	O
.	O
Chs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
thought	O
were	O
against	O
her	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
wth-	O
a	O
safe	O
conscience	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
firmly	O
persuaded	O
XXXX	O
's	O
affection	O
for	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
G	O
:	O
is	O
pure	O
&	O
unalterable	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
feelings	O
are	O
too	O
exquisite	O
for	O
her	O
ever	O
to	O
enjoy	O
tranquil	O
happineſs	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
pity	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
I	O
have	O
suffer	O
'd	O
exquisitely	O
from	O
allowing	O
my	O
sensibility	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
my	O
reason	O
--	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
a	O
more	O
reasonable	O
being	O
.	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
faults	O
&	O
weakneſs	O
's	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
conquer	O
them	O
&	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
not	O
only	O
insure	O
my	O
own	O
happineſs	O
--	O
but	O
contribute	O
to	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
my	O
D——	O
&	O
preserve	O
his	O
love	O
,	O
his	O
confidence	O
,	O
&	O
esteem	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
:	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
at	O
Sandleford	B-place
on	O
Saty	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
there	O
&	O
stay	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
She	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
telling	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
that	O
she	O
should	O
expect	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
long	O
'd	O
to	O
aſsure	O
him	O
of	O
her	O
affection	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H.	I-pers
More	I-pers
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
sincere	O
characters	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
her	O
profeſsions	O
are	O
all	O
from	O
the	O
heart	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
valuable	O
one	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
sat	O
wth	O
..	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
she	O
read	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
poor	O
Woman	O
she	O
had	O
relieved	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
A	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
enquired	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
wd	O
.	O
leave	O
her	O
name	O
or	O
busineſs	O
--	O
said	O
she	O
wd	O
.	O
call	O
again	O
--	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
London	O
--	O
my	O
torment	O
AMaria	B-pers
call	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
At	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Lady	O
Stor	O
monts	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Her	O
Brother	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
&	O
Charles	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
as	O
usual	O
Dumbwaiters	O
&	O
sat	O
long	O
at	O
table	O
--	O
but	O
we	O
neer	O
set	O
long	O
after	O
dinner	O
--	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
deep	O
in	O
Politics	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
seems	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
impartial	O
Politician	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
there	O
never	O
existed	O
one	O
--	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
bias̄	O
'd	O
by	O
party	O
--	O
for	O
example	O
,	O
he	O
both	O
censured	O
&	O
admired	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
staid	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
&	O
I	O
had	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
till	O
10	O
,	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
&	O
chatted	O
on	O
indifferent	O
subjects	O
When	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pit	I-pers
came	O
home	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
leave	O
&	O
had	O
his	O
Chariot	O
.	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
¼	O
past	O
10	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sent	O
an	O
excuse	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
Extracts	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
,	O
wch	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
,	O
scribbling	O
till	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
Friday	O
30	O
th	O
:	O
July	O
1784	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Finish	O
'd	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
's	O
Veillées	O
du	O
Chatteau	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9.	O
breakfasted	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
we	O
talkd	O
of	O
Madme	B-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
--	O
of	O
AMaria	B-pers
--	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D——	I-pers
A	O
M	O
was	O
charm	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
their	O
characters	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
notable	O
Work	O
till	O
12	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
short	O
letter	O
&	O
enclosed	O
a	O
Pacquet	O
of	O
D	O
:	O
for	O
Derbyshire	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
.	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
smart	O
note	O
&	O
some	O
franks	O
from	O
my	O
Cousin	O
his	B-pers
father	I-pers
--	O
hislate	B-pers
Mother	I-pers
came	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Villa	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
being	O
engaged	O
to	O
Challes	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
&	O
return	O
tomorrow	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
again	O
nit	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
--	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
joy	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
reading	O
it	O
twice	O
over	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
--	O
what	O
liberal	O
sentiments	O
&	O
what	O
a	O
Heart	O
has	O
this	O
amiable	O
Man	O
!	O
--	O
how	O
happy	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
endearing	O
name	O
of	O
father	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Lady	O
S——	O
well	O
we	O
din	O
'd	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
.	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
dinner	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
desert	O
was	O
over	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
came	O
home	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
house	O
of	O
Lords	O
--	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
:	I-pers
could	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
dinner	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
solitary	O
meal	O
--	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
join	O
us	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
7.	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
2	O
dear	O
little	O
boys	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
told	O
My	O
Cousin	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
agreeable	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
she	O
seems	O
as	O
sensible	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
merit	O
&	O
amiableneſs	O
as	O
myself	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
acquainted	O
us	O
wth	O
.	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
debate	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
provoked	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Sen	I-pers
:	I-pers
for	O
dividing	O
&	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
foolish	O
measure	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
20	O
Lords	O
--	O
&	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
4	O
on	O
their	O
side	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
he	O
sat	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
near	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
arrived	O
in	O
Town	B-place
yesterday	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Portland	O
place	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
purchased	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
vext	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
inconvenient	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
present	O
situation	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Visits	O
.	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
de	I-pers
Chatres	I-pers
&	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Royal	O
Nursery	O
at	O
10	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Coach	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
The	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
were	O
at	O
home	O
we	O
sat	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
answer	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
letter	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
finish	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Bell	O
went	O
its	O
round	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
.	I-pers
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
near	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
thinking	O
over	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
Providence	O
in	O
granting	O
me	O
the	O
wish	O
of	O
me	O
heart	O
--	O
viz	O
:	O
the	O
being	O
beloved	O
by	O
A	O
virtuous	O
Man	O
.	O
&	O
the	O
desire	O
I	O
felt	O
of	O
so	O
doing	O
my	O
duty	O
in	O
this	O
life	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
his	O
&	O
my	O
being	O
happy	O
hereafter	O
.	O
God	O
Grant	O
we	O
may	O
so	O
live	O
here	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
come	O
we	O
may	O
still	O
be	O
inseparably	O
united	O
.	O
Saty	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
July	O
1784	O
.	O
Joind	O
dear	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
--	O
finish	O
'd	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
worthy	O
father	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Post	O
--	O
wrote	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Isabella	B-pers
wch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
take	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
I	O
excusd	O
myself	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
to	O
dine	O
there	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
sick	O
friends	O
must	O
claim	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
right	O
to	O
ones	O
attentions	O
.	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Cold	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
purchase	O
presents	O
we	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
)	O
meant	O
to	O
give	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Servants	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
civil	O
&	O
as	O
Vails	O
were	O
not	O
allowed	O
we	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
some	O
acknowledgement	O
for	O
their	O
civil	O
behaviour	O
&	O
attention	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Met	O
the	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Cs	I-pers
Member	O
for	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
.	O
he	O
enquired	O
much	O
after	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
inform	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Powis	I-pers
that	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
I	O
bought	O
presents	O
for	O
the	O
Butler	O
&	O
3	O
footmen	O
--	O
in	O
returning	O
home	O
met	O
my	O
Uncle	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wakes	I-pers
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
&	O
sat	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Frederick	B-pers
were	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
--	O
we	O
paid	O
equally	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Isabella	B-pers
I	O
gave	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
presents	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
grateful	O
&	O
pleased	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Coachman	O
Money	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
hired	O
servt	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
Louis	B-pers
was	O
dreſsing	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
word	O
for	O
John	B-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
--	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
present	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
one	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
--	O
&	O
had	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V	I-pers
who	O
dined	O
wth	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
when	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
recd	O
:	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
poor	O
friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	I-pers
--	O
a	O
melancholy	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
her	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
night	O
Miſs	B-pers
L——	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
soon	O
joind	O
us	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
repeat	O
to	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
cld	O
.	O
recollect	O
of	O
many	O
parts	O
of	O
his	O
speeches	O
Yesterday	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
done	O
justice	O
to	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
papers	O
.	O
&	O
many	O
things	O
left	O
out	O
What	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
India	O
Bill	O
was	O
too	O
difuse	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
complicated	O
a	O
Subject	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
render	O
any	O
clear	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
,	O
therefor	O
e	O
I	O
wont	O
attempt	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
as	O
my	O
most	O
dear	O
&	O
excellent	O
friend	O
Lord	B-pers
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
ill	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
&	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
she	O
should	O
grow	O
worse	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
sooner	O
than	O
she	O
intended	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
to	O
beg	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
left	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscowan	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Charge	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
--	O
had	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dowg	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Coach	O
found	O
my	O
worthy	O
friend	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
dared	O
to	O
hope	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
½	O
.	O
She	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
future	O
prospect	O
of	O
happineſs	O
&	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
admiration	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
father	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
tempted	O
to	O
Marry	O
him	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
her	O
85	O
th	O
.	O
Year	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
this	O
dear	O
Woman	O
has	O
all	O
the	O
chearfulneſs	O
&	O
sensibility	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
when	O
young	O
.	O
&	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
faculties	O
are	O
ye	O
.	O
least	O
impaired	O
--	O
he	O
r	O
eye	O
sight	O
only	O
excepted	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
ever	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
will	O
be	O
any	O
Person	O
superiour	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
She	O
is	O
as	O
perfect	O
as	O
human	O
Nature	O
can	O
be	O
--	O
my	O
admiration	O
of	O
her	O
is	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
singular	O
--	O
for	O
this	O
most	O
excellent	O
of	O
Woman	O
is	O
adored	O
by	O
all	O
who	O
are	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
knowing	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
esteem	O
myself	O
happy	O
in	O
having	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
honor	O
--	O
advantage	O
,	O
&	O
privilege	O
of	O
having	O
such	O
frequent	O
opportunities	O
of	O
enjoying	O
her	O
charming	O
society	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
left	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
friend	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
ordered	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
¼	O
before	O
10	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
a	O
terrible	O
cold	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
take	O
Whey	O
&	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
yt	O
.	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
late	O
scribbling	O
&	O
reading	O
.	O
As	O
AMaria	B-pers
has	O
now	O
resolved	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
Town	B-place
till	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
returns	O
from	O
Margate	B-place
(	O
when	O
they	O
will	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
Bullstrode	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
her	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
be	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
give	O
up	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
but	O
wht	O
.	O
relates	O
to	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
being	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
.	O
How	O
flattering	O
to	O
me	O
is	O
the	O
affection	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
contrive	O
to	O
divide	O
my	O
time	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
till	O
ye	O
.	O
confinement	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
is	O
over	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
to	O
day	O
that	O
my	O
Uncle	O
D——	B-pers
is	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
a	O
meſsage	O
from	O
Richmond	B-place
this	O
Morng	O
.	O
Sunday	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
August	O
1784	O
Breakfasted	O
wth	O
.	O
William	B-pers
.	O
her	O
Cold	O
rather	O
better	O
--	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
letters	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Glovers	O
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
Miſs	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
in	O
wch	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
most	O
kind	O
mention	O
made	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Went	O
to	O
May	O
fair	O
Chapel	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
return	O
'd	O
when	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
sent	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
--	O
I	O
sat	O
½	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
as	O
my	O
Jackson	B-pers
was	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
him	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
sitting	O
together	O
he	O
sat	O
wth	O
.	O
us	O
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
let	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
leave	O
us	O
.	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Paintings	O
--	O
Italy	B-place
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
agreeably	O
surprised	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
Visit	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
going	O
to	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
she	O
sat	O
a	O
¼	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
wth-	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Boudoir	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
ten	O
minutes	O
tête	O
á	O
tête	O
,	O
she	O
them	O
left	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
from	O
3	O
till	O
4	O
was	O
alone	O
--	O
read	O
some	O
letters	O
--	O
scribbled	O
in	O
my	O
Diary	O
--	O
then	O
alter	O
'd	O
my	O
dreſs	O
&	O
was	O
ready	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
many	O
days	O
past	O
--	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
wth	O
..	O
us	O
--	O
Politics	O
all	O
dinner	O
time	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
long	O
together	O
after	O
we	O
left	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
they	O
soon	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Drawing	O
room	O
(	O
we	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
dear	O
boys	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
as	O
usual	O
)	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
dined	O
wth	O
..	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
yesterday	O
--	O
that	O
very	O
handsome	O
mention	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
lively	O
&	O
agreeable	O
.	O
the	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langlois	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
to	O
meet	O
Sr.	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
at	O
Brighthelmstone	B-place
--	O
was	O
please	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
Duke	B-pers
de	I-pers
Chartres	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
mention	O
my	O
friend	O
&	O
acquaintance	O
Lord	B-pers
S	I-pers
in	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
proved	O
they	O
liked	O
him	O
.	O
--	O
heard	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
King	O
of	O
France	B-place
was	O
become	O
a	O
great	O
drinker	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
indifferent	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Monsieur	B-pers
Batin	I-pers
&	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
a	O
Niece	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
's	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
8	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
away	O
as	O
Lady	B-pers
Yorke	I-pers
does	O
not	O
let	O
in	O
any	O
Company	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
right	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
&	O
invited	O
them	O
--	O
they	O
staid	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Yorke	I-pers
is	O
a	O
lively	O
pleasant	O
Man	O
--	O
much	O
polished	O
&	O
quite	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
ye	O
:	O
World	O
.	O
his	O
Lady	O
is	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
--	O
polite	O
,	O
well	O
bred	O
but	O
not	O
easy	O
in	O
her	O
Manner	O
--	O
the	O
Young	O
lady	O
is	O
her	O
Niece	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
--	O
an	O
intelligent	O
countenance	O
&	O
sensible	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
alone	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
--	O
we	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Josheph	I-pers
Yorke	I-pers
her	O
affection	O
for	O
our	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
She	O
was	O
Married	O
24	O
Years	O
&	O
her	O
paſsion	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
no	O
other	O
name	O
was	O
as	O
lively	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
moment	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
she	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
object	O
in	O
life	O
but	O
him	O
&	O
only	O
regretted	O
dring	O
because	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
behind	O
&	O
c	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
late	I-pers
Lady	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
5	O
Minutes	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
as	O
,	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veseys	I-pers
was	O
to	O
be	O
wth	O
her	O
this	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
Comfort	O
of	O
hearing	O
she	O
was	O
charming	O
well	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
I	O
sat	O
together	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
Cold	O
better	O
--	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
talking	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
very	O
hoarse	O
I	O
read	O
aloud	O
one	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
's	I-pers
s	O
Sermons	O
(	O
On	O
the	O
Union	O
of	O
Piety	O
&	O
Morality	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
A	B-pers
:	I-pers
M——	I-pers
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
elegant	O
writers	O
we	O
have	O
--	O
he	O
interests	O
and	O
persuades	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
12	O
Monday	O
2	O
st	O
d	O
:	O
August	O
1784	O
--	O
went	O
down	O
at	O
9	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
dear	O
Blair	B-pers
--	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
sat	O
&	O
chatted	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
&	O
read	O
curious	O
Anecdotes	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
Herald	O
till	O
½	O
past	O
10	O
--	O
then	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
--	O
work	O
'd	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Notable	O
work	O
.	O
repaird	O
my	O
finest	O
Screen	O
&	O
c	O
began	O
Blair	B-pers
s	O
Voyages	O
--	O
Recd	O
.	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
from	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
to	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
prevented	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Airing	O
as	O
Cook	B-pers
were	O
come	O
from	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
left	O
a	O
Meſsage	O
wch	O
.	O
affected	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
my	O
Old	O
former	O
Maid	O
(	O
who	O
lived	O
wth	O
.	O
me	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Court	O
)	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Murrays	I-pers
had	O
been	O
dangerously	O
Ill	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
friday	O
I	O
sent	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
immediately	O
--	O
who	O
brought	O
me	O
word	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
bed	O
&	O
lookd	O
wretchedly	O
--	O
had	O
visits	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
&	O
Hannah	B-pers
during	O
ye	O
.	O
Morng	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
pleasure	O
of	O
receiving	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
D——shire	O
friend	O
--	O
Recd	O
:	O
also	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Isabella	B-pers
from	O
Dunkeld	B-place
--	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
A	B-pers
M——	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
Our	O
Cousin	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
Lady	B-pers
S	I-pers
was	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
he	O
is	O
was	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
day	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
India	O
Bill	O
.	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
several	O
Compts-	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
from	O
ye	O
.	O
ladies	O
in	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
8	O
went	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
she	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
were	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
--	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
the	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
recd	O
.	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
as	O
it	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
&	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
s	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
10	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
abt	O
ye	O
.	O
Coach	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
--	O
the	O
On	O
e	O
of	O
the	O
Chairmen	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
employ	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
so	O
many	O
fine	O
speeches	O
of	O
his	O
happineſs	O
in	O
seeing	O
me	O
&	O
c	O
that	O
my	O
fare	O
cost	O
me	O
½	O
a	O
Crown	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
--	O
Uncle	B-pers
William	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
as	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
wrong	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
them	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Margate	B-place
tomorrow	O
I	O
put	O
off	O
answering	O
my	O
The	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
letter	O
till	O
tomorrows	O
Post	O
--	O
we	O
supd	O
&	O
sat	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
till	O
¼	O
past	O
11	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Rooms	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
D——	B-pers
&	O
a	O
day	O
appointed	O
to	O
settle	O
ye	O
.	O
busineſs	O
