TOKEN	NE
Park	O
Street	O
110	O
--	O
Londn-	B-place
April	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1787	O
my	O
Dear	O
Honble	B-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
to	O
shew	O
,	O
You	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
aprove	O
Your	O
obliging	O
intention	O
of	O
never	O
remaining	O
silent	O
so	O
long	O
again	O
,	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
pen	O
to	O
sett	O
the	O
example	O
and	O
thank	O
You	O
for	O
Your	O
kind	O
letter	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
double	O
pleasure	O
,	O
by	O
aſsureing	O
me	O
of	O
Your	O
Health	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
charming	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
already	O
see	O
,	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
a	O
thousand	O
Jolies	O
petites	O
manieres	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
own	O
good	O
humor	O
,	O
and	O
expreſsive	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
sense	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
shew	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
time	O
,	O
enables	O
her	O
to	O
speak	O
.	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
meantime	O
,	O
Mama	O
will	O
already	O
understand	O
her	O
meaning	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
:	O
and	O
(	O
if	O
report	O
says	O
true	O
)	O
in	O
some	O
months	O
hence	O
will	O
present	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
companion	O
&	O
rival	O
,	O
no	O
bad	O
thing	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
spoilt	O
.	O
having	O
said	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
Chere	O
ye	O
Princeſs	O
tis	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
we	O
are	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
Louisa	B-pers
has	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
benefit	O
expected	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
but	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
often	O
remarked	O
that	O
the	O
virtues	O
of	O
those	O
waters	O
are	O
found	O
more	O
strongly	O
after	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
left	O
off	O
.	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
experience	O
the	O
truth	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
looks	O
very	O
thin	O
and	O
complains	O
of	O
nerves	O
and	O
headachs	O
;	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
and	O
unluckily	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
chicken	O
pox	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
children	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
got	O
well	O
again	O
so	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
lucky	O
thing	O
over	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
disapointed	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
very	O
much	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
masters	O
&	O
seen	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
but	O
all	O
this	O
You	O
have	O
from	O
better	O
Authority	O
--	O
so	O
shall	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
Yr	O
.	O
Familly	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
enquired	O
kindly	O
after	O
You	O
a	O
few	O
evenings	O
ago	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Peachy	I-pers
s	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
beged	O
her	O
compts	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
does	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
recover	O
'd	O
her	O
loſs	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caroline	I-pers
is	O
as	O
You	O
heard	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
complaining	O
way	O
,	O
her	O
age	O
is	O
much	O
against	O
expecting	O
much	O
amendment	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
the	O
pleasure	O
she	O
enjoys	O
,	O
with	O
partaking	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
dinner	O
(	O
when	O
invited	O
to	O
one	O
)	O
is	O
often	O
atended	O
with	O
bad	O
consequences	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
is	O
wonderfully	O
well	O
,	O
her	O
Doctor	O
is	O
now	O
the	O
patient	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
town	O
is	O
enquiring	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
who	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
has	O
a	O
21	O
days	O
fever	O
&	O
has	O
had	O
3	O
relapses	O
so	O
thought	O
in	O
danger	O
having	O
told	O
You	O
enough	O
about	O
sick	O
people	O
will	O
change	O
the	O
subject	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
Doctor	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
has	O
had	O
the	O
gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
joy	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
about	O
Him	O
who	O
triumph	O
in	O
the	O
idea	O
that	O
He	O
must	O
now	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
cruel	O
disorder	O
will	O
attack	O
sober	O
people	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
those	O
that	O
sit	O
over	O
the	O
bottle	O
.	O
as	O
he	O
always	O
insisted	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
gout	O
was	O
acquired	O
by	O
sitting	O
too	O
much	O
round	O
the	O
brown	O
table	O
--	O
at	O
H.	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
last	O
thursday	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
took	O
her	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
Faro	O
table	O
as	O
usual	O
at	O
a	O
stated	O
hour	O
,	O
being	O
too	O
great	O
an	O
invalid	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
fashonable	O
late	O
hours	O
--	O
on	O
quiting	O
the	O
table	O
she	O
left	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
play	O
with	O
that	O
for	O
her	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
obliged	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
lose	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
friend	O
undertook	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
than	O
Lady	B-pers
Ferrars	I-pers
sat	O
down	O
&	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
play	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
100	O
Guineas	O
delighted	O
with	O
his	O
luck	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
table	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
carry	O
it	O
imediatly	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
W——	I-pers
.	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
abed	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Familly	O
asleep	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
determined	O
and	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Ferrars	I-pers
drove	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Eliza	I-pers
:	I-pers
Lutterrell	I-pers
after	O
repeatedly	O
knocking	O
frighted	O
Servant	O
out	O
of	O
window	O
begged	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
instantly	O
as	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
F——	I-pers
must	O
speak	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
E	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
the	O
whole	O
familly	O
frightened	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
sences	O
the	O
Prince	O
&	O
Ly	O
.	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
H	O
.	O
R	O
.	O
H	O
.	O
had	O
the	O
grace	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
bedchamber	O
door	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
saying	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
F——	I-pers
sends	O
You	O
a	O
Shower	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
flinging	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
went	O
home	O
leaving	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
in	O
an	O
uproar	O
&	O
the	O
neighbours	O
alarmed	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
gave	O
a	O
great	O
Ball	O
the	O
Prince	O
was	O
there	O
so	O
drunk	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
making	O
violent	O
love	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
&	O
swearing	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
handsomer	O
than	O
all	O
the	O
D——d	O
young	O
things	O
that	O
thought	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
them	O
selves	O
&	O
were	O
so	O
admired	O
--	O
it	O
seems	O
the	O
fashon	O
to	O
marry	O
without	O
wanting	O
house	O
or	O
home	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Duchess	I-pers
of	I-pers
Argyll	I-pers
is	O
trying	O
it	O
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
(	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
)	I-pers
is	O
just	O
Married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
with	O
having	O
only	O
800	O
a	O
yr	O
.	O
to	O
spend	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
handsome	O
coach	O
&	O
Phaeton	O
&	O
gone	O
to	O
Brighton	B-place
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
is	O
next	O
week	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
same	O
fashon	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
--	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
house	O
but	O
are	O
to	O
live	O
among	O
their	O
Friends	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
new	O
scheme	O
&	O
seems	O
an	O
uncomfortable	O
one	O
my	O
Sister	O
joyns	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Neish	I-pers
&	O
self	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
yourself	O
&	O
Capt	B-pers
:	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Affectly	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
lives	O
in	O
George	O
Street	O
Westr	B-place
.	I-place
and	O
is	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
letters	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
him	O
so	O
you	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
way	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
forward	O
it	O
wherever	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
--	O
we	O
go	O
next	O
tuesday	O
to	O
Ockham	B-place
for	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Brother	O
&	O
Gen	B-pers
:	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
will	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
where	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
yet	O
for	O
more	O
then	O
a	O
day	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
16	O
years	O
old	O
a	O
young	O
beauty	O
just	O
presented	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cholomondley	I-pers
.	O
she	O
is	O
daughter	O
to	O
preaty	O
Lord	B-pers
Mulgrave	I-pers
,	O
and	O
daughter	O
in	O
law	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cholomondley	I-pers
that	O
was	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
an	O
extrordinary	O
choice	O
on	O
all	O
sides	O
addio	O
mia	O
Cara	O
Amicia	O
Miſs	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
P.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Duchess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
Bath	B-place
King	O
London	B-place
Apr	O
five	O
1787	O
