TOKEN	NE
Tho	O
I	O
have	O
out	O
lived	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Pen	O
&	O
Ink	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
refuse	O
myself	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
thanking	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
for	O
Her	O
most	O
obliging	O
agreeable	O
Letter	O
--	O
&	O
kind	O
remembra	O
nce	O
of	O
Her	O
wandring	O
Friends	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
d	O
deal	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
sweet	O
Companions	O
hate	O
the	O
deserted	O
Vis	O
a	O
Vis	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
in	O
Margate	B-place
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
never	O
open	O
the	O
Blinds	O
here	O
I	O
see	O
for	O
ever	O
Families	O
dislodging	O
&	O
Strangers	O
th	O
taking	O
their	O
Place	O
without	O
ever	O
enquiring	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
convinced	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
match	O
the	O
midnight	O
Visiters	O
any	O
where	O
out	O
of	O
Clargis	O
Street	O
--	O
the	O
bulk	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
here	O
are	O
as	O
much	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cape	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
certainly	O
the	O
beautiful	O
nymphs	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
Show	O
of	O
Carriages	O
&	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
soon	O
know	O
every	O
lodg	O
worth	O
knowing	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
a	O
great	O
loſs	O
indeed	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
so	O
much	O
benefit	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
few	O
however	O
whose	O
Company	O
I	O
like	O
much	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Room	O
&	O
window	O
that	O
look	O
over	O
buildings	O
to	O
the	O
Au	O
Sea	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
often	O
said	O
how	O
happy	O
are	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
how	O
enjoying	O
the	O
cool	O
Breeze	O
wafted	O
from	O
London	B-place
--	O
alas	O
poor	O
the	B-pers
Dowgr	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
were	O
panting	O
for	O
breath	O
&	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
never	O
recover	O
it	O
the	O
Glaſs	O
at	O
jamaica	O
height	O
&	O
the	O
learned	O
said	O
Barom	O
eter	O
&	O
Thermometer	O
ga	O
kept	O
equal	O
pace	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
that	O
preceded	O
the	O
Sicil	O
ian	O
Earth	O
Quakes	O
which	O
I	O
may	O
venture	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
as	O
chilling	O
cold	O
has	O
now	O
taken	O
place	O
I	O
thank	O
Heaven	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
is	O
well	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
may	O
flatter	O
myself	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
illnes	O
the	O
warm	O
Sea	O
bath	O
he	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
--	O
the	O
Place	O
I	O
think	O
very	O
Picturesque	O
a	O
high	O
Beech	O
over	O
the	O
Sea	O
were	O
many	O
Timber	O
Yards	O
give	O
Benches	O
where	O
the	O
Contemplative	O
might	O
be	O
lull	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
dashing	O
of	O
the	O
Tyde	O
&	O
you	O
might	O
uninterupted	O
indulge	O
your	O
reveries	O
--	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
réve	O
Reve	O
&	O
I	O
&	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
Sleep	O
for	O
the	O
Sea	O
has	O
never	O
but	O
one	O
Story	O
to	O
tell	O
except	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
visited	O
by	O
Shiprack	O
&	O
Storm	O
--	O
the	O
airing	O
Grounds	O
are	O
is	O
the	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
beautiful	O
State	O
of	O
Culivation	O
the	O
Garden	O
Colours	O
of	O
Purple	O
&	O
yellow	O
without	O
a	O
Weed	O
not	O
a	O
hibi	O
s	O
k	O
lost	O
--	O
the	O
Sea	O
washing	O
the	O
Coast	O
Ireland	B-place
which	O
is	O
a	O
vast	O
up	O
pretended	O
Ruin	O
of	O
Monastic	O
&	O
Gothic	O
buildings	O
&	O
Towers	O
are	O
scaterd	O
over	O
a	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
receſs	O
upon	O
a	O
Concave	O
Beech	O
in	O
every	O
plot	O
Shelterd	O
from	O
the	O
Winds	O
--	O
very	O
pretty	O
Villages	O
&	O
tufts	O
of	O
Wood	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
craſy	O
Streets	O
which	O
do	O
not	O
promise	O
any	O
thing	O
has	O
numberles	O
Coffe	O
's	O
Houseses	O
Bookseller	O
Shops	O
&	O
Balconys	O
that	O
project	O
of	O
over	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
Veseys	B-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
--	O
fare	O
well	O
for	O
to	O
night	O
adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
Mr	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
ever	O
y-	O
obliged	O
Affe	O
Mrs	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
Recd	O
.	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
August	O
1783	O
in	O
Kingsgate	B-place
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
