TOKEN	NE
my	O
Dear	O
the	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Wilhelmina	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
Town	O
without	O
sending	O
you	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
regretts	O
at	O
the	O
disapointment	O
I	O
feel	O
at	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
this	O
winter	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
repine	O
at	O
what	O
was	O
proper	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
always	O
judged	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
nothing	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
:	O
but	O
will	O
hope	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
return	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
fortunate	O
enough	O
to	O
meet	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
society	O
--	O
the	O
Town	O
has	O
realy	O
been	O
tipsey	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
so	O
say	O
ever	O
since	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
recovery	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
continual	O
balls	O
riots	O
and	O
rejoicing	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
baulk	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
after	O
the	O
thanksgiving	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
as	O
usual	O
not	O
one	O
Levée	O
has	O
been	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
continuance	O
to	O
disagreable	O
reports	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
avoided	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
apearance	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
his	O
friends	O
say	O
altho	O
'	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
weakened	O
:	O
his	O
legs	O
swell	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
thin	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
this	O
will	O
acount	O
for	O
his	O
not	O
coming	O
forward	O
as	O
usual	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
Stay	O
but	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
satisfaction	O
and	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
reports	O
...	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
had	O
but	O
two	O
drawing	O
rooms	O
both	O
very	O
much	O
crouded	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
atended	O
with	O
fits	O
laughing	O
&	O
screaming	O
:	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
trimmings	O
;	O
Lappets	O
and	O
even	O
trains	O
--	O
the	O
ladies	O
that	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
presented	O
lost	O
their	O
company	O
's	O
and	O
either	O
were	O
pushed	O
before	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
and	O
obliged	O
to	O
present	O
themselves	O
or	O
,	O
never	O
got	O
the	O
honor	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
the	O
last	O
was	O
better	O
regulated	O
a	O
new	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
next	O
the	O
Windows	O
for	O
company	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
,	O
the	O
center	O
was	O
kept	O
shut	O
till	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
who	O
was	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
table	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
so	O
the	O
company	O
paſst	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
and	O
turning	O
under	O
the	O
Canopy	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
prevented	O
any	O
croud	O
or	O
pushing	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
looked	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
play	O
and	O
opera	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
was	O
recieved	O
with	O
such	O
aclamations	O
as	O
overcame	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hiſs	O
that	O
surprised	O
every	O
body	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
drowned	O
without	O
being	O
noticed	O
--	O
last	O
night	O
She	O
gave	O
a	O
great	O
Ball	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
were	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
the	O
Ladies	O
dreſs	O
is	O
the	O
Windsor	B-place
uniform	O
dark	O
blue	O
Laby	O
gown	O
with	O
very	O
broad	O
gold	O
fringe	O
down	O
the	O
sides	O
which	O
are	O
drawn	O
up	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
with	O
two	O
superb	O
taſsels	O
of	O
gold	O
the	O
apron	O
or	O
petitcoat	O
is	O
white	O
crape	O
with	O
two	O
gold	O
fringes	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
trimming	O
narrow	O
and	O
a	O
twist	O
above	O
the	O
fringe	O
of	O
red	O
&	O
blue	O
.	O
the	O
handkercheifs	O
ruffles	O
and	O
caps	O
are	O
all	O
uniform	O
four	O
white	O
plumes	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
.	O
inshort	O
the	O
dreſs	O
altogether	O
is	O
from	O
36	O
to	O
forty	O
pound	O
--	O
a	O
good	O
round	O
sum	O
for	O
a	O
ball	O
dreſs	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
wore	O
--	O
this	O
last	O
fête	O
has	O
ocasioned	O
great	O
heart	O
burning	O
's	O
for	O
while	O
Lady	B-pers
King	I-pers
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
peers	O
daughters	O
the	O
Maids	O
of	O
Honor	O
and	O
commoners	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
invited	O
H.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Pulteney	I-pers
to	O
this	O
it	O
has	O
opened	O
every	O
body	O
's	O
mouth	O
and	O
expectation	O
as	O
many	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
if	O
not	O
a	O
better	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
asked	O
.	O
no	O
doubt	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
reason	O
but	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
one	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
croud	O
upon	O
her	O
hands	O
--	O
you	O
will	O
hear	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
from	O
better	O
authority	O
I	O
imagine	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Copes	I-pers
is	O
in	O
town	O
on	O
Buſsineſs	O
which	O
all	O
his	O
friends	O
are	O
very	O
anxious	O
about	O
its	O
succeſs	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
shock	O
which	O
prevented	O
his	O
coming	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
returned	O
post	O
to	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	O
from	O
Edinbr	B-place
.	I-place
when	O
on	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
it	O
was	O
the	O
sudden	O
death	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
,	O
the	O
youngest	O
Boy	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
strong	O
and	O
fine	O
child	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
crowing	O
in	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	O
's	O
lap	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
siezed	O
with	O
a	O
fit	O
which	O
it	O
never	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
--	O
the	O
teeth	O
was	O
the	O
ocasion	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
quite	O
glad	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Blair	B-place
just	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
country	O
so	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
--	O
tomorrow	O
we	O
sett	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
intend	O
to	O
verifie	O
the	O
old	O
adage	O
that	O
the	O
farthest	O
way	O
about	O
is	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
home	O
as	O
we	O
go	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Grange	O
to	O
visit	O
Lord	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
in	O
our	O
way	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
intend	O
to	O
visit	O
Mr.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Drummond	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
who	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
does	O
Mr.	B-pers
Muirhead	I-pers
--	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
propose	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
who	O
is	O
married	O
&	O
settled	O
near	O
Liverpool	B-place
and	O
after	O
that	O
visit	O
shall	O
sett	O
our	O
faces	O
North	O
and	O
get	O
home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
quite	O
establish	O
her	O
health	O
;	O
in	O
this	O
tour	O
and	O
flatter	O
myself	O
we	O
shall	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
still	O
better	O
than	O
we	O
take	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
likewise	O
hope	O
to	O
return	O
my	O
Charge	O
to	O
Her	O
Father	O
in	O
high	O
health	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
grown	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
aprove	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
use	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
and	O
the	O
expence	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
for	O
her	O
improvement	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
liberal	O
he	O
will	O
think	O
well	O
bestowed	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
easily	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
Him	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
placed	O
such	O
implicit	O
confidence	O
in	O
us	O
and	O
now	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
his	O
only	O
Darling	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
doubly	O
anxious	O
.	O
in	O
spight	O
of	O
Masters	O
and	O
amusements	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
found	O
time	O
for	O
more	O
serious	O
&	O
nesesary	O
ap̄lication	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
confirmed	O
and	O
recieved	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
since	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
one	O
Opera	O
,	O
Ranelagh	O
,	O
Sadlers	O
,	O
Wells	O
,	O
&	O
Astleys	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
idea	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
will	O
hear	O
&	O
read	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
amusement	O
I	O
liked	O
best	O
was	O
an	O
Exhibition	O
at	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Theatre	O
in	O
Lent	O
by	O
4th	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Atholl	I-pers
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
revolution	O
of	O
the	O
Earth	O
Moon	O
&	O
Stars	O
with	O
Comets	O
Eclipses	O
and	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Ebb	O
&	O
flow	O
of	O
the	O
tides	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moral	O
entertainment	O
,	O
was	O
atended	O
by	O
very	O
full	O
houses	O
&	O
a	O
Silence	O
that	O
did	O
them	O
honor	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
Gallerys	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
paper	O
so	O
must	O
leave	O
the	O
Stars	O
to	O
aſsure	O
My	O
Dear	O
Lord	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
I	O
am	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
her	O
Sincere	O
well	O
wisher	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Friend	O
Walker	B-pers
my	O
Sister	O
&	O
Husband	O
present	O
you	O
with	O
their	O
best	O
compts	O
add	O
mine	O
to	O
theirs	O
&	O
make	O
them	O
acceptable	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
admire	O
Wilhelmina	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
'	O
s	O
anxiety	O
&	O
Loyalty	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
continue	O
her	O
improvements	O
of	O
body	O
&	O
mind	O
as	O
they	O
must	O
make	O
you	O
and	O
all	O
so	O
happy	O
.	O
I	O
m	O
ake	O
no	O
doubt	O
she	O
already	O
manages	O
Grand	O
.	O
papa	O
&	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
Papa	O
&	O
Mamma	O
--	O
Gen	O
:	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
are	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
under	O
Surgeons	O
hands	O
three	O
months	O
with	O
his	O
wounded	O
Leg	O
breaking	O
out	O
again	O
so	O
is	O
gone	O
upon	O
his	O
crutches	O
for	O
change	O
of	O
air	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
+	O
my	O
Brother	O
has	O
just	O
put	O
his	O
third	O
&	O
youngest	O
son	O
to	O
Eton	B-place
six	O
year	O
old	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
you	O
know	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
--	O
Addio	O
V	O
'	O
Auguro	O
Ogni	O
Bene	O
--	O
+	O
Miſs	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Leland	I-pers
London	B-place
may	O
twenty	O
89	O
Lord	B-pers
King	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
