TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
of	O
late	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
perform	O
my	O
promise	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
we	O
arrived	O
here	O
only	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Yesterday	O
after	O
having	O
made	O
the	O
tour	O
of	O
North	O
&	O
South	O
Holland	B-place
in	O
the	O
most	O
agreable	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
with	O
the	O
mode	O
of	O
traveling	O
in	O
Tracscutes	O
,	O
&	O
find	O
it	O
so	O
adapted	O
to	O
my	O
natural	O
indolence	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
constitution	O
that	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
by	O
the	O
same	O
conveyance	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
dreaded	O
the	O
tour	O
of	O
Holland	B-place
,	O
&	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
exp	O
e	O
ctation	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
most	O
pleasant	O
one	O
--	O
the	O
Country	O
tho	O
'	O
flat	O
,	O
is	O
beautifull	O
,	O
&	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
look	O
of	O
Cleanlineſs	O
,	O
&	O
plenty	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
agreable	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
North	O
Holland	B-place
it	O
is	O
so	O
totally	O
different	O
from	O
any	O
thing	O
one	O
has	O
seen	O
elsewhire	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
convey	O
to	O
you	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Bruck	B-place
,	O
it	O
resembles	O
the	O
Chinese	O
Villages	O
you	O
see	O
upon	O
Screens	O
--	O
the	O
outsides	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
are	O
painted	O
carved	O
&	O
partly	O
gilt	O
,	O
all	O
look	O
as	O
fresh	O
as	O
if	O
done	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
mixture	O
of	O
colours	O
are	O
not	O
tawdry	O
,	O
but	O
elegant	O
,	O
to	O
each	O
house	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
garden	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Chinese	O
paling	O
,	O
these	O
gardens	O
are	O
full	O
of	O
Parterres	O
of	O
flowers	O
mix	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
shells	O
of	O
different	O
colours	O
,	O
to	O
each	O
house	O
also	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
(	O
which	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Porte	O
fatal	O
)	O
is	O
never	O
open	O
'd	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
Marriage	O
or	O
Funeral	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
step	O
to	O
it	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
raised	O
above	O
the	O
ground	O
)	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
thrown	O
open	O
,	O
these	O
houses	O
are	O
built	O
round	O
Squares	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
&	O
along	O
Canals	O
,	O
with	O
little	O
light	O
bridges	O
thrown	O
over	O
every	O
hunded	O
Yards	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
tall	O
trees	O
which	O
add	O
to	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
prospect	O
.	O
These	O
people	O
are	O
so	O
very	O
neat	O
&	O
formal	O
that	O
they	O
wash	O
their	O
Paths	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
done	O
with	O
brick	O
&	O
sprinkle	O
the	O
sand	O
in	O
patterns	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
of	O
a	O
Saturday	O
(	O
wch	O
.	O
is	O
their	O
washing	O
day	O
)	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
admit	O
you	O
into	O
their	O
houses	O
,	O
&	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
who	O
forced	O
his	O
way	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
houses	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
was	O
surprised	O
at	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Dutch	O
maid	O
who	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
He	O
might	O
not	O
spoil	O
the	O
room	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
wash	O
'd	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
dreſs	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
it	O
without	O
inclosing	O
a	O
swatch	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
description	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
you	O
may	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
better	O
manner	O
with	O
your	O
Crayons	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
not	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
Holland	B-place
,	O
it	O
is	O
un	O
Champ	O
si	O
vaste	O
that	O
would	O
require	O
volumes	O
--	O
we	O
stay	O
'd	O
two	O
days	O
at	O
Antwerp	B-place
&	O
were	O
delighted	O
with	O
Reubens	B-pers
Pictures	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
what	O
a	O
master	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
,	O
&	O
particularly	O
wch	O
.	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Chapeau	O
de	O
Paille	O
--	O
(	O
wch	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
but	O
a	O
Spanish	O
hat	O
)	O
it	O
represents	O
a	O
n	O
beautifull	O
girl	O
about	O
Seventeen	O
with	O
her	O
Arms	O
croſs	O
'd	O
&	O
is	O
much	O
beyond	O
any	O
painting	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
As	O
to	O
Spa	B-place
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
wish	O
to	O
grow	O
partial	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
hitherto	O
I	O
hate	O
it	O
monstrously	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
noisy	O
,	O
diſsipated	O
,	O
Nonsensical	O
&	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
company	O
--	O
tho	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
exceptions	O
as	O
par	O
example	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
little	O
Mrs	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
who	O
looks	O
as	O
beautifull	O
as	O
an	O
Angel	O
&	O
her	O
husband	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
good	O
people	O
I	O
could	O
name	O
--	O
both	O
Ly	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
sick	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
an	O
indigestion	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
cold	O
wch	O
is	O
a	O
reall	O
distreſs	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
little	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
waters	O
&	O
can	O
not	O
begin	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
&	O
therefore	O
bid	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
as	O
you	O
promised	O
--	O
My	O
love	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
s	O
love	O
attends	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
Yr	O
.	O
Most	O
Affect	O
Aunt	O
CHamilton	B-pers
