TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
better	O
forbear	O
walking	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
the	O
Wind	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
troublesome	O
I	O
have	O
forbid	O
the	O
Coach	O
for	O
our	O
usual	O
Visit	O
to	O
Eastbourne	B-place
Place	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
except	O
for	O
a	O
triffling	O
Head-ach	O
proceeding	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
my	O
fixing	O
having	O
fix	O
'd	O
my	O
Eyes	O
so	O
long	O
together	O
upon	O
Objects	O
so	O
high	O
&	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
glaring	O
White	O
as	O
the	O
Cliffs	O
you	O
know	O
are	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
will	O
go	O
off	O
very	O
soon	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	B-pers
Rl	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
till	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
read	O
her	O
Psalms	O
&	O
Chapters	O
,	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
by	O
heart	O
&	O
work	O
,	O
or	O
write	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
any	O
Letter	O
in	O
Contemplation	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
Ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
