TOKEN	NE
maddox	O
Street	O
/	O
Monday	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
was	O
very	O
Sorry	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
this	O
Morning	O
when	O
She	O
did	O
her	O
The	O
favour	O
to	O
Call	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
sent	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Scans	O
of	O
Silk	O
about	O
four	O
and	O
Twenty	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
quite	O
one	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
She	O
does	O
them	O
first	O
She	O
can	O
have	O
more	O
,	O
mrs	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
hopes	O
Prince	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
and	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
are	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
which	O
most	O
give	O
her	O
inexpressable	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Set	O
out	O
for	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
