TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
Me	O
very	O
Whimsical	O
,	O
but	O
If	O
Friday	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
agreable	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
It	O
will	O
suit	O
Me	O
Much	O
Better	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
Wandsworth	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
but	O
pray	O
Answer	O
Me	O
fairly	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
on	O
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
the	O
Interview	O
is	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
Sure	O
your	O
apprehensions	O
would	O
soon	O
vanish	O
;	O
--	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
provoking	O
I	O
Shall	O
give	O
Him	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
;	O
--	O
ever	O
yrs	O
.	O
Most	O
Affecly	O
--	O
Frances	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Tuesday	O
Evening	O
