TOKEN	NE
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
this	O
morning	O
upon	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
she	O
proposed	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
to	O
accompany	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
on	O
a	O
tour	O
to	O
Devon	B-place
Shire	I-place
,	O
&	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
London	B-place
sooner	O
than	O
a	O
month	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
confeſs	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
help	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
surprize	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
engaged	O
in	O
attentions	O
naturally	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
future	O
plan	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
leisure	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
seemingly	O
ill	O
timed	O
excursion	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
myself	O
authorised	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
minute	O
in	O
my	O
enquiries	O
and	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
very	O
little	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
her	O
answers	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
this	O
expedition	O
in	O
compliance	O
with	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
hoped	O
she	O
might	O
receive	O
benefit	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
visible	O
her	O
health	O
has	O
been	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
agitation	O
and	O
anxiety	O
of	O
mind	O
she	O
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
.	O
My	O
decided	O
opinion	O
to	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
cause	O
subsisted	O
,	O
her	O
anxiety	O
wou	O
'd	O
accompany	O
her	O
where	O
ever	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
decline	O
taking	O
any	O
step	O
that	O
might	O
,	O
however	O
unjustly	O
,	O
throw	O
unfavourable	O
insinuations	O
upon	O
your	O
conduct	O
.	O
Relying	O
upon	O
the	O
sincerity	O
of	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
excuses	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
If	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
acted	O
with	O
any	O
judgement	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
the	O
leſs	O
startled	O
at	O
my	O
presuming	O
to	O
offer	O
you	O
my	O
advice	O
tho	O
'	O
unasked	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
very	O
sensibly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
her	O
engagement	O
to	O
you	O
have	O
led	O
her	O
into	O
very	O
mortifying	O
&	O
perplexing	O
situations	O
;	O
these	O
I	O
will	O
allow	O
may	O
hitherto	O
have	O
been	O
unavoidable	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
easily	O
suppose	O
that	O
the	O
continuation	O
of	O
them	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
so	O
likewise	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
really	O
incumbent	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
immediately	O
;	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
many	O
disagreeable	O
surmises	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
annihilated	O
;	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
conversing	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
when	O
they	O
understand	O
circumstances	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
yet	O
strangers	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
wishing	O
to	O
pry	O
into	O
other	O
Persons	O
affairs	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
busineſs	O
in	O
question	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
transacted	O
without	O
a	O
mutual	O
confidence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
leave	O
London	B-place
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
some	O
use	O
in	O
this	O
busineſs	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
therefore	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
my	O
request	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
wou	O
'd	O
afford	O
the	O
greatest	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
merits	O
every	O
attention	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
regard	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
remain	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Bedford	O
Square	O
May	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
DerbyShire	B-place
M	O
r	O
.	O
Dickinson	B-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
May	O
20-85	O
