TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
.	O
Nov	O
.	O
12	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
By	O
return	O
of	O
Post	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
your	O
extreme	O
kindneſs	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
future	O
period	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
profit	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
after	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
hesitation	O
in	O
avowing	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
uneasy	O
suspense	O
,	O
and	O
correspondence	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
relative	O
to	O
material	O
pecuniary	O
concerns	O
;	O
till	O
the	O
arrangement	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
unable	O
to	O
decide	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
:	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
our	O
consultations	O
would	O
be	O
ineffective	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
my	O
answer	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
likewise	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
collecting	O
together	O
,	O
whatever	O
little	O
matters	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
my	O
own	O
from	O
our	O
place	O
in	O
Herefordshire	B-place
,	O
such	O
as	O
Books	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
omitted	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
,	O
telling	O
you	O
the	O
only	O
good	O
there	O
is	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
about	O
me	O
:	O
namely	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
affection	O
and	O
generosity	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
at	O
a	O
future	O
(	O
I	O
hope	O
a	O
distant	O
)	O
period	O
,	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
pecuniary	O
embarraſsment	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
purchased	O
an	O
Annuity	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
decease	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
vested	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Trustees	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
exclusive	O
use	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
my	O
Income	O
must	O
be	O
contracted	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
behave	O
as	O
he	O
ought	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
grieve	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
fatal	O
delusion	O
that	O
poſseſses	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
doubts	O
)	O
I	O
might	O
live	O
upon	O
it	O
with	O
comfort	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
moderate	O
scale	O
that	O
would	O
content	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
judge	O
of	O
my	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
small	O
proof	O
of	O
your	O
friendship	O
that	O
you	O
wish	O
to	O
encounter	O
my	O
company	O
;	O
for	O
even	O
my	O
singing	O
,	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
by	O
grief	O
and	O
illness	O
,	O
extinct	O
:	O
whether	O
it	O
will	O
return	O
,	O
depends	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
on	O
whether	O
things	O
go	O
on	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
allow	O
me	O
any	O
peace	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
Heaven	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
involved	O
in	O
any	O
dispute	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
due	O
.	O
Though	O
his	O
conduct	O
is	O
certainly	O
very	O
blamable	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
retaining	O
such	O
an	O
affection	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
would	O
render	O
his	O
putting	O
himself	O
still	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
wrong	O
,	O
a	O
serious	O
grief	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
account	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
point	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
long	O
delay	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
expect	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
hear	O
from	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
.	O
So	O
rumours	O
had	O
reached	O
you	O
:	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
now	O
understand	O
,	O
been	O
long	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
wilfully	O
slow	O
of	O
belief	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
one	O
credit	O
ill	O
reports	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
period	O
,	O
behaved	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
affection	O
and	O
kindneſs	O
?	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
weakneſs	O
and	O
inconstancy	O
of	O
human	O
nature	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
endleſs	O
disquisition	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
enter	O
upon	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
add	O
a	O
repetition	O
of	O
the	O
extreme	O
obligation	O
I	O
feel	O
,	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
;	O
with	O
my	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
health	O
is	O
perfectly	O
re-established	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
engaged	O
in	O
a	O
correspondence	O
of	O
consultation	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
expectation	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
immediately	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
remove	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
shewn	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
kindneſs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
finished	O
your	O
last	O
;	O
lest	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
convinced	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
independently	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
--	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
most	O
obliged	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
needleſs	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
how	O
happy	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Single	O
.	O
