TOKEN	NE
Cumberland	O
Street	O
Dec	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
1798	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
received	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
with	O
much	O
pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
engagements	O
that	O
had	O
prevented	O
my	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
sooner	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
communicate	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
am	O
indulged	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
well	O
filled	O
,	O
by	O
yourself	O
and	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
de	I-pers
'	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
intention	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
her	O
spectacles	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
had	O
not	O
called	O
on	O
my	O
Aunt	O
while	O
Katherine	B-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
my	O
Sister	O
left	O
Bromley	B-place
Lady	B-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
called	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
invite	O
K	B-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Aunt	O
to	O
Pheasant	O
Grove	O
My	O
Aunt	O
Barnard	B-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
reside	O
in	O
the	O
Town	B-place
of	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
I	O
belive	O
She	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
has	O
just	O
left	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Nanny	B-pers
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
when	O
Mrs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
takes	O
leave	O
of	O
Bromley	B-place
We	O
paſsed	O
a	O
very	O
agreable	O
day	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
,	O
They	O
desired	O
their	O
Compts	O
to	O
yourself	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
we	O
dined	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
Carriage	O
for	O
us	O
and	O
sent	O
us	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boultons	I-pers
this	O
evening	O
.	O
We	O
also	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
out	O
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
goodness	O
to	O
excuse	O
the	O
shortneſs	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
anything	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
follow	O
my	O
example	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Compliments	O
,	O
my	O
Sisters	O
join	O
in	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
Believe	O
me	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yrs	O
affecly	O
M.	B-pers
J.	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
M	O
rs	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
all	O
Enquirers	O
2:7:4	O
4	O
:	O
2	O
2:11	O
..	O
6	O
4:19:3	O
1:1:0	O
6:0:3	O
To	O
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Single	O
Bedfordshire	B-place
Owe	O
Miss	B-pers
Hoyd	I-pers
£	O
0:6:2	O
