TOKEN	NE
In	O
a	O
Work	O
intitled	O
a	O
Sketch	O
of	O
the	O
Denominations	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
World	O
it	O
says	O
“	O
The	O
Socinians	O
have	O
appropriated	O
to	O
themselves	O
the	O
appellation	O
of	O
Unitarians	O
;	O
&	O
by	O
this	O
Name	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
more	O
generally	O
distinguished	O
--	O
Though	O
to	O
this	O
Appelation	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
exclusive	O
Claim	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
is	O
somewhat	O
more	O
correctly	O
descriptive	O
of	O
their	O
Religious	O
Tenets	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
Socinians	O
--	O
since	O
they	O
renounce	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Opinions	O
of	O
Socinians	O
”	O
John	O
Evans	O
,	O
A	O
Sketch	O
of	O
the	O
Denominations	O
into	O
which	O
the	O
Christian	O
World	O
is	O
Divided	O
[	O
...	O
]	O
.	O
London	O
:	O
J.	O
Sammells	O
.	O
3rd	O
edn	O
,	O
p.33	O
.	O
[	O
2nd	O
edn	O
1796	O
;	O
1st	O
edn	O
as	O
'	O
A	O
Brief	O
Sketch	O
[	O
...	O
]	O
'	O
1795	O
.	O
]	O
Monday	O
6	O
Sepr	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
letter	O
was	O
dispatched	O
James	B-pers
&	O
I	O
took	O
advantage	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Gleam	O
a	O
midst	O
the	O
Showers	O
&	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
ride	O
on	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
that	O
is	O
making	O
to	O
Dulverton	B-place
about	O
5	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
previously	O
sent	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
trunk	O
containing	O
some	O
linnen	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
to	O
be	O
in	O
readineſs	O
for	O
us	O
on	O
our	O
little	O
excursion	O
&	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
James	B-pers
recd	O
.	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Paynters	O
were	O
coming	O
here	O
this	O
Evg	O
--	O
which	O
of	O
course	O
deranges	O
our	O
plan	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
Linnen	O
is	O
gone	O
--	O
We	O
were	O
particularly	O
lucky	O
in	O
our	O
ride	O
as	O
we	O
avoided	O
the	O
heavy	O
Showers	O
&	O
only	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
one	O
James	B-pers
took	O
shelter	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
precaution	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
&	O
set	O
the	O
Shower	O
at	O
defiance	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
--	O
the	O
road	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
cut	O
thro	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
places	O
for	O
short	O
distances	O
remain	O
to	O
be	O
levelled	O
--	O
it	O
paſses	O
thro	O
this	O
beautiful	O
Vale	O
--	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
with	O
an	O
Undertaker	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
engaged	O
to	O
level	O
4	O
miles	O
at	O
17/6	O
per	O
Yard	O
wch	O
.	O
amounts	O
to	O
1540£	O
pr	O
Mile	O
&	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Fencing	O
&	O
Stoning	O
would	O
exceed	O
that	O
proportion	O
--	O
therefore	O
the	O
Road	O
will	O
cost	O
more	O
than	O
3000£	O
per	O
Mile	O
--	O
We	O
rode	O
thro	O
Dulverton	B-place
--	O
Col.	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
the	O
celebrated	O
Man	O
--	O
has	O
bought	O
a	O
House	O
&	O
the	O
great	O
Tithes	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Luxmore	I-pers
--	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
disliked	O
here	O
&	O
the	O
Gentn	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
have	O
refused	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Stag	O
Hunt	O
--	O
he	O
consoles	O
himself	O
by	O
giving	O
elegant	O
dinners	O
wh	O
.	O
Champaine	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
people	O
of	O
a	O
Description	O
who	O
will	O
visit	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
observed	O
on	O
the	O
Gate	O
leading	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
magnificent	O
Stags	O
Horns	O
--	O
About	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Dulverton	B-place
is	O
Pixton	B-place
a	O
Seat	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Caernarvon	I-pers
s	O
--	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
small	O
--	O
new	O
&	O
situated	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
a	O
romantic	O
Park	O
commanding	O
a	O
beautiful	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
&	O
of	O
two	O
fine	O
oak	O
woods	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Vale	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Hernery	O
--	O
At	O
this	O
Season	O
the	O
Birds	O
are	O
marauding	O
in	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
&	O
return	O
here	O
to	O
breed	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
Season	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Caernarvon	I-pers
is	O
represented	O
to	O
be	O
inconsoleable	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
died	O
lately	O
&	O
left	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Children	O
--	O
She	O
was	O
Sister	O
to	O
present	O
Sir	B-pers
--	I-pers
Ackland	I-pers
--	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Ramsgate	B-place
&	O
died	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
very	O
unexpectedly	O
--	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
the	O
Devonr	B-place
.	I-place
roads	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pleasant	O
ride	O
--	O
About	O
9	O
OClock	O
the	O
Sir	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Dyke	I-pers
Acland	I-pers
,	I-pers
10th	I-pers
Baronet	I-pers
arrived	O
,	O
unfortunately	O
they	O
mistook	O
their	O
way	O
&	O
came	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
celebrated	O
Hills	O
in	O
this	O
Neighborhood	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
called	O
Hang	O
Mans	O
Hill	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
nearly	O
perpendicular	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
Horse	O
Chaise	O
with	O
a	O
restive	O
Horse	O
--	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Brothers	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
lately	O
broke	O
a	O
blood	O
Veſsel	O
&	O
rode	O
30	O
miles	O
after	O
it	O
&	O
in	O
consequence	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
ever	O
since	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
pronounced	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
absceſs	O
on	O
his	O
Lungs	O
--	O
Since	O
his	O
first	O
Attack	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
out	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
a	O
Gig	O
&	O
going	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
rate	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Grounds	O
.	O
one	O
Wheel	O
hit	O
against	O
a	O
Stump	O
&	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
being	O
very	O
heavy	O
,	O
overbalanced	O
the	O
Vehicle	O
&	O
over	O
they	O
went	O
&	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Nose	O
was	O
broken	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
.	O
the	O
Son	O
afterwards	O
spit	O
blood	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
try	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
&	O
as	O
a	O
younger	O
brother	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
to	O
be	O
ordained	O
he	O
attended	O
him	O
&	O
after	O
the	O
Ordination	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
here	O
--	O
the	O
oldest	O
was	O
so	O
agitated	O
by	O
his	O
exertions	O
in	O
driving	O
(	O
the	O
younger	O
not	O
seeing	O
3	O
Inches	O
from	O
his	O
Nose	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
perspiration	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
persevered	O
in	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Hall	O
on	O
a	O
flag	O
floor	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
heat	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
--	O
He	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
way	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Loſs	O
to	O
his	O
family	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
clever	O
&	O
is	O
the	O
Active	O
Manager	O
in	O
the	O
busineſs	O
--	O
his	O
Father	O
is	O
Auditor	O
to	O
many	O
Men	O
of	O
large	O
fortune	O
in	O
Cornwall	B-place
&	O
gets	O
3000	O
£	O
a	O
Year	O
by	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
busineſs	O
I	O
apprehend	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
will	O
never	O
partake	O
of	O
Xmas	O
fare	O
--	O
After	O
breakfast	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynters	I-pers
advised	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
where	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Case	O
on	O
family	O
Affairs	O
--	O
She	O
says	O
She	O
believes	O
my	O
Sister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
--	O
That	O
She	O
has	O
attributed	O
a	O
Continuance	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
s	O
discountenance	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
interference	O
of	O
poor	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	O
on	O
whom	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
severe	O
in	O
her	O
Admi	O
Anim	O
adversions	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
course	O
people	O
abroad	O
naturally	O
gave	O
credit	O
to	O
her	O
aſsertions	O
&	O
many	O
relieved	O
her	O
Neceſsities	O
--	O
That	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
oldest	O
were	O
totally	O
uneducated	O
&	O
She	O
herself	O
had	O
been	O
many	O
Years	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholic	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
Sarah	B-pers
who	O
married	O
a	O
Cornish	O
Gentleman	O
&	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
&	O
gave	O
&	O
lent	O
them	O
money	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
curious	O
&	O
mortifying	O
that	O
so	O
proud	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
She	O
was	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
meaneſs	O
as	O
to	O
put	O
herself	O
on	O
the	O
footing	O
of	O
a	O
pauper	O
rather	O
than	O
inform	O
her	O
family	O
of	O
her	O
real	O
Situation	O
--	O
I	O
begged	O
her	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
real	O
situation	O
&	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Father	O
--	O
Palombi	B-pers
's	I-pers
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Father	O
devoted	O
most	O
of	O
time	O
to	O
reading	O
--	O
One	O
day	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tickel	I-pers
said	O
to	O
him	O
she	O
wished	O
She	O
/could	O
be	O
turned	O
into	O
a	O
book	O
&	O
then	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
provided	O
She	O
became	O
an	O
Almanack	O
&	O
then	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
throw	O
her	O
aside	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
set	O
a	O
Savages	O
that	O
are	O
employed	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
new	O
Road	O
who	O
are	O
Strangers	O
&	O
earn	O
prodigious	O
Wages	O
&	O
live	O
in	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
eating	O
raw	O
bacon	O
&	O
undreſsed	O
meat	O
&	O
drinking	O
such	O
Quantities	O
of	O
liquor	O
as	O
is	O
scarce	O
credible	O
--	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
fellows	O
was	O
married	O
here	O
lately	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Service	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
promises	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
“	O
in	O
Sickneſs	O
or	O
in	O
health	O
”	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
“	O
hold	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
agreed	O
to	O
that	O
”	O
&	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
on	O
till	O
urged	O
by	O
the	O
Fair	O
One	O
--	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
--	O
“	O
Parson	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
job	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
'd	O
stop	O
&	O
lets	O
have	O
an	O
end	O
o	O
n't	O
”	O
--	O
These	O
Men	O
will	O
earn	O
12/	O
6	O
day	O
(	O
the	O
common	O
native	O
laborers	O
get	O
six	O
)	O
and	O
eat	O
&	O
drink	O
it	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
see	O
here	O
4	O
Vol	O
.	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
History	O
of	O
Music	O
--	O
I	O
pitched	O
upon	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
of	O
Junius	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Type	O
bound	O
in	O
Vellum	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
these	O
were	O
ordered	O
by	O
Junius	O
wch	O
.	O
Burney	B-pers
bought	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
I	O
felt	O
surprised	O
for	O
a	O
Moment	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
examination	O
they	O
were	O
printed	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
in	O
94	O
--	O
The	O
Vignettes	O
to	O
ye	O
Hy	O
of	O
Music	O
are	O
beautiful	O
--	O
drawn	O
by	O
Beasley	B-pers
&	O
engraved	O
by	O
Cipriani	B-pers
--	O
Whilst	O
Bartolozzi	B-pers
&	O
I	O
were	O
talking	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Hill	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
covered	O
with	O
Air	O
of	O
prismatic	O
Colors	O
--	O
the	O
green	O
preponderating	O
--	O
this	O
paſsed	O
off	O
and	O
was	O
succeeded	O
by	O
another	O
Cloud	O
with	O
more	O
Vivid	O
Colors	O
.	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
young	O
folks	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
arrived	O
it	O
vanished	O
,	O
a	O
Third	O
vapour	O
came	O
but	O
the	O
Colors	O
were	O
not	O
as	O
bright	O
--	O
The	O
Sun	O
Shone	O
upon	O
the	O
hill	O
&	O
a	O
watery	O
Cloud	O
was	O
paſsing	O
over	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
once	O
saw	O
a	O
Valley	O
7	O
miles	O
long	O
&	O
1	O
broad	O
near	O
Taxal	B-place
filled	O
with	O
prismatic	O
Air	O
&	O
saw	O
every	O
Object	O
colored	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
varied	O
of	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
similar	O
effect	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Cause	O
&	O
wch	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
hilly	O
Countries	O
--	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
The	O
old	O
Lady	O
has	O
not	O
brought	O
any	O
letter	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
has	O
not	O
made	O
her	O
appearance	O
&	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
are	O
going	O
thro	O
Tiverton	B-place
I	O
will	O
send	O
this	O
by	O
them	O
--	O
The	O
Wind	O
is	O
come	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
North	O
&	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
promising	O
there	O
fore	O
we	O
have	O
fixed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
tomorrow	O
&	O
be	O
there	O
by	O
3	O
OClock	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
finest	O
Organ	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Most	O
Affy	O
Yrs	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynters	I-pers
J.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davy	B-pers
s	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Carver	O
of	O
Chimney	O
pieces	O
&	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
a	O
Milliner	O
Single	O
To	O
Sir	B-pers
Humphrey	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
