TOKEN	NE
Kedleston	B-place
Monday	O
Sept	O
:	O
8	O
th	O
:	O
1788	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
Altho	O
'	O
you	O
desired	O
N.	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
might	O
write	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Acct	O
:	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
here	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
allow	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
being	O
enabled	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Dear	O
Husband	O
,	O
likes	O
this	O
Place	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
thinks	O
the	O
Waters	O
agree	O
&	O
seems	O
really	O
better	O
,	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
in	O
Spirits	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
allowed	O
myself	O
to	O
hope	O
--	O
this	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
Cordial	O
Draught	O
as	O
must	O
do	O
me	O
eſsential	O
good	O
;	O
&	O
the	O
tranquility	O
of	O
The	O
Scene	O
around	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
pleasant	O
Walks	O
&	O
fine	O
Air	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
breathed	O
any	O
more	O
delightful	O
)	O
will	O
I	O
humbly	O
trust	O
strengthen	O
my	O
poor	O
shattered	O
Frame	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
London	B-place
Winter	O
--	O
which	O
hurry	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
allow	O
myself	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
destroy	O
the	O
good	O
which	O
the	O
present	O
qeuit	O
Life	O
I	O
lead	O
here	O
wd	O
.	O
do	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Weather	O
has	O
been	O
remarkably	O
fine	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Soil	O
is	O
so	O
dry	O
,	O
I	O
that	O
after	O
one	O
Day	O
's	O
Rain	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Sunday	O
sennight	O
.	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dry	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morng	O
:	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
out	O
;	O
Ld	B-pers
:	I-pers
Scarsdale	I-pers
is	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
leave	O
to	O
drive	O
&	O
walk	O
about	O
his	O
Park	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
One	O
--	O
&	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
most	O
magnificent	O
Collection	O
of	O
Pictures	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
amusement	O
to	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Husband	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
China	O
Manufactory	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fine	O
Raphael	O
at	O
Okeover	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Adl	B-pers
:	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
one	O
of	O
our	O
Party	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
little	O
sore	O
throat	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
confeſs	O
walking	O
out	O
quietly	O
,	O
&	O
thinking	O
of	O
my	O
Angels	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
greatest	O
Indulgence	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
but	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
I	O
can	O
join	O
the	O
Party	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
a	O
troublesome	O
intruder	O
by	O
my	O
Sadneſs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
their	O
Livelineſs	O
--	O
indeed	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
Exertion	O
has	O
sometimes	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
now	O
as	O
quiet	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
make	O
Nanny	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
;	O
wh	O
:	O
tranquillizes	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
&	O
does	O
her	O
good	O
,	O
poor	O
Soul	O
!	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
reads	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
covered	O
Seat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Field	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
commands	O
a	O
Charming	O
View	O
)	O
&	O
where	O
I	O
breath	O
the	O
sweet	O
Air	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Wedy	O
:	O
Since	O
I	O
wrote	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
awkwardly	O
strained	O
my	O
Knee	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
twice	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Rheumatic	O
attack	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
but	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Curzon	I-pers
an	O
Old	O
Aquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
airing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
miſsed	O
enjoying	O
this	O
fine	O
weather	O
--	O
this	O
Morng	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
walking	O
,	O
&	O
thank	O
God	O
am	O
not	O
fatigued	O
by	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
stronger	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
--	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
talking	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
myself	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
ashamed	O
of	O
doing	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
kindly	O
interested	O
about	O
me	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
ask	O
how	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
your	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
do	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
perfectly	O
well	O
&	O
happily	O
enjoying	O
her	O
daily	O
improvements	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
lately	O
from	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
fear	O
She	O
&	O
Marianne	B-pers
were	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Influenza	O
,	O
&	O
She	O
is	O
unhappy	O
about	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
who	O
is	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
by	O
her	O
account	O
;	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
nervous	O
,	O
wh	O
:	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
Complaint	O
for	O
so	O
young	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
poor	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
give	O
my	O
kind	O
Love	O
--	O
I	O
often	O
think	O
of	O
them	O
Poor	O
Souls	O
;	O
I	O
fear	O
They	O
have	O
no	O
Lady	O
now	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
Them	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
sends	O
you	O
his	O
best	O
wishes	O
&	O
Joins	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Kiſs	O
yr	O
.	O
dr	O
:	O
little	O
Child	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
very	O
Affly	O
:	O
yours	O
PCremorne	B-pers
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Comps	O
.	O
to	O
Miss	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
good	O
accounts	O
from	O
Taxal	B-place
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
quite	O
forgot	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
ever	O
recd	O
:	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
left	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
for	O
you	O
by	O
her	O
Son	O
.	O
--	O
To	O
Ly	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
N	O
o	O
:	O
27	O
.	O
Old	O
Burlington	O
Street	O
London	B-place
