TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dr	O
Sister	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Cheapest	O
Silks	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Coventry	B-place
Croſs	O
on	O
Shan	O
klin	O
Street	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
white	O
flowerd	O
tabby	O
at	O
only	O
five	O
Shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
a	O
plain	O
white	O
one	O
at	O
six	O
&	O
sixpence	O
&	O
lustrings	O
so	O
Cheap	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
two	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
nothing	O
better	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
My	O
Love	O
attends	O
Mr	B-pers
H	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
he	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
Yrs	O
Most	O
Sincerely	O
C.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
1st	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
her	O
sister	O
in	O
law	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
