TOKEN	NE
Horton	B-place
October	O
2	O
d	O
1785	O
My	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
's	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
made	O
me	O
happier	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
expreſs	O
--	O
Had	O
I	O
known	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
waited	O
till	O
now	O
to	O
have	O
inquired	O
after	O
you	O
and	O
given	O
you	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
myself	O
.	O
Without	O
delaying	O
a	O
Day	O
longer	O
I	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
the	O
neceſsary	O
information	O
your	O
letter	O
contains	O
,	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
beginning	O
with	O
the	O
subject	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
most	O
pleasure	O
to	O
dwell	O
upon	O
,	O
your	O
happineſs	O
--	O
The	O
description	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
situation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
those	O
amiable	O
People	O
so	O
nearly	O
connected	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
breathes	O
the	O
spirit	O
of	O
happineſs	O
and	O
enjoyment	O
--	O
Indeed	O
my	O
dear	O
you	O
are	O
particularly	O
marked	O
amongst	O
the	O
fortunate	O
,	O
for	O
however	O
truly	O
amiable	O
was	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
your	O
choice	O
,	O
however	O
truly	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
affections	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
mere	O
accident	O
chance	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
minds	O
consonant	O
to	O
his	O
and	O
your	O
own	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
members	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
--	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
certainly	O
among	O
the	O
very	O
rare	O
instances	O
where	O
so	O
many	O
advantages	O
are	O
united	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
wondering	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
thanking	O
God	O
most	O
sincerely	O
for	O
having	O
thus	O
fixed	O
your	O
happineſs	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
well	O
deserved	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
gratefully	O
enjoyed	O
--	O
To	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
regular	O
account	O
of	O
myself	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
begin	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
with	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
of	O
August	O
--	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
that	O
Drawing	O
room	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
who	O
is	O
at	O
D	O
.	O
Place	O
near	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
spent	O
that	O
fortnight	O
betwēn	O
her	O
and	O
St	O
Leonards	O
,	O
but	O
chiefly	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
--	O
after	O
the	O
Dr	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
to	O
Richmond	O
Park	O
,	O
&	O
stayed	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Coronation	O
,	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
--	O
we	O
had	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
both	O
the	O
time	O
before	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
we	O
made	O
several	O
very	O
pleasant	O
parties	O
both	O
by	O
Water	O
&	O
Land	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Staines	B-place
,	O
Clivden	B-place
,	O
Park	O
Place	O
near	O
Henley	B-place
Genrl	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
's	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
we	O
paſsed	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
every	O
Day	O
on	O
the	O
Water	O
which	O
was	O
quite	O
delightful	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
pleasantest	O
warks	O
&	O
drives	O
into	O
the	O
Forest	O
--	O
the	O
latterend	O
of	O
my	O
visit	O
tho	O
'	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
the	O
most	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
quite	O
alone	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Bell	B-pers
was	O
so	O
unwell	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
her	O
without	O
suffering	O
infinitly	O
from	O
anxiety	O
--	O
my	O
own	O
Health	O
however	O
was	O
perfectly	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
exertions	O
I	O
always	O
make	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
receiving	O
any	O
other	O
injury	O
that	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
feelings	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
finding	O
Bell	B-pers
infinitly	O
better	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
free	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Complaints	O
--	O
she	O
still	O
eats	O
&	O
sleeps	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
her	O
spirits	O
are	O
much	O
improved	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
visits	O
to	O
our	O
Friends	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
kinds	O
&	O
friendship	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
perfectly	O
uneceſsary	O
&	O
superfluous	O
to	O
my	O
convictio	O
n	O
are	O
still	O
very	O
pleasing	O
&	O
gratefully	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
truly	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
you	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
peaceful	O
&	O
happy	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
return	O
here	O
no	O
more	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
m	O
y	O
Father	O
leaves	O
this	O
on	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
and	O
London	B-place
on	O
the	O
15	O
th	O
of	O
November	O
--	O
They	O
mean	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
in	O
France	B-place
,	O
but	O
where	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
fixed	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
trial	O
preparing	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
a	O
separation	O
from	O
my	O
beloved	O
Sister	O
and	O
best	O
Friend	O
of	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
comfort	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
my	O
hope	O
--	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	B-place
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
no	O
plan	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
is	O
fixed	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
fixture	O
in	O
London	B-place
till	O
after	O
XmaſsChristmaſs	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
pray	O
return	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
not	O
meaning	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
ready	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
in	O
kind	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
Bell	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
would	O
have	O
written	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
well	O
--	O
my	O
F	O
's	O
best	O
Compts	O
&	O
c	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
--	O
adieu	O
your	O
sincere	O
&	O
affec	O
CMG——	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
single	O
Sheet	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Octbr	O
.	O
1785	O
