TOKEN	NE
2	O
3	O
0	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
.	O
1799	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
my	O
dear	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
and	O
entertaining	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
merry	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
you	O
the	O
delectable	O
manuscript	O
.	O
poor	O
dears	O
,	O
I	O
daresay	O
you	O
made	O
them	O
all	O
very	O
truly	O
happy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
had	O
my	O
fears	O
that	O
those	O
poor	O
dear	O
W	O
:	O
girls	O
were	O
ill	O
fated	O
mortals	O
.	O
the	O
only	O
chance	O
and	O
salvation	O
for	O
them	O
is	O
the	O
eldest	O
girl	O
marrying	O
well	O
into	O
some	O
respectable	O
connexion	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
religion	O
.	O
I	O
foresaw	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
vortex	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
world	O
the	O
moment	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
unhappily	O
without	O
a	O
proper	O
introduction	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
several	O
the	O
short	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
to	O
introduce	O
them	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
W-	I-pers
&	O
whom	O
they	O
heard	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
sung	O
so	O
delightfully	O
,	O
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Clarges	I-pers
,	O
with	O
many	O
others	O
such	O
,	O
were	O
running	O
mad	O
after	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fn	I-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
her	O
.	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
young	O
and	O
so	O
unknowing	O
that	O
one	O
pity	O
's	O
rather	O
than	O
blames	O
their	O
misdoings	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
much	O
flattered	O
by	O
your	O
kind	O
invitations	O
,	O
he	O
begs	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
at	O
all	O
events	O
determined	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
attempt	O
before	O
he	O
leaves	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
if	O
he	O
poſsibly	O
can	O
breakfast	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
begs	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
fraction	O
of	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
will	O
undertake	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
hour	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
exert	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
he	O
can	O
promise	O
.	O
the	O
lady	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
bent	O
upon	O
picking	O
up	O
a	O
visit	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
quarter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
and	O
by	O
Hook	O
or	O
Crook	O
she	O
'll	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
grievously	O
disapointed	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
chaise	O
and	O
the	O
Postillion	O
on	O
horseback	O
to	O
attend	O
Mr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
from	O
Hoccliffe	B-place
home	O
.	O
I	O
prepared	O
the	O
fatted	O
Calf	O
for	O
his	O
reception	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
dinner	O
time	O
arrived	O
John	B-pers
returns	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
Hoccliffe	B-place
last	O
night	O
by	O
the	O
liverpool	B-place
mail	O
with	O
particular	O
directions	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
immediatly	O
by	O
a	O
special	O
Meſsenger	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
before	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
waiting	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
ride	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
orders	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
parcel	O
contained	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
cold	O
,	O
that	O
Dr	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
was	O
displeased	O
at	O
finding	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
leſs	O
would	O
he	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
to	O
you	O
how	O
this	O
has	O
vexed	O
and	O
disapointed	O
me	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fatal	O
foreboding	O
that	O
something	O
would	O
disapoint	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
on	O
now	O
the	O
croaking	O
humour	O
is	O
begun	O
.	O
love	O
and	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
both	O
.	O
Affecly	O
ever	O
Yrs	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
JH	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
thurdy	O
morning	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
.	O
With	O
your	O
good	O
sense	O
&	O
having	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
presumptuous	O
in	O
me	O
to	O
advise	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
advise	O
--	O
think	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
these	O
unfortunate	O
Girls	O
--	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
HL	O
family	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
told	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
their	O
Great	O
Protector	O
from	O
that	O
knowledge	O
.	O
&	O
from	O
knowing	O
Breaks	O
's	O
Connexion	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
poor	O
Mother	O
could	O
Confide	O
to	O
him	O
during	O
her	O
Life	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
T-ble	I-pers
wd	O
undo	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
those	O
Eyes	O
were	O
clos	O
'd	O
--	O
your	O
good	O
Heart	O
makes	O
you	O
feel	O
all	O
the	O
anxiety	O
so	O
natural	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Heart	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Experience	O
sufficient	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
Cold	O
to	O
the	O
trubles	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
friendship	O
with	O
--	O
these	O
people	O
are	O
new	O
ac	O
quaintances	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
therefore	O
leave	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
fate	O
.	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
create	O
uneasineſs	O
to	O
your	O
self	O
--	O
&	O
with	O
my	O
sincere	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
many	O
happy	O
years	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
yrs	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
yrs	O
truly	O
affect	O
DBloſset	B-pers
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
