TOKEN	NE
18	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1781	O
Babel	B-place
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
Dear	O
Astrea	B-pers
&	O
I	O
deserve	O
Your	O
reproaches	O
for	O
my	O
silence	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
I	O
feel	O
incapable	O
of	O
exerting	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
neglect	O
&	O
postpone	O
doing	O
the	O
very	O
things	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
derive	O
comfort	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
receiving	O
Your	O
letters	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
greatest	O
,	O
&	O
yet	O
I	O
delay	O
writing	O
&	O
thereby	O
lose	O
many	O
letters	O
from	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
answer	O
Your	O
enquiries	O
respecting	O
the	O
Synod	O
;	O
after	O
tomorrow	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
once	O
a	O
fortnight	O
--	O
therefore	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
of	O
Augt	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
Synod	O
day	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
Mercury	B-pers
s	O
Birth	O
day	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
most	O
probable	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
held	O
.	O
--	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
has	O
a	O
Cold	O
&	O
we	O
are	O
left	O
this	O
week	O
at	O
Babel	B-place
--	O
Ah	O
how	O
you	O
would	O
feel	O
for	O
me	O
did	O
You	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
through	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
deceitful	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
most	O
treacherous	O
and	O
dangerous	O
young	O
person	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
--	O
imagine	O
to	O
yourself	O
my	O
surprize	O
when	O
Rhea	B-pers
after	O
having	O
told	O
me	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
question	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
conversation	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
wth	O
.	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
last	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
being	O
perfectly	O
aſsured	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
was	O
astonished	O
at	O
this	O
addreſs	O
:	O
Rhea	B-pers
then	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Elise	B-pers
had	O
repeated	O
to	O
her	O
what	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
had	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
against	O
ye	O
.	O
person	O
who	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
lately	O
about	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
Ill	O
;	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
in	O
confidence	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
lady	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
base	O
in	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
repeated	O
it	O
wth	O
.	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
making	O
mischief	O
;	O
but	O
wt	O
.	O
renders	O
it	O
so	O
shocking	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
a	O
falsehood	O
.	O
Rhea	B-pers
behaved	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
candour	O
&	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
fair	O
opportunity	O
of	O
clearing	O
myself	O
.	O
after	O
this	O
instance	O
of	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
's	O
disposition	O
for	O
mischief-making	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
not	O
harsher	O
a	O
severer	O
epithet	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
continual	O
dread	O
of	O
some	O
secret	O
stab	O
.	O
--	O
for	O
how	O
is	O
poſsible	O
to	O
guard	O
against	O
such	O
a	O
being	O
.	O
this	O
affair	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
stronger	O
impression	O
upon	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
think	O
it	O
has	O
done	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
wish	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
this	O
situation	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
conceal	O
from	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
unhappy	O
--	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
on	O
any	O
account	O
mention	O
this	O
trait	O
of	O
Atoſsa	B-pers
s	O
character	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
prejudice	O
the	O
world	O
greatly	O
against	O
her	O
were	O
it	O
made	O
public	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
one	O
exception	O
--	O
when	O
You	O
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
are	O
alone	O
together	O
show	O
her	O
this	O
letter	O
--	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
You	O
sympathize	O
together	O
in	O
concern	O
for	O
Your	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
kind	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walshingham	I-pers
Hero	B-pers
abt	O
.	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
--	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
intends	O
coming	O
to	O
Babel	B-place
as	O
soon	O
as	O
her	O
Affairs	O
are	O
settled	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
may	O
look	O
forward	O
for	O
some	O
happy	O
meetings	O
before	O
Winter	O
as	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
Hero	B-pers
will	O
invite	O
You	O
.	O
Helen	B-pers
&	O
her	O
Daughter	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Walk	O
every	O
Evening	O
--	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
the	O
topic	O
of	O
every	O
tea	O
table	O
within	O
ten	O
Miles	O
;	O
(	O
for	O
very	O
slight	O
notice	O
is	O
taken	O
of	O
ym	O
.	O
by	O
Osyris	B-pers
,	O
Rhea	B-pers
&	O
even	O
P	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
)	O
--	O
they	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
proper	O
spirit	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
astonishment	O
at	O
the	O
family	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
so	O
delicate	O
,	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
leas	O
t	O
fatigue	O
overcomes	O
ym	O
.	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
heat	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
&	O
walk	O
two	O
hours	O
--	O
one	O
Eveg	O
.	O
last	O
week	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Rain	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
party	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
scandal	O
--	O
where	O
I	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
all	O
yt	O
.	O
this	O
place	O
affords	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
some	O
hours	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Germans	O
are	O
going	O
from	O
Old	O
Babel	B-place
various	O
are	O
the	O
reason	O
's	O
aſsign	O
'd	O
for	O
their	O
quitting	O
that	O
place	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
meet	O
we	O
will	O
talk	O
over	O
what	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
importance	O
enough	O
--	O
or	O
of	O
too	O
much	O
importance	O
to	O
write	O
.	O
What	O
would	O
I	O
not	O
give	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
wth	O
..	O
You	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
tell	O
Benedict	B-pers
&	O
Isabella	B-pers
yt	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
for	O
them	O
when	O
you	O
quit	O
H——	O
.	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
W	O
-	O
have	O
not	O
visited	O
You	O
--	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
content	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
ignorant	O
stupid	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
there	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
regret	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
T	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
A——	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
Man	O
but	O
is	O
so	O
devour	O
'd	O
by	O
Nerves	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
Neighbour	O
for	O
Benedict	B-pers
--	O
pray	O
take	O
some	O
pains	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
greatly	O
interested	O
abt	O
.	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
poor	O
Mothers	O
sake	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
delighted	O
if	O
You	O
find	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
proper	O
companion	O
for	O
Is——	B-pers
as	O
they	O
are	O
suitable	O
in	O
age	O
,	O
situation	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
has	O
talents	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
amiable	O
--	O
when	O
Yo	O
.	O
see	O
her	O
say	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
from	O
me	O
&	O
aſsure	O
her	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
wrote	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
often	O
think	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
--	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
ashamed	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
if	O
she	O
will	O
aſsure	O
send	O
me	O
her	O
forgiveneſs	O
by	O
You	O
I	O
will	O
venture	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
letter	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
Yours	O
put	O
together	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
complain	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
promise	O
also	O
(	O
if	O
Yo	O
.	O
will	O
send	O
me	O
frank	O
's	O
directed	O
to	O
H	O
.	O
)	O
to	O
write	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
We	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
--	O
fail	O
not	O
to	O
answer	O
this	O
in	O
full	O
immediately	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
You	O
Adieu	O
I	O
rejoice	O
yt	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
B	B-pers
has	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Balls	O
--	O
at	O
Miranda	B-pers
s	O
,	O
at	O
Bushy	B-place
Park	I-place
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Egremont	I-pers
give	O
's	O
one	O
soon	O
They	O
talk	O
much	O
of	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
s	O
attachment	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aylesford	I-pers
&	O
yt	O
.	O
Miſ	B-pers
Thynne	I-pers
is	O
to	O
marry	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fairford	I-pers
.	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
F.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
Bro	O
.	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boston	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
some	O
East	O
India	O
Lady	O
.	O
West	B-place
India	I-place
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
Irby	I-pers
at	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
s	O
Horton	B-place
near	O
Northampton	B-place
18	O
th	O
July	O
1781	O
