TOKEN	NE
June	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
East	B-place
Bourne	I-place
Suſsex	B-place
I	O
must	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
wave	O
the	O
ungrateful	O
subject	O
,	O
of	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
mak	O
ing	O
e	O
comments	O
upon	O
the	O
conduct	O
of	O
people	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
receive	O
civilities	O
,	O
&	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
friendship	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
a	O
dupe	O
than	O
condemn	O
without	O
having	O
sure	O
grounds	O
for	O
objection	O
--	O
yet	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
can	O
approve	O
the	O
wrong	O
--	O
or	O
reject	O
the	O
right	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
suffer	O
always	O
so	O
exquisitely	O
from	O
finding	O
myself	O
deceived	O
in	O
a	O
*	O
Lady	B-pers
S——	I-pers
character	O
that	O
I	O
dread	O
when	O
once	O
I	O
have	O
form	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
I	O
have	O
err	O
'd	O
in	O
judg	O
e	O
ment	O
.	O
--	O
do	O
not	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
get	O
into	O
a	O
habit	O
of	O
listening	O
&	O
giving	O
credit	O
to	O
common	O
report	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
inattention	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
wd	O
.	O
deserve	O
the	O
severe	O
epithets	O
of	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
makes	O
use	O
of	O
--	O
viz	O
.	O
arrogance	O
--	O
inhumanity	O
--	O
pride	O
&	O
insolence	O
--	O
a	O
few	O
moments	O
reflection	O
upon	O
the	O
distrest	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
both	O
on	O
his	O
Uncle	O
s	O
&	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
ought	O
besides	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
public	O
affairs	O
wch-	O
as	O
a	O
Minister	O
he	O
was	O
deeply	O
interested	O
in	O
,	O
--	O
ought	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
more	O
charitable	O
.	O
--	O
notwithstanding	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
hold	O
his	B-pers
Lordship	I-pers
excused	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
natural	O
to	O
have	O
treated	O
wth	O
.	O
hospitality	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
owed	O
protection	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
therefore	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
falsely	O
represented	O
.	O
--	O
What	O
would	O
I	O
not	O
give	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
here	O
--	O
the	O
environs	O
are	O
charming	O
--	O
every	O
day	O
we	O
take	O
different	O
airings	O
&	O
are	O
more	O
&	O
more	O
delighted	O
with	O
the	O
country	O
--	O
You	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
pleased	O
too	O
with	O
our	O
stile	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
our	O
little	O
society	O
is	O
just	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
wish	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
,	O
--	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
equally	O
pleas	O
'd	O
wth	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
--	O
their	O
manner	O
and	O
conversation	O
is	O
perfectly	O
to	O
my	O
taste	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
more	O
of	O
ym	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
give	O
You	O
their	O
char	O
ac	O
ters	O
--	O
nothing	O
affords	O
one	O
a	O
better	O
opportunity	O
than	O
living	O
with	O
people	O
in	O
a	O
domestic	O
way	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Compts-	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
&	O
in	O
better	O
spirits	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
she	O
is	O
quite	O
like	O
a	O
parent	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Petersham	B-place
--	O
yet	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
regret	O
it	O
--	O
that	O
place	O
will	O
recall	O
me	O
oftener	O
to	O
your	O
mind	O
--	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
the	O
little	O
excursions	O
you	O
took	O
last	O
year	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
--	O
you	O
will	O
remember	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
mark	O
of	O
your	O
confidence	O
--	O
the	O
strict	O
tie	O
of	O
our	O
friendship	O
takes	O
its	O
date	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
&	O
place	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
tell	O
Sir	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
I	O
hope	O
never	O
to	O
lose	O
his	O
good	O
opinion	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sensibly	O
pleased	O
with	O
his	O
expreſsions	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
--	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Bell	B-pers
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Dear	O
friend	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
get	O
franks	O
&	O
send	O
me	O
some	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
--	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walshingham	I-pers
.	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
June	O
24	O
th	O
1780	O
