TOKEN	NE
Abbey	B-place
March	O
3	O
d	O
1772	O
Thank	O
God	O
it	O
is	O
once	O
more	O
given	O
me	O
to	O
thank	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
her	O
own	O
and	O
her	O
Mama	O
's	O
kind	O
interestedneſs	O
about	O
Us	O
:	O
bellieve	O
me	O
ours	O
for	O
you	O
is	O
not	O
leſs	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
last	O
(	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
pleasd	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
once	O
more	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
--	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
will	O
agree	O
better	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
than	O
London	B-place
)	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
his	O
Physicians	O
&	O
I	O
unable	O
almost	O
to	O
Support	O
the	O
Load	O
that	O
oprest	O
me	O
--	O
thank	O
God	O
that	O
Danger	O
is	O
over	O
:	O
it	O
has	O
ended	O
in	O
the	O
Gout	O
&	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
fifeteen	O
Weeks	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
the	O
first	O
good	O
Day	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
just	O
add	O
:	O
that	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
nor	O
Ever	O
able	O
even	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
till	O
last	O
Post	O
judge	O
then	O
my	O
Dear	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
better	O
Correspondant	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
my	O
own	O
Health	O
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
but	O
leſs	O
violently	O
than	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
expected	O
as	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
feaver	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Aprehended	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
contracted	O
very	O
Severe	O
Hysterick	O
complaints	O
.	O
my	O
Br	O
:	O
&	O
all	O
his	O
familly	O
are	O
well	O
I	O
expect	O
them	O
in	O
London	B-place
in	O
May	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
Happy	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
good	O
friends	O
in	O
Sr	B-pers
Wilm	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
&	O
hope	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
Use	O
in	O
setling	O
matters	O
properly	O
&	O
Aimicably	O
betwixt	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
--	O
be	O
asured	O
we	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
all	O
is	O
now	O
as	O
yo	O
u	O
wish	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
--	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
or	O
write	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Wilm	I-pers
do	O
remember	O
us	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
manner	O
asure	O
him	O
we	O
Sympathized	O
most	O
affectionatly	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
&	O
our	O
Great	O
Loſs	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
--	O
.	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
wonder	O
we	O
have	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
arriveal	O
or	O
Burial	O
of	O
her	O
Corps	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
aboard	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
:	O
have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
joins	O
your	O
Young	O
friends	O
&	O
me	O
in	O
offers	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
affectionate	O
compts	O
:	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
Yourself	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
very	O
much	O
grown	O
&	O
all	O
much	O
Yours	O
.	O
&	O
so	O
will	O
ever	O
remain	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
Cousin	O
&	O
most	O
faithful	O
Humble	O
Sert	O
:	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
