TOKEN	NE
5	O
,	O
Charles	O
Street	O
Westmr=	B-place
5	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1799	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
threaten	O
to	O
invade	O
the	O
Capital	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
good	O
terms	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
obey	O
your	O
commands	O
by	O
instantly	O
acknowledging	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
your	O
Letter	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
doing	O
so	O
is	O
matter	O
of	O
much	O
inconvenience	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Pen	O
being	O
hardly	O
fit	O
to	O
write	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
time	O
not	O
affording	O
me	O
leisure	O
enough	O
to	O
mend	O
it	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
Route	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
advice	O
how	O
to	O
travel	O
?	O
True	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
with	O
all	O
poſsible	O
assurance	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
travelled	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
persist	O
in	O
doing	O
so	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
sufficiently	O
subdued	O
my	O
Pride	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
jumble	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
in	O
the	O
Stage	O
Coach	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
your	O
Mail	O
Coaches	O
,	O
that	O
Respect	O
which	O
I	O
owe	O
to	O
the	O
safety	O
of	O
my	O
bones	O
prevents	O
my	O
thinking	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Attempt	O
.	O
My	O
stay	O
here	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
till	O
towards	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
My	O
intention	O
then	O
was	O
(	O
if	O
poſsible	O
)	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
Archy	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
North	O
.	O
Having	O
stupidly	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
Road	O
Book	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
far	O
this	O
plan	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
practicable	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
one	O
difficulty	O
will	O
be	O
removed	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
endeavour	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
intentions	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
care	O
about	O
You	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
shall	O
certainly	O
quarrel	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
your	O
Guid	O
Mon	O
&	O
your	O
Bairn	O
are	O
deserving	O
of	O
my	O
regard	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
bilious	O
lately	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
call	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
for	O
M	O
rs	O
-	O
Castor	O
(	O
Oil	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
you	O
mean	O
)	O
.	O
Really	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
trouble	O
to	O
recollect	O
who	O
you	O
could	O
poſsibly	O
wish	O
me	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
anybody	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
After	O
much	O
puzzling	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
word	O
with	O
a	O
magnifying	O
Glaſs	O
,	O
I	O
suspect	O
,	O
your	O
intention	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
Carter	B-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
School	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Greek	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
encounter	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Blue	O
Stocking	O
Aſsociates	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
shall	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
Old	O
Cis	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
scold	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Committee	O
for	O
dividing	O
waste	O
Grounds	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Molesworth	B-place
.	O
Say	O
everything	O
kind	O
for	O
Me	O
,	O
to	O
your	O
Lord	O
&	O
Master	O
,	O
Your	O
Child	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
Your	O
Affece	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Fifth	O
March	O
1799	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
