TOKEN	NE
St	O
Jamess	O
26	O
th	O
Jany	O
1789	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
since	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
not	O
dangeri	O
n	O
g	O
or	O
painfully	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
not	O
of	O
my	O
Horton	B-place
Rheumatism	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
,	O
particularly	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
violent	O
Cold	O
&	O
fever	O
with	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Limbs	O
,	O
which	O
kept	O
me	O
three	O
days	O
in	O
bed	O
--	O
this	O
fine	O
weather	O
has	O
quite	O
recovered	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
again	O
taking	O
my	O
Bark	O
which	O
was	O
suspend	O
ed	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
constantly	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
thank	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
l	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
having	O
openly	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
vexed	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
feared	O
having	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
by	O
something	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
day	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
correspondence	O
yet	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
conscious	O
of	O
self	O
reproach	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
merited	O
yours	O
,	O
of	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
averse	O
to	O
an	O
explanation	O
I	O
forbore	O
to	O
preſs	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
28	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
ten	O
years	O
older	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
you	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
for	O
near	O
12	O
years	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
had	O
more	O
experie	O
nces	O
of	O
various	O
kinds	O
than	O
most	O
people	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
--	O
much	O
vexation	O
,	O
many	O
diſsappointments	O
,	O
of	O
then	O
in	O
reasonable	O
plans	O
&	O
hopes	O
of	O
happineſs	O
,	O
&	O
many	O
,	O
of	O
those	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
unnatural	O
for	O
a	O
warm	O
imagination	O
&	O
a	O
cœur	O
sensible	O
to	O
form	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
days	O
of	O
enthusiasm	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
blasée	O
d	O
upon	O
most	O
subjects	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
learnt	O
to	O
apreciate	O
things	O
at	O
their	O
just	O
value	O
&	O
price	O
&	O
the	O
days	O
of	O
romance	O
are	O
over	O
!	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
easily	O
deceived	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
virtue	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
profeſsions	O
of	O
Friendship	O
I	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
sceptic	O
in	O
either	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
inclined	O
,	O
without	O
blindneſs	O
&	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
ingratitude	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
bleſsed	O
with	O
so	O
many	O
Friends	O
,	O
whose	O
virtues	O
excite	O
my	O
admiration	O
&	O
respect	O
whilst	O
their	O
kindneſs	O
&	O
long	O
attachme	O
nt	O
to	O
me	O
constitute	O
my	O
happineſs	O
--	O
And	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
myself	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
worse	O
Friend	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
reasonable	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
Health	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
succeſses	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
feel	O
her	O
power	O
,	O
&	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
,	O
has	O
principles	O
&	O
reason	O
to	O
teach	O
her	O
the	O
proper	O
objects	O
on	O
which	O
to	O
exert	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
discretion	O
&	O
moderation	O
that	O
ought	O
always	O
to	O
attend	O
on	O
power	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
dangerous	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
clever	O
child	O
--	O
to	O
herself	O
&	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
governing	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
fatal	O
one	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
woman	O
--	O
this	O
I	O
particularly	O
addreſs	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
has	O
not	O
forgot	O
all	O
the	O
useful	O
admonitions	O
&	O
instructions	O
given	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
Subject	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
&	O
thumbs	O
away	O
with	O
proper	O
Spirit	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Bell	B-pers
are	O
quite	O
well	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
who	O
looks	O
like	O
Death	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
,	O
uncomfortable	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
his	O
Complaint	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
trust	O
it	O
is	O
attended	O
with	O
no	O
alarmi	O
n	O
g	O
symptoms	O
of	O
danger	O
nor	O
will	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
threatens	O
no	O
consequences	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
easy	O
upon	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
the	O
leſs	O
so	O
from	O
not	O
knowi	O
n	O
g	O
what	O
to	O
wish	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
country	O
air	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
moderate	O
degree	O
of	O
diſsipation	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
chearful	O
&	O
comfortable	O
style	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
next	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
led	O
the	O
a	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
quietn	O
eſs	O
&	O
retirement	O
since	O
we	O
came	O
--	O
indeed	O
a	O
whole	O
week	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
--	O
one	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
aſsembly	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
s	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
noise	O
,	O
crowd	O
&	O
heat	O
stupified	O
&	O
overcame	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hardly	O
recovered	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
twelve	O
--	O
what	O
does	O
not	O
habit	O
reconcile	O
one	O
to	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
enable	O
one	O
to	O
bear	O
!	O
my	O
reason	O
&	O
inclination	O
can	O
never	O
again	O
make	O
their	O
peace	O
or	O
agree	O
wth	O
the	O
absurdity	O
&	O
stupidity	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
three	O
Months	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
,	O
felt	O
no	O
heat	O
&	O
shall	O
come	O
home	O
without	O
feeling	O
the	O
least	O
tired	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
in	O
To	O
u	O
n	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
principally	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
wh	O
ere	O
his	O
duty	O
,	O
&	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
confine	O
h	O
im	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
sometime	O
in	O
Somersetshire	B-place
wth	O
his	O
Family	O
--	O
I	O
believe	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
is	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
greatest	O
hopes	O
of	O
his	O
recovery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
found	O
ation	O
vain	O
of	O
these	O
hopes	O
is	O
open	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Dr	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
's	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
the	O
Committee	O
on	O
the	O
Ex	O
:	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
highly	O
of	O
Dr	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
's	O
good	O
sense	O
skill	O
&	O
what	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
heart	O
character	O
&	O
good	O
intentions	O
which	O
are	O
sincere	O
as	O
his	O
endeavours	O
to	O
promote	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
recovery	O
&	O
unmixed	O
with	O
political	O
or	O
worldly	O
motives	O
,	O
on	O
hi	O
m	O
I	O
pin	O
my	O
Faith	O
&	O
shall	O
thank	O
God	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
allowed	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Physicians	O
)	O
to	O
have	O
fair	O
play	O
&	O
the	O
sole	O
,	O
uninterrupted	O
,	O
unopposed	O
management	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
--	O
As	O
to	O
party	O
,	O
the	O
rage	O
of	O
it	O
runs	O
so	O
high	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
extreme	O
of	O
violence	O
as	O
is	O
inconceivable	O
,	O
it	O
disunites	O
families	O
diſsolves	O
Friendships	O
,	O
banishes	O
even	O
good	O
manners	O
&	O
common	O
civility	O
,	O
&	O
requires	O
the	O
sacrifice	O
of	O
reason	O
&	O
common	O
Sense	O
!	O
God	O
help	O
us	O
--	O
what	O
sad	O
times	O
&	O
what	O
a	O
dreary	O
black	O
prospect	O
!	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
luck	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
tourbillon	O
--	O
remember	O
us	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
soon	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
hear	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
can	O
interest	O
you	O
,	O
depend	O
on	O
my	O
letti	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
kno	O
w	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
once	O
more	O
your	O
sincere	O
&	O
affec	O
:	O
C.M.G	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bell	B-pers
never	O
comes	O
here	O
now	O
or	O
very	O
late	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
engaged	O
wth	O
my	O
table	O
which	O
grows	O
extremely	O
pretty	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
