TOKEN	NE
N	O
o	O
:	O
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
Street	O
London	B-place
Jan	O
:	O
27	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
,	O
independently	O
of	O
your	O
most	O
kind	O
letter	O
just	O
received	O
,	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
Post	O
,	O
to	O
communicate	O
the	O
afflicting	O
intelligence	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
yesterday	O
--	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Mother	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
has	O
no	O
one	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
dreadful	O
communication	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
perhaps	O
not	O
immediately	O
receive	O
it	O
:	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
papers	O
will	O
be	O
your	O
first	O
informers	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
:	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
my	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mother	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
deplorable	O
state	O
from	O
a	O
confirmed	O
Asthma	O
,	O
which	O
baffled	O
medicine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
her	O
Physician	O
,	O
to	O
Dawlish	B-place
in	O
Devonshire	B-place
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
purity	O
of	O
the	O
air	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
letter	O
,	O
from	O
its	O
going	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Hill	O
Top	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
till	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
yesterday	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
fatal	O
one	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
She	O
expired	O
on	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
:	O
,	O
but	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
her	O
arrival	O
at	O
Dawlish	B-place
.	O
The	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
water	O
upon	O
the	O
Chest	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
am	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
deepest	O
affliction	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
heart	O
like	O
yours	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
unneceſsary	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
circumstances	O
can	O
blunt	O
the	O
pang	O
of	O
nature	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
a	O
Mother	O
.	O
My	O
poor	O
Father	O
's	O
situation	O
,	O
too	O
,	O
is	O
dreadful	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
entreat	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
dreadful	O
miserable	O
solitude	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
will	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
I	O
did	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
offer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
mercy	O
that	O
this	O
blow	O
did	O
not	O
reach	O
me	O
in	O
Herefordshire	B-place
;	O
for	O
but	O
as	O
,	O
were	O
it	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
soothings	O
of	O
friendship	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
after	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
already	O
suffered	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
extinguished	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
settled	O
in	O
an	O
excellent	O
house	O
here	O
,	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
abode	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
better	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
her	O
nursing	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
within	O
immediate	O
reach	O
of	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
should	O
I	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
easily	O
persuaded	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
these	O
three	O
weeks	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
friend	O
besides	O
those	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
my	O
Sister	O
(	O
who	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
expectation	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
town	O
)	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
beginning	O
to	O
get	O
considerably	O
better	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
shock	O
threw	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Your	O
letter	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
was	O
eleven	O
days	O
in	O
reaching	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
those	O
vile	O
Croſs-Posts	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Your	O
warm	O
interest	O
in	O
what	O
concerns	O
us	O
,	O
is	O
particularly	O
gratifying	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
ashamed	O
of	O
that	O
long	O
epistle	O
all	O
about	O
ourselves	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
burning	O
instead	O
of	O
sending	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
glad	O
it	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
even	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
your	O
health	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
answering	O
any	O
questions	O
--	O
therefore	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
proceed	O
any	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
hope	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
entirely	O
lost	O
the	O
cough	O
you	O
complained	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
answer	O
your	O
questions	O
--	O
my	O
eldest	O
niece	O
is	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Rodney	I-pers
--	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
Ceylon	B-place
with	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
employment	O
there	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
E	I-pers
:	I-pers
B	I-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
her	O
husband	O
are	O
in	O
embarraſsed	O
circumstances	O
,	O
already	O
--	O
not	O
entirely	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
from	O
improvidence	O
;	O
but	O
partly	O
from	O
diminution	O
of	O
his	O
Barbadoes	B-place
receipts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
Husbands	O
and	O
Mother	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
see	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
caution	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
totally	O
ignorant	O
of	O
my	O
affairs	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
should	O
he	O
ever	O
mention	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Nothing	O
has	O
gone	O
wrong	O
with	O
my	O
B	O
:	O
,	O
whom	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
“	O
a	O
certain	O
young	O
man	O
”	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
best	O
keep	O
as	O
smooth	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Your	O
kind	O
suggestions	O
for	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
in	O
D	O
.	O
are	O
very	O
wise	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
considered	O
.	O
He	O
stands	O
well	O
with	O
the	O
D	O
.	O
&	O
Dſs	O
.	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
material	O
use	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
;	O
and	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
forget	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
you	O
have	O
shewn	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
wrote	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
proposing	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
the	O
Hill	O
Top	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
B	B-place
.	I-place
I	O
must	O
receive	O
him	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
--	O
ever	O
your	O
obliged	O
and	O
affectionate	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
retains	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
having	O
married	O
her	O
Cousin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
longing	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
should	O
soon	O
have	O
written	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
had	O
this	O
sad	O
neceſsity	O
for	O
doing	O
so	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
.	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
.	O
