TOKEN	NE
The	O
Dſs	B-pers
Dr.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
and	O
all	O
yr-	O
good	O
friends	O
are	O
very	O
kin	O
d	O
in	O
interesting	O
themselves	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
including	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
good	O
wishes	O
--	O
which	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
sake	O
--	O
will	O
--	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
--	O
be	O
gratified	O
in	O
their	O
fullest	O
extent	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
from	O
Taxal	B-place
--	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
with	O
the	O
amiable	O
partner	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
--	O
May	O
you	O
--	O
best	O
of	O
women	O
--	O
derive	O
that	O
happineſs	O
from	O
a	O
union	O
with	O
yr-	O
D	B-pers
.	I-pers
which	O
y	O
o	O
ur	O
virtue	O
and	O
universal	O
Goodneſs	O
will	O
justly	O
e	O
ntitle	O
you	O
to	O
--	O
and	O
God	O
grant	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
always	O
thrō	O
the	O
whole	O
Course	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
--	O
be	O
as	O
sensible	O
as	O
I	O
now	O
am	O
of	O
your	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bleſsings	O
I	O
shall	O
enjoy	O
for	O
being	O
your	O
Husband	O
--	O
and	O
may	O
I	O
for	O
ever	O
preserve	O
that	O
Solicitude	O
for	O
yr-	O
happineſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
invariably	O
felt	O
from	O
our	O
earliest	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
and	O
for	O
ever	O
will	O
be	O
your	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
My	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
London	B-place
