TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
June	O
r	O
-	O
1814	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
ever	O
condescended	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
or	O
speak	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
mine	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
abuse	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
.	O
If	O
so	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
unreasonable	O
,	O
for	O
You	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Royal	O
Occupation	O
's	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
my	O
scribbling	O
.	O
They	O
,	O
happily	O
finished	O
ten	O
Days	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
outlived	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
dying	O
in	O
an	O
Alderman	O
like	O
manner	O
,	O
from	O
overeating	O
,	O
and	O
overdrinking	O
.	O
As	O
sitting	O
never	O
agrees	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
some	O
little	O
inclination	O
in	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
to	O
refuse	O
to	O
do	O
their	O
Duty	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
begun	O
to	O
walk	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
convinced	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
no	O
longer	O
to	O
consider	O
themselves	O
as	O
Royals	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
insist	O
on	O
their	O
performing	O
Plebian	O
functions	O
,	O
properly	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
time	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
You	O
,	O
your	O
better	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
excellent	O
Daughter	O
,	O
find	O
Yourselves	O
amidst	O
the	O
Bustle	O
of	O
Emperors	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
's	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
How	O
shocked	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
that	O
Great	O
Men	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
truly	O
Great	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
expose	O
their	O
frailties	O
to	O
the	O
Vulgar	O
Eye	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
any	O
Man	O
conceive	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
degrading	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
cast	O
a	O
Reflexion	O
on	O
Himself	O
?	O
The	O
Letters	O
which	O
have	O
lately	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
Newspapers	O
vex	O
me	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
the	O
Advisers	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
Advisers	O
in	O
the	O
busineſs	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
of	O
rejoicing	O
,	O
for	O
accommodating	O
our	O
differences	O
with	O
Foreign	O
Foes	O
,	O
our	O
domestic	O
Squabbles	O
should	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
public	O
Mind	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
lamented	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
was	O
made	O
a	O
Post	O
Captain	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Ship	O
the	O
Erne	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
from	O
Heluvet	B-place
to	O
Bourdeaux	B-place
,	O
with	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Troops	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
he	O
proceeds	O
to	O
America	B-place
,	O
without	O
coming	O
to	O
Britain	B-place
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
has	O
left	O
the	O
Snake	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
on	O
board	O
Admiral	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
)	O
at	O
Port	B-place
Royal	I-place
,	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
At	O
least	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
by	O
Admiral	B-pers
George	I-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Admiral	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
dated	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Youth	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
this	O
change	O
in	O
his	O
Situation	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Sons	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
about	O
themselves	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
unneceſsary	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
,	O
unleſs	O
they	O
want	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
indeed	O
,	O
they	O
do	O
condescend	O
to	O
put	O
Pen	O
to	O
Paper	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
is	O
in	O
high	O
preservation	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
waiting	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Staff	O
General	O
's	O
,	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dalrymple	I-pers
.	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
back	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
what	O
his	O
fate	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
still	O
to	O
learn	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
His	O
Royal	O
Highneſs	O
the	O
Commander	O
in	O
Chief	O
,	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
London	B-place
I	O
took	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Plans	O
of	O
my	O
Ho	O
use	O
at	O
Thirlestane	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
Edification	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
punish	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Mind	O
not	O
to	O
finish	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
though	O
all	O
my	O
Doors	O
,	O
Windows	O
&	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
during	O
my	O
Absence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
on	O
finding	O
they	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Selkirkshire	B-place
.	O
Next	O
Week	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
sent	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Weeks	O
hence	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
go	O
to	O
Thirlestane	O
to	O
look	O
how	O
the	O
Plasterers	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
but	O
,	O
take	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Yourself	O
.	O
My	O
Rib	O
&	O
c	O
send	O
her	O
Civilities	O
&	O
their	O
Civilities	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Napier	B-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
June	O
1814	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
,	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
