TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
Oct	O
28	O
th	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
murmuring	O
at	O
my	O
cold	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
Sandleford	B-place
,	O
for	O
having	O
deprived	O
me	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
yours	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
company	O
till	O
this	O
morning	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
best	O
amends	O
for	O
my	O
loſs	O
,	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
your	O
obliging	O
letter	O
.	O
My	O
churlish	O
cold	O
kept	O
me	O
in	O
bed	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
departed	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
also	O
lost	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Mongewell	B-place
.	O
After	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
confinement	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
air	O
in	O
my	O
chaise	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
some	O
shelterd	O
place	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
walk	O
.	O
These	O
little	O
excursions	O
are	O
very	O
delightfull	O
at	O
all	O
seasons	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
particularly	O
at	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Seasons	O
have	O
all	O
performd	O
their	O
labours	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
things	O
seem	O
subsiding	O
into	O
gentle	O
peace	O
,	O
&	O
sweet	O
tranquillity	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Robin	O
red	O
breast	O
chaunts	O
the	O
Vespers	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
My	O
time	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
now	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
sere	O
&	O
yellow	O
leaf	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
,	O
Macbeth	O
V.iii	O
,	O
perhaps	O
makes	O
me	O
sympathise	O
more	O
with	O
the	O
tranquillity	O
of	O
Autumn	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
gayity	O
of	O
Spring	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
gaudy	O
pomp	O
,	O
&	O
splender	O
of	O
summer	O
,	O
&	O
its	O
bustling	O
labours	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
next	O
visit	O
to	O
Sandleford	B-place
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
short	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
Grandson	O
Edward	B-pers
will	O
in	O
another	O
year	O
pay	O
due	O
homage	O
to	O
the	O
rosy	O
cheeks	O
&	O
dimpled	O
smile	O
of	O
pretty	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Parents	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
to	O
present	O
their	O
best	O
respects	O
,	O
&	O
present	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
offer	O
mine	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
give	O
ye	O
little	O
Lady	O
s	O
rosy	O
cheek	O
a	O
kiſs	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
cold	O
has	O
left	O
such	O
a	O
weakneſs	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
as	O
fortunately	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
prevents	O
my	O
troubling	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
longer	O
letter	O
.	O
With	O
sincere	O
esteem	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
&	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Eliz	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
May	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
desire	O
my	O
best	O
compts	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
?	O
Newbury	B-place
.	O
October	O
the	O
twenty	O
eighth	O
1788	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
's	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
near	O
Northampton	B-place
M	O
free	O
Montagu	B-pers
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Octer	O
.	O
28	O
--	O
1788	O
