TOKEN	NE
Lower	O
Lodge	O
ye	O
2	O
8	O
9	O
th	O
October	O
83	O
I	O
ought	O
my	O
dear	O
to	O
have	O
thanked	O
you	O
much	O
sooner	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
&	O
obliging	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
fully	O
employed	O
my	O
Time	O
is	O
&	O
that	O
besides	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
Pen	O
of	O
a	O
ready	O
writer	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
had	O
paſsed	O
your	O
Summer	O
so	O
pleasantly	O
,	O
nothing	O
can	O
equal	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
finding	O
that	O
those	O
we	O
love	O
,	O
really	O
Love	O
us	O
,	O
may	O
you	O
ever	O
have	O
that	O
Satisfaction	O
is	O
my	O
sincere	O
wish	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
&	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
is	O
free	O
from	O
Gout	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Burley	B-place
I	O
expect	O
her	O
in	O
about	O
Ten	O
days	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
I	O
am	O
likewise	O
in	O
some	O
hopes	O
of	O
seeing	O
either	O
to	O
day	O
or	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
.	O
News	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
Situation	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
hitherto	O
thank	O
God	O
escaped	O
Bleeding	O
or	O
a	O
Blister	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
sincerly	O
wish	O
you	O
well	O
&	O
happy	O
&	O
am	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
