TOKEN	NE
Buxton	B-place
June	O
14	O
th	O
1772	O
As	O
I	O
find	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
is	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
write	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
wont	O
let	O
her	O
Epistle	O
come	O
alone	O
--	O
its	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
I	O
beg	O
a	O
n	O
to	O
be	O
Uneasy	O
but	O
am	O
Happy	O
to	O
find	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
(	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
)	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
I	O
wish	O
that	O
to	O
perfect	O
her	O
cure	O
to	O
contribute	O
to	O
yr	O
own	O
Amusement	O
&	O
make	O
us	O
Happy	O
you'de	O
come	O
here	O
&	O
paſs	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
now	O
;	O
these	O
Watters	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
infinite	O
use	O
to	O
both	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
Nerves	O
Spiritts	O
&	O
twenty	O
different	O
disorders	O
particularly	O
those	O
of	O
a	O
Cronick	O
Nature	O
--	O
we	O
hope	O
our	O
being	O
here	O
will	O
be	O
rather	O
an	O
inducement	O
to	O
trie	O
their	O
Vertues	O
--	O
We	O
came	O
here	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
Health	O
--	O
the	O
night	O
beffore	O
last	O
&	O
propose	O
staying	O
some	O
Weeks	O
when	O
he	O
joins	O
the	O
Regt	O
:	O
at	O
Canterbury	B-place
&	O
I	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
folks	O
at	O
Edr	B-place
:	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
&	O
to	O
receive	O
yr	O
orders	O
to	O
get	O
rooms	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
--	O
haveing	O
many	O
Letters	O
to	O
write	O
I	O
reffer	O
you	O
for	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
--	O
accept	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
s	O
best	O
compts	O
&	O
mine	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
acceptable	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
bellieve	O
me	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
most	O
Sincearly	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
