TOKEN	NE
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
Deal	B-place
Kent	I-place
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
gratified	O
by	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
yours	O
&	O
happy	O
to	O
learn	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Family	O
were	O
well	O
the	O
distance	O
I	O
am	O
from	O
you	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
bar	O
to	O
the	O
comforts	O
of	O
society	O
&	O
a	O
Bulletin	O
of	O
health	O
is	O
extremely	O
interesting	O
were	O
you	O
to	O
add	O
no	O
more	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
reflect	O
on	O
this	O
&	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
delightful	O
Tour	O
you	O
have	O
in	O
contemplation	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
intended	O
departure	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
however	O
I	O
will	O
direct	O
this	O
to	O
yourself	O
or	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
that	O
in	O
case	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
your	O
flight	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
any	O
trouble	O
to	O
you	O
What	O
you	O
said	O
respecting	O
our	O
residing	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
interests	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
sentiments	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
:	O
our	O
being	O
fixed	O
here	O
which	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
does	O
not	O
happen	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
's	O
health	O
only	O
my	O
own	O
from	O
debility	O
of	O
constitution	O
though	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
enjoy	O
a	O
good	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
&	O
am	O
exempted	O
from	O
all	O
pain	O
&	O
suffering	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
appears	O
to	O
require	O
the	O
bracing	O
air	O
of	O
the	O
Sea-Coast	O
I	O
have	O
scarcely	O
any	O
degree	O
of	O
strength	O
&	O
this	O
air	O
with	O
constantly	O
taking	O
the	O
tincture	O
of	O
bark	O
appears	O
to	O
revive	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
manner	O
I	O
was	O
affected	O
by	O
a	O
severe	O
Cough	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
though	O
the	O
winter	O
was	O
mild	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
a	O
year	O
without	O
a	O
Cold	O
or	O
the	O
least	O
tendency	O
to	O
coughing	O
added	O
to	O
this	O
inducement	O
the	O
air	O
agrees	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
whose	O
health	O
is	O
more	O
imperfect	O
than	O
mine	O
&	O
the	O
consideration	O
of	O
expence	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
comfortable	O
&	O
neatly	O
furnished	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Deal	O
for	O
nearly	O
half	O
the	O
price	O
which	O
makes	O
a	O
considerable	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
Income	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
invitation	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
in	O
the	O
spring	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accept	O
&	O
have	O
just	O
received	O
another	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
which	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
avail	O
myself	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
will	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
returned	O
from	O
your	O
Northern	O
expedition	O
--	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
I	O
am	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
visit	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
Town	O
she	O
is	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
gratified	O
by	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
love	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
as	O
by	O
hers	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
resolution	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
I	O
shall	O
sometimes	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
visit	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
leave	O
my	O
Sister	O
with	O
all	O
neceſsary	O
comforts	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
with	O
whom	O
we	O
now	O
lodge	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
attentive	O
to	O
her	O
we	O
engage	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
Girl	O
to	O
serve	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
another	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
our	O
Landlady	O
)	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
deafneſs	O
which	O
has	O
of	O
late	O
years	O
increased	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
interesting	O
account	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
dear	O
Children	O
it	O
pleases	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
the	O
youngest	O
resemble	O
his	O
amiable	O
Mother	O
because	O
she	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
striking	O
likeneſs	O
of	O
my	O
beloved	O
Friend	O
which	O
makes	O
a	O
strong	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
my	O
mind	O
whenever	O
I	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
resemblance	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Eyes	O
&	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
face	O
--	O
àpropos	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
employed	O
in	O
reading	O
&	O
destroying	O
Letters	O
from	O
Friends	O
in	O
time	O
pas	O
t	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
exceſsively	O
interested	O
in	O
reading	O
over	O
some	O
of	O
yours	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
but	O
swet	O
sweet	O
gratification	O
folios	O
from	O
Bullstrode	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
introduction	O
there	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
were	O
liked	O
encomiums	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
in	O
yourself	O
such	O
anxiety	O
respecting	O
the	O
suspence	O
&	O
difficulties	O
of	O
some	O
circumstances	O
not	O
explained	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
continue	O
the	O
Diary	O
you	O
attribute	O
to	O
my	O
memory	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
more	O
than	O
it	O
merits	O
though	O
it	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
tenacious	O
one	O
in	O
many	O
respects	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
L	B-place
though	O
absent	O
on	O
your	O
arrival	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
first	O
lodged	O
in	O
Queen	O
Street	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
probable	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
mentioned	O
for	O
you	O
were	O
out	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
London	B-place
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Horwood	B-place
with	O
my	O
dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
recollection	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
at	O
any	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
excepting	O
a	O
Lodging	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
remembered	O
had	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
&	O
fro	O
from	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
respecting	O
la	O
belle	O
paſsion	O
I	O
know	O
know	O
two	O
amiable	O
minds	O
minds	O
are	O
deeply	O
engaged	O
by	O
the	O
powerful	O
charm	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
attentive	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Letters	O
what	O
you	O
wish	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
suceeded	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
discontinuance	O
of	O
the	O
Journal	O
extract	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
was	O
expected	O
at	O
Bullstrode	O
27	O
or	O
29	O
Nov	O
18	O
1784	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
returned	O
to	O
Derb	O
the	O
Country	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
weeks	O
from	O
3	O
Dec	O
1784	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
resolve	O
this	O
--	O
Now	O
my	O
dear	O
Brother	O
believing	O
you	O
are	O
sufficiently	O
occupied	O
before	O
your	O
departure	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
a	O
Letter	O
but	O
I	O
intreat	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
&	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
&	O
safe	O
return	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
truly	O
vexed	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
comply	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
A——	I-pers
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Niece	O
is	O
happily	O
settld	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	B-place
with	O
her	O
four	O
Children	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
pretty	O
House	O
a	O
Garden	O
full	O
of	O
fruit	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ponies	O
&	O
a	O
Cow	O
the	O
plaice	O
is	O
pretty	O
&	O
she	O
invites	O
me	O
&	O
Isabella	B-pers
I	O
am	O
grieved	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
N	I-pers
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Palsy	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
all	O
comforts	O
attend	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
you	O
travel	O
yours	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
C	I-pers
Remember	O
me	O
particularly	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
&	O
dear	O
f	O
naughty	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
write	O
on	O
your	O
return	O
x	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
or	O
Lady	B-pers
William	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
