TOKEN	NE
Caulk	B-place
Decr	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
1786	O
My	O
dear	O
Ly-	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
I	O
did	O
not	O
Receive	O
your	O
last	O
kind	O
Letter	O
till	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
am	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
Post	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
Hope	O
this	O
May	O
find	O
you	O
Well	O
at	O
Warwick	B-place
Castle	I-place
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
Sorry	O
to	O
Hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
been	O
so	O
Ill	O
;	O
Hope	O
He	O
Will	O
find	O
every	O
Benefit	O
from	O
,	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
Should	O
be	O
very	O
Happy	O
to	O
Meet	O
you	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
dislikes	O
it	O
so	O
Much	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
Absolute	O
neceſsity	O
,	O
can	O
perswade	O
Him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
&	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
We	O
Were	O
there	O
He	O
Would	O
not	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
Shall	O
be	O
Much	O
Obliged	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
enclosed	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Mine	O
,	O
Her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Is	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Most	O
Eminent	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
a	O
very	O
Worthy	O
good	O
Man	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
Recommend	O
Him	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
His	O
Wife	O
a	O
very	O
Sensible	O
excellent	O
Woman	O
;	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
Time	O
Acquainted	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
Family	O
,	O
&	O
devotes	O
All	O
Her	O
Time	O
&	O
Care	O
;	O
to	O
their	O
Education	O
,	O
It	O
Is	O
some	O
Time	O
Since	O
I	O
Have	O
Heard	O
from	O
Her	O
;	O
so	O
Much	O
I	O
feel	O
almost	O
afraid	O
to	O
Enquire	O
after	O
Her	O
Family	O
,	O
least	O
She	O
May	O
have	O
suffered	O
any	O
Loſs	O
;	O
--	O
If	O
you	O
Wish	O
for	O
any	O
addition	O
to	O
your	O
Society	O
in	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
&	O
like	O
a	O
pleasant	O
&	O
Improving	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
Recommend	O
to	O
you	O
Sr.	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
;	O
I	O
think	O
She	O
Is	O
a	O
Person	O
you	O
would	O
like	O
Much	O
;	O
&	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
w	O
.	O
the	O
Affection	O
,	O
&	O
Unanimity	O
that	O
prevails	O
in	O
Her	O
Family	O
;	O
--	O
She	O
Is	O
Really	O
a	O
very	O
Valuable	O
Woman	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
Hope	O
also	O
you	O
will	O
See	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
s	O
Pictures	O
,	O
&	O
Recommend	O
Him	O
,	O
If	O
in	O
your	O
Power	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
w	O
.	O
your	O
young	O
Cousins	O
at	O
W.	B-place
Castle	I-place
,	O
they	O
are	O
charming	O
Children	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
have	O
Alarmed	O
Lawrence	B-pers
as	O
to	O
Winchester	B-place
;	O
My	O
Br	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
intends	O
sending	O
His	O
Eldest	O
Son	O
there	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
;	O
Which	O
gives	O
Me	O
great	O
Uneasineſs	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
aſsured	O
bad	O
Fevers	O
frequently	O
prevail	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
,	O
Which	O
deprived	O
Us	O
,	O
of	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
;	O
has	O
been	O
this	O
Autumn	O
at	O
Winchester	B-place
,	O
&	O
been	O
fatal	O
to	O
a	O
Physicians	O
Wife	O
&	O
Son	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
Opinion	O
It	O
Is	O
not	O
a	O
Healthy	O
Place	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
numbers	O
escape	O
this	O
Disorder	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Melancholy	O
Event	O
of	O
our	O
Loſs	O
;	O
&	O
being	O
aſsured	O
,	O
this	O
very	O
dangerous	O
kind	O
of	O
Fever	O
,	O
frequently	O
Happens	O
,	O
Spring	O
&	O
Autumn	O
,	O
gives	O
Me	O
a	O
Prejudice	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
over	O
;	O
&	O
Makes	O
Me	O
very	O
Anxious	O
My	O
Brother	O
Should	O
fix	O
on	O
some	O
other	O
School	O
;	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
Mean	O
to	O
send	O
His	O
Son	O
,	O
till	O
Spring	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
forbear	O
Mentioning	O
My	O
Opinion	O
&	O
fears	O
;	O
that	O
He	O
May	O
Make	O
every	O
Satisfactory	O
Enquiry	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
Much	O
Interested	O
for	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooke	I-pers
,	O
He	O
Is	O
a	O
Most	O
Interesting	O
charming	O
Boy	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
My	O
Recipes	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
Use	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
now	O
desire	O
to	O
offer	O
My	O
Advice	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
,	O
Still	O
desiring	O
Him	O
not	O
to	O
trust	O
entirely	O
to	O
Me	O
;	O
but	O
first	O
Enquire	O
of	O
the	O
faculty	O
,	O
If	O
It	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
diservice	O
;	O
--	O
in	O
His	O
Case	O
;	O
--	O
for	O
a	O
Bilious	O
Disorder	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
,	O
w	O
.	O
great	O
Succeſs	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
Raw	O
Egg	O
,	O
twice	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
before	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
&	O
before	O
Dinner	O
;	O
It	O
Must	O
be	O
fresh	O
,	O
or	O
new	O
laid	O
--	O
first	O
break	O
the	O
Shell	O
;	O
&	O
turn	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Whole	O
Egg	O
,	O
White	O
,	O
Yolk	O
,	O
&	O
Liquid	O
,	O
It	O
contains	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
&	O
Swallow	O
It	O
;	O
--	O
this	O
Must	O
be	O
persevered	O
in	O
for	O
Months	O
;	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
tried	O
It	O
,	O
for	O
near	O
two	O
Years	O
w	O
.	O
great	O
Benefits	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
If	O
Miſs	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
Attends	O
in	O
Lying-In	O
Cases	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
Sure	O
,	O
He	O
Is	O
Reckoned	O
a	O
very	O
Eminent	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
Respectable	O
Character	O
;	O
His	O
Wife	O
also	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
Sure	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
Her	O
;	O
--	O
but	O
dont	O
let	O
Me	O
fix	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Attendance	O
,	O
When	O
you	O
are	O
confined	O
,	O
but	O
Make	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
the	O
Most	O
Established	O
Person	O
in	O
that	O
Line	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
Hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
dislike	O
My	O
Introducing	O
to	O
your	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
,	O
It	O
Is	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
Liberty	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
Really	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
her	O
Much	O
;	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
Suit	O
as	O
to	O
Disposition	O
&	O
turn	O
of	O
Mind	O
exactly	O
;	O
I	O
Shall	O
be	O
Anxious	O
to	O
know	O
;	O
--	O
if	O
this	O
finds	O
you	O
at	O
W.	B-place
Castle	I-place
,	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
My	O
Br	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
&	O
am	O
ever	O
very	O
Sincerely	O
&	O
Affecly	O
.	O
Yours	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
Hope	O
I	O
Shall	O
Hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
Soon	O
as	O
convenient	O
after	O
your	O
Arrival	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
