TOKEN	NE
Deal	O
Castle	O
.	O
July	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
Our	O
Dear	O
little	O
Prince	O
looks	O
so	O
charmingly	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
Pen	O
to	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
bragging	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
last	O
Letters	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
fresh	O
Irruption	O
;	O
he	O
now	O
bathes	O
two	O
days	O
out	O
of	O
Three	O
,	O
which	O
seems	O
to	O
agree	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
certainly	O
is	O
clearer	O
to	O
day	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
we	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
Shewing	O
him	O
Yesterday	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
who	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
obliging	O
Visit	O
thō	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
at	O
Walmer	B-place
but	O
for	O
a	O
Short	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
business	O
being	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
Sea-men	O
for	O
manning	O
the	O
Ships	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
want	O
of	O
Men	O
;	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
&	O
my	O
Lady	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Settle	O
here	O
before	O
September	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
time	O
Lord	B-pers
Guilford	I-pers
usually	O
is	O
at	O
Waldershare	B-place
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Lewisham	I-pers
s	O
Match	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
gives	O
such	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
all	O
parties	O
.	O
This	O
Mornings	O
Post	O
has	O
brought	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Rockingham	I-pers
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
surprise	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
so	O
bad	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
Post	O
before	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
comes	O
into	O
his	O
great	O
Estate	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Fifteen	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
apiece	O
to	O
his	O
three	O
Sisters	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Milbanke	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
Sturgeon	I-pers
,	O
&	O
how	O
near	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
Children	O
,	O
does	O
this	O
vast	O
Estate	O
come	O
,	O
to	O
young	O
Sturgeon	O
Ly	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
s	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
failure	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Fitzwilliam	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
a	O
poor	O
Sickly	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
)	O
stands	O
heir	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
makes	O
a	O
great	O
difference	O
in	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
s	O
Situation	O
as	O
to	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Dear	O
you	O
will	O
present	O
my	O
humble	O
Duty	O
to	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Royl	O
Highneſses	O
&	O
accept	O
of	O
my	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
last	O
Letters	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Ever	O
most	O
sincerely	O
&	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Com̄ps	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
.	O
