TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
had	O
the	O
favour	O
to	O
receive	O
your	O
obliging	O
note	O
last	O
night	O
inclosed	O
with	O
the	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Blue	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
this	O
very	O
first	O
opportunity	O
to	O
obey	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
s	O
Commands	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
you	O
the	O
yellow	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
knoted	O
but	O
about	O
ten	O
scans	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
till	O
the	O
Blue	O
is	O
finished	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
pre	O
sent	O
My	O
respectful	O
Duty	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
tell	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
I	O
will	O
the	O
great	O
pleasure	O
doe	O
the	O
Blue	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
posible	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
take	O
Care	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
Safe	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
s	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
have	O
regrated	O
very	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
intended	O
by	O
some	O
unlucky	O
thing	O
or	O
other	O
been	O
preven	O
ted	O
I	O
dont	O
yet	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
doeing	O
my	O
Self	O
that	O
plea	O
sure	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
any	O
Conveniency	O
Come	O
I	O
will	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
allways	O
happy	O
of	O
any	O
opportunity	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sincerly	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
affectionat	O
and	O
much	O
obliged	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Maddox	O
Street	O
June	O
29	O
th	O
1779	O
P	O
:	O
S	O
:	O
has	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
yet	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
aſsured	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
where	O
near	O
Kew	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
then	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
