TOKEN	NE
Pray	O
tell	O
Mrs.-	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
--	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
&	O
will	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
,	O
send	O
our	O
Subscription	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
The	O
Clergyman	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
)	O
if	O
She	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
our	O
compliments	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bernard	I-pers
to	O
desire	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
&	O
the	O
other	O
Subscribers	O
,	O
wd	O
:	O
send	O
their	O
Subscriptions	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sd	O
:	O
wait	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
poſsibly	O
could	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Clifton	B-place
,	O
to	O
thank	O
her	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
with	O
by	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
:	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
