TOKEN	NE
Caserta	B-place
Janry	O
.	O
28	O
th	O
1779	O
I	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
your	O
Mind	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
composed	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
was	O
so	O
obliging	O
as	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
inclose	O
a	O
short	O
letter	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
expreſs	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Affection	O
&	O
the	O
part	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
which	O
concerns	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
you	O
can	O
never	O
doubt	O
of	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
constant	O
inhabitants	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
December	O
excepting	O
one	O
day	O
on	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
dinner	O
to	O
forty	O
four	O
English	O
who	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
The	O
Court	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
little	O
Court	O
consisting	O
of	O
one	O
Lady	O
in	O
waiting	O
,	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Bedchamber	O
,	O
the	O
Grand	O
Chambellan	O
,	O
the	O
Grand	O
Veneur	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
First	O
Minister	O
)	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
only	O
come	O
occasionally	O
--	O
the	O
English	O
are	O
not	O
pleas	O
'd	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
distant	O
from	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
as	O
they	O
all	O
come	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
every	O
time	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
Caserta	B-place
which	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
convenience	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Auberge	O
which	O
they	O
can	O
go	O
to	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
pays	O
his	O
Court	O
&	O
keeps	O
his	O
health	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
&	O
almost	O
constant	O
exercise	O
he	O
uses	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
seldom	O
miſses	O
going	O
out	O
shooting	O
with	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
when	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
thinks	O
the	O
Sport	O
will	O
be	O
good	O
which	O
is	O
usually	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
--	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
dine	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
comes	O
home	O
just	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
returns	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Palace	O
where	O
he	O
plays	O
at	O
a	O
Game	O
called	O
Biribis	O
wth-	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
&	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sup	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
--	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
footing	O
is	O
a	O
curious	O
one	O
for	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Minister	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bourbon	O
family	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
makes	O
it	O
still	O
more	O
particular	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
&	O
Spanish	O
Minister	O
come	O
but	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
a	O
formal	O
way	O
,	O
&	O
usually	O
come	O
together	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
keep	O
one	O
another	O
in	O
Countenance	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
must	O
appear	O
very	O
strange	O
to	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
extraordinary	O
Court	O
in	O
Europe	B-place
,	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
Spanish	O
étiquette	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
no	O
étiquette	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
family	O
(	O
which	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
poor	O
little	O
Hereditary	O
Prince	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
&	O
died	O
was	O
as	O
extraordinary	O
as	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
he	O
perish	O
'd	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
near	O
two	O
hours	O
during	O
all	O
wch	O
.	O
time	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
little	O
Prince	O
&	O
in	O
so	O
feeling	O
&	O
affecting	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
(	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
of	O
the	O
changeableneſs	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
yet	O
could	O
not	O
refrain	O
from	O
tears	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
blow	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
recover	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
near	O
lying	O
in	O
.	O
--	O
in	O
this	O
Situation	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
remaind	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
her	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
three	O
weeks	O
was	O
as	O
gay	O
as	O
ever	O
&	O
even	O
laughing	O
upon	O
subjects	O
which	O
one	O
would	O
have	O
imagined	O
must	O
have	O
renew	O
'd	O
her	O
grief	O
--	O
since	O
this	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
lain	O
in	O
very	O
happily	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
intent	O
upon	O
nothing	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
getting	O
the	O
Rei	O
n	O
s	O
of	O
Government	O
intirely	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
hands	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
scheme	O
she	O
makes	O
a	O
rapid	O
progreſs	O
,	O
for	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
unused	O
to	O
any	O
serious	O
application	O
,	O
is	O
glad	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
tired	O
out	O
with	O
Memorials	O
,	O
&	O
Affairs	O
of	O
State	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
his	O
Gun	O
&	O
leave	O
the	O
termination	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
who	O
has	O
sufficient	O
Art	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
the	O
instrument	O
of	O
fulfilling	O
the	O
plans	O
he	O
has	O
himself	O
laid	O
--	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
has	O
not	O
decreas	O
'd	O
her	O
aſsiduity	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
affair	O
of	O
consequence	O
has	O
been	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
tho	O
'	O
still	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
plays	O
at	O
Biribis	O
every	O
evening	O
,	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
desisted	O
from	O
going	O
since	O
her	B-pers
My	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
by	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
desire	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
&	O
play	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
last	O
Night	O
&	O
is	O
gone	O
again	O
this	O
evening	O
after	O
Shooting	O
from	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
all	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
My	O
letter	O
was	O
to	O
paſs	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Neapolitan	O
Post	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
my	O
letter	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
enables	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
with	O
that	O
freedom	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
otherwise	O
dare	O
use	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
telling	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
trifling	O
events	O
which	O
happen	O
here	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
tire	O
&	O
not	O
interest	O
you	O
;	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
people	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
mention	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
good	O
fortune	O
which	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
Ldy	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
who	O
with	O
her	O
Lord	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
company	O
,	O
a	O
Prince	B-pers
Marsico	I-pers
a	O
favourite	O
of	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
putrid	O
fever	O
&	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
mention	O
'd	O
James	O
's	O
powder	O
to	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
&	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
with	O
the	O
directions	O
how	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
in	O
waiting	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
for	O
Prince	B-pers
Marsico	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Lady	O
in	O
waiting	O
either	O
lost	O
or	O
forgot	O
it	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
accidentally	O
known	O
in	O
Naples	B-place
that	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
intended	O
the	O
Prince	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
which	O
Ld	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
flew	O
to	O
Prince	B-pers
Marsico	I-pers
's	O
Palace	O
&	O
notwithstanding	O
repeated	O
denials	O
insisted	O
upon	O
admittance	O
,	O
tired	O
with	O
resisting	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
length	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Sick	O
room	O
where	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Patient	O
convuls	O
'd	O
&	O
Senseleſs	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Doctors	O
aſsuring	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
hours	O
to	O
live	O
,	O
--	O
he	O
then	O
propos	O
'd	O
the	O
powder	O
which	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
sooner	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
then	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
powder	O
with	O
succeſs	O
,	O
&	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
hours	O
the	O
Prince	B-pers
Marsico	I-pers
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
--	O
the	O
Pignatellis	O
(	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
)	O
full	O
of	O
gratitude	O
immediately	O
went	O
&	O
visited	O
Ly	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
&	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
they	O
intend	O
to	O
ask	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
receive	O
her	O
at	O
Court	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
return	O
for	O
the	O
obligation	O
they	O
are	O
under	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
but	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
doubtfull	O
if	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
who	O
knows	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
from	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
me	O
)	O
her	O
former	O
life	O
will	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
receive	O
her	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
publickly	O
here	O
with	O
the	O
D.	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
,	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
easy	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
channel	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
neither	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
myself	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
--	O
The	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Belmonte	I-pers
Sister	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
Count	B-pers
Pignatelli	I-pers
Minister	O
in	O
England	B-place
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
my	O
permiſsion	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
who	O
she	O
said	O
had	O
paid	O
great	O
Court	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
her	O
letter	O
is	O
curious	O
&	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
too	O
long	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
you	O
)	O
to	O
this	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
follow	O
her	O
inclination	O
,	O
as	O
no	O
civility	O
Ly	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
receiv	O
'd	O
could	O
ever	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
smallest	O
displeasure	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
likely	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
well	O
receiv	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
here	O
as	O
I	O
hear	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
clever	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
many	O
presents	O
a	O
method	O
which	O
has	O
great	O
weight	O
with	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
satisfied	O
with	O
being	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
from	O
the	B-place
Capital	I-place
having	O
time	O
here	O
for	O
many	O
occupations	O
which	O
are	O
perpetually	O
interrupted	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
the	O
greatest	O
inconvenience	O
I	O
feel	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
constant	O
application	O
sometimes	O
hurts	O
my	O
eyes	O
&	O
forces	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
a	O
book	O
often	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
interesting	O
paſsage	O
which	O
when	O
one	O
is	O
alone	O
is	O
a	O
real	O
mortification	O
--	O
at	O
these	O
moments	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
sending	O
a	O
wish	O
towards	O
England	B-place
,	O
&	O
thinking	O
how	O
happy	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
to	O
be	O
quietly	O
&	O
comfortably	O
settled	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
drive	O
away	O
the	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
at	O
present	O
any	O
likelihood	O
of	O
our	O
meeting	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
good	O
fortune	O
.	O
--	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
situation	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
your	O
good	O
sense	O
teaches	O
you	O
to	O
prize	O
it	O
&	O
I	O
see	O
with	O
pleasure	O
(	O
by	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
)	O
how	O
full	O
of	O
love	O
&	O
gratitude	O
your	O
heart	O
is	O
to	O
tThe	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
for	O
h	O
H	O
er	O
great	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
Our	O
Queen	B-pers
&	O
other	O
Queens	O
!	O
--	O
j'en	O
suis	O
temoin	O
--	O
if	O
ever	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Opportunity	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
dutifull	O
&	O
respectfull	O
both	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
to	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Grace	O
for	O
we	O
really	O
feel	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
very	O
soon	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
all	O
the	O
young	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
do	O
:	O
&	O
particularly	O
the	O
beautifull	O
little	O
Prince	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
--	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
handsome	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
joins	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
kind	O
love	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yr	O
very	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
CHamilton	B-pers
I	O
hope	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
sometimes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
her	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
which	O
pleas	O
'd	O
me	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
expreſs	O
great	O
family	O
happineſs	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
perfect	O
regard	O
,	O
friendship	O
&	O
esteem	O
for	O
Ld	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
