TOKEN	NE
Windsor	O
Castle	O
Feb	O
:	O
2	O
.	O
Accept	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
the	O
sincere	O
Congratulations	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Friend	O
upon	O
an	O
Event	O
which	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
must	O
afford	O
you	O
the	O
highest	O
degree	O
of	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
unites	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
these	O
Congratulations	O
which	O
we	O
beg	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
also	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
the	O
Bride	O
.	O
Our	O
settling	O
in	O
London	B-place
is	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
great	O
uncertainty	O
not	O
depending	O
upon	O
ourselves	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
before	O
the	O
middle	O
or	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
month	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
arrival	O
in	O
town	B-place
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
my	O
first	O
business	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
in	O
person	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
happy	O
occasion	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
with	O
real	O
regard	O
and	O
esteem	O
your	O
faithful	O
Servt	O
J.	B-pers
Sarum	I-pers
