TOKEN	NE
Buxton	B-place
9	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
1790	O
My	O
ever	O
Dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
relief	O
from	O
Bathing	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
certainly	O
better	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
pains	O
are	O
moved	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
quite	O
comfortable	O
except	O
from	O
a	O
few	O
twinges	O
in	O
my	O
Ancles	O
which	O
frighten	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
pain	O
is	O
mounted	O
from	O
the	O
lowest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
into	O
my	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
most	O
probably	O
will	O
vanish	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
Our	O
Louisa	B-pers
behaves	O
like	O
an	O
Angel	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
charming	O
Creature	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
perspire	O
after	O
Bathing	O
,	O
She	O
slept	O
with	O
Grandpapa	B-pers
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
amused	O
by	O
a	O
whispering	O
Conversation	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
great	O
friends	O
--	O
We	O
hope	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
&	O
pray	O
come	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
havg	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
Hair	O
cut	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
defer	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
undergo	O
that	O
Operation	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bad	O
news	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
will	O
distreſs	O
you	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
The	O
newspaper	O
came	O
about	O
5	O
Minutes	O
ago	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
an	O
Acct-	O
of	O
the	O
sudden	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Athol	I-pers
--	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
and	O
died	O
at	O
4	O
oClock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
s	O
House	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
--	O
Pray	O
bring	O
tomorrow	O
another	O
flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
talkg	O
of	O
E	B-pers
:	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
said	O
nobody	O
knew	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
--	O
he	O
adverted	O
to	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
which	O
he	O
laught	O
at	O
&	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
contracted	O
a	O
habit	O
like	O
her	O
late	O
Aunt	O
M	B-pers
of	O
appea	O
ring	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
to	O
attract	O
peoples	O
attention	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
thrō	O
it	O
all	O
--	O
he	O
hinted	O
at	O
something	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
explain	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
marked	O
out	O
somebody	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
--	O
He	O
always	O
speaks	O
differently	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
&	O
thinks	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
resolution	O
never	O
to	O
marry	O
--	O
Louisa	B-pers
says	O
“	O
tell	O
Chevr	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
am	O
here	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
&	O
see	O
me	O
when	O
Mamma	B-pers
&	O
Aunts	O
come	O
&	O
he	O
must	O
see	O
the	O
fine	O
Houses	O
thats	O
all	O
&	O
if	O
he	O
pleases	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
Talian	O
leſsion	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
”	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
riding	O
out	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
a	O
mio	O
fratello	O
e	O
a	O
mia	O
sorella	O
&	O
credere	O
che	O
io	O
sono	O
Molto	O
Affettuosamente	O
Vostro	O
felici	O
e	O
Vostro	O
fedele	O
Marito	O
JD——	B-pers
13,14	O
kiſses	O
from	O
Louisa	B-pers
Dickenson	B-pers
