TOKEN	NE
Wandsworth	B-place
hill	I-place
Augst	O
.	O
23	O
d	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
happineſs	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
continued	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſsible	O
all	O
yesterday	O
&	O
eat	O
some	O
boiled	O
Chicken	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
appetite	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
night	O
&	O
begun	O
nursing	O
her	O
little	O
Boy	O
this	O
morning	O
very	O
succeſsfully	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
high	O
spirits	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
goes	O
on	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
wish	O
--	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
little	O
Boy	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
strong	O
likeneſs	O
between	O
him	O
&	O
George	B-pers
--	O
Papa	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
his	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
excuse	O
haste	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
your	O
most	O
affecte-	O
&	O
c	O
Elizath	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
