TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
letter	O
that	O
has	O
just	O
now	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
reduces	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
absolute	O
despair	O
;	O
the	O
continual	O
intense	O
pain	O
that	O
my	O
dear	O
Daugr=	O
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
during	O
this	O
calamitous	O
illneſs	O
has	O
brought	O
on	O
a	O
twisting	O
of	O
the	O
intestines	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
apprehend	O
must	O
terminate	O
in	O
a	O
mortification	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
repent	O
not	O
having	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
her	O
illneſs	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
demonstrate	O
no	O
real	O
intelligence	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
at	O
least	O
show	O
that	O
my	O
affection	O
is	O
without	O
bounds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
ample	O
supply	O
in	O
hand	O
to	O
furnish	O
every	O
neceſsary	O
expence	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
can	O
give	O
you	O
proper	O
information	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
wish	O
that	O
the	O
Physicians	O
shoud	O
be	O
paid	O
most	O
liberally	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
remain	O
in	O
cruel	O
agitation	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
as	O
no	O
Post	O
leaves	O
London	B-place
till	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
strength	O
but	O
to	O
add	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
remain	O
your	O
most	O
faithful	O
&	O
obliged	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bath	B-place
May	O
2	O
7	O
6	O
th	O
1810	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
May	O
1810	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
