TOKEN	NE
usual	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
provoked	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
prevented	O
first	O
ye	O
Porter	O
--	O
After	O
tea	O
I	O
strummed	O
famously	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
&	O
having	O
no	O
Ears	O
however	O
to	O
offend	O
but	O
my	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
disturbed	O
the	O
Rats	O
from	O
their	O
quarters	O
--	O
after	O
supper	O
wch	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
much	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
amongst	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
friendly	O
nature	O
“	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
be	O
candid	O
and	O
honest	O
&	O
to	O
say	O
at	O
once	O
that	O
the	O
Ladies	O
here	O
were	O
not	O
pleased	O
wh-	O
his	O
Juvenilities	O
when	O
last	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
ones	O
prated	O
&	O
the	O
old	O
Hens	O
became	O
very	O
broody	O
&	O
wrote	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
possesssion	O
of	O
&	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
laughed	O
heartily	O
on	O
finding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Semper	O
idem	O
&	O
pleaded	O
--	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1805	O
23	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Woburn	B-place
--	O
his	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
cold	O
as	O
the	O
weather	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
--	O
the	O
She	O
Grace	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
almost	O
naked	O
--	O
I	O
paſsed	O
her	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
dismiſsed	O
at	O
ten	O
yards	O
&	O
bowed	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
looked	O
sour	O
&	O
just	O
inclined	O
her	O
empty	O
head	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lady	O
with	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
decently	O
dreſsed	O
the	O
Dſs	O
.	O
wore	O
nankeen	O
Gaiters	O
that	O
came	O
high	O
up	O
the	O
Legs	O
Her	O
under	O
Garment	O
was	O
White	O
&	O
very	O
thin	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
occasionally	O
descended	O
below	O
the	O
knees	O
when	O
the	O
Wind	O
permitted	O
&	O
a	O
crimson	O
shawl	O
drawn	O
round	O
her	O
shoulders	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Park	O
a	O
person	O
overtook	O
me	O
(	O
Mr.	B-pers
G	I-pers
)	O
&	O
said	O
Sir	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Ds	O
dreſs	O
I	O
ansd	O
.	O
yes	O
--	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
mouth	O
&	O
shewed	O
his	O
white	O
teeth	O
in	O
astonishment	O
,	O
why	O
Sir	O
Ill	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
neither	O
shift	O
nor	O
under	O
petticoat	O
that	O
reached	O
to	O
her	O
knees	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
wind	O
blew	O
against	O
her	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
Every	O
thing	O
--	O
surely	O
no	O
modest	O
or	O
virtuous	O
Woman	O
could	O
dreſs	O
so	O
indecently	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
as	O
”	O
——	O
do	O
n't	O
read	O
this	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
L——	I-pers
After	O
tea	O
scraped	O
away	O
like	O
Fury	O
--	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
--	O
poor	O
Fury	O
is	O
disconsolate	O
&	O
fine	O
Lady	O
like	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
call	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
she	O
pricks	O
up	O
her	O
Ears	O
&	O
looks	O
about	O
her	O
appetite	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
guardianship	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Pincher	O
&	O
attends	O
me	O
--	O
24	O
--	O
a	O
great	O
&	O
dirty	O
Fair	O
here	O
--	O
Yrs	O
.	O
is	O
just	O
arrived	O
and	O
delighted	O
me	O
wth-	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
yr-	O
journey	O
&	O
your	O
arrival	O
at	O
C	B-place
--	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
Style	O
--	O
go	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
continue	O
the	O
Delight	O
of	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Lowndes	O
again	O
on	O
Saturday	O
--	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Stockgrove	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
You	O
depend	O
on	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
stay	O
very	O
long	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
turn	O
the	O
House	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
&	O
I	O
wish	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
would	O
turn	O
the	O
Windows	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
--	O
this	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
Winslow	O
--	O
that	O
house	O
was	O
built	O
by	O
Government	O
in	O
Queen	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
s	O
Reign	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lowndes	I-pers
was	O
high	O
in	O
office	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
contrived	O
&	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
lined	O
with	O
Oak	O
wch	O
.	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
dismal	O
appearance	O
&	O
when	O
the	O
Sun	O
penetrates	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
oak	O
is	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
wood	O
itself	O
much	O
injured	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
unpardonable	O
Sin	O
to	O
hint	O
even	O
at	O
the	O
difference	O
a	O
little	O
paint	O
wd	O
.	O
make	O
--	O
s	O
trange	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
new	O
saſh	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
frames	O
before	O
were	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
my	O
arm	O
--	O
ten	O
years	O
hence	O
he	O
may	O
paint	O
the	O
rest	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
sumptuous	O
hospitality	O
there	O
indeed	O
like	O
the	O
good	O
old	O
english	O
times	O
as	O
they	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
improperly	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Enjoyments	O
then	O
were	O
mainly	O
animal	O
eating	O
&	O
drinking	O
&	O
we	O
contrive	O
to	O
fill	O
our	O
stomacks	O
in	O
these	O
grumbling	O
days	O
of	O
taxation	O
&	O
are	O
not	O
plagued	O
with	O
so	O
innumerable	O
a	O
body	O
of	O
Toadys	O
,	O
besides	O
Society	O
is	O
on	O
a	O
different	O
footing	O
--	O
if	O
the	O
times	O
dont	O
grow	O
worse	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
grumble	O
--	O
from	O
India	B-place
on	O
a	O
comfortable	O
seperate	O
Maintenance/	O
pretty	O
doing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Isakey	I-pers
is	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
Mr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
--	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Aunt	O
in	O
town	B-place
&	O
she	O
seemed	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
&	O
she	O
despairs	O
of	O
ever	O
receiving	O
Louisa	B-pers
s	O
promised	O
Letter	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
warn	O
you	O
I	O
like	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
are	O
quite	O
brave	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
Be	O
happy	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
feel	O
contented	O
--	O
Love	O
to	O
L	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
P	B-pers
.	I-pers
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
affy	O
J.D——	B-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
84	O
High	O
Street	O
Cheltenham	B-place
Glocesters-	B-place
Louisa	B-pers
feels	O
greatly	O
as	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
suppose	O
she	O
would	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
aſsembly	O
,	O
where	O
Miſses	O
who	O
are	O
always	O
seen	O
have	O
the	O
advantage	O
--	O
M	O
r	O
&	O
M	O
rs	O
Bail	O
s	O
ingle	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Cheltenham	B-place
Glocestershire	B-place
