TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Your	O
very	O
obliging	O
letter	O
of	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
came	O
safe	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
agreeable	O
retreat	O
near	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
settled	O
since	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
present	O
no	O
house	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
may	O
probably	O
get	O
one	O
before	O
the	O
winter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
informed	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
freed	O
yourself	O
from	O
a	O
certain	O
embaraſsment	O
;	O
you	O
stood	O
upon	O
false	O
ground	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
danger	O
and	O
difficulties	O
were	O
entirely	O
on	O
your	O
side	O
;	O
such	O
a	O
situation	O
was	O
not	O
new	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
happened	O
a	O
similar	O
instance	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
family	O
more	O
than	O
fifty	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
foundation	O
of	O
much	O
perplexity	O
and	O
of	O
little	O
credit	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
interested	O
in	O
your	O
happineſs	O
and	O
have	O
therefore	O
no	O
difficulty	O
in	O
offering	O
my	O
sentiments	O
without	O
reserve	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
mention	O
'd	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
imagined	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
amiſs	O
in	O
not	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
notification	O
of	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
her	O
second	O
son	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
letting	O
her	O
know	O
,	O
in	O
very	O
civil	O
terms	O
what	O
my	O
sentiments	O
sentiments	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
instance	O
of	O
my	O
having	O
been	O
neglected	O
;	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
little	O
attention	O
I	O
was	O
honor	O
'd	O
with	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
I	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
worthy	O
of	O
its	O
continuance	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
system	O
was	O
recurr	O
'd	O
to	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
did	O
what	O
was	O
proper	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
offering	O
my	O
congratulations	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
answer	O
.	O
What	O
their	O
ideas	O
or	O
intentions	O
may	O
be	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
easily	O
conjecture	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
as	O
yet	O
very	O
undecided	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
themselves	O
struck	O
with	O
the	O
propriety	O
of	O
having	O
some	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
interests	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
so	O
nearly	O
connected	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
receive	O
little	O
trouble	O
from	O
my	O
importunities	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
now	O
too	O
old	O
to	O
engage	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
train	O
of	O
solicitations	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
my	O
situation	O
and	O
pretensions	O
are	O
already	O
fully	O
understood	O
,	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
meanneſs	O
to	O
preſs	O
the	O
subject	O
upon	O
them	O
with	O
any	O
further	O
recommendatory	O
arguments	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
describe	O
my	O
alarms	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
frightful	O
tumults	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
something	O
similar	O
might	O
have	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
,	O
but	O
fortunately	O
proper	O
precautions	O
were	O
opportunely	O
interposed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
on	O
improving	O
and	O
beautifying	O
my	O
little	O
Villa	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
great	O
merit	O
from	O
its	O
charming	O
situation	O
,	O
indeed	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
surpaſs	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
plantations	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
making	O
are	O
already	O
so	O
well	O
advanced	O
as	O
nearly	O
to	O
answer	O
their	O
design	O
;	O
the	O
summer	O
has	O
hitherto	O
been	O
so	O
remarkably	O
cold	O
that	O
the	O
country	O
has	O
been	O
leſs	O
agreeable	O
than	O
it	O
usually	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
season	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
desires	O
to	O
offer	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
M	O
rs	O
.	O
Stratford	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
but	O
proposes	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
August	O
upon	O
some	O
family	O
business	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
my	O
Son	O
from	O
school	O
to	O
paſs	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
leisure	O
moment	O
,	O
Adieu	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
sincerely	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectt	O
.	O
Uncle	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Latour	O
--	O
Clontarf	B-place
near	O
Dublin	B-place
June	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
F.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
June	O
25	O
:	O
1780	O
.	O
