TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Rev	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
constant	O
hurry	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
since	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
coud	O
have	O
prevented	O
my	O
returning	O
you	O
thanks	O
much	O
sooner	O
for	O
your	O
most	O
obliging	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
sincerity	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
really	O
distreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
in	O
person	O
that	O
my	O
sentiments	O
towards	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
coud	O
wish	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
felt	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
by	O
the	O
accounts	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
conduct	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
more	O
zealous	O
friend	O
than	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
whose	O
judgement	O
can	O
be	O
better	O
relied	O
upon	O
;	O
he	O
informs	O
me	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
his	O
party	O
to	O
Spa	B-place
.	O
Your	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
danger	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
made	O
me	O
tremble	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
sufferd	O
by	O
the	O
frights	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
weak	O
nerves	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
is	O
amazingly	O
improved	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
without	O
partiality	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Girl	O
with	O
many	O
accomplishments	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
your	O
steadineſs	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
preparing	O
for	O
our	O
departure	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
House	O
in	O
Dublin	B-place
for	O
one	O
year	O
&	O
propose	O
to	O
paſs	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
at	O
my	O
Living	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
indulgence	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
residence	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
as	O
yet	O
experienced	O
the	O
least	O
favor	O
or	O
aſsistance	O
from	O
my	O
Friends	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
owing	O
entirely	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartry	I-pers
that	O
I	O
am	O
re	O
duced	O
to	O
this	O
disagreeable	O
neceſsity	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shoud	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
h	O
a	O
ve	O
yielded	O
to	O
were	O
it	O
not	O
from	O
the	O
attention	O
due	O
on	O
my	O
part	O
to	O
my	O
Children	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
in	O
Ireland	B-place
she	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
heartily	O
disposed	O
to	O
obey	O
her	O
comm	O
ands	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
never	O
meant	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
smallest	O
uneasineſs	O
,	O
n	O
or	O
had	O
I	O
any	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
busineſs	O
that	O
occasion	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
expreſs	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
regret	O
having	O
miſsd	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
hardly	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
another	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
real	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
knowing	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
good	O
connections	O
&	O
with	O
persons	O
that	O
are	O
sensible	O
of	O
your	O
merit	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
independence	O
is	O
the	O
prime	O
object	O
in	O
this	O
life	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
when	O
you	O
inform	O
of	O
any	O
decisive	O
step	O
Daughter	O
desire	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
affectionate	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affect	O
.	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bath	B-place
May	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
1776	O
.	O
