TOKEN	NE
4	O
August	O
1789	O
Bath	B-place
I	O
sent	O
you	O
a	O
Letter	O
yesterday	O
&	O
informed	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
s	O
.	O
at	O
7	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
returned	O
from	O
some	O
country	O
expedition	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
excuse	O
,	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
&	O
her	O
young	O
Ladies	O
who	O
sang	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
duet	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
played	O
a	O
very	O
difficult	O
Concerto	O
on	O
the	O
Harpsichord	O
with	O
very	O
great	O
execution	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
my	O
Taste	O
is	O
improved	O
or	O
vitiated	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
confeſs	O
that	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
Harpsichord	O
Leſson	O
does	O
not	O
gratify	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
dislike	O
to	O
the	O
instrument	O
--	O
&	O
what	O
is	O
commonly	O
called	O
fine	O
playing	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
an	O
expeditious	O
jumbling	O
of	O
Keys	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilberforce	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
going	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
--	O
the	O
company	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
ten	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H.y——	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
supper	O
--	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
a	O
meſsage	O
came	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
with	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
supper	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
declined	O
of	O
course	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
till	O
near	O
eleven	O
&	O
then	O
called	O
at	O
the	B-pers
Rundells	I-pers
&	O
staid	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
12	O
--	O
As	O
no	O
Letters	O
arrived	O
yesterday	O
from	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
doubts	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
construction	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
upon	O
my	O
letter	O
which	O
gave	O
you	O
an	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
inflammation	O
in	O
my	O
Leg	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
talked	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
might	O
fix	O
your	O
resolution	O
--	O
however	O
as	O
the	O
weather	O
seemed	O
so	O
fine	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
better	O
not	O
to	O
defer	O
my	O
journey	O
or	O
rather	O
little	O
tour	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
at	O
no	O
short	O
distance	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
accordingly	O
this	O
morning	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
Set	O
out	O
for	O
Bristol	B-place
and	O
called	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
--	O
when	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
chosen	O
an	O
unlucky	O
time	O
as	O
Hannah	B-pers
was	O
going	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
mentioned	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilberforce	I-pers
's	O
intention	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
must	O
be	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
eldest	O
only	O
,	O
Patty	B-pers
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
the	O
School	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
wells	O
--	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonhouse	I-pers
seemed	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
poor	O
Creature	O
he	O
has	O
suffered	O
excruciating	O
pain	O
lately	O
in	O
having	O
a	O
carbuncle	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
mortified	O
he	O
never	O
closed	O
his	O
Eyes	O
for	O
ten	O
days	O
&	O
nights	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
48	O
hours	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
sleep	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
medicine	O
for	O
his	O
old	O
malady	O
the	O
stone	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
afraid	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
gain	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
head	O
--	O
he	O
complains	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Madeira	O
every	O
day	O
which	O
confuses	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
spoke	O
with	O
great	O
affection	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
&	O
regard	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
happy	O
it	O
made	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
improved	O
in	O
my	O
Looks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
500	O
Pr	O
.	O
Cent	O
better	O
than	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
2	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
a	O
publication	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Brownes	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
wrote	O
in	O
our	O
Language	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
the	O
Subject	O
is	O
the	O
negligence	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
&	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Lady	O
was	O
better	O
--	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
distreſs	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
&	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
illness	O
wch	O
.	O
proved	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Bilious	O
Fever	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
--	O
I	O
was	O
charmed	O
with	O
the	O
view	O
of	O
Clifton	B-place
from	O
an	O
opposite	O
hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Exeter	B-place
road	O
,	O
which	O
commands	O
a	O
short	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
the	O
rocks	O
,	O
the	O
scattered	O
houses	O
on	O
Clifton	B-place
,	O
part	O
of	O
Bristol	B-place
&	O
the	O
adjacent	O
country	O
all	O
round	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
cordial	O
reception	O
from	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
Patty	B-pers
who	O
was	O
arrived	O
here	O
before	O
me	O
--	O
This	O
little	O
Cottage	O
is	O
exactly	O
what	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
find	O
--	O
very	O
neat	O
prettily	O
furnished	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
rooms	O
small	O
--	O
the	O
little	O
pleasure	O
ground	O
very	O
well	O
planted	O
with	O
shrubs	O
,	O
&	O
an	O
exceſsive	O
pretty	O
Roothouse	O
about	O
50	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
generally	O
breakfast	O
&	O
drink	O
tea	O
it	O
has	O
no	O
pretensions	O
&	O
is	O
exactly	O
what	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
in	O
our	O
grove	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
made	O
at	O
very	O
little	O
expence	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Sketch	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
the	O
house	O
--	O
We	O
waited	O
dinner	O
an	O
hour	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wilberforce	I-pers
but	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Hannah	B-pers
very	O
low	O
She	O
attributed	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
Accident	O
that	O
had	O
happened	O
which	O
had	O
damped	O
all	O
their	O
summer	O
enjoyment	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
month	O
that	O
the	O
Sisters	O
can	O
live	O
together	O
here	O
--	O
a	O
Lady	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
a	O
first	O
visit	O
was	O
overturned	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Phaeton	O
(	O
luckily	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
rivulet	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
nearly	O
suffocated	O
by	O
the	O
Mud	O
&	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
injured	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
turned	O
in	O
bed	O
for	O
3	O
weeks	O
--	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
,	O
apparently	O
dead	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
upon	O
a	O
litter	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
terrible	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Sisters	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
only	O
one	O
spare	O
bed	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
exert	O
themselves	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
Husband	O
s	O
spirits	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
almost	O
distracted	O
--	O
Patty	B-pers
exerted	O
herself	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
of	O
course	O
very	O
agreeable	O
--	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
s	O
coming	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
with	O
great	O
glee	O
--	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
seemed	O
very	O
cool	O
upon	O
that	O
Subject	O
--	O
I	O
said	O
:	O
“	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
of	O
course	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
meet	O
her	O
.	O
”	O
No	O
,	O
She	O
knows	O
my	O
summer	O
engagements	O
and	O
is	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
excuse	O
me	O
”	O
--	O
this	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
odd	O
--	O
has	O
there	O
been	O
an	O
Eclairciſsement	O
here	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
“	O
probably	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
there	O
at	O
your	O
return	O
“	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
uncertain	O
”	O
which	O
was	O
repeated	O
--	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
on	O
Acct	O
.	O
of	O
Health	O
&	O
I	O
disengaged	O
--	O
casual	O
engagements	O
would	O
be	O
set	O
aside	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
--	O
5	O
/	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
a	O
Mr-	B-pers
——	I-pers
who	O
's	O
name	O
I	O
dont	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
recollect	O
came	O
to	O
breakfast	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
brother	O
to	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
who	O
has	O
wrote	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
the	O
Abolition	O
of	O
the	O
Slave	O
Trade	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
subject	O
very	O
near	O
Hannah	B-pers
's	O
heart	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
nothing	O
else	O
was	O
talked	O
of	O
--	O
a	O
thousand	O
instances	O
of	O
barbarity	O
were	O
spoken	O
of	O
,	O
wch	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
horror	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
a	O
human	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
diabolical	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
came	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
miles	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
off	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
s	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
an	O
enthusiast	O
in	O
the	O
cause	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
written	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
thing	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
it	O
Bishop	O
Bonner	O
's	O
Ghost	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
a	O
compliment	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	B-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
--	O
in	O
forming	O
a	O
confession	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
--	O
She	O
wrote	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
's	O
who	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
--	O
&	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
printing	O
it	O
at	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
--	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
excuse	O
me	O
for	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
that	O
the	O
Roses	O
Strawberries	O
&	O
Cowslips	O
did	O
not	O
always	O
blow	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
delightful	O
in	O
Season	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
prefixed	O
a	O
print	O
of	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
--	O
a	O
few	O
copies	O
were	O
reserved	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
the	O
author	O
.	O
--	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Leave	O
with	O
many	O
civil	O
things	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
arrived	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
s	O
at	O
2	O
--	O
I	O
traveled	O
thrō	O
a	O
delightful	O
Country	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
friendly	O
reception	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
F——	I-pers
who	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
bilious	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
very	O
civil	O
&	O
attentive	O
--	O
6	O
/	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
house	O
where	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
enjoys	O
retirement	O
--	O
in	O
some	O
respects	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pleasant	O
situation	O
--	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
country	O
and	O
beautiful	O
views	O
from	O
its	O
neighborhood	O
--	O
but	O
11	O
miles	O
from	O
market	O
&	O
post	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
dear	O
&	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
on	O
any	O
Acct	O
.	O
/	O
6	O
/	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
ride	O
upon	O
the	O
downs	O
which	O
command	O
an	O
extensive	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Severn	O
covered	O
with	O
Ships	O
&	O
small	O
veſsels	O
&	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
prospect	O
of	O
the	O
Welsh	O
Coast	O
,	O
&	O
Glocestershire	B-place
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
me	O
the	O
Story	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fust	I-pers
's	O
elopement	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
blackest	O
affair	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
--	O
/7/	O
at	O
one	O
oClock	O
to	O
day	O
I	O
left	O
Capenor	O
Lodge	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
wished	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
longer	O
&	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
complied	O
with	O
her	O
desire	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
divest	O
my	O
self	O
of	O
my	O
anxiety	O
about	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
already	O
prolonged	O
my	O
Tour	O
a	O
day	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
intended	O
--	O
at	O
Clifton	B-place
I	O
accidentally	O
met	O
Miſs	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
's	O
Dr.	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
's	O
nieces	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
Milnes	I-pers
&	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
looking	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
uneasy	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
flushed	O
&	O
feverish	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M——	I-pers
who	O
does	O
not	O
yet	O
admit	O
Strangers	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
--	O
he	O
poor	O
man	O
was	O
but	O
indifferent	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
keeps	O
up	O
his	O
Spirits	O
wonderfully	O
--	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
&	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
many	O
kind	O
things	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
to	O
compliment	O
you	O
upon	O
my	O
good	O
looks	O
--	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
Ladies	O
at	O
their	O
Lodging	O
--	O
the	O
set	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
pleasant	O
one	O
to	O
me	O
they	O
seemed	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
Tea	O
--	O
but	O
proceeded	O
homewards	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
receiving	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Int	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
too	O
which	O
I	O
kiſsed	O
20	O
times	O
--	O
Indeed	O
my	O
dearest	O
Wife	O
--	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
parted	O
any	O
more	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
bear	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
a	O
separation	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
no	O
earthly	O
consideration	O
can	O
make	O
me	O
any	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
yr-	O
company	O
--	O
two	O
hearts	O
,	O
so	O
firmly	O
&	O
so	O
affy	O
.	O
united	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
in	O
every	O
sense	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
dearly	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
in	O
person	O
very	O
soon	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
's	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
word	O
that	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
on	O
Monday	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
come	O
leisurely	O
--	O
to	O
Worcester	B-place
the	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
to	O
Birmingham	B-place
&	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Eveg-	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
ye-	O
happineſs	O
of	O
embracing	O
you	O
--	O
if	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
shd	O
.	O
not	O
be	O
wet	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
Mira	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
arrives	O
there	O
at	O
8	O
oClock	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
ride	O
home	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
save	O
me	O
7/6	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
fond	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
from	O
Buxton	B-place
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
sleep	O
within	O
six	O
Miles	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Mary	B-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
not	O
come	O
yet	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
my	O
Sisters	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
vary	O
the	O
Scene	O
--	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
turn	O
out	O
well	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
David	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
is	O
here	O
--	O
I	O
like	O
him	O
--	O
there	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
seamanlike	O
Bluntneſs	O
about	O
him	O
--	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
most	O
Affy	O
.	O
&	O
faithfully	O
your	O
JD	B-pers
The	O
harvest	O
is	O
begun	O
&	O
there	O
are	O
yet	O
many	O
hundred	O
acres	O
of	O
Graſs	O
uncut	O
--	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
now	O
intensely	O
hot	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
No	O
Thunder	O
at	O
all	O
My	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gaskell	I-pers
--	O
I	O
see	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
strutting	O
about	O
with	O
his	O
pupil	O
every	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
as	O
fair	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
be	O
provided	O
for	O
When	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
writes	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
how	O
surprised	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
see	O
two	O
,	O
00	O
,	O
s	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
might	O
alledge	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
mistake	O
of	O
mine	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
x	O
post	O
