TOKEN	NE
I	O
thank	O
you	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
acknowledging	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
knew	O
the	O
perplexity	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
about	O
my	O
future	O
destination	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
forgive	O
my	O
not	O
having	O
written	O
again	O
from	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
during	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
stay	O
,	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
's	O
making	O
a	O
visit	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
relieve	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
,	O
from	O
playing	O
company	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
really	O
was	O
not	O
equal	O
.	O
Till	O
the	O
question	O
in	O
your	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
escaped	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
mentioned	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
and	O
my	O
good	O
friend	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
are	O
extremely	O
kind	O
in	O
thinking	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
affairs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
still	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
torment	O
of	O
suspense	O
;	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
tells	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
points	O
to	O
be	O
adjusted	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
will	O
reengage	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
personal	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
left	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
answered	O
my	O
question	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
frank	O
and	O
handsome	O
manner	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
satisfied	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
nothing	O
better	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
What	O
these	O
points	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
alludes	O
to	O
,	O
neither	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
nor	O
I	O
,	O
can	O
tell	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
written	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
letters	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
are	O
written	O
scribbled	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
of	O
busineſs	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
explanatory	O
.	O
I	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
your	O
ideas	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
affairs	O
being	O
“	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
train	O
,	O
”	O
may	O
be	O
verified	O
:	O
of	O
your	O
kind	O
anxiety	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
with	O
real	O
affliction	O
that	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
melancholy	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
excellent	O
and	O
accomplished	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
.	O
God	O
grant	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
derive	O
experience	O
comfort	O
from	O
the	O
offices	O
of	O
friendship	O
she	O
will	O
receive	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
At	O
all	O
events	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
derive	O
satisfaction	O
from	O
bestowing	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
Cheltenham	B-place
(	O
which	O
agreed	O
so	O
well	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
before	O
)	O
will	O
counteract	O
the	O
ill	O
effects	O
I	O
should	O
otherwise	O
apprehend	O
from	O
so	O
trying	O
a	O
scene	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
find	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
able	O
to	O
recollect	O
former	O
transient	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
aſsure	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
wishes	O
for	O
her	O
recovery	O
.	O
Have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
.	O
--	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
chance	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
of	O
persuading	O
my	O
Father	O
to	O
an	O
excursion	O
to	O
Cheltenham	B-place
:	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
at	O
best	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
having	O
resided	O
in	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
poor	O
Mother	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
insuperable	O
bar	O
,	O
even	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
preference	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
goes	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
in	O
July	O
:	O
should	O
things	O
turn	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
delightful	O
opportunity	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
justice	O
,	O
kindly	O
anxious	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
pitied	O
on	O
the	O
score	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
family	O
;	O
for	O
Captain	B-pers
Halliday	I-pers
's	O
affairs	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
state	B-place
of	I-place
West-India	B-place
property	O
,	O
are	O
likewise	O
deranged	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
amiable	O
wife	O
is	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
seventh	O
approaching	O
.	O
For	O
Captain	B-pers
Rodney	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
's	O
husband	O
)	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
succeeded	O
in	O
getting	O
an	O
appointment	O
in	O
Ceylon	B-place
,	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
his	O
former	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
add	O
1200£	O
per	O
annum	O
to	O
his	O
income	O
.	O
With	O
all	O
her	O
gaieties	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
n	O
kind	O
excellent	O
Mother	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
J	I-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
;	O
and	O
accept	O
,	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
my	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
affectionate	O
interest	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
movements	O
are	O
very	O
uncertain	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
best	O
continue	O
to	O
direct	O
here	O
:	O
your	O
letters	O
will	O
be	O
immediately	O
forwarded	O
,	O
should	O
I	O
be	O
absent	O
.	O
Hoping	O
for	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
I	O
remain	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
your	O
sincerely	O
obliged	O
and	O
affectionate	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
N	O
o	O
:	O
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
May	O
19	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D.	I-pers
senr	I-pers
:	I-pers
?	O
P.S	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
such	O
an	O
interlined	O
scrawl	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
half	O
ashamed	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
from	O
haste	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
lose	O
the	O
Post	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
