TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
fly	O
towards	O
Leighton-house	O
im̄ediately	O
were	O
my	O
wings	O
at	O
Leisure	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
employd	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
;	O
and	O
must	O
do	O
more	O
by	O
and	O
bye	O
--	O
after	O
my	O
Hay	O
is	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
weather	O
would	O
permit	O
;	O
otherwise	O
,	O
the	O
Hay	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fumier	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
to	O
fulfil	O
my	O
Engagements	O
towards	O
the	O
west	O
.	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
flatter	O
yourselves	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
under	O
your	O
benign	O
roof	O
this	O
sum̄er	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
poſitively	O
swear	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
Embrace	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
settled	O
yet	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
nor	O
can	O
I	O
gueſs	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Great	O
Hall	O
at	O
Leighton	O
house	O
which	O
can	O
contain	O
all	O
the	O
Tackles	O
for	O
the	O
Squir	O
's	O
Sports	O
which	O
he	O
propoſes	O
to	O
enjoy	O
--	O
may	O
health	O
be	O
the	O
reward	O
for	O
the	O
fatigue	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
:	I-pers
destroy	O
'd	O
our	O
having	O
met	O
this	O
sum̄er	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
are	O
alive	O
and	O
inclined	O
,	O
to	O
enjoy	O
many	O
days	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
Lieghton	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Hampton	B-place
.	O
I	O
must	O
quit	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
time	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
own	O
--	O
so	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
Yours	O
for	O
Ever	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
London	B-place
June	O
July	O
the	O
1	O
:	O
1797	O
.	O
Excuse	O
hurry	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
1797	O
July	O
