TOKEN	NE
not	O
in	O
book	O
needs	O
typing	O
Nerots	O
Hotel	O
Kings	O
Street	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Wed	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
shoud	O
fly	O
to	O
you	O
immediately	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
engaged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Kingston	B-place
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Philipps	I-pers
family	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
again	O
on	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Sunday	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
excursion	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
&	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
enjoy	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
your	O
Society	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
affectionately	O
my	O
Dear	O
Niece	O
W.H	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
Sir	B-pers
Wm-	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Letters	O
