TOKEN	NE
Dover	O
Street	O
July	O
20	O
th	O
1792	O
After	O
the	O
flattering	O
Encouragement	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
they	O
left	O
London	B-place
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
I	O
wd	O
have	O
heard	O
long	O
since	O
of	O
their	O
Safe	O
Arrival	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
dickenson	I-pers
&	O
their	O
sweet	O
little	O
Girl	O
at	O
Taxall	B-place
--	O
but	O
having	O
long	O
expected	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
long	O
bien	O
disappointed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
to	O
Enquire	O
Why	O
you	O
have	O
thus	O
disappointed	O
me	O
&	O
why	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
soon	O
forgotten	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
Town	B-place
if	O
one	O
may	O
trust	O
to	O
the	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
is	O
quite	O
deserted	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Several	O
large	O
Parties	O
lately	O
--	O
&	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
famous	O
Cherubio	O
Sing	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
without	O
some	O
difficulty	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
so	O
much	O
more	O
however	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
most	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
Usually	O
turn	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
yr	O
Uncle	B-pers
&	O
Aunt	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
from	O
yr	O
.	O
Uncle	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
prosperous	O
journey	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
all	O
well	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
alarm	O
'd	O
about	O
you	O
fearing	O
that	O
you	O
or	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
had	O
relaps	O
'd	O
&	O
yr	O
old	O
complaints	O
return	O
'd	O
Since	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
yr	O
Physichin	O
--	O
how	O
delightful	O
the	O
Country	O
must	O
be	O
this	O
lovely	O
Weather	O
we	O
taste	O
it	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
in	O
the	O
Environs	O
of	O
London	O
Dr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
to	O
Tring	B-place
my	O
Mother	O
&	O
I	O
leave	O
London	B-place
the	O
.9	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
quiet	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
.	O
The	O
Federation	O
day	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
Balls	O
are	O
Equal	O
at	O
the	O
Clubs	O
if	O
the	O
Nobility	O
will	O
be	O
restor	O
'd	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
tell	O
Mr	B-pers
dickenson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
in	O
Spite	O
of	O
his	O
Loyalty	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
private	O
meetings	O
of	O
Levellers	O
&	O
there	O
were	O
Several	O
commemorations	O
about	O
England	B-place
but	O
no	O
disturbance	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
(	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
or	O
Cousin	O
s	O
)	O
into	O
Kent	B-place
--	O
she	O
still	O
hopes	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
next	O
Winter	O
in	O
Italy	B-place
--	O
where	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
find	O
all	O
the	O
Health	O
&	O
happineſs	O
she	O
Expects	O
we	O
had	O
see	O
take	O
leave	O
pleasant	O
party	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
where	O
I	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
miſs	O
'd	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
has	O
publish	O
'd	O
a	O
Novel	O
call	O
'd	O
Desmond	O
--	O
Her	O
chief	O
object	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
revolution	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
caus	O
'd	O
such	O
an	O
Universal	O
indignation	O
that	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
can	O
not	O
dispose	O
of	O
their	O
Copies	O
--	O
my	O
indignation	O
arises	O
from	O
the	O
Story	O
which	O
is	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
opinions	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
Subject	O
more	O
dangerous	O
than	O
another	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
makes	O
a	O
Woman	O
Aimiable	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
another	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
artfully	O
made	O
the	O
Lover	O
an	O
Angel	O
&	O
the	O
Husband	O
a	O
devil	O
.	O
but	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
dickenson	I-pers
what	O
Woman	O
who	O
Suffers	O
her	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
astray	O
from	O
her	O
duty	O
will	O
not	O
find	O
faults	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
poſeſs	O
'd	O
or	O
perfections	O
in	O
her	O
lover	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
Claims	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
very	O
homespun	O
doctrines	O
but	O
I	O
trust	O
they	O
are	O
honest	O
--	O
alth	O
'	O
o	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
allow	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
harm	O
--	O
so	O
the	O
Paſsion	O
is	O
carried	O
on	O
with	O
great	O
delicacy	O
--	O
yet	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
diſsimulation	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
very	O
lately	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Penningtons	O
&	O
writes	O
in	O
good	O
Spirits	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Palmerston	I-pers
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Blagden	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
are	O
all	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
on	O
their	O
road	O
to	O
Dover	B-place
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
Paris	B-place
--	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
this	O
morning	O
Lord	B-pers
Wycombe	I-pers
s	O
Match	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Raat	I-pers
is	O
certainly	O
off	O
the	O
Story	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
Six	O
thousand	O
a	O
year	O
might	O
be	O
settled	O
on	O
the	O
Title	O
--	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Children	O
,	O
such	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
Avarice	O
in	O
so	O
Young	O
a	O
Man	O
gives	O
leaves	O
a	O
Woman	O
little	O
reason	O
to	O
regret	O
him	O
--	O
A	O
dieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
Accept	O
yr	O
self	O
&	O
present	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
my	O
Humble	O
&	O
my	O
United	O
Compliments	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
--	O
Embrace	O
Cordially	O
yr	O
sweet	O
Child	O
&	O
may	O
she	O
be	O
the	O
Comfort	O
of	O
yr	O
old	O
Age	O
--	O
&	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
Subscribe	O
my	O
self	O
yr	O
most	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affect	O
Servt	O
.	O
DBloſset	B-pers
NB	O
:	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fair	O
opportunity	O
of	O
a	O
Cover	O
for	O
this	O
&	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
year	O
round	O
--	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C——r	I-pers
--	O
I	O
never	O
pay	O
money	O
with	O
more	O
pleasure	O
than	O
when	O
the	O
Post	O
office	O
is	O
the	O
gainer	O
--	O
