TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
word	O
in	O
my	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
various	O
circumstances	O
that	O
prevented	O
my	O
accepting	O
your	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
House	I-place
.	O
Immediately	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
more	O
effectually	O
prevented	O
from	O
thinking	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
a	O
second	O
very	O
severe	O
fit	O
of	O
illneſs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
now	O
recovering	O
,	O
but	O
much	O
reduced	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
weak	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
consultation	O
)	O
had	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
lose	O
no	O
time	O
in	O
securing	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
establishment	O
,	O
as	O
every	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
would	O
will	O
become	O
scarcer	O
and	O
consequently	O
dearer	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
advance	O
of	O
the	O
Season	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
accordingly	O
,	O
set	O
several	O
friends	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
illness	O
has	O
retarded	O
my	O
proceedings	O
,	O
by	O
impeding	O
my	O
seeking	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
soon	O
getting	O
suited	O
;	O
and	O
am	O
the	O
more	O
patient	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
with	O
prudence	O
,	O
remove	O
;	O
particularly	O
in	O
this	O
severe	O
weather	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Holman	I-pers
since	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
slightest	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
favourable	O
change	O
in	O
that	O
quarter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
pecuniary	O
busineſs	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
punctually	O
adhere	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
promises	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
will	O
afford	O
me	O
,	O
be	O
enabled	O
to	O
live	O
pretty	O
comfortably	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
very	O
moderate	O
scale	O
I	O
shall	O
adopt	O
.	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
am	O
once	O
settled	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
endeavour	O
to	O
tranquillize	O
and	O
occupy	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
owe	O
all	O
my	O
illneſs	O
to	O
agitation	O
and	O
grieving	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
never	O
were	O
such	O
letters	O
of	O
egotism	O
as	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
kind	O
family	O
wish	O
to	O
hear	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
wrote	O
me	O
word	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
obliging	O
letter	O
of	O
invitation	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
induced	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
have	O
escaped	O
the	O
Colds	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
generally	O
consequent	O
to	O
this	O
weather	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
present	O
them	O
my	O
kindest	O
regards	O
,	O
and	O
accept	O
them	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
conclude	O
,	O
as	O
writing	O
is	O
rather	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
Believe	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
your	O
truly	O
obliged	O
&	O
affectionat	O
e	O
Jane	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
.	I-place
Dec	O
:	O
8	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
Single	O
