TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
29	O
th	O
.	O
Decemr-	O
1779	O
I	O
must	O
begin	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
affair	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
settled	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
,	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
She	O
approved	O
of	O
the	O
Method	O
taken	O
&	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
wished	O
--	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
Merit	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
impoſsible	O
,	O
&	O
begged	O
that	O
no	O
further	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
on	O
either	O
Sides	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
meet	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
talk	O
more	O
fully	O
upon	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
chuse	O
to	O
put	O
upon	O
paper	O
--	O
indeed	O
the	O
theme	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
most	O
agreable	O
I	O
could	O
fix	O
upon	O
--	O
The	O
footing	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
with	O
your	O
Uncle	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
pleases	O
me	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
you	O
the	O
utmost	O
justice	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
he	O
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
flogged	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
Old	O
Ly-	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
means	O
anything	O
by	O
her	O
enquiries	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
it	O
was	O
intended	O
as	O
a	O
reproof	O
to	O
Ly-	B-pers
S——	I-pers
for	O
not	O
paying	O
her	O
proper	O
attention	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
once	O
in	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Atholl	O
's	O
treated	O
us	O
so	O
cavalierly	O
,	O
en	O
paſsant	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
propose	O
calling	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
should	O
my	O
duty	O
bring	O
m	O
y	O
e	O
to	O
London	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
send	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Us	O
.	O
They	O
'll	O
find	O
me	O
as	O
Saucy	O
as	O
they	O
can	O
be	O
Ly-	B-pers
S——	I-pers
could	O
not	O
poſsibly	O
comment	O
upon	O
my	O
Answer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
wrote	O
with	O
Spirit	O
,	O
I	O
wo'nt	O
allow	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
Saucy	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
a	O
word	O
You	O
people	O
about	O
Court	O
hardly	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
.	O
Nothing	O
is	O
yet	O
settled	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
Departure	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
orders	O
every	O
post	O
.	O
My	O
Company	O
consists	O
of	O
only	O
ten	O
persons	O
,	O
including	O
Serjts-	O
Corporals	O
&	O
Drummers	O
&	O
Private	O
s	O
.	O
Great	B-place
Marlow	I-place
,	O
Bucks	B-place
,	O
is	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
stationed	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
A.	I-pers
Oughton	I-pers
is	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
but	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mention	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
fear	O
from	O
that	O
circumstance	O
,	O
his	O
health	O
is	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
Apologies	O
,	O
but	O
write	O
when	O
convenient	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
upon	O
Ceremony	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
write	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
letter	O
having	O
renewed	O
Ideas	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
wish	O
to	O
forget	O
--	O
Poor	O
Lord	B-pers
DeLawarr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
concerned	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Yours	O
Affectionately	O
.	O
N——	B-pers
