TOKEN	NE
Your	O
obliging	O
,	O
Friendly	O
,	O
&	O
most	O
entertaining	O
letter	O
arrived	O
this	O
morning	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
returning	O
my	O
grateful	O
thanks	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
former	O
instances	O
of	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
&	O
attention	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
your	O
progreſs	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
pleasant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
it	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
gratified	O
with	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
your	O
friends	O
;	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
that	O
weather	O
along	O
with	O
every	O
other	O
favorable	O
circumstance	O
,	O
may	O
attend	O
you	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
conclusion	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
of	O
worth	O
&	O
judgement	O
,	O
feel	O
as	O
you	O
mention	O
,	O
for	O
Mrs-	B-pers
W.Walsingham	I-pers
;	O
who	O
will	O
want	O
now	O
every	O
support	O
&	O
comfort	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
her	O
spirits	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
,	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
hard	O
&	O
severe	O
treatment	O
she	O
meets	O
with	O
:	O
newspapers	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
hoped	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
,	O
look	O
into	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
friendly	O
concern	O
you	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
wch	O
I	O
shall	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
again	O
hearing	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
kind	O
desire	O
.	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
enquiries	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
I	O
may	O
now	O
say	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
!	O
tho	O
Monday	O
night	O
we	O
were	O
much	O
alarmed	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
who	O
was	O
taken	O
so	O
very	O
ill	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
us	O
all	O
apprehend	O
an	O
inflamation	O
in	O
his	O
bowell	O
,	O
;	O
his	O
complaint	O
is	O
now	O
entirely	O
removed	O
,	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
has	O
recovered	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
from	O
an	O
indisposition	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
this	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
too	O
is	O
now	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
shared	O
with	O
us	O
all	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
pleasures	O
&	O
advantages	O
we	O
derived	O
from	O
yours	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
agreeable	O
visit	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
politer	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
observation	O
of	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
wch	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
full	O
,	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
proceeding	O
only	O
from	O
my	O
partial	O
view	O
&	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
often	O
speaks	O
of	O
the	O
sweet	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
desires	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
her	O
a	O
Love	O
&	O
kiſs	O
for	O
her	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
indebted	O
to	O
you	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
to	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
kindly	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
does	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
..	O
we	O
both	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
particularly	O
delighted	O
wth	O
the	O
paragraph	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
De	I-pers
Vescie	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
welfare	O
every	O
one	O
must	O
be	O
interested	O
who	O
knows	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
&	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
you	O
left	O
here	O
,	O
desire	O
I	O
would	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
aſsure	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
of	O
their	O
sincere	O
regards	O
,	O
&	O
good	O
neſs	O
wishes	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
gratefull	O
sense	O
entertain	O
'd	O
here	O
of	O
the	O
friendly	O
&	O
polite	O
attention	O
,	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
both	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dearest	O
Madam	O
your	O
very	O
affecte	O
&	O
much	O
obliged	O
P	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
Wherwell	B-place
Novbr	O
ye	O
6	O
1788	O
