TOKEN	NE
Tingmouth	B-place
June	O
12	O
th	O
1785	O
A	O
few	O
moments	O
only	O
am	O
I	O
allowed	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Tidings	O
I	O
recd	O
:	O
from	O
you	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
last	O
night	O
--	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
most	O
sincerely	O
&	O
so	O
does	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
rejoice	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
happy	O
after	O
all	O
your	O
Agitation	O
&	O
Anxiety	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
before	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
say	O
when	O
I	O
W	O
e	O
shall	O
return	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
Places	O
to	O
see	O
&	O
c	O
wh	O
:	O
must	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
Weather	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
yr	O
:	O
Uncle	O
this	O
Morng	O
:	O
&	O
he	O
mentioned	O
you	O
with	O
great	O
Regard	O
--	O
Frederick	B-pers
is	O
talking	O
so	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
about	O
his	O
being	O
hungry	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
write	O
,	O
he	O
begs	O
to	O
be	O
Respectfully	O
remembered	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
w	O
h	O
:	O
I	O
must	O
add	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
my	O
Anger	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prettiest	O
Spot	O
in	O
the	O
known	O
World	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
do	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
here	O
--	O
&	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
o	O
for	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
's	O
sake	O
--	O
pray	O
make	O
our	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
Yrs	O
:	O
Affly	O
:	O
&	O
sincerely	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
Dinner	O
coming	O
we	O
leave	O
this	O
tomorrow	O
for	O
Exeter	B-place
--	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
happy	O
Dickenson	B-pers
is	O
so	O
near	O
You	O
--	O
just	O
now	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
.	O
PDartrey	B-pers
quite	O
well	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
well	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
troublesome	O
complaint	O
in	O
her	O
Nose	O
--	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
Patience	O
&	O
She	O
does	O
not	O
mind	O
it	O
--	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
kindest	O
Love	O
to	O
Dr	O
:	O
Thos	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Julia	B-pers
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
Death	O
'till	O
yesterday	O
--	O
Vesey	B-pers
begs	O
I	O
will	O
add	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
gathered	O
you	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Moſs	O
from	O
Stonehenge	B-place
--	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hancock	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vesey	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
London	B-place
