TOKEN	NE
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
March	O
4	O
th	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
On	O
mentioning	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
the	O
Pavillion	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
wishes	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	O
she	O
said	O
She	O
recollected	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
Town	B-place
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
desires	O
you	O
wd	O
.	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
various	O
&	O
new	O
Occupations	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
fully	O
employ	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
C.Finch	B-pers
