TOKEN	NE
Audley	O
End	O
Febry	O
9	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
dearest	O
I	O
received	O
yr	O
letter	O
this	O
morning	O
--	O
&	O
can	O
not	O
Suffer	O
a	O
Post	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
without	O
Thanking	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
most	O
heartily	O
do	O
I	O
Pray	O
to	O
almighty	O
God	O
for	O
ye	O
restoration	O
of	O
yr	O
Comfort	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
acted	O
so	O
wisely	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
the	O
dear	O
Child	O
of	O
yr	O
Hear	O
ts	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Convalescent	O
stile	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
highest	O
opinion	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
of	O
Northampton	B-place
his	O
reputation	O
is	O
unimpeach	O
'd	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
right	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Patient	O
immediately	O
under	O
his	O
Eye	O
.	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
this	O
in	O
Time	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
&	O
Scene	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
all	O
good	O
--	O
besides	O
a	O
Sound	O
Constitution	O
free	O
from	O
all	O
fr	O
s	O
--	O
a	O
well	O
form	O
'd	O
figure	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
bleſs	O
'd	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
disposition	O
.	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
difficulty	O
's	O
to	O
Struggle	O
with	O
but	O
this	O
t	O
y	O
Cold	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
taken	O
too	O
fast	O
a	O
hold	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
time	O
so	O
uncommonly	O
well	O
brought	O
up	O
as	O
to	O
hours	O
--	O
Eating	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
(	O
for	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
indulg	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
Spoyl	O
'd	O
Child	O
)	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
Greatest	O
advantages	O
both	O
to	O
yr	O
selves	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
forbearances	O
,	O
which	O
cd	O
t	O
other	O
Children	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
more	O
thought	O
of	O
by	O
her	O
--	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
add	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
--	O
which	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
that	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
aſsistance	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
command	O
me	O
&	O
depend	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
if	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Northampton	B-place
could	O
ease	O
yr	O
attentions	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
a	O
lodging	O
--	O
in	O
short	O
any	O
thing	O
--	O
&	O
every	O
thing	O
will	O
I	O
do	O
most	O
willingly	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
comfort	O
or	O
Service	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
News	O
I	O
hear	O
--	O
imprimis	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Roxburgh	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
B——	I-pers
s	O
.	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
report	O
that	O
the	O
definitive	O
Treaty	O
is	O
arrived	O
--	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Consolation	O
to	O
the	O
largest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
only	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
lost	O
their	O
Places	O
will	O
Sulk	O
--	O
a	O
report	O
also	O
of	O
instability	O
--	O
Pitt	B-pers
has	O
been	O
at	O
Wickham	B-pers
with	O
Lord	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Walmer	B-place
--	O
if	O
he	O
des	O
ts	O
after	O
behaving	O
so	O
well	O
--	O
we	O
can	O
only	O
repeat	O
,	O
(	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
add	O
we	O
have	O
often	O
experienc	O
'd	O
)	O
Oh	O
how	O
faillible	O
is	O
human	O
Nature	O
--	O
&	O
how	O
uncertain	O
,	O
are	O
human	O
resolutions	O
--	O
Pitt	B-pers
s	O
Character	O
was	O
never	O
Aimiable	O
til	O
he	O
supported	O
Government	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
you	O
angry	O
about	O
yr	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
--	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
repeat	O
this	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
very	O
horrid	O
Story	O
--	O
when	O
first	O
she	O
took	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
interfere	O
with	O
this	O
Clergyman	O
.	O
She	O
wrote	O
to	O
Windham	B-pers
,	O
informing	O
him	O
that	O
this	O
Curate	O
had	O
neglected	O
his	O
duty	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Man	O
--	O
Windham	B-pers
writes	O
to	O
his	O
Nephew	O
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
Wells	O
--	O
who	O
supposing	O
his	O
Uncle	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
fact	O
matter	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
without	O
some	O
Enquiry	O
--	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
doting	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bath	O
&	O
Wells	O
.	O
besides	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
from	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
London	O
--	O
accordingly	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
dismiſs	O
'd	O
with	O
Contumely	O
--	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
Windham	B-pers
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
implicated	O
hastily	O
in	O
this	O
busineſs	O
he	O
therefore	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
revisions	O
--	O
&	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
large	O
sum	O
of	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
telling	O
this	O
Story	O
in	O
their	O
--	O
way	O
--	O
he	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Conductors	O
of	O
the	O
Anti	O
Jacobin	O
--	O
on	O
whom	O
he	O
could	O
depend	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
large	O
sums	O
from	O
Wilberforce	B-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
from	O
the	O
Bp	O
of	O
L——n	O
also	O
,	O
to	O
invent	O
their	O
Story	O
--	O
but	O
this	O
they	O
positively	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
&	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
the	O
correspondence	O
--	O
&	O
insisting	O
the	O
truth	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
investigated	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
&	O
declares	O
--	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
deepest	O
conspiracy	O
amongst	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
propegate	O
Methodism	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
heard	O
of	O
--	O
now	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
admire	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
cd	O
tell	O
a	O
falsehood	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
partial	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
because	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
Government	O
(	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
office	O
)	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
thoroughly	O
Convinc	O
'd	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
cd	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
Ca	O
t	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
visitor	O
for	O
2	O
Nights	O
lord	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
.	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
Gentlemanly	O
&	O
pleasant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
this	O
morning	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
Severely	O
ill	O
&	O
had	O
medical	O
advice	O
she	O
is	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
Walk	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
--	O
she	O
writes	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Mendip	I-pers
has	O
given	O
most	O
unequivocal	O
Proofs	O
of	O
his	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
Widow	O
by	O
leaving	O
her	O
every	O
thing	O
for	O
too	O
her	O
Life	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
croſs	O
to	O
her	O
letting	O
--	O
that	O
the	O
World	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
most	O
Unjust	O
Will	O
for	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
she	O
has	O
outlived	O
him	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
sees	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
at	O
present	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
constantly	O
with	O
Ly	B-pers
Mendip	I-pers
--	O
tell	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
with	O
my	O
kind	O
love	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
danc	O
'd	O
a	O
Cottillion	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Nevilles	I-pers
--	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
my	O
breath	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
shorter	O
than	O
my	O
partners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
beyond	O
any	O
expectations	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
beg	O
she	O
will	O
make	O
haste	O
&	O
get	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
that	O
at	O
our	O
return	O
to	O
Beds	B-place
:	I-place
she	O
may	O
know	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
dancing	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
ly	I-pers
is	O
here	O
at	O
present	O
&	O
on	O
Thursday	O
were	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
--	O
pray	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
--	O
&	O
accept	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
s	O
kindest	O
Compts	O
.	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
--	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
dear	O
Lou	B-pers
--	O
Concludes	O
me	O
most	O
Sincely	O
&	O
Affecly	O
yrs	O
DBlosset	B-pers
if	O
Milk	O
agrees	O
,	O
ask	O
Dr.	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
if	O
Lou	B-pers
may	O
not	O
take	O
to	O
bad	O
Milk	O
--	O
Skim	O
it	O
well	O
--	O
Put	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
after	O
the	O
Bread	O
is	O
taken	O
out	O
Soke	O
it	O
.	O
when	O
the	O
S	O
rises	O
like	O
a	O
Custard	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
--	O
put	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
again	O
&	O
bake	O
it	O
--	O
&	O
take	O
of	O
the	O
Scum	O
Til	O
after	O
baking	O
the	O
Scum	O
ceases	O
--	O
then	O
it	O
is	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
tea	O
Cups	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
luke	O
warm	O
--	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
brown	O
Sugar	O
Candy	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
Nourishing	O
--	O
&	O
Cooling	O
--	O
show	O
this	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
this	O
recipe	O
to	O
a	O
Physician	O
&	O
to	O
a	O
Great	O
Man	O
at	O
Reading	B-place
--	O
they	O
have	O
adopted	O
it	O
&	O
thank	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
writes	O
that	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
s	O
death	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
reverse	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
debilitated	O
in	O
Mind	O
&	O
Body	O
--	O
she	O
died	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
home	O
at	O
Hadleigh	B-place
&	O
had	O
every	O
comfort	O
the	O
B	O
s	O
's	O
could	O
give	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
Mrs	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Valued	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
as	O
she	O
ought	O
since	O
Mrs	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
's	O
Marriage	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
better	O
for	O
Dr	B-pers
Kerrs	I-pers
Medicines	O
--	O
tell	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
well	O
immediately	O
--	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
our	O
dance	O
--	O
When	O
she	O
gets	O
Stout	O
.	O
she	O
will	O
go	O
&	O
see	O
her	O
Grand	O
--	O
Native	O
Air	O
--	O
has	O
it	O
Advantages	O
--	O
th	O
'	O
o	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
too	O
Cold	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
out	O
to	O
yr	O
dear	O
Child	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
part	O
is	O
a	O
Confidence	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
Support	O
your	O
self	O
--	O
I	O
pray	O
God	O
to	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
these	O
exertions	O
so	O
Virtuous	O
--	O
&	O
so	O
Pious	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
reason	O
for	O
despair	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
interested	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
keep	O
her	O
up	O
--	O
&	O
also	O
Her	O
grandfather	O
--	O
poor	O
person	O
Walden	B-place
Febry	O
nine	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
GriffinBraybrooke	B-pers
Northampton	B-place
free	O
