TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
Novr	O
:	O
12	O
th	O
:	O
1772	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
'T	O
is	O
highly	O
flattering	O
to	O
my	O
Vanity	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
creature	O
of	O
your	O
Age	O
,	O
so	O
warmly	O
soliciting	O
a	O
friendship	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
but	O
you	O
were	O
sincerely	O
po	O
d	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
ask	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
particularly	O
attach	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
th	O
e	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
&	O
if	O
it	O
ever	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
aſsistance	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
o	O
f	O
r	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
shoud	O
think	O
my	O
self	O
extreamly	O
happy	O
.	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
then	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
freedom	O
,	O
be	O
asured	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
receive	O
your	O
letters	O
with	O
pleasure	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
thoughts	O
on	O
whatever	O
you	O
propose	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
truth	O
&	O
candour	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
your	O
learning	O
Latin	O
is	O
no	O
secret	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
mention	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
reflections	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
highest	O
opinion	O
of	O
you	O
imaginable	O
.	O
there	O
are	O
few	O
Wom	O
e	O
n	O
who	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
trusted	O
with	O
learning	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
exception	O
.	O
&	O
whilst	O
you	O
can	O
preserve	O
that	O
humility	O
for	O
wch	O
:	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
remarkable	O
.	O
you	O
may	O
safely	O
learn	O
all	O
the	O
languages	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
advise	O
is	O
t	O
to	O
give	O
yourself	O
up	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
s	O
tudy	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
hurt	O
your	O
health	O
,	O
remember	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
creatures	O
form	O
'd	O
for	O
society	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
so	O
wholly	O
converse	O
with	O
old	O
Authors	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
neglect	O
the	O
chearful	O
conversation	O
of	O
our	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
too	O
severe	O
an	O
application	O
to	O
study	O
naturally	O
gives	O
the	O
mind	O
too	O
serious	O
a	O
turn	O
,	O
&	O
indisposes	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
social	O
duties	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
let	O
study	O
therefore	O
be	O
your	O
amusement	O
,	O
not	O
your	O
Occupation	O
;	O
&	O
never	O
be	O
asham	O
'd	O
of	O
improving	O
your	O
mind	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
raises	O
your	O
vanity	O
,	O
&	O
leads	O
you	O
to	O
look	O
down	O
with	O
contempt	O
on	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
either	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Capacity	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
same	O
opportuni	O
ti	O
es	O
of	O
improving	O
their	O
minds	O
with	O
yourself	O
.	O
this	O
I	O
think	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
your	O
case	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
may	O
safely	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
You	O
'	O
l	O
excuse	O
the	O
incoherency	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
lost	O
a	O
most	O
favourite	O
bosom	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
sometime	O
attempt	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
&	O
perhaps	O
(	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
happy	O
to	O
meet	O
)	O
shew	O
you	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
L	O
ette	O
rs	O
m	O
y	O
Spirits	O
(	O
already	O
weakend	O
)	O
cou	O
'd	O
ill	O
b	O
such	O
a	O
shock	O
;	O
Your	O
little	O
friend	O
is	O
at	O
School	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
imp	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
home	O
at	O
Xmas	O
,	O
my	O
other	O
Girl	O
is	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
she	O
often	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
extreamly	O
like	O
in	O
her	O
dispositions	O
.	O
Jack	B-pers
is	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
or	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
joyned	O
me	O
in	O
sincere	O
regards	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Your	O
affect	O
friend	O
S	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Northampton	B-place
