TOKEN	NE
x	O
8	O
Typed	O
To	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
Febry	O
1785	O
What	O
excuse	O
shall	O
I	O
make	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
for	O
so	O
un	O
un	O
common	O
a	O
silence	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
constantly	O
engaged	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
spend	O
a	O
whole	O
day	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
every	O
Morning	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
wth	O
.	O
people	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
however	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
have	O
prevented	O
my	O
finding	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
You	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
Mind	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
an	O
uncomfortable	O
unsettled	O
state	O
you	O
will	O
readily	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
reasons	O
for	O
not	O
writing	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
find	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
unhappy	O
--	O
&	O
could	O
I	O
disguise	O
my	O
feelings	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
But	O
as	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
my	O
unhappineſs	O
no	O
longer	O
exists	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
with	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
Dr	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
last	O
night	O
that	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
certainty	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	B-place
as	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
was	O
still	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
an	O
Invalid	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
know	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
D——	I-pers
to	O
Texier	B-pers
s	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
much	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
his	O
Translation	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
School	O
for	O
S	O
c	O
andal	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
went	O
wth	O
.	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honor	O
&	O
last	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Macklin	B-pers
perform	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Merchant	O
of	O
Venice	O
&	O
Love	O
á	O
la	O
Mode	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
party	O
You	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
delighted	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
Stage	O
veteren	O
in	O
his	O
85	O
Year	O
performing	O
keeping	O
up	O
these	O
Characters	O
to	O
admiration	O
--	O
See	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
love	O
!	O
what	O
think	O
you	O
of	O
that	O
sensible	O
amiable	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
combating	O
wth	O
.	O
him	O
for	O
8	O
or	O
ten	O
Years	O
&	O
at	O
last	O
forced	O
to	O
own	O
his	O
sway	O
publikly	O
by	O
marrying	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fortunate	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
quite	O
a	O
good	O
creature	O
;	O
he	O
will	O
nurse	O
her	O
wth	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
tenderneſs	O
--	O
&	O
except	O
when	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q	I-pers
or	O
Madame	B-pers
SSchwellenberg	I-pers
requires	O
his	O
attendance	O
never	O
leave	O
her	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
is	O
in	O
great	O
Beauty	O
this	O
Winter	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
wonderfully	O
well	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
is	O
vastly	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
so	O
fortunate	O
as	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
high	O
Health	O
,	O
grow	O
fat	O
&	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
support	O
Balls	O
Aſsemblies	O
Operas	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
night	O
after	O
night	O
--	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
an	O
extroadinary	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
--	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
appetite	O
,	O
no	O
sleep	O
no	O
spirits	O
sufficient	O
for	O
existance	O
--	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
folio	O
letters	O
--	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
ye	O
.	O
Packets	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
in	O
charity	O
to	O
send	O
into	O
Derbyshire	B-place
you	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
unreasonable	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
thousand	O
vexations	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
&	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
my	O
letters	O
(	O
&	O
c	O
ought	O
I	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
credit	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
?	O
)	O
keep	O
up	O
his	O
spirits	O
--	O
our	O
affairs	O
are	O
going	O
on	O
--	O
but	O
when	O
all	O
matters	O
will	O
be	O
settled	O
God	O
knows	O
--	O
patience	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
virtue	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
lay	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
stock	O
now	O
that	O
it	O
as	O
will	O
serve	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
told	O
me	O
yes	O
terday	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Clermont	I-pers
told	O
her	O
that	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dſs	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
was	O
again	O
Pregnant	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
meant	O
to	O
lead	O
a	O
sober	O
quiet	O
life	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
If	O
our	O
People	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bon-ton	O
go	O
on	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
begun	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
scarcity	O
of	O
them	O
next	O
Year	O
--	O
judge	O
--	O
this	O
week	O
there	O
are	O
5	O
Balls	O
running	O
each	O
to	O
begin	O
after	O
great	O
Aſsemblies	O
--	O
Almacks	O
besides	O
--	O
&	O
6	O
&	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
hour	O
they	O
break	O
up	O
--	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
selects	O
&	O
invites	O
the	O
Company	O
either	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Opera	O
or	O
an	O
Aſsembly	O
--	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
way	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
desirous	O
of	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
chosen	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
might	O
put	O
Your	O
name	O
down	O
as	O
a	O
subscriber	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Poor	O
Milkwoman	O
s	O
Verses	O
wch	O
.	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
published	O
this	O
spring	O
,	O
pray	O
inform	O
me	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Sub	O
:	O
is	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
is	O
much	O
as	O
usual	O
always	O
tormented	O
wth	O
:	O
an	O
headach	O
we	O
never	O
meet	O
without	O
talking	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
she	O
desired	O
when	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
affectionate	O
love	O
--	O
the	O
Glovers	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
--	O
the	O
Dear	O
old	O
Man	O
never	O
fails	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
there	O
drinking	O
your	O
health	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
and	O
her	O
Children	O
are	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
live	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
--	O
She	O
leads	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
exemplary	O
life	O
of	O
any	O
Young	O
Woman	O
of	O
fashion	O
in	O
London	B-place
I	O
think	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
never	O
look	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
Winter	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
will	O
lose	O
them	O
her	O
good	O
looks	O
during	O
ye	O
.	O
absence	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
as	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
many	O
apprehensions	O
abt	O
.	O
him	O
--	O
Julia	B-pers
is	O
delightful	O
as	O
to	O
Temper	O
--	O
manners	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
she	O
grows	O
thin	O
&	O
&	O
though	O
in	O
health	O
appears	O
very	O
delicate	O
,	O
Master	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
is	O
astonishingly	O
tall	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
encreased	O
in	O
bulk	O
--	O
he	O
grows	O
every	O
day	O
more	O
&	O
more	O
like	O
his	O
late	O
Brother	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
(	O
tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
this	O
)	O
is	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
&	O
as	O
lively	O
as	O
a	O
Bird	O
at	O
full	O
liberty	O
--	O
he	O
looks	O
ye	O
.	O
picture	O
of	O
happineſs	O
&	O
good	O
humour	O
.	O
Are	O
Dr	O
.	O
Marianna	B-pers
s	O
complaints	O
leſsen	O
'd	O
?	O
I	O
must	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
health	O
is	O
perfectly	O
reestablish	O
'd	O
--	O
My	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
&	O
Charlotte	B-pers
.	O
have	O
you	O
detirmin	O
'd	O
abt	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
?	O
I	O
say	O
nothing	O
on	O
yt	O
.	O
subject	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
advise	O
.	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
do	O
not	O
punish	O
me	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
silent	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
Dearest	O
friend	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
You	O
&	O
that	O
my	O
heart	O
must	O
cease	O
to	O
beat	O
ere	O
my	O
affection	O
for	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
leſsen	O
'd	O
.	O
Ever	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
most	O
afft	O
.	O
fd	O
.	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Courteenhall	B-place
near	O
Northampton	B-place
