TOKEN	NE
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Most	O
sincerely	O
do	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
very	O
kind	O
letter	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
know	O
certain	O
you	O
must	O
all	O
have	O
been	O
must	O
shocked	O
at	O
the	O
unexpected	O
&	O
heavy	O
loſs	O
we	O
have	O
sustained	O
indeed	O
my	O
greatest	O
consolation	O
under	O
this	O
heavy	O
affliction	O
is	O
the	O
aſsertion	O
of	O
her	O
go	O
d	O
o	O
dneſs	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
never	O
existed	O
one	O
more	O
amiable	O
or	O
more	O
deserving	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
the	O
Almighty	O
will	O
reward	O
her	O
for	O
ever	O
in	O
another	O
world	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
agitated	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
much	O
composed	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
resigned	O
to	O
his	O
decree	O
for	O
no	O
doubt	O
what	O
he	O
ordains	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
duty	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
his	O
will	O
--	O
I	O
felt	O
very	O
grateful	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
great	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
dear	O
Fanny	B-pers
&	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
accept	O
your	O
friendly	O
invitation	O
for	O
I	O
fear	O
that	O
Uppingham	B-place
must	O
now	O
be	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
wretched	O
place	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
gone	O
there	O
myself	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
had	O
the	O
dreadful	O
intelligence	O
but	O
the	O
Bishop	O
who	O
is	O
all	O
goodneſs	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
me	O
then	O
able	O
to	O
travel	O
so	O
far	O
by	O
myself	O
&	O
poor	O
Sister	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
sensible	O
to	O
anything	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
convulsions	O
therefore	O
my	O
being	O
there	O
probably	O
might	O
fuly	O
have	O
aggravated	O
their	O
distreſs	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
seriously	O
ill	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
we	O
hope	O
recovering	O
her	O
strength/	O
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
most	O
affectionately	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
ever	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
yr	O
greatly	O
obliged	O
&	O
very	O
Affte	O
MJJackson	B-pers
St	B-place
Asaph	I-place
Novr	O
23	O
d	O
-	O
--	O
St	B-place
Asaph	I-place
November	O
Twenty	O
Third	O
1803	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
St	B-pers
Asaph	I-pers
Bedfordshire	B-place
