TOKEN	NE
35	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
St	O
:	O
London	B-place
.	O
Jan	O
:	O
29	O
th	O
:	O
1807	O
.	O
Many	O
thanks	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
immediate	O
and	O
affectionate	O
reply	O
to	O
my	O
sad	O
communication	O
.	O
What	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
so	O
kindly	O
urge	O
,	O
is	O
most	O
natural	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
generality	O
of	O
parents	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
subject	O
to	O
no	O
risque	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
grieve	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
feelings	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
very	O
peculiar	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
post	O
with	O
yours	O
,	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
expreſsive	O
of	O
unchanged	O
affection	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
peremptorily	O
declining	O
a	O
meeting	O
,	O
unleſs	O
I	O
declared	O
my	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
opinions	O
(	O
you	O
understand	O
me	O
)	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
,	O
can	O
judge	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
yourself	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Even	O
were	O
I	O
impreſsed	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
unequivocal	O
belief	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
declaration	O
must	O
give	O
eternal	O
offence	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
whom	O
my	O
life	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spent	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
if	O
two	O
persons	O
are	O
diametrically	O
opposite	O
in	O
their	O
ideas	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
scarcely	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
but	O
silence	O
can	O
fail	O
to	O
offend	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
almost	O
distracted	O
,	O
with	O
accumulated	O
afflictions	O
.	O
My	O
complaint	O
(	O
that	O
you	O
kindly	O
and	O
anxiously	O
enquire	O
after	O
)	O
is	O
extreme	O
depreſsion	O
and	O
weakneſs	O
,	O
brought	O
on	O
by	O
agitation	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
The	O
storm	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
remember	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
miscarriage	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
in	O
itself	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
streſs	O
upon	O
the	O
constitution	O
and	O
nerves	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
pregnancy	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
thank	O
Heaven	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
are	O
entitled	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
confidence	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Cousin	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
mention	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
F	O
.	O
has	O
explained	O
in	O
this	O
last	O
letter	O
,	O
his	O
intentions	O
towards	O
me	O
--	O
which	O
are	O
,	O
100£	O
.	O
per	O
annum	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
interest	O
of	O
2000£.	O
,	O
during	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
death	O
(	O
which	O
God	O
avert	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
poſsible	O
!	O
)	O
the	O
2000£	O
principal	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
off	O
his	O
estates	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
H	O
.	O
had	O
has	O
remaining	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
1900£	O
.	O
--	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
F	O
.	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
leaves	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
6000£	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
promised	O
at	O
my	O
marriage	O
should	O
be	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
future	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
interest	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
present	O
.	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
consolation	O
my	O
situation	O
will	O
admit	O
of	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
kindneſs	O
of	O
real	O
friends	O
;	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
too	O
troublesome	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
mourning	O
is	O
making	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
affairs	O
I	O
have	O
described	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
the	O
poſsibility	O
,	O
unleſs	O
my	O
finances	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
to	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
obtrude	O
myself	O
as	O
an	O
inmate	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
take	O
my	O
departure	O
at	O
a	O
moment	O
's	O
warning	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
unwelcome	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
confeſs	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
would	O
be	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
disposition	O
of	O
my	O
F	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
determined	O
,	O
which	O
encreases	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
giving	O
offence	O
by	O
acting	O
in	O
opposition	O
to	O
his	O
wishes	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
addreſs	O
of	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Orr	I-pers
--	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
that	O
her	O
residence	O
is	O
somewhere	O
near	O
Worcester	B-place
--	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
Cheltenham	B-place
.	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mann	I-pers
requests	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
best	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
obliging	O
wishes	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
ideas	O
would	O
perfectly	O
coincide	O
with	O
yours	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
peculiarity	O
of	O
the	O
circumstances	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
at	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
.	O
I	O
feel	O
the	O
highest	O
obligation	O
for	O
the	O
concern	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
take	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
sincere	O
love	O
attends	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
.	O
Many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
attention	O
to	O
my	O
tranquillity	O
,	O
in	O
transcribing	O
your	O
own	O
letter	O
.	O
Nothing	O
could	O
be	O
safer	O
or	O
kinder	O
to	O
your	O
U	O
.	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
S	O
.	O
ister	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
,	O
but	O
announced	O
myself	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
letter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sad	O
news	O
)	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
B	B-place
.	I-place
but	O
does	O
not	O
expect	O
the	O
offer	O
to	O
be	O
accepted	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
and	O
kind	O
friend	O
.	O
leaves	O
London	O
Monday-Thursday	O
&	O
Saturday	O
at	O
9	O
oClock	O
in	O
the	O
morng	O
&	O
sets	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
--	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
John	O
Street	O
Smithfield	B-place
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
.	O
--	O
