TOKEN	NE
Buxton	B-place
June	O
26	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
Two	O
lines	O
I	O
am	O
ſure	O
will	O
content	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
when	O
I	O
aſsure	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
so	O
recovered	O
that	O
I	O
propose	O
setting	O
off	O
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
where	O
she	O
is	O
ſure	O
that	O
her	O
Letters	O
will	O
always	O
find	O
a	O
kind	O
reception	O
at	O
the	B-place
Abbey	I-place
from	O
me	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
long	O
one	O
from	O
that	O
quarter	O
ſoon	O
&	O
I	O
expect	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
night	O
from	O
my	O
last	O
however	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
hear	O
why	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
ſuch	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
town	B-place
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
wait	O
yr	O
pleaſure	O
to	O
unriddle	O
these	O
Matters	O
Adieu	O
My	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
been	O
My	O
dear	O
ward	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
note	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
night	O
God	O
bliſs	O
you	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
yrs	O
unchangable	O
as	O
yourſelf	O
