TOKEN	NE
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
after	O
Mother	O
illness	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
My	O
sincere	O
concern	O
for	O
your	O
distreſs	O
prevented	O
my	O
writing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
some	O
doubt	O
&	O
so	O
much	O
anxiety	O
&	O
fatigue	O
accompanied	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
painful	O
an	O
addition	O
to	O
so	O
trying	O
a	O
state	O
the	O
having	O
to	O
answer	O
or	O
even	O
excuse	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
officious	O
kindneſses	O
of	O
ones	O
friends	O
often	O
proves	O
--	O
but	O
now	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
rightly	O
though	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
so	O
painfully	O
exerting	O
yourself	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
love	O
&	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
forbear	O
as	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
of	O
that	O
number	O
to	O
expreſs	O
by	O
Letter	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
have	O
grieved	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
every	O
comfort	O
that	O
your	O
excellent	O
principles	O
can	O
afford	O
you	O
this	O
melancholy	O
case	O
will	O
I	O
trust	O
admit	O
of	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
change	O
a	O
bleſsed	O
one	O
for	O
her	O
you	O
mourn	O
for	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
more	O
entirely	O
&	O
resignedly	O
you	O
can	O
submit	O
to	O
so	O
painful	O
a	O
trial	O
for	O
yourself	O
the	O
greater	O
must	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
reward	O
and	O
consolation	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
my	O
str	O
.	O
was	O
quite	O
charmed	O
with	O
her	O
sweet	O
&	O
friendly	O
behaviour	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dr	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
most	O
truly	O
Yrs	O
.	O
S.	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
Burley	B-place
Decr	O
.	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
1778	O
