TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
10	O
th	O
-	O
June	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Be	O
comforted	O
.	O
People	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
Time	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Gout	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
never	O
have	O
it	O
very	O
severely	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
paid	O
You	O
a	O
Visit	O
;	O
as	O
You	O
will	O
now	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
your	O
Friends	O
,	O
when	O
You	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
Lambs	O
Wool	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Cloth	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
Exercise	O
,	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
increased	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Meat	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
unavoidably	O
swallow	O
during	O
the	O
General	O
Assembly	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
induced	O
the	O
Gout	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
,	O
most	O
kindly	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
spare	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
propose	O
going	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
next	O
Week	O
.	O
That	O
Lord	B-pers
Haddington	I-pers
has	O
been	O
presented	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
perfectly	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
Gouty	O
Mother	O
gone	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
pleased	O
.	O
If	O
Louisa	B-pers
should	O
accidentally	O
see	O
You	O
,	O
her	O
next	O
Speech	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
will	O
be	O
“	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
broad	O
as	O
Your	O
“	O
Mother	O
--	O
”	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
that	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
eyed	O
her	O
from	O
head	O
to	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
could	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
dont	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
said	O
anything	O
kind	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
have	O
sent	O
any	O
kind	O
Meſsage	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
approve	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
They	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
pretended	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
interested	O
about	O
You	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
old	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
She	O
is	O
certainly	O
smitten	O
with	O
Cis	B-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
may	O
have	O
imbibed	O
the	O
same	O
tender	O
paſsion	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
Peace	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
avoids	O
your	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
was	O
so	O
intent	O
on	O
her	O
Cards	O
,	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
's	O
party	O
,	O
the	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
either	O
Lady	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
,	O
or	O
your	O
Daughter	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
makes	O
a	O
Tour	O
of	O
the	B-place
Cumberland	I-place
Lakes	I-place
before	O
She	O
arrives	O
at	O
Lanrick	O
Castle	O
.	O
(	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
that	O
same	O
place	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
mine	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
my	O
Grandfather	O
s	O
imprudence	O
sent	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
going	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
Macgregor	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
has	O
built	O
a	O
good	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
property	O
since	O
he	O
purchased	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
healthy	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
surprised	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
a	O
Young	O
Widow	O
.	O
Having	O
written	O
that	O
much	O
to	O
You	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
proper	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
this	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
should	O
be	O
addreſsed	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
certainly	O
your	O
better	O
half	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
bound	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
persuaded	O
You	O
to	O
have	O
finished	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
Adieu	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Should	O
it	O
be	O
publickly	O
known	O
that	O
You	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Pen	O
to	O
finish	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Letter	O
,	O
when	O
She	O
chose	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Gadding	O
,	O
all	O
our	O
Wives	O
would	O
rise	O
in	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
and	O
attempt	O
to	O
make	O
Jerries	O
of	O
Us	O
all	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
protest	O
against	O
your	O
continuing	O
to	O
indulge	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
unreasonable	O
fancies	O
.	O
The	O
accounts	O
from	O
Manchester	B-place
are	O
very	O
unpleasant	O
indeed	O
.	O
No	O
sooner	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
news	O
reach	O
Edinburgh	B-place
than	O
the	O
Devils	O
immediately	O
circulated	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
similar	O
Riots	O
at	O
Glasgow	B-place
.	O
That	O
there	O
are	O
people	O
wicked	O
enough	O
to	O
wish	O
for	O
such	O
disturbances	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
England	B-place
&	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
I	O
firmly	O
believe	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
still	O
left	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
portion	O
of	O
good	O
Sense	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bulk	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Demons	O
will	O
not	O
succeed	O
in	O
creating	O
that	O
Confusion	O
they	O
aim	O
at	O
.	O
Our	O
Manufacturers	O
have	O
remained	O
very	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
glad	O
that	O
our	O
Cousins	O
have	O
behaved	O
properly	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Captain	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
owes	O
her	O
some	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Torment	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
had	O
graciously	O
condescended	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
expreſsed	O
her	O
approbation	O
of	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
the	O
Presentation	O
Party	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
fixed	O
my	O
Eye	O
on	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
poſsibly	O
have	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
recollection	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
about	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
.	O
With	O
best	O
love	O
from	O
all	O
here	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
,	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Tenth	O
June	O
1808	O
Napier	B-pers
26	O
,	O
Duke	O
Street	O
Manchester	O
Square	O
London	B-place
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
