TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
April	O
2	O
d	O
1774	O
Saucy	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
alway	O
known	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
I	O
now	O
think	O
she	O
has	O
even	O
outdone	O
her	O
own	O
saucineſs	O
what	O
to	O
insist	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
ask	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Mrs-	B-pers
R——	I-pers
&	O
to	O
deſire	O
me	O
to	O
mistrust	O
every	O
thing	O
good	O
under	O
the	O
Cloak	O
of	O
an	O
Old	O
Maiden	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ſay	O
they	O
ever	O
had	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
good	O
opinion	O
but	O
the	O
fondneſs	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
always	O
shewen	O
my	O
Dear	O
Ward	O
had	O
reconciled	O
me	O
at	O
least	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
let	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
before	O
you	O
had	O
ſent	O
so	O
very	O
absolute	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
me	O
never	O
to	O
trust	O
them	O
,	O
So	O
pray	O
my	O
dear	O
Girl	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
affair	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
&	O
hide	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
transaction	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
judge	O
between	O
the	O
Old	O
&	O
the	O
Young	O
Maiden	O
for	O
ſurely	O
the	O
thing	O
is	O
terrible	O
ſince	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
so	O
very	O
high	O
and	O
ſince	O
news	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
Northampton	B-place
let	O
me	O
have	O
your	O
little	O
Heart	O
unburdened	O
entirely	O
that	O
my	O
mind	O
may	O
be	O
at	O
ease	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
she	O
has	O
ſaid	O
or	O
done	O
ſomething	O
off	O
or	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
perhaps	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
should	O
rather	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
yourself	O
then	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
pray	O
indulge	O
that	O
peevish	O
humour	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
&	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
en	O
veritie	O
without	O
hiding	O
any	O
one	O
thing	O
especially	O
as	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
partial	O
judge	O
so	O
write	O
as	O
ſoon	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
had	O
yours	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
ſurprised	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
has	O
not	O
wrote	O
after	O
all	O
he	O
ſaid	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
ſeen	O
him	O
ſince	O
but	O
shall	O
write	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
either	O
to	O
night	O
or	O
tomorrow	O
tho	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
being	O
holyday	O
time	O
Could	O
I	O
ever	O
imagine	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
would	O
think	O
my	O
telling	O
her	O
my	O
own	O
happineſs	O
)	O
should	O
be	O
call	O
ing	O
me	O
teizingly	O
provoking	O
had	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
wrote	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
a	O
Volume	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
thouſands	O
I	O
mention	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
seventy	O
Envy	O
that	O
oldmaidish	O
attendant	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
but	O
for	O
you	O
a	O
Young	O
amiable	O
Girl	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
teens	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
very	O
waspish	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
peevish	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
best	O
friends	O
happineſs	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
riddel	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
take	O
all	O
your	O
Rhetoric	O
to	O
reconcile	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Envy	O
a	O
little	O
eaſier	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
having	O
no	O
room	O
big	O
enough	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
spare	O
from	O
this	O
very	O
small	O
house	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
rooms	O
next	O
door	O
and	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
Boxes	O
&	O
trunks	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
reduced	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
Hundreds	O
instead	O
of	O
thouſands	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
full	O
as	O
peevish	O
as	O
your	O
peevish	O
Ladyship	O
can	O
be	O
for	O
the	O
blood	O
of	O
you	O
so	O
will	O
not	O
write	O
one	O
word	O
more	O
to	O
night	O
.	O
Yes	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
on	O
in	O
purpose	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
one	O
thing	O
to	O
oblige	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
would	O
rather	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
finished	O
.	O
So	O
your	O
Young	O
Lady	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
your	O
gout	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
bearable	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
than	O
bear	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
poſsible	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
make	O
Mama	O
uneaſy	O
if	O
she	O
percieves	O
you	O
dont	O
like	O
her	O
and	O
make	O
your	O
absence	O
as	O
short	O
as	O
poſsible	O
and	O
then	O
get	O
quit	O
of	O
it	O
her	O
&	O
take	O
care	O
never	O
to	O
invite	O
her	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
as	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
unpardonable	O
both	O
to	O
plague	O
the	O
Girl	O
&	O
yourself	O
for	O
believe	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
your	O
gout	O
she	O
will	O
very	O
soon	O
see	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
ſense	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
then	O
be	O
as	O
little	O
to	O
hers	O
so	O
then	O
the	O
seldomer	O
you	O
are	O
together	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
Picture	O
was	O
certainly	O
not	O
clear	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
puts	O
off	O
her	O
marriage	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
as	O
does	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
his	O
going	O
from	O
Northampton	B-place
where	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
idle	O
&	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
employed	O
else	O
where	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
think	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
ignorant	O
of	O
his	O
affairs	O
I	O
beg	O
pardon	O
for	O
speaking	O
abt	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
so	O
now	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
anſ	O
wered	O
yo	O
shall	O
only	O
add	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
all	O
my	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
yours	O
most	O
affcly-	O
N——	B-pers
I	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
four	O
ages	O
from	O
Ovid	B-pers
&	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
printed	O
if	O
you	O
like	O
them	O
perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
send	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
ſame	O
author	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
open	O
this	O
letter	O
again	O
hav	O
ing	O
forgot	O
to	O
inclose	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
sealed	O
it	O
Send	O
yr	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
inclosed	O
frankly	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
correct	O
&	O
amend	O
them	O
Sir	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
Warrender	I-pers
Haddington	B-place
Burghs	I-place
free	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
