TOKEN	NE
Stan	O
.	O
St	O
:	O
Novr	O
:	O
30	O
.	O
Although	O
my	O
Eyes	O
are	O
still	O
weak	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
writing	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
in	O
ansr	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
kind	O
&	O
tendre	O
Letter	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
indeed	O
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
Letter	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
received	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Hand	O
how	O
grateful	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
My	O
poor	O
sad	O
Heart	O
to	O
receive	O
your	O
sympathy	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
Dear	O
Husband	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
Worthy	O
Father	O
&	O
Sisters	O
:	O
pray	O
thank	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
for	O
my	O
poor	O
dr	O
:	O
afflicted	O
Husband	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
sensible	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
their	O
kind	O
C	O
ompaſsion	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
bleſs	O
God	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
in	O
his	O
great	O
Mercy	O
wonderfully	O
supported	O
us	O
under	O
these	O
trying	O
&	O
tender	O
Afflictions	O
--	O
such	O
as	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
thought	O
must	O
have	O
sunk	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Dust	O
;	O
but	O
God	O
Almighty	O
has	O
given	O
us	O
resignedgnation	O
to	O
his	O
all	O
wise	O
Dispensations	O
--	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
He	O
cause	O
Trouble	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
Sorrow	O
as	O
those	O
without	O
hope	O
:	O
Our	O
sweet	O
Angels	O
are	O
I	O
humbly	O
trust	O
in	O
Peace	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
“	O
Wicked	O
cease	O
from	O
Troubling	O
,	O
“	O
&	O
the	O
Weary	O
be	O
at	O
rest	O
;	O
”	O
Job	O
3:17	O
--	O
had	O
They	O
lived	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
The	O
Wicked	O
might	O
have	O
sullied	O
their	O
sweet	O
Souls	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
their	O
poor	O
dr	O
:	O
Father	O
&	O
I	O
sd.-	O
have	O
have	O
been	O
wretched	O
,	O
at	O
present	O
we	O
are	O
only	O
sorrowful	O
--	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
now	O
“	O
sow	O
in	O
Tears	O
”	O
Psalm	O
126:5	O
,	O
I	O
humbly	O
trust	O
if	O
we	O
bear	O
Fruit	O
in	O
our	O
hour	O
of	O
Calamity	O
Affliction	O
,	O
do	O
our	O
duty	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
God	O
sees	O
good	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
Life	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
,	O
through	O
his	O
Mercy	O
,	O
“	O
reap	O
in	O
Joy	O
”	O
Psalm	O
126:5	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
Mornings	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
&	O
bore	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
w	O
as	O
sadly	O
sweet	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
my	O
poor	O
Husband	O
has	O
walked	O
ther	O
e	O
on	O
ce	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
myself	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sadly	O
grieved	O
Dr.-	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
does	O
not	O
spend	O
this	O
Winter	O
in	O
Town	B-place
--	O
it	O
wd	O
:	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Comfort	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
soon	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
gratification	O
.	O
to	O
me	O
poor	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
greatly	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Headach	O
--	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
is	O
Gout	O
.	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
's	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
at	O
College	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
.	O
Poor	O
young	O
Man	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
mean	O
Sr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
:	I-pers
The	O
sad	O
Scene	O
he	O
kindly	O
went	O
through	O
here	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
staid	O
by	O
my	O
Dear	O
Child	O
's	O
Bedside	O
'till	O
the	O
last	O
momen	O
t	O
of	O
his	O
precious	O
Life	O
)	O
has	O
sadly	O
shaken	O
his	O
Nerves	O
&	O
Spirits	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
when	O
he	O
gets	O
Pupils	O
at	O
Cambridge	B-place
he	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
very	O
sincerely	O
that	O
you	O
yr	O
worthy	O
Husband	O
,	O
&	O
yr	O
:	O
sweet	O
little	O
Child	O
are	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
yr	O
:	O
little	O
Dear	O
--	O
may	O
She	O
be	O
a	O
Bleſsing	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
reward	O
yr	O
:	O
anxious	O
Cares	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
begs	O
his	O
kind	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Joins	O
me	O
in	O
kind	O
wishes	O
&	O
best	O
Comps	O
:	O
to	O
Ld.-	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
.	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
yrs	O
:	O
most	O
Affly	O
:	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
yr	O
:	O
Eyes	O
are	O
recovered	O
.	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
them	O
to	O
much	O
.	O
To	O
PCremorne	B-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
