TOKEN	NE
Canterbury	B-place
March	O
3	O
d	O
1773	O
I	O
was	O
favored	O
with	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
letter	O
dated	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
Feby	O
last	O
night	O
for	O
wh-	O
I	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
thank	O
her	O
&	O
am	O
quite	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
well	O
,	O
indeed	O
My	O
Dear	O
Girl	O
Your	O
stile	O
shews	O
it	O
&	O
I	O
find	O
by	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
happy	O
&	O
free	O
from	O
all	O
disagreeable	O
thoughts	O
&	O
in	O
high	O
spirits	O
altho	O
your	O
subject	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
grave	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
of	O
your	O
Age	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
surprise	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
an	O
end	O
as	O
you	O
so	O
very	O
far	O
excell	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
know	O
&	O
whos	O
dispoſition	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
amiable	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
to	O
your	O
friends	O
in	O
having	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
your	O
friendship	O
&	O
the	O
greatest	O
comfort	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
having	O
such	O
a	O
Daughter	O
to	O
be	O
continually	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
repay	O
these	O
Cares	O
which	O
she	O
once	O
took	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
younger	O
days	O
&	O
indeed	O
its	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
left	O
for	O
Children	O
to	O
repay	O
the	O
many	O
anxious	O
moments	O
Parents	O
has	O
about	O
their	O
Children	O
them	O
both	O
when	O
young	O
&	O
grown	O
up	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
older	O
they	O
grow	O
,	O
their	O
gratatude	O
declines	O
greatly	O
in	O
but	O
too	O
many	O
and	O
some	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
horred	O
though	O
of	O
wishing	O
them	O
gone	O
for	O
ever	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
the	O
more	O
easily	O
gratify	O
some	O
favourite	O
paſsion	O
or	O
other	O
--	O
Your	O
Situation	O
in	O
Life	O
My	O
dear	O
Girl	O
to	O
a	O
mind	O
like	O
yours	O
is	O
truely	O
enviable	O
/but	O
how	O
few	O
can	O
enjoy	O
such	O
a	O
mind/	O
in	O
having	O
a	O
Mother	O
that	O
knows	O
&	O
does	O
indulge	O
her	O
daughter	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
deſires	O
,	O
being	O
aſsured	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
does	O
or	O
will	O
deſire	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
whats	O
reasonable	O
there	O
the	O
Mother	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
full	O
as	O
enviable	O
as	O
the	O
Daughter	O
if	O
not	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
nothing	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
Parent	O
so	O
much	O
joy	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
their	O
Children	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
wish	O
as	O
for	O
my	O
Friendſhip	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
ſincere	O
way	O
you	O
may	O
always	O
depend	O
upon	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
instructions	O
the	O
Guardian	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
amiable	O
Ward	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
think	O
otherwise	O
the	O
very	O
best	O
on	O
any	O
subject	O
she	O
deſires	O
she	O
shall	O
always	O
have	O
&	O
may	O
command	O
when	O
she	O
pleaſes	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
dispute	O
with	O
either	O
you	O
or	O
Mr	B-pers
Fordyce	I-pers
whither	O
we	O
should	O
turn	O
from	O
all	O
Vanity	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
Vice	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
obſerving	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
but	O
will	O
only	O
put	O
you	O
in	O
mind	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
to	O
Rev	B-pers
.	I-pers
James	I-pers
Fordyce	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
young	O
Women	O
in	O
general	O
which	O
makes	O
a	O
great	O
difference	O
when	O
a	O
Mind	O
is	O
weak	O
&	O
eaſily	O
carried	O
of	O
by	O
a	O
bad	O
example	O
then	O
the	O
turning	O
from	O
Vanity	O
&	O
Vice	O
is	O
not	O
only	O
right	O
,	O
but	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
a	O
Mind	O
is	O
properly	O
cultivated	O
when	O
young	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
educations	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
that	O
mind	O
be	O
strengthened	O
to	O
good	O
when	O
it	O
sees	O
others	O
unhappy	O
by	O
following	O
vanity	O
&	O
Vice	O
,	O
&	O
must	O
not	O
that	O
mind	O
still	O
with	O
greater	O
energy	O
praise	O
God	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
advantages	O
that	O
good	O
education	O
has	O
given	O
them	O
over	O
those	O
weak	O
minds	O
that	O
goes	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
bad	O
way	O
.	O
Its	O
a	O
doubt	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
you	O
both	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
preaches	O
to	O
ye	O
weak	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Saviour	O
says	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
righteous	O
,	O
but	O
ſinners	O
to	O
repentance	O
the	O
parable	O
of	O
the	O
Fig	O
tree	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
likeways	O
on	O
my	O
ſide	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
so	O
far	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
that	O
its	O
better	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
vices	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
than	O
gain	O
knowledge	O
by	O
knowing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
one	O
lives	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
impoſsible	O
at	O
least	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
almost	O
every	O
moment	O
in	O
ſome	O
thing	O
or	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
Correspondant	O
in	O
Mr	B-pers
Fordyce	I-pers
/he	O
may	O
not	O
like	O
my	O
instructions	O
so	O
well/	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
me	O
an	O
opertunity	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
Falstaff	O
says	O
Hotspur	O
did	O
rebellion	O
&	O
in	O
confidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
yourself	O
was	O
the	O
ſubject	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
give	O
over	O
but	O
will	O
contrive	O
if	O
poſsible	O
to	O
add	O
more	O
before	O
the	O
post	O
goes	O
out	O
to	O
night	O
.	O
Juſt	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
down	O
to	O
add	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
a	O
Mr-	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
s	O
)	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
in	O
from	O
London	B-place
to	O
See	O
me	O
&	O
is	O
ſitting	O
by	O
me	O
so	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
know	O
excuse	O
me	O
Please	O
my	O
Compts-	O
to	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mr	B-pers
Dunkerley	I-pers
most	O
affctly	O
Yours	O
you	O
shall	O
know	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
our	O
change	O
of	O
quarters	O
from	O
this	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
review	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Norwich	B-place
,	O
Bury	B-place
,	O
Ipswich	B-place
&	O
Sudbery	B-place
once	O
me	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
Adieu	O
To	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Northamptonshire	B-place
Mary	B-pers
Free	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
