TOKEN	NE
Do	O
not	O
impute	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
neglect	O
of	O
mine	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
your	O
not	O
having	O
heared	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
your	O
note	O
till	O
this	O
day	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Adelphi	O
where	O
it	O
Lay	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
before	O
this	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
again	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
,	O
and	O
very	O
happy	O
I	O
was	O
indeed	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
charming	O
Mistreſs	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
will	O
You	O
believe	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
Danced	O
at	O
two	O
Balls	O
at	O
Sandleford	B-place
?	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
performed	O
my	O
part	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
was	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
feast	O
at	O
the	O
Harvest-home	O
,	O
a	O
jolly	O
old	O
framer	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
Danced	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Think	O
of	O
my	O
Bold	O
undertaking	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
afforded	O
a	O
most	O
mirthful	O
Scene	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
poor	O
hands	O
plenty	O
of	O
blue	O
spots	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
not	O
at	O
Sandleford	B-place
,	O
the	O
Primate	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
was	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Spare	O
rooms	O
left	O
.	O
Since	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
dined	O
twice	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
asked	O
much	O
after	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
particularly	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
married	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
till	O
after	O
Christms-	O
.	O
have	O
I	O
said	O
right	O
?	O
will	O
not	O
that	O
be	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
is	O
your	O
dear	O
mind	O
at	O
rest	O
?	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
goes	O
on	O
as	O
You	O
c	O
ould	O
wish	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
,	O
Your	O
welfare	O
is	O
therefore	O
nearest	O
at	O
my	O
heart	O
!	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
make	O
you	O
happy	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
devoutly	O
wish	O
may	O
be	O
soon	O
accomplished	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
forgot	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
You	O
about	O
,	O
that	O
abominable	O
book	O
Les	O
sent	O
Nouvelles	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
word	O
and	O
honor	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
into	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
offended	O
you	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shocked	O
to	O
Death	O
with	O
seeing	O
the	O
pictures	O
only	O
,	O
without	O
reading	O
the	O
Stories	O
.	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
thought	O
me	O
rude	O
to	O
let	O
such	O
a	O
book	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
such	O
books	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
rather	O
sick	O
then	O
merry	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
read	O
them	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
and	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Your	O
most	O
faithful	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Adelphi	O
Novr	O
.	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
:	O
1784	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
her	O
Grace	O
the	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	B-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
Bulstrode	O
Near	O
Gerrards	B-place
Croſs	I-place
Bucks	B-place
