TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
Dec	O
:	O
10	O
th	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
received	O
your	O
second	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
which	O
indeed	O
most	O
justly	O
reproaches	O
my	O
silence	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
plagued	O
&	O
tormented	O
to	O
death	O
on	O
vario	O
us	O
accounts	O
&	O
by	O
various	O
circumstances	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
indulgent	O
&	O
make	O
even	O
more	O
allowances	O
for	O
me	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
first	O
kind	O
letter	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
near	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
--	O
&	O
thank	O
you	O
most	O
sincerely	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
all	O
your	O
kind	O
wishes	O
for	O
my	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
attend	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
the	O
dear	O
King	B-pers
had	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
his	O
illneſs	O
--	O
nothing	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
can	O
convey	O
to	O
your	O
mind	O
a	O
just	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
joy	O
,	O
applause	O
&	O
acclamation	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
were	O
receivd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
affecti	O
n	O
g	O
thing	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
the	O
whole	O
House	O
which	O
was	O
fuller	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
than	O
it	O
could	O
hold	O
,	O
sung	O
6	O
times	O
over	O
God	O
save	O
the	O
King	O
--	O
this	O
they	O
repeated	O
as	O
often	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
for	O
ten	O
days	O
&	O
for	O
this	O
week	O
past	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
every	O
day	O
intendi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
every	O
day	O
being	O
prevented	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
how	O
impoſsible	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
moment	O
's	O
leisure	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
not	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
other	O
Friends	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
shamefuly	O
remiſs	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
yet	O
written	O
to	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mr	B-pers
Young	I-pers
to	O
inform	O
him	O
of	O
my	O
intended	O
marriage	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
much	O
at	O
heart	O
&	O
yet	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
yet	O
found	O
the	O
moment	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
tormented	O
to	O
death	O
about	O
Houses	O
seen	O
a	O
hundred	O
,	O
all	O
too	O
small	O
,	O
s	O
o	O
dear	O
,	O
dirty	O
or	O
too	O
far	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
difficulty	O
or	O
the	O
price	O
--	O
at	O
length	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
reduced	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
neat	O
shell	O
in	O
South	O
Audley	O
Street	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
clean	O
,	O
comfortably	O
,	O
nicely	O
furnished	O
&	O
gives	O
us	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
us	O
&	O
fix	O
upon	O
a	O
comfortable	O
habitation	O
for	O
life	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
had	O
been	O
very	O
unwell	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
the	O
Gout	O
flying	O
about	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
now	O
,	O
&	O
goes	O
on	O
Monday	O
in	O
to	O
Somersetshire	B-place
to	O
carry	O
his	O
Children	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Ilchester	I-pers
s	O
for	O
th	O
e	O
Holydays	O
--	O
he	O
returns	O
for	O
new	O
years	O
day	O
&	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
marriage	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
early	O
days	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
a	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	O
's	O
&	O
niece	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
to	O
succeed	O
me	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
very	O
proper	O
mark	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
regard	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
she	O
is	O
very	O
pretty	O
amiable	O
&	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
one	O
of	O
11	O
Children	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
eligible	O
situation	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
yet	O
told	O
you	O
nothi	O
n	O
g	O
of	O
my	O
Health	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
perfect	O
ly	O
good	O
thank	O
God	O
&	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
these	O
3	O
weeks	O
or	O
Month	O
past	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
extreme	O
ly	O
in	O
the	O
information	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
have	O
given	O
up	O
Taxal	B-place
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
two	O
the	O
c	O
i	O
rcumstance	O
of	O
two	O
families	O
in	O
a	O
H	O
ouse	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
one	O
,	O
howeve	O
r	O
well	O
they	O
are	O
united	O
,	O
besides	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
really	O
no	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
or	O
receive	O
you	O
r	O
Friend	O
's	O
a	O
comfort	O
one	O
can	O
not	O
dispense	O
with	O
if	O
one	O
lives	O
the	O
whole	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
you	O
flatter	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
pleasur	O
e	O
of	O
seei	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
when	O
will	O
it	O
be	O
?	O
n	O
ot	O
till	O
the	O
spring	O
I	O
imagine	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
has	O
I	O
think	O
lost	O
her	O
good	O
looks	O
&	O
Health	O
since	O
she	O
left	O
Margate	B-place
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
at	O
Paris	B-place
&	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
&	O
love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
who	O
I	O
hope	O
improves	O
in	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
that	O
can	O
add	O
to	O
you	O
r	O
comfort	O
&	O
happineſs	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
affec	O
:	O
&	O
sincerely	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
G——	I-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
