TOKEN	NE
Welwyn	B-place
,	O
31	O
st	O
:	O
August	O
1781	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
last	O
troubled	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
with	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
mentioned	O
an	O
Application	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
be	O
appointed	O
D	O
.	O
Adjutant	O
General	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
morning	O
been	O
informed	O
that	O
my	O
request	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
granted	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
presumption	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
She	O
will	O
feel	O
herself	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
degree	O
interested	O
in	O
anything	O
that	O
concerns	O
me	O
--	O
if	O
She	O
had	O
felt	O
a	O
wish	O
for	O
my	O
succeſs	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
probably	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
have	O
pardoned	O
an	O
unintentional	O
Neglect	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
add	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
the	O
greatest	O
esteem	O
&	O
regard	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
that	O
I	O
experience	O
the	O
deepest	O
concern	O
at	O
her	O
having	O
ceased	O
to	O
treat	O
me	O
as	O
her	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
