TOKEN	NE
28	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1782	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
My	O
friend	O
in	O
excuse	O
for	O
having	O
so	O
long	O
delay	O
'd	O
writing	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
to	O
offer	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
indolent	O
&	O
stupid	O
,	O
yet	O
was	O
I	O
unreasonable	O
enough	O
every	O
Morning	O
to	O
be	O
expecting	O
letters	O
from	O
You	O
&	O
to	O
feel	O
disappointed	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
any	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
yet	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
feel	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
longer	O
the	O
first	O
upon	O
your	O
list	O
of	O
friends	O
--	O
this	O
idea	O
of	O
mine	O
does	O
not	O
proceed	O
from	O
any	O
mean	O
jealousy	O
of	O
disposition	O
--	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
affection	O
I	O
bear	O
towards	O
you	O
&	O
wch	O
:	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
feel	O
,	O
has	O
an	O
adequate	O
return	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
winter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
unhappy	O
--	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
notwithstanding	O
to	O
conceal	O
my	O
apprehension	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
lose	O
the	O
share	O
I	O
still	O
retain	O
'd	O
of	O
your	O
Affection	O
by	O
tormenting	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
co	O
njectures	O
--	O
and	O
my	O
Dear	O
friend	O
pardon	O
me	O
for	O
having	O
now	O
mention	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
long	O
endulged	O
myself	O
in	O
laying	O
my	O
heart	O
open	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
the	O
present	O
impulse	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Lady	B-pers
W——	I-pers
next	O
week	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
her	O
yesterday	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
better	O
&	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
airings	O
on	O
Horseback	O
--	O
that	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Jebb	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
leave	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
strongly	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
try	O
Buxton	B-place
;	O
She	O
fears	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
if	O
he	O
finds	O
himself	O
better	O
when	O
he	O
gets	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
use	O
all	O
your	O
influence	O
in	O
persuading	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
a	O
very	O
precarious	O
life	O
and	O
that	O
every	O
precaution	O
is	O
necessary	O
for	O
its	O
preservation	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
love	O
all	O
your	O
anxieties	O
about	O
yor	O
.	O
F	O
have	O
long	O
been	O
over	O
&	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
again	O
.	O
how	O
long	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
?	O
and	O
when	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
pay	O
your	O
Visit	O
to	O
Hero	B-pers
?	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Thursby	I-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
twice	O
&	O
had	O
two	O
delightful	O
rides	O
wth	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
T——	I-pers
as	O
he	O
brought	O
Horses	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
call	O
&	O
tell	O
you	O
about	O
our	O
little	O
excursions	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
not	O
accompanied	O
their	B-pers
M——	I-pers
to	O
Kew	B-place
&	O
London	B-place
either	O
this	O
week	O
or	O
the	O
last	O
--	O
my	O
time	O
has	O
been	O
equally	O
occupied	O
as	O
for	O
during	O
their	O
absence	O
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
Eveg	O
out	O
of	O
waiting	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Thursday	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
Hero	B-pers
&	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
come	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
enquire	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Ever	O
tenderly	O
yours	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Free	O
Wake	O
Horton	B-place
Newport	O
Pagn	O
el	O
Bucks	B-place
