TOKEN	NE
11	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
½	O
past	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
April	O
1799	O
:	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
You	O
intended	O
sending	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Fool	O
's	O
Errand	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
ordered	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
be	O
conveyed	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
25	O
or	O
6	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
lives	O
at	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
your	O
former	O
Commands	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
in	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
the	O
Abigail	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
old	O
Dame	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
smart	O
Valet	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Week	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
propose	O
going	O
North	O
.	O
Our	O
Illustrious	O
Cousins	O
,	O
Cathcarts	O
,	O
Mansfield	O
Greville	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
Atholl	O
's	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
entered	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
Cathcarts	O
excepted	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
The	O
Cathcarts	O
twice	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Mansfield	O
Greville	O
's	O
I	O
have	O
called	O
on	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
getting	O
admittance	O
.	O
Greville	B-pers
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
disposed	O
of	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
the	O
invitation	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
repeated	O
.	O
Twice	O
have	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
at	O
the	O
Atholl	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	O
has	O
been	O
pigging	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Litter	O
I	O
suppose	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
fit	O
for	O
roasting	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
bidden	O
to	O
the	O
Feast	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Name	O
for	O
the	O
Mansfields	O
Portland	O
Place	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
taken	O
no	O
Notice	O
whatever	O
of	O
Me	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
State	O
of	O
Affection	O
We	O
bear	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
fashion	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
when	O
You	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
you	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
feel	O
grateful	O
for	O
my	O
condescension	O
in	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
Good	O
Night	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Miſs	O
Brat	O
,	O
Countrywoman	O
&	O
c	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affect	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Second	O
April	O
1799	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
.	I-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
