TOKEN	NE
Waltham	B-place
Abbey	I-place
Monday	O
Morng	O
.	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
Octr	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
would	O
delight	O
your	O
tender	O
Heart	O
,	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
you	O
must	O
prepare	O
yourself	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
nature	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
severe	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
now	O
no	O
more	O
--	O
He	O
was	O
relieved	O
from	O
his	O
Miseries	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
11	O
O'Clock	O
or	O
Later	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
&	O
Daughter	O
came	O
got	O
here	O
from	O
Banktop	B-place
yesterday	O
evening	O
,	O
&	O
met	O
her	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Berwick	I-pers
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
--	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
at	O
Hodsden	B-place
to	O
prepare	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
,	O
&	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
William	B-pers
,	O
whose	O
Afflictions	O
have	O
shewn	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
properest	O
manner	O
,	O
&	O
whose	O
Conduct	O
has	O
been	O
exemplary	O
indeed	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Wakes	I-pers
are	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
one	O
could	O
expect	O
--	O
Dear	O
Charlotte	B-pers
was	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
wonderfull	O
Child	O
.	O
Expreſses	O
have	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
&	O
as	O
much	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
as	O
the	O
time	O
would	O
admit	O
.	O
Your	O
's	O
most	O
sincerely	O
W.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
Kind	O
Comps	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
,	O
let	O
this	O
go	O
without	O
sending	O
one	O
Line	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
,	O
is	O
resigned	O
&	O
tolerably	O
composed	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
constantly	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
'till	O
She	O
leaves	O
this	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
'till	O
She	O
can	O
settle	O
about	O
where	O
She	O
will	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
Letters	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
her	O
upon	O
Busineſs	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
add	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
truly	O
yours	O
PCremorne	B-pers
I	O
fear	O
this	O
will	O
affect	O
you	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
beseech	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
way	O
to	O
too	O
much	O
grief	O
for	O
our	O
dr	O
Friend	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
cd	O
have	O
hoped	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
with	O
his	O
kindest	O
Love	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
Sheat	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
but	O
just	O
let	O
blood	O
,	O
he	O
hopes	O
will	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
tomorrow	O
's	O
Post	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
tolerably	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
making	O
himself	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
he	O
really	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
and	O
Sisters	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
My	O
Dr	O
:	O
Sir	O
--	O
Pray	O
read	O
this	O
Letter	O
&	O
shew	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
judge	O
proper	O
to	O
Dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickinson	B-pers
Yr	O
:	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obliged	O
PCremorne	B-pers
To	O
--	O
J.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Jun	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Taxall	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
Oct	O
:	O
31	O
st	O
:	O
1785	O
