TOKEN	NE
Caserta	B-place
6	O
th	O
of	O
March	O
1787	O
.	O
Sir	O
It	O
was	O
with	O
great	O
pleasure	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
obliging	O
Letter	O
acquainting	O
me	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
safe	O
delivery	O
of	O
a	O
Daughter	O
--	O
I	O
most	O
heartily	O
wish	O
you	O
both	O
a	O
Continuance	O
of	O
every	O
earthly	O
happineſs	O
--	O
by	O
her	O
last	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
soon	O
Answer	O
fully	O
I	O
perceive	O
she	O
is	O
perfectly	O
happy	O
and	O
indeed	O
she	O
deserves	O
it	O
for	O
for	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
poſseſsing	O
an	O
excellent	O
affectionate	O
heart	O
and	O
a	O
strong	O
well	O
cultivated	O
Understanding	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
fail	O
making	O
you	O
happy	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
with	O
pleasure	O
see	O
that	O
she	O
does	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
visit	O
to	O
Great	B-place
Britain	I-place
in	O
a	O
years	O
time	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
much	O
pleasure	O
in	O
making	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
I	O
am	O
Sir	O
your	O
most	O
obedient	O
humble	O
Sert	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
March	O
1787	O
To	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
