TOKEN	NE
31	O
st	O
.	O
March	O
1788	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
So	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
indeed	O
I	O
hardly	O
expected	O
you	O
from	O
what	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
impatient	O
&	O
anxious	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
comfort	O
,	O
when	O
shall	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
pleasure	O
--	O
shall	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
this	O
Evening	O
at	O
9	O
o	O
clock	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
or	O
will	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
tomorrow	O
Eveni	O
n	O
g	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
--	O
or	O
shall	O
I	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
hour	O
tomorrow	O
morni	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
at	O
any	O
hour	O
--	O
consider	O
of	O
all	O
these	O
proposals	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
which	O
you	O
accept	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
arrange	O
things	O
accordingly	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
dine	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
in	O
my	O
great	O
cap	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
do	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
better	O
tho	O
'	O
last	O
night	O
my	O
fever	O
was	O
very	O
high	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
unwell	O
for	O
these	O
some	O
weeks	O
past	O
and	O
having	O
now	O
grown	O
worse	O
I	O
shall	O
probably	O
get	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
quiet	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
stout	O
&	O
well	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
Ball	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
stare	O
at	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
amiable	O
&	O
good	O
naturd	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
little	O
Dance	O
whils	O
t	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
--	O
just	O
ten	O
couple	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
room	O
will	O
hold	O
;	O
It	O
will	O
probably	O
be	O
very	O
pleasant	O
,	O
at	O
leas	O
t	O
a	O
small	O
thing	O
has	O
always	O
a	O
bette	O
r	O
chance	O
of	O
being	O
so	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sorry	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
George	B-pers
as	O
myself	O
were	O
I	O
unable	O
to	O
enjoy	O
it	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
&	O
is	O
enjoying	O
this	O
heavenly	O
weather	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
since	O
Thursday	O
&	O
where	O
he	O
stays	O
till	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
aired	O
&	O
cleaned	O
after	O
the	O
Ball	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
come	O
&	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
s	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
Saville	O
Row	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
where	O
we	O
all	O
reckon	O
on	O
your	O
prom	O
ise	O
of	O
comi	O
n	O
g	O
next	O
summer	O
--	O
&	O
bri	O
n	O
gi	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
little	O
rosy	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
your	O
letter	O
because	O
what	O
with	O
hurry	O
&	O
what	O
with	O
indolence	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
power	O
or	O
resolution	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
constantly	O
had	O
the	O
idea	O
&	O
the	O
inclination	O
--	O
But	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
silence	O
or	O
judge	O
by	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
regard	O
but	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
interested	O
about	O
you	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
adieu	O
send	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
affecly	O
yours	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
No	O
5	O
George	O
Street	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
