TOKEN	NE
Our	O
dear	O
Child	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
born	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
1787	O
Friday	O
at	O
3	O
oclock	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
in	O
Abbey	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
:	O
--	O
