TOKEN	NE
I	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
yr-	O
Note	O
my	O
Dr	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
my	O
Toilette	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
at	O
least	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
your	O
Fever	O
,	O
I	O
most	O
sincerely	O
wish	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
my	O
Dear	O
&	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Sincere	O
,	O
therefore	O
be	O
aſsured	O
whatever	O
lays	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
that	O
can	O
either	O
relieve	O
your	O
Mind	O
or	O
Body	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
most	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Mlle	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
love	O
&	O
will	O
most	O
willingly	O
supply	O
yr-	O
place	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
answer	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
ever	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
hard	O
Duty	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
can	O
relieve	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sincerely	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
&	O
embrace	O
you	O
to	O
morrow	O
Evg	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
really	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
justice	O
&	O
say	O
that	O
they	O
really	O
have	O
very	O
frequently	O
inquired	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
Prſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
has	O
sent	O
her	O
Love	O
,	O
Dr	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
another	O
very	O
Sore	O
Boil	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
of	O
a	O
Smart	O
Gauze	O
Cloak	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
this	O
Evg	O
--	O
they	O
send	O
their	O
Love	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
Sincely	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
MCG——	B-pers
½	O
pt	O
4	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
