TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Friday	O
--	O
Yesterday	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
a	O
s	O
I	O
should	O
my	O
Dear	O
have	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
excellent	O
Epistles	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Dr	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
went	O
with	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Stag	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
graciously	O
off	O
ered	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Harleyford	B-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
gladly	O
accepted	O
,	O
&	O
really	O
found	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
better	O
then	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
her	O
Deafneſs	O
I	O
own	O
would	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
compl	O
ains	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
uneasy	O
feel	O
of	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
&	O
the	O
violent	O
fit	O
of	O
Coughing	O
she	O
still	O
has	O
Morg	O
&	O
Evg	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
looks	O
are	O
not	O
bad	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
find	O
her	O
too	O
much	O
fallen	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
that	O
what	O
I	O
always	O
suspected	O
is	O
true	O
&	O
that	O
Ld	B-pers
Winchilsea	I-pers
s	O
departure	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
is	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Complaint	O
,	O
she	O
talked	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
cryed	O
,	O
so	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
said	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
thinks	O
her	O
Disorder	O
greatly	O
Nervous	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
my	O
Dear	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
mends	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
perpetually	O
&	O
if	O
my	O
earnest	O
Prayers	O
could	O
succeed	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
be	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
are	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
it	O
may	O
seem	O
odd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
litteraly	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
rather	O
suspect	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
s	O
,	O
our	O
Life	O
here	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
afford	O
Subject	O
for	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
is	O
as	O
usual	O
the	O
most	O
pleasing	O
best	O
hum	O
ored	O
Creature	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
of	O
infinite	O
Service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
&	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
flatter	O
myself	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
Air	O
will	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dst	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
really	O
well	O
,	O
Love	O
to	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
&	O
Chi	B-pers
,	I-pers
Chi	I-pers
,	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
Affy	O
Yr	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
enclosed	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Pſs	B-pers
Elzh	I-pers
from	O
Pſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
but	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
perverse	O
fit	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
declared	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
send	O
it	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
