TOKEN	NE
Feb	O
ye	O
13	O
th	O
Sir	O
You	O
would	O
have	O
received	O
my	O
congratulations	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
happy	O
event	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
s	O
safe	O
delivery	O
of	O
a	O
Daughter	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
cruel	O
disorder	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
had	O
not	O
renderd	O
me	O
incapable	O
of	O
writing	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
I	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
quite	O
relieved	O
from	O
this	O
complaint	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
now	O
violent	O
enough	O
to	O
hinder	O
my	O
expreſsing	O
my	O
joy	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
&	O
gratitude	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
communication	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
hope	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
one	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
virtues	O
&	O
talents	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
treat	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
presumptionus	O
expectation	O
,	O
these	O
most	O
valuable	O
poſseſsions	O
being	O
rarely	O
hereditary	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
instructions	O
&	O
example	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
will	O
receive	O
from	O
its	B-pers
Mother	I-pers
&	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
security	O
for	O
the	O
p	O
a	O
ccomplishment	O
of	O
your	O
wishes	O
,	O
&	O
hopes	O
;	O
for	O
what	O
talents	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
depreſs	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
dullneſs	O
of	O
a	O
Swiſs	O
?	O
or	O
what	O
virtues	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
impaired	O
by	O
the	O
levities	O
of	O
a	O
French	O
Governeſs	O
?	O
But	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
important	O
&	O
delicate	O
task	O
of	O
education	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
be	O
attended	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
tender	O
&	O
virtuous	O
Parents	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
dear	O
Sir	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
&	O
sincere	O
congratulations	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
aſsure	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
regret	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
Stranger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Sir	O
Your	O
most	O
Obedt	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
complimts	O
to	O
Eliz	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
,	O
&	O
inform	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
from	O
ye	O
disorder	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
return	O
my	O
thanks	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
news	O
&	O
obliging	O
manner	O
of	O
imparting	O
manner	O
of	O
imparting	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Rundal	I-pers
Febry	O
13	O
th	O
1787	O
Recd	O
.	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
