TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
recd	O
:	O
your	O
Letter	O
&	O
the	O
pretty	O
Work	O
Bag	O
too	O
late	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
thanks	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
&	O
I	O
are	O
vastly	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
is	O
so	O
well	O
recovered	O
.	O
pray	O
aſsure	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
with	O
our	O
duty	O
how	O
we	O
rejoiced	O
in	O
the	O
good	O
account	O
you	O
sent	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	O
&	O
thank	O
her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highness	I-pers
,	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
for	O
her	O
pretty	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
value	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
deserves	O
,	O
&	O
f	O
te	O
ll	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
gift	O
,	O
&	O
leave	O
it	O
as	O
such	O
to	O
little	O
Julia	B-pers
's	O
great	O
grand	O
Daughter	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highneſs	I-pers
how	O
much	O
I	O
wish	O
her	O
many	O
very	O
happy	O
returns	O
of	O
this	O
Day	O
.	O
--	O
my	O
duty	O
attends	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
&	O
your	O
two	O
pretty	O
little	O
Princeſses	O
.	O
Julia	B-pers
can	O
not	O
,	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
fold	O
up	O
her	O
Gloves	O
like	O
Princess	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
--	O
but	O
She	O
will	O
try	O
--	O
She	O
did	O
try	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
quite	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
with	O
her	O
pencil	O
&	O
paper	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
She	O
was	O
drawing	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
said	O
not	O
drawing	O
,	O
Mama	O
,	O
only	O
writing	O
my	O
proper	O
Dipthongs	O
ai	O
,	O
ae	O
,	O
au	O
.	O
aw	O
&	O
c	O
only	O
thin	O
g	O
k	O
how	O
ridiculous	O
!	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dr	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
Yrs	O
:	O
very	O
Affectionately	O
PDartrey	B-pers
Chelsea	B-place
Sept	O
:	O
29	O
th	O
:	O
1781	O
--	O
