TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
badneſs	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
and	O
the	O
uncertainty	O
of	O
what	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
has	O
prevented	O
my	O
haveing	O
waited	O
of	O
you	O
Since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
town	B-place
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
of	O
you	O
Soon	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
nothing	O
will	O
prevent	O
my	O
haveing	O
that	O
pleasure	O
.	O
the	O
2	O
5	O
th	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
you	O
dont	O
mean	O
any	O
thing	O
unpolite	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
friendship	O
for	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
just	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
hint	O
,	O
that	O
mrs	B-pers
Cherteris	I-pers
thinks	O
it	O
od	O
you	O
send	O
her	O
a	O
Card	O
without	O
inviting	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
you	O
Can	O
easyly	O
Send	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Servant	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
its	O
not	O
being	O
Sent	O
Sooner	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
this	O
as	O
I	O
mean	O
it	O
kind	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
beleive	O
me	O
very	O
Sincerly	O
Dear	O
madam	O
your	O
much	O
obliged	O
Servant	O
Cath	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
maddox	O
Street	O
Tuesday	O
19	O
th	O
