TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
August	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
1786	O
My	O
dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
I	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
pen	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
enquiries	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
your	O
worthy	O
Father	O
&	O
sisters	O
;	O
who	O
I	O
can	O
easily	O
imagine	O
are	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
sorry	O
for	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
must	O
miſs	O
your	O
charming	O
spirits	O
&	O
your	O
conversation	O
,	O
we	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
both	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
very	O
seldom	O
wish	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
company	O
with	O
us	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
excepting	O
this	O
last	O
week	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Eton	B-place
to	O
fetch	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
who	O
will	O
stay	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
happy	O
in	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
amiable	O
man	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
absent	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Luxmore	I-pers
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
gay	O
here	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
publick	O
breakfast	O
at	O
the	O
Wells	O
,	O
their	O
were	O
an	O
hundred	O
&	O
forty	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
musick	O
from	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
charming	O
band	O
it	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
danced	O
three	O
dances	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
made	O
up	O
a	O
Country	O
dance	O
for	O
twelve	O
couple	O
;	O
every	O
body	O
was	O
pleased	O
which	O
is	O
saying	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
our	O
entertainment	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
another	O
this	O
day	O
seven-night	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Dalkeith	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
were	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
M——	I-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
one	O
of	O
the	O
sisters	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
,	O
is	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Bruſsels	B-place
,	O
very	O
amiable	O
&	O
very	O
accomplished	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
home	O
her	O
sisters	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
take	O
against	O
her	O
father	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
refused	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
good	O
&	O
indulgent	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
merit	O
the	O
treatment	O
he	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
every	O
ill-treatment	O
which	O
malice	O
ill-nature	O
&	O
hatred	O
can	O
devise	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Anna	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
Bourdieu	I-pers
s	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
very	O
shortly	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
Bond	O
&	O
the	O
printing	O
of	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
s	O
work	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
is	O
settled	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
,	O
after	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
vilest	O
treatment	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Chollet	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
,	O
their	O
is	O
nothing	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
was	O
bad	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
against	O
my	O
dear	O
Father	O
,	O
whose	O
Charecter	O
was	O
too	O
well	O
known	O
thank	O
God	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
to	O
Suffer	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
them	O
worthleſs	O
people	O
but	O
never	O
so	O
very	O
bad	O
a	O
they	O
really	O
are	O
.	O
In	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
a	O
A	O
thenaid	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
settled	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
next	O
Febry-	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Copies	O
are	O
one	O
thousand	O
;	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Strohoff	I-pers
thinks	O
they	O
will	O
all	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
happy	O
to	O
read	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
praises	O
of	O
little	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
that	O
her	O
little	O
cousin	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
favorite	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
felt	O
so	O
interested	O
for	O
any	O
one	O
upon	O
so	O
short	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
Minikin	B-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
therefore	O
quite	O
glad	O
she	O
suits	O
you	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
Sally	B-pers
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
had	O
sold	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
&	O
had	O
purchased	O
a	O
most	O
charming	O
peice	O
of	O
ground	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Oxford	O
Street	O
opposite	O
Hyde	O
park	O
&	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
building	O
a	O
the	O
gentleman	O
wish	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
house	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
move	O
into	O
it	O
this	O
week	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
desires	O
to	O
be	O
most	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
yourself	O
&	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
Your	O
charming	O
old	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
she	O
has	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
several	O
times	O
.	O
Your	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
no	O
doubt	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
heard	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
attempt	O
upon	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
precaution	O
of	O
sending	O
an	O
expreſs	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
desire	O
that	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
might	O
not	O
hear	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
when	O
he	O
himself	O
arrived	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
princeſses	O
were	O
,	O
&	O
saluted	O
them	O
with	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
“	O
well	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
hurt	O
”	O
&	O
repeated	O
it	O
twice	O
over	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
&	O
princeſses	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
was	O
in	O
agonies	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
princeſses	O
burst	O
into	O
tears	O
,	O
which	O
reliev	O
'd	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
so	O
much	O
that	O
t	O
S	O
he	O
shed	O
tears	O
immediately	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
was	O
much	O
hurt	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
imprudence	O
&	O
greatly	O
alarm	O
'd	O
for	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
for	O
she	O
hardly	O
recover	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
whole	O
evening	O
.	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
came	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
make	O
his	O
enquiries	O
,	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
saw	O
him	O
but	O
not	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
on	O
his	O
birthday	O
they	O
left	O
Wind——r	B-place
.	O
the	B-pers
K——	I-pers
resents	O
his	O
with	O
The	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
all	O
his	O
debts	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
your	O
excellent	O
husband	O
&	O
make	O
my	O
Compts	O
.	O
acceptable	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
F.——	I-pers
&	O
your	O
Sisters	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
A	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Children	O
go	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
Children	O
at	O
Eton	B-place
.	O
They	O
are	O
fine	O
children	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
god	O
daughter	O
is	O
my	O
favorite	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
lovely	O
lively	O
sensible	O
child	O
,	O
the	O
dear	O
little	O
boy	O
too	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
child	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
nursed	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
&	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
us	O
with	O
tears	O
in	O
Her	O
eyes	O
.	O
--	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
your	O
affectionate	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
M	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
presents	O
her	O
best	O
Compts-	O
pray	O
send	O
us	O
word	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
well	O
for	O
my	O
Mother	O
and	O
self	O
ar	O
e	O
very	O
anxious	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
