TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
26	O
th	O
-	O
Septr-	O
1807	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
You	O
wonder	O
at	O
my	O
not	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
?	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
You	O
commanded	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
your	O
having	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
explains	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
recollection	O
of	O
your	O
habitual	O
disobedience	O
,	O
fresh	O
in	O
my	O
Memory	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
You	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
profit	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
suited	O
my	O
conveniency	O
.	O
Certainly	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
arrived	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
reached	O
my	O
Domicile	O
without	O
any	O
strange	O
Adventures	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
interrogated	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
view	O
of	O
discovering	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
since	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
say	O
Yes	O
,	O
or	O
No	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
I	O
comforted	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
belief	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
And	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
convinced	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
Your	O
Scrap	O
of	O
Paper	O
undeceived	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
my	O
most	O
extreme	O
acknowledgements	O
are	O
due	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
escort	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
trouble	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
took	O
in	O
opening	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
Gates	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Stony	B-place
Stratford	I-place
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
so	O
reasonable	O
(	O
as	O
indeed	O
they	O
always	O
have	O
been	O
)	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
proceed	O
on	O
my	O
Journey	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
slept	O
at	O
Welford	B-place
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
;	O
reached	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
's	O
before	O
Dinner	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
left	O
Stapleford	O
Hall	O
,	O
at	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
dined	O
at	O
Newcastle	B-place
on	O
Thursday	O
;	O
drunk	O
Tea	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
George	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
sleep	O
at	O
Framlington	B-place
;	O
started	O
from	O
thence	O
at	O
Six	O
O'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
arrived	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
before	O
Ten	O
O'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
&	O
unexpected	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
for	O
me	O
sooner	O
,	O
than	O
dinner	O
Time	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Admiral	B-pers
Vashon	I-pers
telling	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
Son	O
Francis	B-pers
to	O
Leith	B-place
,	O
by	O
Ten	O
O'Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
off	O
to	O
seek	O
his	O
Fortune	O
on	O
the	O
Mighty	O
Deep	O
.	O
This	O
Summons	O
was	O
obeyed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
sailed	O
in	O
the	O
Shannon	O
Frigate	O
to	O
arrive	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
in	O
the	B-place
North	I-place
Seas	I-place
,	O
&	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
conveyed	O
to	O
the	O
Southward	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
join	O
Captain	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Resistance	O
Frigate	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
Letter	O
from	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
sailed	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
high	O
Spirits	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
experienced	O
no	O
Sea	O
Sickneſs	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
weather	O
had	O
been	O
rough	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shannon	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
prize	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
after	O
shipping	O
off	O
Francis	B-pers
,	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
as	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
Selkirkshire	B-place
,	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
County	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
new	O
Militia	O
Act	O
agoing	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
in	O
State	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Library	O
,	O
surrounded	O
by	O
the	O
Portraits	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
Ancestors	O
,	O
smiling	O
(	O
or	O
grinning	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
)	O
very	O
graciously	O
,	O
on	O
their	O
hopeful	O
Representative	O
.	O
This	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
interrupted	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
living	O
Scyon	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
to	O
remain	O
there	O
peaceably	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
scribbling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
quickly	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
Your	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
will	O
not	O
be	O
delivered	O
by	O
Me	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
her	O
Sister	O
Lady	B-pers
Kinnaird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
fail	O
instantly	O
to	O
aſsure	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
was	O
gratified	O
by	O
her	O
Lord	O
's	O
Succeſs	O
&	O
good	O
Conduct	O
,	O
at	O
Copenhagen	B-place
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
most	O
sincere	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
poſsible	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
have	O
behaved	O
with	O
more	O
prudence	O
,	O
humanity	O
,	O
and	O
propriety	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
trust	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Services	O
will	O
be	O
rewarded	O
as	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
they	O
have	O
already	O
given	O
his	O
Son	O
Frederick	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Troop	O
of	O
Dragoons	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
uncommon	O
steady	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
wishes	O
attend	O
Your	O
Husband	O
,	O
your	O
Daughter	O
,	O
&	O
your	O
Ball	O
.	O
The	O
papers	O
will	O
announce	O
the	O
grand	O
Illumination	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Saloon	O
at	O
Leighton	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Gardens	O
&	O
Grotto	O
decorated	O
with	O
coloured	O
Lamps	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
darken	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Rib	O
,	O
begs	O
her	O
Civilities	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
mine	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
