TOKEN	NE
letter	O
of	O
a	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
cousin	O
Rev	B-pers
AH	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Wolverton	B-place
Thursday	O
1	O
st	O
Sepbr	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
of	O
yesterday	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
full	O
contemplation	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
most	O
happy	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
&	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
next	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
things	O
going	O
on	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
require	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
singular	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
in	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
Encrease	O
has	O
a	O
complaint	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
&	O
altogether	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
visiting	O
order	O
&	O
with	O
much	O
regret	O
must	O
decline	O
accepting	O
your	O
kind	O
Invitation	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
recollection	O
of	O
our	O
Children	O
Arch	B-pers
is	O
at	O
school	O
&	O
Fanny	B-pers
going	O
on	O
in	O
her	O
usual	O
joy	O
of	O
leſsons	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
migration	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
return	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
us	O
most	O
kindly	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
Ms	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Cousin	O
most	O
Faithfully	O
Yrs	O
AH	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Bedford	B-place
shire	I-place
