TOKEN	NE
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
Sept	O
..	O
19	O
1783	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
expected	O
your	O
forgiveneſs	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
I	O
have	O
deserved	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
permitted	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
letter	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
with	O
out	O
writing	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
to	O
you	O
myself	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
looks	O
well	O
eats	O
,	O
drinks	O
,	O
&	O
walks	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
better	O
health	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
to	O
judge	O
by	O
your	O
own	O
feelings	O
how	O
happy	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
be	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
these	O
three	O
weeks	O
past	O
,	O
&	O
next	O
week	O
we	O
expect	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Strothoff	I-pers
to	O
stay	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
newspapers	O
the	O
accounts	O
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Society	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
earthquakes	O
in	O
Meſsina	B-place
,	O
&	O
the	O
two	O
Calabria	B-place
's	O
,	O
surely	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
known	O
more	O
distreſs	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
dreadful	O
;	O
how	O
happy	O
are	O
we	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
subject	O
to	O
such	O
misfortunes	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
very	O
bad	O
storms	O
of	O
Thunder	O
&	O
lighting	O
during	O
this	O
summer	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
William	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
recover	O
'd	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
better	O
since	O
your	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
no	O
doubt	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
happy	O
in	O
having	O
so	O
amiable	O
&	O
so	O
sincere	O
a	O
friend	O
as	O
yourself	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
nurse	O
Sr	B-pers
..	I-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
Friendship	O
in	O
general	O
is	O
I	O
fear	O
too	O
much	O
as	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
represents	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Edwin	O
&	O
Angelina	O
And	O
what	O
is	O
friendship	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
name	O
,	O
A	O
Charm	O
that	O
lulls	O
to	O
Sleep	O
;	O
A	O
shade	O
that	O
follows	O
wealth	O
&	O
fame	O
And	O
leaves	O
the	O
wretch	O
to	O
weep	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
ever	O
to	O
enjoy	O
&	O
to	O
deserve	O
your	O
friendship	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
favor	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
from	O
my	O
infancy	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
r	O
ry	O
to	O
say	O
my	O
mother	O
has	O
been	O
disappointed	O
in	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
friendship	O
from	O
some	O
which	O
would	O
surprize	O
&	O
perhaps	O
hurt	O
you	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
hint	O
at	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
trust	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
pen	O
&	O
paper	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
sometimes	O
faithleſs	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
our	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Miss	B-pers
A.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
last	O
night	O
&	O
flatter	O
myself	O
I	O
improve	O
by	O
her	O
conversation	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
seven	O
weeks	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
we	O
read	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
s	O
letters	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
improving	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
s	O
Roman	O
history	O
&	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
entertaind	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Our	O
Neighbourhood	O
is	O
very	O
agreeable	O
the	O
Card	O
parties	O
have	O
began	O
we	O
have	O
one	O
this	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Grenville	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
which	O
time	O
will	O
be	O
elaps	O
'd	O
next	O
Sunday	O
,	O
excuse	O
the	O
blunders	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
letter	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
the	O
sincerest	O
regard	O
yours	O
.	O
M	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
have	O
sent	O
inclosed	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
I	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
news	O
paper	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
them	O
by	O
heart	O
so	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
return	O
them	O
I	O
thought	O
them	O
very	O
pretty	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lenton	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
compliments	O
to	O
you	O
M	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
