TOKEN	NE
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
I	O
send	O
you	O
this	O
Brush	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
Unhurt	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
an	O
Unreasonable	O
time	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
want	O
of	O
Paper	O
to	O
finish	O
--	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
my	O
Sister	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Carriage	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
,	O
but	O
we	O
recollected	O
that	O
you	O
Expected	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
our	O
morg	O
dreſses	O
--	O
the	O
Weather	O
lately	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
bad	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
peep	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
besides	O
the	O
Melancholy	O
Event	O
which	O
has	O
cut	O
us	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
--	O
you	O
can	O
easily	O
imagine	O
what	O
a	O
Survivor	O
must	O
Suffer	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Separation	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
lived	O
for	O
Years	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
she	O
had	O
Loved	O
from	O
her	O
Childhood	O
,	O
&	O
who	O
was	O
as	O
worthy	O
of	O
her	O
Affection	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
most	O
Sanguine	O
Hopes	O
could	O
form	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
rous	O
'd	O
herself	O
Sufficiently	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
what	O
I	O
sd	O
expect	O
from	O
her	O
--	O
in	O
her	O
deplorable	O
Situation	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
resigned	O
&	O
thankful	O
for	O
four	O
Years	O
of	O
uninterrupted	O
happineſs	O
--	O
which	O
she	O
Sensible	O
is	O
lost	O
for	O
ever	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
Also	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ricks	I-pers
who	O
is	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
writes	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jalabert	I-pers
had	O
resolution	O
to	O
be	O
Alone	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
when	O
he	O
expir	O
'd	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
)	O
without	O
a	O
Pang	O
--	O
you	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
an	O
Unhappy	O
Stranger	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
excuse	O
my	O
writing	O
so	O
long	O
upon	O
this	O
Subject	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
about	O
Friday	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Letter	O
send	O
it	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morg	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Love	O
from	O
all	O
to	O
all	O
--	O
Concludes	O
me	O
yrs	O
most	O
Affecly	O
DBloſset	B-pers
Monday	O
Night	O
Novbr	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
98	O
