TOKEN	NE
Vigo	B-place
in	O
Galicia	B-place
on	O
the	O
Coast	O
of	O
Spain	B-place
Thursday	O
June	O
28	O
1781	O
My	O
dear	O
dear	O
Sophia	B-pers
You	O
will	O
have	O
heard	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Habback	I-pers
that	O
Your	O
poor	O
Mama	O
is	O
a	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
uneas	O
e	O
y	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
You	O
know	O
how	O
well	O
I	O
am	O
treated	O
,	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
and	O
old	O
Spanish	O
General	O
near	O
90	O
.	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
great	O
dinner	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
met	O
all	O
the	O
Officers	O
in	O
the	O
force	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
the	O
American	O
Captain	O
who	O
took	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
poor	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dillon	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
poor	O
Man	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
but	O
every	O
body	O
was	O
complimenting	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
upon	O
his	O
humane	O
&	O
generous	O
behaviour	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
hope	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
get	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Oporto	B-place
in	O
Portugal	B-place
,	O
&	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Ship	O
to	O
convey	O
us	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
England	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
never	O
expect	O
me	O
now	O
till	O
You	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
my	O
greatest	O
grief	O
in	O
being	O
taken	O
was	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
from	O
seeing	O
my	O
dear	O
litle	O
Lambs	O
&	O
from	O
either	O
seeing	O
or	O
hearing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Your	O
dear	O
dear	O
Papa	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
sail	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
June	O
17	O
th	O
-	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
Packet	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
I	O
love	O
since	O
May	O
15	O
th	O
-	O
give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
dear	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Louisa	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
fea	O
r	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
still	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
I	O
can	O
Thank	O
her	O
at	O
Harleyford	B-place
for	O
all	O
her	O
goodness	O
&	O
c	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
what	O
a	O
comfort	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
being	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Copy	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Copy	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
s	O
letter	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
