TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
Octr	O
11	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleaſure	O
of	O
recieving	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
s	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
instant	O
after	O
so	O
very	O
long	O
a	O
ſilence	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
yourself	O
in	O
the	O
Wilds	O
of	O
Kent	B-place
however	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
returned	O
home	O
&	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
health	O
after	O
so	O
much	O
diſsipation	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
aſsamed	O
of	O
yourself	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
scold	O
about	O
your	O
not	O
writing	O
ſooner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
such	O
a	O
neglect	O
to	O
your	O
Guardian	O
wont	O
happen	O
again	O
&	O
I	O
order	O
the	O
Siroce	O
Winds	O
to	O
blow	O
in	O
Italy	B-place
and	O
never	O
preſume	O
appearing	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
at	O
least	O
at	O
Hamilton	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
excuse	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
own	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
percieve	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
yours	O
however	O
believe	O
me	O
we	O
are	O
extremely	O
sorry	O
about	O
your	O
Earach	O
&	O
hope	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
sent	O
it	O
about	O
its	O
buſineſs	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
had	O
none	O
plaguing	O
you	O
you	O
desire	O
our	O
opinion	O
about	O
your	O
London	B-place
journey	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
after	O
Christmas	O
and	O
which	O
My	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
you	O
shall	O
have	O
wtout	O
the	O
least	O
disguise	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Lady	O
of	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
ſee	O
no	O
reason	O
for	O
denying	O
yourself	O
a	O
Months	O
amusement	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
tho	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ſay	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
a	O
constant	O
residence	O
there	O
or	O
indeed	O
in	O
any	O
place	O
where	O
so	O
constant	O
a	O
round	O
of	O
nonſenſical	O
absurd	O
doings	O
are	O
continually	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
nobody	O
in	O
their	O
senſes	O
could	O
have	O
patience	O
with	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
breach	O
of	O
Duty	O
you	O
mention	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
entirely	O
left	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
feelings	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
your	O
Mama	O
can	O
ever	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
ſay	O
she	O
ſeems	O
much	O
pleased	O
wt	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
that	O
it	O
distreſses	O
you	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
the	O
reverse	O
to	O
wit	O
had	O
it	O
pleased	O
you	O
and	O
distreſsed	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
then	O
have	O
advised	O
Northampton	B-place
instead	O
of	O
London	B-place
as	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
ſorry	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
deſire	O
a	O
thing	O
contrary	O
to	O
your	O
Mama	O
s	O
opinion	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
you	O
may	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
anxiety	O
leave	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Month	O
but	O
would	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
tho	O
MrsMiſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
should	O
be	O
perswaded	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
leave	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
more	O
as	O
she	O
may	O
wt	O
pleasure	O
give	O
the	O
first	O
leave	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
be	O
aſsured	O
will	O
be	O
given	O
with	O
reluctance	O
whatever	O
face	O
may	O
be	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
&	O
very	O
natural	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
One	O
thing	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
'll	O
remember	O
above	O
all	O
things	O
,	O
never	O
on	O
any	O
condition	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
publick	O
place	O
without	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
indeed	O
to	O
as	O
few	O
private	O
places	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
without	O
her	O
&	O
never	O
make	O
any	O
great	O
intimacys	O
with	O
the	O
London	B-place
Miſses	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
above	O
all	O
Miſses	O
the	O
most	O
hatefull	O
in	O
my	O
humble	O
opinion	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
many	O
whos	O
behaviour	O
is	O
reckoned	O
to	O
be	O
faultleſs	O
&	O
whos	O
Characters	O
are	O
admired	O
by	O
the	O
beau	O
monde	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
extremely	O
ſorry	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
a	O
much	O
higher	O
opinion	O
of	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
so	O
My	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
dont	O
let	O
your	O
Good	O
nature	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
people	O
till	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
acquaint	O
with	O
their	O
Characters	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
eaſy	O
where	O
people	O
are	O
bred	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Cradle	O
to	O
diſsemble	O
their	O
thoughts	O
&	O
where	O
a	O
ſort	O
of	O
affected	O
politeneſs	O
paſses	O
for	O
good	O
Nature	O
and	O
amiableneſs	O
&	O
hides	O
often	O
a	O
very	O
very	O
bad	O
heart	O
.	O
Now	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
you	O
have	O
both	O
our	O
opinions	O
about	O
your	O
London	B-place
Scheme	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
on	O
to	O
anſwer	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
--	O
My	O
Health	O
continues	O
on	O
the	O
mending	O
hand	O
&	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
ſome	O
times	O
r	O
e	O
turns	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
stomach	O
yet	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
at	O
present	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
Six	O
Years	O
past	O
&	O
am	O
in	O
greater	O
spirits	O
than	O
you	O
ever	O
ſaw	O
me	O
in	O
&	O
am	O
quite	O
fit	O
for	O
your	O
ſaucineſs	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
ſee	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
fine	O
order	O
by	O
being	O
twenty	O
times	O
more	O
ſaucy	O
than	O
your	O
ſaucy	O
Ladyship	O
could	O
be	O
for	O
your	O
Life	O
so	O
Madam	O
you	O
may	O
let	O
your	O
Mama	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
keep	O
you	O
in	O
few	O
order	O
was	O
I	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
,	O
but	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
happen	O
this	O
year	O
of	O
God	O
without	O
some	O
time	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
should	O
fall	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
very	O
right	O
when	O
you	O
ſaw	O
me	O
shake	O
my	O
head	O
abt	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
&	O
controversy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
perverse	O
Gipsey	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
thinking	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
proper	O
to	O
have	O
ſaid	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
polite	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
Fanchon	O
is	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
Cloe	O
&	O
Fairry	O
is	O
are	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
--	O
I	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Satire	O
in	O
Beatie	B-pers
s	O
verses	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
must	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
likeways	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
truth	O
in	O
them	O
likeways	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
hinted	O
ſuch	O
things	O
formerly	O
when	O
writing	O
about	O
a	O
certain	O
Lady	O
s	O
learning	O
Latin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
propose	O
seeing	O
town	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
which	O
I	O
regreate	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleaſure	O
of	O
meeting	O
you	O
&	O
of	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ambitious	O
of	O
knowing	O
from	O
the	O
good	O
Character	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
other	O
people	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
family	O
are	O
all	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
&	O
will	O
certainly	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
tho	O
its	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
fixed	O
when	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
is	O
appointed	O
Maid	O
of	O
Honor	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
in	O
the	O
most	O
flattering	O
manner	O
poſsible	O
&	O
without	O
any	O
bodys	O
knowing	O
of	O
a	O
vacancy	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
who	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Keck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
daughter	O
of	O
Lord	B-pers
Hereford	I-pers
s	O
at	O
a	O
boarding	O
school	O
in	O
Norwich	B-place
many	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
th	O
e	O
n	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
maried	O
to	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
imagine	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
his	O
Wife	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
decamped	O
so	O
eaſily	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
by	O
what	O
you	O
ſay	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
greatly	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
sending	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
Book	O
to	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atkinſon	I-pers
s	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mr-	B-pers
Ruſsell	I-pers
I	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
off	O
the	O
Picture	O
that	O
you	O
promised	O
me	O
before	O
mary	B-pers
and	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
this	O
Winter	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
wise	O
is	O
enough	O
and	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
moſt	O
respectfull	O
way	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
return	O
her	O
my	O
most	O
ſincere	O
thanks	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
--	O
Miracles	O
are	O
are	O
not	O
ceased	O
ſince	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
dont	O
viſit	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ſay	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ſorry	O
for	O
it	O
from	O
what	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
and	O
if	O
she	O
continues	O
in	O
the	O
ſame	O
stile	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
connexion	O
better	O
broke	O
off	O
than	O
continued	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ſorry	O
Miſs	B-pers
Kingford	I-pers
is	O
still	O
obliged	O
to	O
remain	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
&	O
am	O
afraid	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
ſoon	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
&	O
friends	O
as	O
they	O
take	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
notice	O
or	O
ever	O
speak	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
ſeveral	O
hints	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
with	O
you	O
but	O
they	O
allowed	O
the	O
ſubject	O
to	O
drop	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
so	O
I	O
imagine	O
from	O
all	O
that	O
,	O
things	O
are	O
worse	O
than	O
he	O
ſeems	O
to	O
think	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
the	O
storm	O
would	O
ſoon	O
blow	O
over	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
bite	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
a	O
quite	O
different	O
opinion	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
perswaded	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
offended	O
at	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
ſorry	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
time	O
is	O
paſsing	O
away	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
better	O
employed	O
than	O
walking	O
the	O
Streets	O
&	O
environs	O
of	O
the	O
sweet	O
Mr-	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
I	O
hear	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
nor	O
indeed	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
the	O
Queens	O
Dragoons	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
little	O
about	O
ſince	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
but	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
their	O
giving	O
a	O
County	O
a	O
Ball	O
and	O
they	O
returned	O
it	O
a	O
few	O
day	O
ago	O
so	O
you	O
see	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
regreat	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
so	O
much	O
as	O
Colonel	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
does	O
them	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
&	O
my	O
three	O
eldest	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
be	O
most	O
affectionately	O
yours	O
.	O
If	O
Mary	B-pers
s-	O
verses	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
added	O
yours	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
half	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
Letter	O
as	O
this	O
remember	O
that	O
Madam	O
adieu	O
.	O
