TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
Novr	O
.	O
1805	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
In	O
reply	O
to	O
your	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
telling	O
You	O
that	O
my	O
Daughter	O
walked	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
basked	O
in	O
the	O
Sun	O
for	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
,	O
this	O
forenoon	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
refresh	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
that	O
mode	O
of	O
airing	O
Invalids	O
,	O
to	O
sending	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Carriage	O
,	O
&	O
always	O
practise	O
it	O
.	O
No	O
accounts	O
from	O
my	O
Son	O
William	B-pers
yet	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
the	O
Gazette	O
has	O
relieved	O
my	O
Anxiety	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appears	O
from	O
the	O
Returns	O
that	O
no	O
Officer	O
,	O
or	O
Midshipman	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
or	O
wounded	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
The	O
Defence	O
.	O
Her	O
loſs	O
was	O
7	O
Seamen	O
&	O
Marines	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
29	O
ditto	O
wounded	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Your	O
Hub	O
,	O
as	O
You	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
affectionate	O
&	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Lady	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
s	O
Friends	O
here	O
say	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
her	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
is	O
true	O
.	O
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
Twenty	O
Sixth	O
November	O
1805	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
