TOKEN	NE
14	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1782	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
Your	O
Dear	O
letter	O
this	O
day	O
week	O
&	O
postpon	O
'd	O
writing	O
to	O
You	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
answer	O
Your	O
question	O
respecting	O
the	O
drawing	O
Rooms	O
--	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
till	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
&	O
then	O
you	O
may	O
reckon	O
the	O
fortnight	O
Drawing	O
Rooms	O
.	O
dating	O
ym	O
.	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
25	O
th	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
delighted	O
that	O
You	O
can	O
send	O
me	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Your	O
health	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
You	O
never	O
deceive	O
me	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Hero	B-pers
--	O
&	O
flatter	O
myself	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
good	O
Odour	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
on	O
her	O
ye	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
liberty	O
--	O
and	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
Morng	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Walker	B-pers
s	O
Lecture	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
me	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
to	O
Brislaws	B-pers
(	O
these	O
two	O
Genius	O
's	O
being	O
here	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
Miſs	B-pers
Crewes	I-pers
were	O
also	O
of	O
both	O
these	O
Parties	O
--	O
do	O
You	O
know	O
ym	O
.	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
form	O
even	O
an	O
Outline	O
of	O
their	O
Characters	O
Hero	B-pers
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
You	O
but	O
not	O
one	O
word	O
drop	O
'd	O
of	O
Your	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
venture	O
the	O
question	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
Your	O
Father	O
say	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
changes	O
in	O
the	O
Ministry	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinking	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
;	O
&	O
Ld	O
.	O
Shelborne	O
,	O
I	O
pronounce	O
is	O
already	O
a	O
great	O
in	O
favor	O
ite	O
You	O
reproach	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
congratulated	O
You	O
on	O
finding	O
Your	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
glad	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
promise	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
procure	O
You	O
the	O
hair	O
You	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
remember	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
on	O
no	O
account	O
boast	O
of	O
having	O
this	O
invaluable	O
Treasure	O
in	O
Your	O
poſseſsion	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
are	O
Your	O
Studies	O
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
&	O
what	O
book	O
's	O
of	O
amusement	O
have	O
You	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
finished	O
Potters	O
translation	O
of	O
Euripides	O
--	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
only	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
published	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
could	O
have	O
read	O
it	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
paſsages	O
would	O
have	O
equally	O
pleased	O
each	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
begun	O
some	O
books	O
on	O
Natural	O
History	O
&	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
acquire	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
in	O
my	O
favorite	O
studies	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
--	O
particularly	O
too	O
as	O
Monr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
'Luc	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
settle	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
apply	O
to	O
explain	O
wt	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
comprehend	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
advertised	O
another	O
Novel	O
by	O
Miss	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
who	O
wrote	O
Evelina	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
first	O
production	O
was	O
a	O
wonderful	O
proof	O
of	O
genius	O
for	O
that	O
Kind	O
of	O
Writing	O
.	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
young	O
&	O
had	O
no	O
aſsistance	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Cecilia	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
5	O
Vol	O
:	O
s	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
lounging	O
book	O
for	O
You	O
at	O
Horton	B-place
.	O
--	O
pray	O
get	O
it	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
You	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
best	O
love	O
--	O
remember	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
great	O
est	O
Comforts	O
is	O
receiving	O
letters	O
from	O
You	O
--	O
Adieu	O
God	O
Bless	O
You	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Is	B-pers
:	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
she	O
has	O
lost	O
ye	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
side	O
.	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
franks	O
for	O
me	O
