TOKEN	NE
Wilton	B-place
Lodge	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
1793	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
was	O
safely	O
delivered	O
,	O
this	O
afternoon	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
sleep	O
since	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
will	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
on	O
former	O
occasions	O
.	O
Try	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
example	O
.	O
Be	O
a	O
good	O
Girl	O
,	O
&	O
produce	O
a	O
Boy	O
too	O
,	O
without	O
playing	O
any	O
more	O
tricks	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
shabby	O
in	O
You	O
not	O
to	O
visit	O
my	O
Farm	O
,	O
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
female	O
Brat	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
ever	O
with	O
great	O
sincerity	O
&	O
affection	O
,	O
your	O
much	O
attached	O
Brother	O
&	O
Friend	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birchhall	O
Manchester	B-place
by	O
Carlisle	B-place
