TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
afishing	O
&	O
sketching	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
caught	O
only	O
4	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
had	O
forestalled	O
me	O
&	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
on	O
horseback	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
I	O
made	O
3	O
--	O
from	O
Vie	O
ws	O
contained	O
in	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
road	O
leading	O
to	O
Oakford	B-place
bridge	O
Col	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Teale	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
Dr	O
.	O
alias	O
Apoy	O
of	O
Bampton	B-place
came	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
All	O
the	O
Neighbors	O
in	O
succession	O
were	O
invited	O
but	O
all	O
engaged	O
--	O
Col.	B-pers
Teale	I-pers
has	O
an	O
estate	O
about	O
2	O
Miles	O
off	O
&	O
a	O
Cottage	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
improving	O
--	O
he	O
married	O
a	O
Lady	O
of	O
Tiverton	B-place
&	O
genteelish	O
Woman	O
--	O
Col.	B-pers
Teale	I-pers
has	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
gay	O
World	O
&	O
has	O
much	O
the	O
Appearance	O
of	O
an	O
Irishman	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
fond	O
of	O
Gambling	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
friend	O
of	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Picton	I-pers
who	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Neighborhood	O
in	O
Pembrokeshire	B-place
or	O
Herefordshire	B-place
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
which	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Moon	O
till	O
late	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
preſsed	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
it	O
rose	O
--	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
Cards	O
&	O
a	O
Supper	O
&	O
they	O
all	O
set	O
off	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eleven	O
Friday	O
--	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
after	O
breakfast	O
&	O
the	O
Christening	O
of	O
2	O
Children	O
--	O
I	O
with	O
the	O
Pointer	O
&	O
James	B-pers
&	O
his	O
Grehounds	O
we	O
met	O
Col.	B-pers
Teale	I-pers
by	O
appointment	O
--	O
Two	O
Hares	O
were	O
found	O
&	O
one	O
was	O
killed	O
--	O
The	O
Pointer	O
would	O
not	O
attend	O
me	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
two	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
I	O
returned	O
but	O
James	B-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
before	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
leisurely	O
as	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
intensely	O
hot	O
--	O
no	O
Sun	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
close	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Calcutta	B-place
Heat	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
perspired	O
more	O
--	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
Solr	O
.	O
of	O
Manchester	B-place
&	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
--	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
profeſsion	O
to	O
give	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Notice	O
that	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
miserable	O
,	O
old	O
Houses	O
in	O
Manr	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
wanted	O
for	O
a	O
bridge	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
road	O
that	O
is	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
Bury	B-place
--	O
I	O
rejoiced	O
at	O
this	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
advantage	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
time	O
&	O
will	O
increase	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
her	O
property	O
considerably	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
Brickdale	I-pers
came	O
to	O
pay	O
their	O
Wedding	O
Visit	O
--	O
They	O
are	O
lately	O
married	O
--	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregorie	I-pers
&	O
has	O
lived	O
much	O
in	O
Town	B-place
&	O
has	O
the	O
Airs	O
of	O
a	O
fashonable	O
Woman	O
They	O
are	O
a	O
large	O
Couple	O
--	O
They	O
prevented	O
us	O
setting	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
where	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
s	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
walked	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
horse	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
before	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
receive	O
yrs	O
.	O
of	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
We	O
found	O
ourselves	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
dinner	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
dinner	O
was	O
not	O
spoilt	O
--	O
the	O
Trout	O
were	O
excellent	O
&	O
the	O
MoorGed	O
or	O
Hepper	O
nearly	O
so	O
--	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
Teeth	O
--	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
to	O
dine	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
some	O
Ladies	O
to	O
Tea	O
&	O
Cards	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
an	O
Altarpiece	O
of	O
Cosway	B-pers
s	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
put	O
up	O
--	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
presumptious	O
in	O
me	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Opinion	O
but	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
fixed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
I	O
would	O
then	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
aſsisting	O
in	O
the	O
decision	O
--	O
The	O
party	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
nobody	O
who	O
understood	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
&	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lady	O
playing	O
very	O
keenly	O
at	O
Casino	O
--	O
it	O
was	O
observed	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
old	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
&	O
particularly	O
as	O
a	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sidgood	I-pers
who	O
is	O
98	O
&	O
who	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
took	O
a	O
ride	O
on	O
a	O
double	O
horse	O
11	O
miles	O
&	O
back	O
again	O
one	O
day	O
--	O
She	O
observed	O
She	O
was	O
rather	O
looking	O
upwards	O
&	O
is	O
turned	O
the	O
round	O
Corner	O
of	O
80	O
herself	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
mentioned	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Apple	O
Tree	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
that	O
has	O
twice	O
produced	O
9	O
Hogsheads	O
of	O
Cyder	O
from	O
the	O
Apples	O
of	O
each	O
year	O
--	O
&	O
generally	O
produces	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Hogs	O
.	O
this	O
must	O
require	O
for	O
9	O
Hog	O
.	O
250	O
pecks	O
of	O
Fruit	O
--	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
became	O
dusk	O
leaving	O
Miſs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
--	O
We	O
met	O
Mr.	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
returng	O
from	O
his	O
pastoral	O
Occupations	O
--	O
he	O
engaged	O
us	O
to	O
dine	O
wh-	O
him	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
saying	O
that	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
set	O
out	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
--	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
&	O
made	O
the	O
Engagement	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
desired	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
to	O
find	O
Birds	O
on	O
his	O
Estate	O
--	O
My	O
old	O
Dogs	O
pace	O
doesnt	O
much	O
exceed	O
my	O
own	O
Therefore	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
fag	O
--	O
No	O
Matter	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
surprised	O
at	O
what	O
Miſs	B-pers
E.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
with	O
her	O
long	O
Bow	O
took	O
Aim	O
at	O
respecting	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
One	O
day	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
--	O
the	O
Conversation	O
led	O
to	O
Religion	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
liberal	O
minded	O
Christian	O
&	O
believed	O
in	O
the	O
Doctrine	O
without	O
superstitious	O
prejudices	O
&	O
had	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
a	O
natural	O
Religion	O
taken	O
naturally	O
from	O
the	O
Scriptures	O
--	O
He	O
might	O
choose	O
to	O
hocus	O
me	O
but	O
he	O
spoke	O
seriously	O
&	O
left	O
that	O
impreſsion	O
on	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
that	O
Louisa	B-pers
is	O
made	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
suppose	O
that	O
Ly	B-pers
Cis	I-pers
.	I-pers
may	O
doat	O
on	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
judge	O
of	O
Human	O
Nature	O
&	O
Manners	O
&	O
more	O
Excellence	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
under	O
her	O
Roof	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
has	O
a	O
very	O
entertaining	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
peculiar	O
manner	O
of	O
ingratiating	O
herself	O
when	O
alone	O
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
with	O
her	O
profeſsions	O
is	O
at	O
her	O
Wits	O
Ends	O
&	O
provoked	O
that	O
all	O
her	O
fine	O
speechs	O
must	O
be	O
seen	O
thro	O
'	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
hold	O
our	O
Tongue	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
saying	O
Things	O
that	O
really	O
have	O
no	O
Meaning	O
wh-	O
English	O
people	O
who	O
are	O
more	O
downright	O
than	O
foreigners	O
--	O
It	O
gives	O
me	O
pleasure	O
that	O
you	O
approve	O
of	O
the	O
Carriage	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
happy	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
pleased	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
a	O
shooting	O
or	O
rather	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
but	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
first	O
--	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
last	O
night	O
we	O
found	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
returned	O
--	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
on	O
Horseback	O
fm-	O
Tiverton	B-place
&	O
was	O
much	O
fatigued	O
--	O
he	O
fancies	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Cough	O
from	O
sleeping	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
broken	O
pane	O
of	O
Glaſs	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
evidently	O
declining	O
very	O
fast	O
--	O
On	O
thursday	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
fm-	O
Mr.	B-pers
Js	I-pers
.	I-pers
Paynter	I-pers
--	O
when	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
me	O
Aye	O
--	O
says	O
she	O
two	O
&	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
thumper	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
one	O
as	O
youll	O
find	O
--	O
the	O
postage	O
was	O
3/3	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
which	O
was	O
exchanged	O
for	O
one	O
She	O
had	O
before	O
&	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
improperly	O
drawn	O
--	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
is	O
as	O
usual	O
--	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
my	O
sister	O
lately	O
but	O
She	O
was	O
well	O
&	O
that	O
Trade	O
&	O
consequently	O
Wages	O
were	O
higher	O
&	O
they	O
looked	O
for	O
a	O
better	O
winter	O
for	O
the	O
labouring	O
Claſses	O
--	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
--	O
Probably	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
on	O
thursday	O
or	O
friday	O
next	O
--	O
Kiſs	O
our	O
dear	O
Girl	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
D	O
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
