TOKEN	NE
Schaw	O
Park	O
June	O
10	O
th	O
1773	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
obligeing	O
Letter	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
greatest	O
Pleasure	O
--	O
.	O
doubly	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
lenth	O
of	O
yr	O
Sillence	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
fear	O
you	O
was	O
tired	O
of	O
so	O
Stupid	O
a	O
Correspondant	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
you	O
turned	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
buſsied	O
Situation	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
disadvantage	O
as	O
to	O
deprive	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
how	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
do	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
leisure	O
to	O
read	O
&	O
be	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
yr	O
Letters	O
though	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
fairly	O
my	O
Inability	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
a	O
punctual	O
Correspondant	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
procureing	O
yr	O
Indulg	O
e	O
nce	O
for	O
these	O
Irregularity	O
's	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
happen	O
--	O
but	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
intended	O
depriveing	O
myself	O
of	O
that	O
Pleasure	O
yr	O
Letters	O
never	O
faill	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
return	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
for	O
all	O
yr	O
Goodneſs	O
to	O
;	O
&	O
attention	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
:	O
bellieve	O
me	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
gratefuly	O
Sensible	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
had	O
prevailled	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
--	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
her	O
Health	O
&	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
very	O
Happy	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
both	O
of	O
you	O
may	O
Ever	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
best	O
Wishes	O
for	O
yr	O
Health	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
!	O
pray	O
wt	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
?	O
of	O
whom	O
neither	O
my	O
Lord	O
nor	O
you	O
mentions	O
one	O
Word	O
--	O
.	O
if	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
Northampton	B-place
pray	O
make	O
my	O
best	O
compts	O
:	O
acceptable	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
with	O
my	O
Br	O
:	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
&	O
am	O
very	O
Happy	O
with	O
him	O
&	O
his	O
familly	O
,	O
as	O
fine	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
:	O
this	O
place	O
too	O
is	O
dellightfull	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
s	O
return	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
Edr	B-place
:	I-place
this	O
I	O
imagine	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
28	O
th	O
or	O
29	O
th	O
mean	O
time	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
under	O
my	O
Brs	O
:	O
s	O
Cover	O
at	O
Schaw	O
Park	O
by	O
Alloa	B-place
part	O
of	O
yr	O
young	O
friends	O
are	O
here	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
are	O
well	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
much	O
yours	O
,	O
&	O
yr	B-pers
Mamma	I-pers
's	O
they	O
join	O
with	O
my	O
Br	O
:	O
&	O
me	O
&	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
familly	O
in	O
Affect	O
:	O
compts	O
:	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
ever	O
am	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
most	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
