TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
.	O
March	O
the	O
2	O
nd	O
-	O
1790	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Intention	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
one	O
Interruption	O
or	O
another	O
the	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
his	O
Departure	O
,	O
prevented	O
me	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
perhaps	O
a	O
Letter	O
may	O
be	O
more	O
acceptable	O
to	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
than	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
then	O
--	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
wou	O
'd	O
of	O
Course	O
,	O
tell	O
you	O
any	O
little	O
Article	O
of	O
News	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
during	O
his	O
Stay	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
very	O
agreeably	O
surprised	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
see	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
nor	O
how	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
good	O
accounts	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
charming	O
little	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Our	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
and	O
her	O
this	O
Season	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Disappointment	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
however	O
,	O
your	O
Reasons	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
take	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
comfort	O
ourselves	O
with	O
the	O
Idea	O
that	O
ce	O
qui	O
est	O
différé	O
,	O
n'est	O
pas	O
perdu	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
French	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
your	O
Cottage	O
(	O
as	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
very	O
commodious	O
and	O
pretty	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
do	O
Credit	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
Taste	O
in	O
Architecture	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
his	O
first	O
Eſsay	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
having	O
exchanged	O
his	O
Living	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
for	O
one	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
--	O
He	O
has	O
lost	O
considerably	O
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
is	O
not	O
discontented	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
that	O
sounds	O
rather	O
odd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
easy	O
about	O
holding	O
the	O
Living	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
and	O
never	O
residing	O
upon	O
it	O
--	O
This	O
one	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
will	O
serve	O
us	O
for	O
a	O
Villa	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
some	O
Amusement	O
to	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
think	O
all	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
with	O
his	O
Regiment	O
at	O
Nottingham	B-place
--	O
We	O
are	O
in	O
daily	O
Expectation	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
had	O
a	O
Concert	O
--	O
only	O
small	O
musical	O
Parties	O
en	O
famille	O
--	O
You	O
ask	O
me	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mathew	I-pers
--	O
she	O
no	O
longer	O
aſsists	O
me	O
by	O
singing	O
--	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Taste	O
to	O
despise	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Marchesi	I-pers
's	O
Style	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
with	O
so	O
little	O
Politeneſs	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Season	O
of	O
my	O
learning	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
our	O
Intercourse	O
ceased	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
another	O
great	O
Singer	O
here	O
now	O
--	O
Sigr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Pacchierotti	I-pers
--	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
mention	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
a	O
most	O
amiable	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
clever	O
,	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Opera-House	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
built	O
in	O
Leicester-Square	O
--	O
Gallini	B-pers
is	O
to	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
O'Reilly	I-pers
is	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Management	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Marchesi	I-pers
is	O
expected	O
in	O
London	B-place
this	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
Joy	O
.	O
Madame	B-pers
Mara	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
serious	O
Opera	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Theatre	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
is	O
made	O
as	O
commodious	O
as	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
spacious	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
--	O
but	O
certainly	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Opera	O
there	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
pretty	O
often	O
at	O
the	O
Play	O
this	O
Season	O
,	O
though	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
has	O
not	O
performed	O
--	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
near	O
losing	O
her	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
certainly	O
recovering	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
the	O
other	O
Morning	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
amazingly	O
reduced	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
Symptom	O
,	O
as	O
Bulk	O
after	O
so	O
violent	O
an	O
Illneſs	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
natural	O
--	O
consequently	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
unwholesome	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
tolerable	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
very	O
handsome	O
and	O
interesting	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
good	O
Accounts	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
ago	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Dublin	B-place
--	O
I	O
hear	O
oftener	O
of	O
her	O
than	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
lazy	O
Creature	O
at	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
nothing	O
wou	O
'd	O
make	O
my	O
Brother	O
more	O
happy	O
than	O
visiting	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
he	O
in	O
your	O
Neighbourhood	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
his	O
Regiment	O
will	O
be	O
sometimes	O
quartered	O
at	O
Manchester	B-place
You	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
your	O
Daughter	O
is	O
not	O
spoilt	O
--	O
You	O
are	O
mistaken	O
yourself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
imagined	O
she	O
was	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
too	O
well	O
persuaded	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
Judgement	O
in	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
Youth	O
,	O
to	O
fear	O
your	O
spoiling	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
GrandPapa	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
says	O
he	O
is	O
pretty	O
much	O
under	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
's	O
Dominion	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
join	O
in	O
best	O
Wishes	O
and	O
Regards	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
remain	O
affectionately	O
yours	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
