TOKEN	NE
Naples	B-place
Jan	O
27	O
--	O
The	O
various	O
frightfull	O
and	O
disagreeable	O
accidents	O
wch	O
.	O
befel	O
us	O
on	O
our	O
journey	O
really	O
made	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
incapable	O
of	O
holding	O
a	O
pen	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
recollection	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
adventures	O
affected	O
my	O
nerves	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
(	O
after	O
having	O
once	O
wrote	O
down	O
ye	O
.	O
circumstanc	O
es	O
)	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
Secretary	O
write	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
3	O
copies	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
give	O
(	O
those	O
friends	O
who	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
interest	O
themselves	O
about	O
me	O
)	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
wch-	O
yu	O
.	O
will	O
find	O
inclosed	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
attempted	O
writing	O
it	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
still	O
feel	O
as	O
if	O
ye	O
.	O
Horses	O
were	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
courage	O
for	O
ever	O
--	O
Our	O
journey	O
thro	O
'	O
Holland	B-place
was	O
delightful	O
--	O
neither	O
fears	O
or	O
difficulties	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Hoorn	B-place
,	O
Medenblick	B-place
,	O
&	O
Hemaer	B-place
&	O
where	O
enchanted	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
scene	O
--	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Antwerp	B-place
&	O
to	O
Spa	B-place
where	O
we	O
staid	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Duſseldorf	B-place
,	O
to	O
Bonn	B-place
from	O
whence	O
we	O
embark	O
'd	O
&	O
went	O
up	O
ye	O
.	O
Rhine	O
to	O
Mayence	B-place
,	O
from	O
thence	O
by	O
land	O
to	O
Manheim	B-place
,	O
to	O
Augsbourg	B-place
--	O
Inspruck	B-place
&	O
to	O
Mantua	B-place
where	O
our	O
ill	O
luck	O
began	O
,	O
by	O
terrible	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
near	O
being	O
carried	O
away	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
Po	O
,	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
Torrent	O
--	O
we	O
rested	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
at	O
Florence	B-place
&	O
Bologna	B-place
,	O
&	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Radicofani	B-place
found	O
ye	O
.	O
Old	O
Chateau	O
there	O
(	O
wch	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
only	O
lodging	O
place	O
on	O
a	O
n	O
bare	O
bleak	O
Mountain	O
)	O
crack	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
&	O
partly	O
shook	O
down	O
by	O
repeated	O
Earthquakes	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
however	O
obliged	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
House	O
trembled	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
Night	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
burst	O
our	O
door	O
wch	O
.	O
was	O
bolted	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
wth-	O
the	O
accident	O
,	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
inclose	O
,	O
after	O
wch	O
.	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
at	O
Rome	B-place
to	O
wait	O
for	O
our	O
poor	O
Courier	O
&	O
recruit	O
ourselves	O
wch	O
I	O
(	O
however	O
)	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
one	O
evening	O
out	O
except	O
when	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
launch	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
eight	O
Ladies	O
to	O
present	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
terrible	O
piece	O
of	O
Work	O
about	O
Ldy	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
ye	O
.	O
ninth	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
improper	O
in	O
my	O
situation	O
either	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
or	O
to	O
attempt	O
presenting	O
her	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
as	O
I	O
obliged	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
all	O
I	O
present	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
above	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
that	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Maynard	I-pers
--	O
was	O
here	O
in	O
another	O
Character	O
with	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
&	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Betty	I-pers
whom	O
yu	O
know	O
were	O
at	O
Turin	B-place
in	O
ye	O
same	O
Situation	O
wth	O
us	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
right	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
easy	O
tho	O
'	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Maynard	I-pers
says	O
he	O
will	O
complain	O
to	O
our	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
my	O
not	O
receiving	O
Ldy-	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
--	O
a	O
fine	O
complaint	O
!	O
he	O
says	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
presented	O
immediately	O
to	O
our	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
when	O
she	O
gets	O
home	O
&	O
that	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
can	O
not	O
refuse	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
doubt	O
that	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
&	O
is	O
still	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
hunting	O
steats	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
expect	O
him	O
tomorrow	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
my	O
hurries	O
.	O
Naples	B-place
27	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
1778	O
