TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
immediately	O
after	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
Suffolk	B-place
I	O
enclosed	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
a	O
Post	O
Bill	O
for	O
Twenty	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
payable	O
at	O
Meſsrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ransom	I-pers
Morland	I-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	O
And	O
as	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
has	O
this	O
day	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
dated	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
your	O
Compts	O
.	O
without	O
any	O
mention	O
whatever	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
I	O
conclude	O
it	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
therefore	O
my	O
apprehensions	O
lest	O
my	O
letter	O
may	O
have	O
miscarried	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Bill	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
by	O
my	O
desire	O
directed	O
the	O
letter	O
more	O
distinctly	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
myself	O
saw	O
it	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
careful	O
Postman	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
's	I-pers
desiring	O
that	O
the	O
proper	O
precautions	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
observed	O
if	O
the	O
Bill	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
offer	O
'd	O
for	O
Payment	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Bill	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
hands	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
immediate	O
notice	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
particular	O
dislike	O
to	O
sending	O
Bills	O
in	O
letters	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
hereafter	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
draw	O
upon	O
Meſsrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ransom	I-pers
Morland	I-pers
&	I-pers
amp	I-pers
;	I-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
regularly	O
as	O
your	O
Interest	O
money	O
shall	O
become	O
due	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
directions	O
for	O
your	O
punctual	O
payment	O
.	O
The	O
Bill	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
sent	O
some	O
days	O
sooner	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
detain	O
'd	O
at	O
Stanton	B-place
by	O
the	O
illneſs	O
of	O
my	O
Curate	O
,	O
which	O
threw	O
the	O
whole	O
busineſs	O
of	O
my	O
Parish	O
upon	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
return	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
June	O
to	O
continue	O
till	O
November	O
&	O
my	O
whole	O
Family	O
is	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
&	O
got	O
things	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
their	O
reception	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
hear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
my	O
God	O
Daughter	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affectionate	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
--	O
249	O
April	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
--	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
