TOKEN	NE
Pheasant	B-place
Grove	I-place
Tuesday	O
Night	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Your	O
Animation	O
&	O
midnight	O
Livelineſs	O
,	O
have	O
affected	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Marianne	B-pers
are	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
even	O
drowsey	O
as	O
I	O
usually	O
am	O
,	O
should	O
much	O
prefer	O
a	O
chearful	O
Chatting	O
Hour	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
still	O
&	O
composed	O
Occupation	O
of	O
putting	O
on	O
my	O
Night	O
Cap	O
,	O
&	O
going	O
to	O
Rest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
to	O
begin	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
mighty	O
change	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
have	O
miſsed	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
you	O
at	O
Courteen-hall	O
--	O
we	O
drank	O
your	O
Health	O
,	O
&	O
all	O
agreed	O
you	O
were	O
tired	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
having	O
walked	O
about	O
with	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Journey	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
's	O
Leg	O
is	O
better	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
good	O
dear	O
little	O
Louisa	B-pers
quite	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
this	O
Morning	O
very	O
pleasantly	O
,	O
first	O
visiting	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Weddel	I-pers
,	O
&	O
then	O
lounging	O
(	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
that	O
Word	O
,	O
)	O
about	O
Lord	B-pers
Campden	I-pers
s	O
Grounds	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Day	O
,	O
&	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
comfortable	O
&	O
agreable	O
.	O
Tomorrow	O
I	O
leave	O
this	O
pretty	O
Place	O
,	O
&	O
my	O
dr	O
&	O
kind	O
Friend	O
;	O
I	O
expect	O
my	O
Husband	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
all	O
is	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
his	O
Reception	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
say	O
Adieu	O
,	O
my	O
dr	O
:	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Kind	O
Remembrances	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Kiſs	O
d	O
r	O
:	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
tell	O
yr	O
:	O
self	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Yrs	O
:	O
Affly	O
PC	B-pers
you	O
are	O
always	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
appear	O
interested	O
about	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Therefore	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
--	O
all	O
our	O
Letters	O
are	O
very	O
comfortable	O
and	O
satisfactory	O
.	O
Remember	O
me	O
most	O
Affectionately	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
kiſs	O
the	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
Louisa	B-pers
for	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
Affectionately	O
yours	O
Marianne	B-pers
--	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
We	O
wished	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
our	O
letter	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
upon	O
your	O
arrival	O
at	O
Birch	B-place
Hall	I-place
for	O
which	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
will	O
now	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
prevented	O
writing	O
until	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
Dr	O
Richard	B-pers
this	O
morning	O
gives	O
us	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
arrived	O
safe	O
&	O
in	O
good	O
time	O
on	O
Monday	O
at	O
C	O
.	O
Hall	O
.	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
doubt	O
if	O
the	O
weather	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
as	O
fine	O
as	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
was	O
lovely	O
.	O
Poor	O
Wm	B-pers
has	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
fortunate	O
in	O
getting	O
his	O
Hay	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
this	O
Post	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Dr	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
She	O
complains	O
that	O
her	O
Elementary	O
Head	O
,	O
has	O
sadly	O
felt	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
this	O
damp	O
&	O
rainy	O
Novem	O
ber	O
Summer	O
.	O
She	O
intends	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
pleasure	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
your	O
society	O
at	O
P.	B-place
Grove	I-place
,	O
nor	O
with	O
what	O
satisfaction	O
I	O
shall	O
look	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
renewal	O
of	O
it	O
next	O
Spring	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
deep	O
in	O
Visiting	O
&	O
Letter	O
Debts	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
now	O
indulge	O
myself	O
in	O
scribbling	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
wait	O
with	O
impatience	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
your	O
good	O
Husband	O
s	O
ancle	O
does	O
;	O
how	O
you	O
liked	O
your	O
Visit	O
to	O
poor	O
Dr	O
.	O
William	B-pers
;	O
how	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
friends	O
at	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
