TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
expreſs	O
my	O
obligations	O
for	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
letters	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
yesterday	O
&	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
aware	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
danger	O
that	O
attends	O
my	O
dear	O
daughter	O
's	O
disorder	O
my	O
affliction	O
&	O
anxiety	O
are	O
inexpreſsible	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
precisely	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
here	O
,	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
greatest	O
apprehensions	O
for	O
her	O
but	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
inflated	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
dreadful	O
manner	O
with	O
excruciating	O
pain	O
she	O
returned	O
to	O
her	O
usual	O
shape	O
in	O
one	O
night	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
since	O
frequent	O
relapses	O
,	O
I	O
consider	O
her	O
in	O
very	O
great	O
danger	O
&	O
am	O
therefore	O
anxious	O
beyond	O
measure	O
that	O
the	O
ablest	O
advice	O
may	O
be	O
immediately	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
Having	O
had	O
many	O
opportunities	O
of	O
discovering	O
my	O
dearest	O
daughter	O
's	O
excellent	O
disposition	O
during	O
her	O
late	O
severe	O
trials	O
,	O
I	O
flatterd	O
myself	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
permitted	O
to	O
enjoy	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
this	O
life	O
,	O
some	O
years	O
of	O
happineſs	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
granted	O
,	O
it	O
woud	O
ill	O
become	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
dispensations	O
of	O
providence	O
with	O
patience	O
&	O
humble	O
resignation	O
;	O
the	O
reflexion	O
of	O
my	O
having	O
acquitted	O
myself	O
to	O
this	O
dear	O
&	O
invaluable	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
crisis	O
of	O
her	O
affliction	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
principal	O
consolation	O
,	O
shoud	O
it	O
be	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
Providence	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
myself	O
so	O
overcome	O
with	O
distreſs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
my	O
quitting	O
this	O
painful	O
subject	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
without	O
repeating	O
my	O
most	O
grateful	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
your	O
very	O
affectionate	O
attention	O
,	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
May	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
My	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
49	O
.	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
