TOKEN	NE
Account	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
Queens	O
House	O
Friday	O
16	O
th	O
:	O
Febry	O
.	O
1781	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
oClock	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
--	O
Augusta	B-pers
--	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
--	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
(	O
&	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Attendants	O
viz	O
:	O
Lord	B-pers
Southampton	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
John	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
)	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Governor	O
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
)	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
aſsembled	O
in	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
first	O
apartment	O
--	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
their	O
M	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
Company	O
waited	O
--	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
drawing	O
Room	O
ceremony	O
wch	O
.	O
lasted	O
some	O
time	O
--	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Sal	O
l	O
oon	O
were	O
then	O
thrown	O
open	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
younger	O
part	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
family	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
--	O
viz	O
:	O
Prince	B-pers
Ernest	I-pers
,	O
Prince	B-pers
Augustus	I-pers
--	O
Prince	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
Prince	B-pers
Octavious	I-pers
,	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
,	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
and	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Prince	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
&	O
Prince	B-pers
William	I-pers
absent	O
the	O
first	O
at	O
Hanover	B-place
--	O
the	O
lat	O
t	O
er	O
at	O
Sea	O
)	O
The	O
Ball	O
began	O
with	O
Country	O
Dances	O
&	O
every	O
two	O
dances	O
partners	O
chang	O
'd	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
&	O
Augusta	B-pers
danced	O
wth	O
.	O
P.	B-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Westmorland	I-pers
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
;	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
&	O
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
danced	O
together	O
till	O
Supper	O
time	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
)	O
&	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
)	O
--	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
danc	O
'd	O
wth	O
:	O
&	O
ask	O
'd	O
most	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ladies	O
--	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
apartments	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
and	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
walk	O
about	O
&	O
make	O
Card	O
Parties	O
--	O
In	O
one	O
Room	O
was	O
Tea	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
with	O
Pages	O
and	O
proper	O
attendants	O
--	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
Room	O
&	O
other	O
apartments	O
were	O
entirely	O
free	O
not	O
crouded	O
wth-	O
Lookers	O
on	O
or	O
attendants	O
.	O
the	O
young	O
Princes	O
&	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
proper	O
hours	O
--	O
Princeſs	B-pers
R	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
staid	O
the	O
conclusion	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
--	O
Their	O
M	O
:	O
Princeſs	B-pers
R	I-pers
&	O
A	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
4	O
Ladies	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Bedchamber	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
private	O
stair	O
to	O
their	O
Supper	O
Room	O
viz	O
one	O
of	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
apartments	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
&	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
rest	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Company	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Great	O
Stairs	O
--	O
in	O
one	O
Apartment	O
was	O
a	O
Table	O
for	O
the	O
Chaperons	O
--	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Dancers	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
was	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
head	O
,	O
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
as	O
Chaperon	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
lower	O
end	O
--	O
After	O
Supper	O
they	O
Return	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q——	I-pers
apartments	O
Country	O
Dances	O
were	O
renew	O
'd	O
and	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
concluded	O
with	O
Minuets	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
sat	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Ball	O
Room	O
ye	O
.	O
Whole	O
Eveg	O
.	O
&	O
had	O
the	O
Ladies	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
dancers	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
to	O
sit	O
next	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Whist	O
after	O
Supper	O
.	O
About	O
½	O
past	O
five	O
the	O
Ball	O
ended	O
.	O
The	O
Ladies	O
were	O
all	O
Dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
Sacks	O
--	O
&	O
wore	O
long	O
lappets	O
.	O
Dancers	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Princeſs	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Prince	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Princeſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Campbell	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
:	I-pers
Talbot	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
Waldegrave	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
John	I-pers
Clinton	I-pers
Ldy.Hart	B-pers
.	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Lewisham	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Lewisham	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eliz	I-pers
.	I-pers
Conway	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Fairford	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Isabella	I-pers
Conway	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tryphena	I-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
Lord	B-pers
Courtown	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Thynne	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Legge	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
North	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Wyndham	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
North	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
West	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
North	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
C	I-pers
Sackville	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Fitz-Roy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
Philip	I-pers
Hales	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Hotham	I-pers
Who	O
did	O
not	O
dance	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Argyll	I-pers
Dutcheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Argyle	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Roxburghe	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
Holderneſse	I-pers
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Montague	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Peterborough	I-pers
)	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Waldegrave	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Waldegrave	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gower	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gower	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Guilford	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Egremont	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hertford	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hertford	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hillsborough	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Courtown	I-pers
,	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Aylesbury	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
North	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
Ldy.C	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Ld.G	B-pers
Germaine	I-pers
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Southampton	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
North	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Southampton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Bruyeres	I-pers
