TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
has	O
been	O
prevented	O
hitherto	O
by	O
illneſs	O
from	O
calling	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickison	I-pers
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
intends	O
herself	O
that	O
pleasure	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
Dickison	I-pers
would	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
dine	O
in	O
Portman	O
Square	O
either	O
on	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Sunday	O
next	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
would	O
consider	O
themselves	O
as	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
them	O
hope	O
the	O
short	O
notice	O
will	O
be	O
excused	O
on	O
acct	O
of	O
their	O
short	O
stay	O
in	O
town	B-place
,	O
&	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
early	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
O'clock	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickison	I-pers
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
makes	O
early	O
hours	O
neceſsary	O
.	O
Thursday	O
Aprill	O
18	O
1799	O
