TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
laid	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
greatest	O
poſsible	O
obligations	O
by	O
your	O
unwearied	O
attentions	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
unfortunate	O
daughter	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
fatal	O
moment	O
has	O
paſs	O
'd	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
entrust	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
funeral	O
to	O
my	O
worthy	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
private	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
not	O
unbecoming	O
the	O
beloved	O
object	O
,	O
every	O
exp	O
ect	O
ense	O
shall	O
be	O
immediately	O
defray	O
'd	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
regard	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
's	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
behaved	O
with	O
great	O
attention	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
I	O
expreſsly	O
forbid	O
that	O
her	O
body	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
open	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
knowing	O
what	O
a	O
dangerous	O
disorder	O
might	O
be	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
putrid	O
effluvia	O
;	O
as	O
this	O
apprehension	O
is	O
is	O
founded	O
in	O
reason	O
,	O
I	O
shudder	O
at	O
exposing	O
the	O
lives	O
of	O
good	O
&	O
innocent	O
persons	O
to	O
any	O
hazard	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
reason	O
I	O
recommend	O
that	O
the	O
funeral	O
shoud	O
be	O
accellerated	O
;	O
with	O
my	O
best	O
regards	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
your	O
dear	O
Daughter	O
I	O
remain	O
your	O
Faithful	O
,	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Brock	O
St	O
.	O
Bath	B-place
June	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
this	O
letter	O
that	O
somebody	O
had	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
prepare	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
body	O
opened	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
proposed	O
such	O
a	O
neceſsary	O
Inspection	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
J	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
