TOKEN	NE
June	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
1782	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
your	O
three	O
interesting	O
Letters	O
without	O
longing	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
they	O
give	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
feel	O
I	O
am	O
punishing	O
instead	O
of	O
rewarding	O
your	O
kindness	O
,	O
by	O
intruding	O
on	O
your	O
time	O
without	O
a	O
probability	O
of	O
saying	O
one	O
word	O
that	O
can	O
either	O
interest	O
or	O
amuse	O
you	O
.	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
with	O
to	O
condole	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Loſs	O
of	O
her	O
Friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Pulteney	I-pers
,	O
wch	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
hurt	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
today	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
Love	O
.	O
Her	O
Conversation	O
&	O
Friendship	O
is	O
a	O
are	O
delightful	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
my	O
Situation	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
former	O
such	O
an	O
Appendage	O
to	O
Deal	O
Castle	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
ye	O
Kingdom	O
can	O
boast	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
confined	O
to	O
place	O
or	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
looks	O
ever	O
to	O
Eternity	O
,	O
for	O
virtuous	O
Friendship	O
surely	O
outlives	O
the	O
Grave	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
recd	O
.	O
the	O
Letter	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
at	O
your	O
return	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
but	O
am	O
sorry	O
it	O
found	O
you	O
so	O
unwell	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
from	O
this	O
Influenza	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
turn	O
'd	O
every	O
place	O
into	O
an	O
Hospital	O
.	O
thank	O
God	O
we	O
have	O
escaped	O
here	O
,	O
thō	O
many	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
at	O
Deal	B-place
.	O
My	O
Son	O
's	O
Arrival	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
most	O
joyful	O
Event	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
he	O
is	O
thought	O
to	O
look	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
eſsentially	O
so	O
,	O
thō	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
free	O
from	O
Cold	O
,	O
his	O
Stay	O
was	O
short	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
visit	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
poor	O
Made	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Fite	I-pers
does	O
not	O
gain	O
ground	O
,	O
it	O
really	O
will	O
be	O
unfortunate	O
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
Studies	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
remain	O
an	O
Invalid	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
distreſsing	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
as	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
situated	O
.	O
My	O
Spanish	O
Reading	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
fancy	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
's	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
tis	O
very	O
entertaining	O
&	O
interesting	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Visits	O
to	O
day	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
great	O
Sea	O
Commanders	O
that	O
are	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
blocking	O
up	O
the	O
Dutch	O
in	O
the	O
Texel	B-place
,	O
a	O
great	O
Event	O
to	O
me	O
such	O
Visitors	O
,	O
who	O
literally	O
know	O
not	O
a	O
Soul	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
but	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
&	O
the	O
latter	O
has	O
been	O
long	O
confined	O
with	O
Illneſs	O
.	O
If	O
ever	O
you	O
hear	O
our	O
Names	O
here	O
mention	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
our	O
Stay	O
is	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
suppose	O
yr	O
.	O
Ansr	O
.	O
will	O
be	O
that	O
you	O
hear	O
nothing	O
abt	O
.	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
certainly	O
mends	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
conclude	O
they	O
will	O
continue	O
him	O
here	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
run	O
on	O
(	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
talk	O
'd	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
use	O
many	O
more	O
words	O
to	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
convince	O
you	O
how	O
unwillingly	O
I	O
quit	O
you	O
even	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
without	O
a	O
poſsibility	O
of	O
a	O
Word	O
in	O
return	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
