TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
termination	O
of	O
Hostilities	O
with	O
America	B-place
he	O
had	O
presented	O
a	O
Memorial	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
stating	O
the	O
impracticability	O
of	O
conquering	O
America	B-place
&	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Independence	O
of	O
that	O
Country	O
must	O
be	O
established	O
--	O
he	O
offered	O
a	O
Plan	O
for	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Consideration	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
repay	O
this	O
Country	O
for	O
the	O
immense	O
Sums	O
expended	O
in	O
the	O
prosecut	O
ing	O
ion	O
of	O
the	O
War	O
--	O
reestablish	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
&	O
ruin	O
France	B-place
--	O
this	O
plan	O
was	O
to	O
withdraw	O
the	O
whole	O
force	O
from	O
America	B-place
at	O
once	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
Transports	O
sufficient	O
&	O
ready	O
&	O
employ	O
the	O
whole	O
Army	O
in	O
conquering	O
the	B-place
French	I-place
West	I-place
India	I-place
Islands	I-place
which	O
he	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Minister	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
easy	O
Task	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
unprovided	O
against	O
so	O
powerful	O
an	O
Attack	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
lamented	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
induce	O
Lord	B-pers
North	I-pers
to	O
pursue	O
Measures	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
advantageous	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
&	O
so	O
honorably	O
to	O
himself	O
