TOKEN	NE
14	O
Dear	O
Sr	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
Seen	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
you	O
letter	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
known	O
then	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
all	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
joy	O
,	O
and	O
sorrow	O
,	O
which	O
befalls	O
you	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
rusht	O
to	O
my	O
heart	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
feal	O
more	O
for	O
Yourselves	O
then	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
town	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
will	O
permit	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
upon	O
her	O
halve	O
after	O
two	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
for	O
not	O
longer	O
then	O
She	O
can	O
let	O
me	O
Stay	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
all	O
!	O
Ever	O
your	O
true	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Hampton	B-place
Wednesday	O
Octr	O
.	O
the	O
26	O
:	O
To	O
E	B-pers
:	I-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
32	O
London	B-place
