TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Tuesday	O
28	O
Decbr	O
1779	O
--	O
My	O
Dearest	O
--	O
Tho	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
very	O
lively	O
to	O
comunicate	O
yet	O
my	O
Vanity	O
aſsures	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
your	O
Friend	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
unacceptable	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
&	O
happy	O
,	O
whether	O
all	O
the	O
Company	O
is	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
aver	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
masks	O
of	O
Ennui	O
in	O
a	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
who	O
upon	O
Paper	O
shall	O
be	O
nameleſs	O
.	O
The	O
Weather	O
certainly	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
propitious	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
never	O
walked	O
,	O
therefore	O
except	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
my	O
Gentlemen	O
till	O
4	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
I	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
as	O
usual	O
I	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
Coffee	O
then	O
leave	O
them	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
&	O
return	O
when	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
is	O
so	O
gracious	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
one	O
I	O
may	O
go	O
&	O
drink	O
Tea	O
,	O
our	O
three	O
first	O
Evgs	O
after	O
that	O
were	O
spent	O
in	O
a	O
Circle	O
/for	O
tho	O
I	O
tried	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
destroy	O
it/	O
round	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagedorn	I-pers
s	O
Fire	O
till	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
last	O
Night	O
we	O
had	O
Musick	O
&	O
a	O
Commerce	O
Party	O
which	O
I	O
liked	O
,	O
it	O
consisted	O
of	O
the	O
Princeſs	O
's	O
,	O
Genl	B-pers
Budé	I-pers
Col	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
comfortable	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
delight	O
the	O
knowing	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
Dearest	O
by	O
this	O
dull	O
Journal	O
how	O
very	O
little	O
I	O
really	O
see	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
rains	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Princes	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
Hunt	O
once	O
before	O
they	O
leave	O
Windsor	B-place
,	O
last	O
Night	O
they	O
got	O
Straits	O
as	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
this	O
Morgs	O
diversion	O
but	O
use	O
leſs	O
,	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
ll	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
Weather	O
that	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
ingly	O
have	O
sent	O
our	O
Foo	O
tmen	O
,	O
this	O
my	O
Drt	O
is	O
a	O
fruitful	O
Narrative	O
of	O
our	O
Xm̄as	O
Hollidays	O
Amusement	O
,	O
tho	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
comfortable	O
circumstance	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
viz	O
that	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
breakfast	O
till	O
pt	O
nine	O
,	O
by	O
wc̄h	O
means	O
we	O
avoid	O
dreſsing	O
by	O
Candle	O
Light	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Affectionately	O
Yr	O
.	O
MC	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
