TOKEN	NE
Copy	O
of	O
what	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
was	O
graciously	O
pleased	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
a	O
blank	O
leaf	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
she	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
giving	O
.	O
Haller	B-pers
intended	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
this	O
Book	O
for	O
his	O
Daughter	O
s	O
happineſs	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
claim	O
the	O
title	O
of	O
a	O
Parent	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
give	O
this	O
work	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
as	O
a	O
proof	O
how	O
truly	O
I	O
interest	O
myself	O
in	O
Hers	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Queens	O
House	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
January	O
1781	O
London	B-place
.	O
