TOKEN	NE
There	O
is	O
a	O
Spirit	O
of	O
curiosity	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
Letters	O
going	O
from	O
hence	O
which	O
prevents	O
my	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
otherwise	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
constrain	O
'd	O
unleſs	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
oppertunity	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
at	O
present	O
have	O
)	O
of	O
sending	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
Roman	O
Post	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
past	O
inquiry	O
,	O
your	O
last	O
of	O
ye	O
27	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
gave	O
me	O
true	O
pleasure	O
,	O
as	O
almost	O
every	O
line	O
is	O
a	O
fresh	O
proof	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
&	O
Sensibility	O
of	O
your	O
heart	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
situations	O
I	O
should	O
wish	O
you	O
(	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
quiet	O
)	O
a	O
leſs	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Yours	O
there	O
is	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
claim	O
upon	O
you	O
for	O
gratitude	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
unworthy	O
of	O
the	O
bleſsings	O
you	O
enjoy	O
if	O
you	O
felt	O
them	O
leſs	O
Sensibly	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
fruits	O
of	O
that	O
Sensibility	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
redoubled	O
ardour	O
in	O
fulfilling	O
those	O
dutys	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
Heart	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
upon	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
s	O
recovery	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
proper	O
oppertunity	O
)	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
most	O
respectful	O
&	O
Dutifull	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
last	O
was	O
dated	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
ye	O
28	O
th	O
.	O
or	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Janry	O
from	O
Caserta	B-place
where	O
we	O
remain	O
'd	O
(	O
except	O
ten	O
days	O
of	O
the	O
Carnival	O
)	O
till	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
Calm	O
of	O
Caserta	B-place
for	O
the	O
hurry	O
of	O
Naples	B-place
,	O
however	O
my	O
pennance	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
very	O
long	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
this	O
fortnight	O
at	O
our	O
Villa	O
near	O
Portici	B-place
where	O
the	O
Court	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
lovely	O
situation	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
Volcano	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
throwing	O
up	O
liquid	O
fire	O
)	O
&	O
the	O
only	O
objection	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
other	O
circumstances	O
which	O
interrupt	O
my	O
quiet	O
more	O
than	O
our	O
neighbour	O
Vesuvius	O
,	O
for	O
example	O
,	O
to	O
morrow	O
is	O
the	B-pers
Empreſs	I-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
day	O
&	O
the	O
Grand	O
Maitreſse	O
has	O
just	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
ball	O
at	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Alas	O
!	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
carry	O
three	O
English	O
Ladies	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
Ly	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
is	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
James	O
's	O
powder	O
has	O
been	O
almost	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Specifick	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
fevers	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
refused	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
my	O
Duty	O
not	O
)	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
vexation	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
.	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
has	O
always	O
,	O
&	O
still	O
does	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
right	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Her	B-pers
Majty	I-pers
.	I-pers
thinks	O
herself	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
part	O
I	O
acted	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
surprised	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
keep	O
you	O
in	O
suspence	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Caserta	B-place
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
Marsico	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
favourite	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Bedchamber	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
refused	O
admittance	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
forced	O
his	O
way	O
into	O
his	O
apartment	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
surrounded	O
by	O
Physicians	O
who	O
all	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
four	O
hours	O
to	O
live	O
,	O
Ld	B-pers
M——	I-pers
then	O
insisted	O
upon	O
administring	O
the	O
powders	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
succeſs	O
--	O
&	O
the	O
Patient	O
was	O
soon	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
Ly	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
then	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
nursing	O
character	O
offerd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Prince	O
s	O
broths	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
attention	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
the	O
y	O
family	O
tried	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
what	O
way	O
they	O
could	O
best	O
expreſs	O
their	O
gratitude	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Maynards	I-pers
,	O
who	O
let	O
them	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
most	O
desired	O
was	O
a	O
presentation	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	I-pers
Naples	I-pers
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
difficult	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prince	O
s	O
Sister	O
(	O
a	O
Lady	O
of	O
the	O
bedchamber	O
)	O
undertook	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
maitreſse	O
who	O
positively	O
refused	O
to	O
undertake	O
it	O
unleſs	O
I	O
desired	O
it	O
,	O
She	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
threw	O
herself	O
at	O
her	O
feet	O
in	O
tears	O
,	O
&	O
told	O
her	B-pers
Majty	I-pers
.	I-pers
it	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
service	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
her	O
family	O
to	O
permit	O
her	O
to	O
present	O
Ly	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
after	O
two	O
hours	O
begging	O
&	O
praying	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
consented	O
upon	O
condition	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
disagreable	O
to	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
was	O
sounded	O
,	O
&	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
perfectly	O
indifferent	O
to	O
him	O
provided	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
channel	O
of	O
her	O
presentation	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
carried	O
in	O
private	O
by	O
Pce	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marsico	I-pers
's	O
Sister	O
but	O
without	O
the	O
Grand	O
maitreſse	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
said	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
glad	O
her	O
humanity	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
subjects	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
an	O
oppertunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
her	O
well	O
--	O
this	O
satisfied	O
Ld	B-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
for	O
the	O
time	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
The	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
gave	O
so	O
open	O
a	O
mortification	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
shew	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
had	O
been	O
purely	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
intreaties	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
resist	O
--	O
You	O
know	O
the	B-pers
Q——n	I-pers
s	O
character	O
&	O
I	O
leave	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
reflexions	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
proceeding	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
only	O
add	O
the	O
Speech	O
of	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
of	O
fashion	O
to	O
some	O
Neapolitans	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
--	O
“	O
en	O
verité	O
Meſsieurs	O
vous	O
êtes	O
bien	O
heureux	O
d'avoir	O
des	O
Souverains	O
qui	O
veut	O
bien	O
se	O
charger	O
de	O
la	O
recconoiſsance	O
de	O
leurs	O
sujets	O
.	O
”	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
been	O
reading	O
Monsr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
's	O
Letters	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
there	O
are	O
parts	O
of	O
them	O
which	O
entertain	O
'd	O
me	O
much	O
particularly	O
his	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
simplicity	O
&	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
near	O
the	O
Glaciere	B-place
de	I-place
Buet	I-place
--	O
I	O
k	O
h	O
ave	O
had	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Peasants	O
of	O
the	O
Valley	B-place
of	I-place
Chamouni	I-place
who	O
are	O
quite	O
in	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
those	O
he	O
mentions	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
traits	O
of	O
their	O
Character	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
honor	O
&	O
love	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
so	O
unspoil	O
'd	O
a	O
race	O
,	O
but	O
Monsr	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
has	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Switzerland	B-place
very	O
worthy	O
his	O
notice	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
imagine	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Bailliage	B-place
of	I-place
Frutingen	I-place
twelve	O
leagues	O
from	O
the	O
City	B-place
of	I-place
Berne	I-place
--	O
the	O
extent	O
of	O
the	O
Bailliage	O
is	O
very	O
considerable	O
&	O
the	O
country	O
exceſsively	O
rich	O
&	O
fertile	O
&	O
the	O
union	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
as	O
great	O
as	O
their	O
Simplicity	O
(	O
&	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
I	O
am	O
tempted	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
former	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
customs	O
is	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
quite	O
peculiar	O
to	O
themselves	O
,	O
when	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
declares	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
building	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
day	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
proposes	O
beginning	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
report	O
goes	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
setts	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
workmen	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
engaged	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
sometimes	O
twenty	O
,	O
thirty	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
&	O
none	O
come	O
empty	O
handed	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
little	O
wooden	O
pails	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
one	O
brings	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
cake	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
they	O
consign	O
to	O
the	O
Mistreſs	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
after	O
having	O
wash	O
'd	O
their	O
pails	O
while	O
they	O
work	O
makes	O
baignés	O
(	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
cake	O
they	O
are	O
fond	O
of	O
)	O
&	O
puts	O
a	O
portion	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
each	O
pail	O
--	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
other	O
workmen	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
&	O
so	O
on	O
every	O
day	O
till	O
they	O
have	O
finish	O
'd	O
building	O
the	O
house	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
these	O
workmen	O
are	O
the	O
Farmers	O
&	O
their	O
Servants	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Bailliage	O
who	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
can	O
spare	O
give	O
one	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
three	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
days	O
labour	O
to	O
aſsist	O
their	O
Brother	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Bailliage	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
finish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
particular	O
friends	O
bring	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
sometimes	O
a	O
window	O
is	O
the	O
present	O
of	O
one	O
friend	O
,	O
sometimes	O
two	O
club	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Arms	O
of	O
the	O
presenter	O
(	O
for	O
they	O
all	O
pretend	O
to	O
Arms	O
)	O
is	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
coulour	O
'd	O
Glaſs	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
--	O
when	O
all	O
this	O
is	O
finish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
farmer	O
&	O
his	O
Wife	O
send	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
aſsisted	O
in	O
building	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
feast	O
,	O
where	O
nothing	O
is	O
spared	O
,	O
(	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
must	O
mention	O
one	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
never	O
forgot	O
--	O
viz	O
--	O
the	O
bottoms	O
of	O
sugar	O
loaves	O
hollow	O
'd	O
out	O
into	O
cups	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
thick	O
cream	O
which	O
Frutigen	B-place
is	O
famous	O
for	O
,	O
)	O
all	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
inhabitant	O
&	O
native	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
whose	O
truth	O
I	O
can	O
depend	O
upon	O
.	O
--	O
all	O
this	O
bonhomie	O
&	O
friendlineſs	O
of	O
heart	O
(	O
when	O
I	O
reflect	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
often	O
makes	O
mine	O
ache	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
difference	O
of	O
manners	O
&	O
sentiments	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
obliged	O
to	O
live	O
among	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
live	O
here	O
a	O
hundred	O
Years	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
ways	O
of	O
this	O
Italian	O
World	O
--	O
but	O
thank	O
God	O
both	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
resources	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
house	O
which	O
makes	O
our	O
comfort	O
independent	O
of	O
them	O
&	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
small	O
society	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
i	O
t	O
n	O
any	O
country	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
happy	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
people	O
now	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
England	O
(	O
wth	O
.	O
our	O
Small	O
fortune	O
)	O
we	O
dare	O
not	O
look	O
homewards	O
,	O
unleſs	O
it	O
was	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
pleasure	O
to	O
command	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
Services	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
probable	O
.	O
--	O
as	O
the	O
case	O
is	O
,	O
My	O
Dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
unlikely	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
that	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
more	O
frequently	O
.	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
wish	O
to	O
See	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
me	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
&	O
will	O
give	O
yourself	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
a	O
Painters	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
(	O
an	O
honest	O
simple	O
little	O
Soul	O
worthy	O
of	O
being	O
an	O
inhabitant	O
of	O
Buet	B-place
)	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
us	O
upon	O
canvas	O
,	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
painting	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
Zoffani	B-pers
s	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
succeeds	O
admirably	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
add	O
his	O
direction	O
afterwards	O
for	O
I	O
must	O
ask	O
it	O
of	O
Sr	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
joins	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
kind	O
--	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
Ly	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
pray	O
make	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
esteem	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Yr	O
Sincerely	O
Affectionate	O
Aunt	O
C	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Wednesday	O
May	O
ye	O
12	O
th	O
--	O
Allen	B-pers
s	O
direction	O
is	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Taſsy	I-pers
s	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Leicester	B-place
Fields	I-place
--	O
Taſsy	B-pers
makes	O
Seals	O
&	O
pastes	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Moston	I-pers
knows	O
where	O
Allen	B-pers
lives	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
read	O
over	O
my	O
letter	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
legible	O
--	O
