TOKEN	NE
Gt	O
Cumberland	O
St	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
13	O
th	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
am	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
request	O
,	O
happy	O
to	O
report	O
to	O
you	O
progreſs	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
of	O
continued	O
good	O
Accts	O
:	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
M	I-pers
:	I-pers
continues	O
daily	O
recovery	O
&	O
the	O
Little	O
One	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
--	O
She	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
very	O
sincere	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
congratulations	O
&	O
cordial	O
good	O
Wishes	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
late	O
&	O
comfortable	O
addition	O
to	O
our	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
My	O
Sister	O
immediately	O
on	O
receipt	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
well	O
at	O
present	O
excepting	O
a	O
slight	O
cold	O
with	O
which	O
most	O
have	O
been	O
more	O
or	O
leſs	O
plagued	O
lately	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
requested	O
kind	O
Compts	O
.	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
had	O
you	O
not	O
informed	O
me	O
He	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
&	O
not	O
speedily	O
expected	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
very	O
Sincere	O
&	O
Faithful	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
Robt	B-pers
:	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
London	B-place
January	O
Thirteen	O
1800	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
free	O
RF	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
Beds	B-place
:	I-place
