TOKEN	NE
Copy	O
of	O
Lr	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
--	O
15	O
June	O
1810	O
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
day	O
paid	O
the	O
last	O
tribute	O
of	O
Esteem	O
&	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
yr	O
amiable	O
Daughter	O
by	O
attending	O
her	O
Interment	O
at	O
Paddington	B-place
Church	O
as	O
Chief	O
Mourner	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
did	O
not	O
attend	O
the	O
Funeral	O
--	O
having	O
mentioned	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
in	O
Justice	O
say	O
that	O
his	O
behaviour	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
during	O
her	O
last	O
illneſs	O
was	O
extremely	O
attentive	O
&	O
proper	O
&	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
afford	O
her	O
great	O
Consolation	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
dwell	O
on	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
sad	O
subject	O
but	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
truly	O
sincere	O
Condole	O
nces	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
on	O
the	O
severe	O
loſs	O
you	O
have	O
sustained	O
&	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
we	O
participate	O
in	O
your	O
feelings	O
on	O
this	O
melancholy	O
Event	O
--	O
I	O
remain	O
My	O
dr	O
Sir	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
--	O
J.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
