TOKEN	NE
Clifton	B-place
Sat	O
June	O
9	O
th	O
:	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
recd	O
:	O
your	O
Letter	O
this	O
Morng	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
--	O
&	O
during	O
my	O
airing	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
easily	O
imagine	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
little	O
else	O
than	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
hasten	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
an	O
answer	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
distreſsed	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
grieved	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
think	O
your	O
health	O
may	O
materially	O
suffer	O
by	O
the	O
continuance	O
in	O
your	O
Place	O
--	O
it	O
hurts	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
this	O
,	O
on	O
many	O
accounts	O
--	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
strong	O
a	O
Plea	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Argument	O
against	O
it	O
--	O
but	O
surely	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
provided	O
you	O
recover	O
yr	O
:	O
health	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
can	O
make	O
no	O
difference	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sadly	O
grieved	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
mention	O
your	O
Scheme	O
during	O
Dr	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
s	O
absence	O
;	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
'till	O
something	O
is	O
settled	O
on	O
her	O
account	O
in	O
case	O
her	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
may	O
hinder	O
her	O
return	O
.	O
--	O
do	O
my	O
dr	O
:	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
grieve	O
my	O
very	O
heart	O
to	O
have	O
you	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
ingratitude	O
to	O
the	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
of	O
unkindneſs	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cha	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
you	O
know	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
difference	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
another	O
in	O
your	O
Place	O
--	O
besides	O
the	O
great	O
distreſs	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
Person	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
whilst	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cha	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
absent	O
--	O
do	O
my	O
dr	O
:	O
Friend	O
let	O
me	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
postpone	O
yr.-	O
Scheme	O
of	O
writing	O
'till	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cha	I-pers
's	O
return	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
know	O
how	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
act	O
--	O
unleſs	O
you	O
are	O
really	O
so	O
ill	O
(	O
wh	O
:	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
,	O
)	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
attend	O
without	O
risk	O
to	O
yr.-	O
Constitution	O
--	O
if	O
Docr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Turton	I-pers
who	O
is	O
yr	O
:	O
Friend	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Physician	O
,	O
thinks	O
you	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
this	O
Summer	O
with	O
out	O
this	O
hazard	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
were	O
I	O
not	O
your	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
loved	O
you	O
disinterestedly	O
I	O
should	O
I	O
not	O
giv	O
e	O
this	O
advice	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
might	O
enjoy	O
so	O
much	O
more	O
of	O
your	O
Company	O
&	O
conversation	O
by	O
yr	O
:	O
giving	O
up	O
yr	O
:	O
Place	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
writing	O
in	O
haste	O
--	O
the	O
Dinner	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
--	O
&	O
soon	O
after	O
Dinner	O
I	O
expect	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Son	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
&	O
be	O
aſsured	O
--	O
I	O
advice	O
this	O
on	O
yr	O
:	O
account	O
--	O
Yrs	O
:	O
ever	O
PD	B-pers
let	O
me	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
I	O
beg	O
--	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
--	O
whatever	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
upon	O
principle	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
hope	O
--	O
you	O
will	O
upon	O
mature	O
consideration	O
p	O
os	O
tpone	O
speaking	O
;	O
--	O
&	O
when	O
you	O
&	O
I	O
meet	O
;	O
we	O
will	O
settle	O
according	O
as	O
affairs	O
turn	O
out	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
mean	O
respecting	O
our	O
Dr	O
:	O
Ly	B-pers
:	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
'till	O
then	O
provided	O
you	O
are	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
surely	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
on	O
--	O
The	B-pers
Q	I-pers
--	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
Ill	O
,	O
must	O
see	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
attend	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
you	O
might	O
tell	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
as	O
She	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
in	O
so	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
friendly	O
a	O
manner	O
to	O
you	O
)	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
unhappy	O
at	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
your	O
duty	O
&	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
your	O
Place	O
:	O
--	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
all	O
this	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
write	O
--	O
do	O
pray	O
consider	O
well	O
before	O
you	O
write	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
many	O
reasons	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
put	O
off	O
yr	O
:	O
Scheme	O
till	O
next	O
Winter	O
I	O
writ	O
to	O
you	O
last	O
post	O
&	O
sent	O
it	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
I	O
imagined	O
you	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
said	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Tooth	O
drawn	O
wch	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sorry	O
for	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
very	O
particularly	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
Pray	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Letter	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
:	O
James	O
's	O
palace	O
London	B-place
