TOKEN	NE
Albemarle	O
Street	O
Jany	O
:	O
13	O
th	O
:	O
1786	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
My	O
Mother	O
&	O
myself	O
receiv	O
'd	O
your	O
letter	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
thanking	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
ask	O
whether	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
nothing	O
could	O
or	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
sincerer	O
joy	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
say	O
Madam	O
Prudence	O
forbids	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Lady	O
whose	O
orders	O
must	O
be	O
obey	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
often	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
&	O
wish	O
you	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
nay	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
satisf	O
y	O
us	O
,	O
after	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
absence	O
from	O
the	O
friend	O
we	O
so	O
dearly	O
love	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
dearest	O
mother	O
gave	O
her	O
sincere	O
joy	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
very	O
happy	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
pray	O
assure	O
him	O
from	O
from	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sincere	O
welcome	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
comes	O
just	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
when	O
he	O
arrives	O
,	O
how	O
our	O
Dear	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
will	O
be	O
surprized	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
happy	O
will	O
she	O
be	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
dear	O
brother	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
going	O
this	O
evening	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
concert	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Reveley	I-pers
s	O
in	O
Clifford	O
Street	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
A.	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
has	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
some	O
thoughts	O
relative	O
to	O
my	O
late	O
dear	O
Father	O
's	O
manuscripts	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
has	O
sent	O
me	O
your	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
rejoiced	O
that	O
you	O
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
not	O
giving	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Doctor	B-pers
Brocklesby	I-pers
,	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
consult	O
Dr.	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
certainly	O
will	O
have	O
nothing	O
done	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
advise	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
even	O
into	O
Doctor	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
s	O
hands	O
a	O
single	O
line	O
of	O
the	O
manuscripts	O
but	O
a	O
fair	O
copy	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
were	O
you	O
M	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
you	O
would	O
transcribe	O
them	O
yourself	O
;	O
Alas	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
too	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
health	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
undertaking	O
,	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
soon	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
why	O
you	O
think	O
Copies	O
are	O
requisite	O
;	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
aſsistance	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
publish	O
the	O
plays	O
first	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
much	O
more	O
admired	O
as	O
an	O
Epic	O
writer	O
than	O
a	O
Dramatic	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
advise	O
the	O
Athenaid	O
to	O
be	O
immediately	O
publish	O
'd	O
but	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
alteration	O
,	O
their	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
things	O
which	O
had	O
my	O
dearest	O
Father	O
been	O
living	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
alter	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
added	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
poem	O
would	O
very	O
much	O
increase	O
his	O
fame	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
plays	O
would	O
then	O
be	O
read	O
with	O
admiration	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
printer	O
is	O
often	O
very	O
careleſs	O
he	O
would	O
himself	O
attend	O
the	O
preſs	O
,	O
that	O
full	O
Justice	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
so	O
admirable	O
a	O
poem	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
sincerely	O
for	O
his	O
kind	O
offer	O
,	O
for	O
attending	O
the	O
preſs	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
laborious	O
peice	O
of	O
busineſs	O
;	O
he	O
approv	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
waiting	O
to	O
consult	O
Dr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
you	O
must	O
not	O
suffer	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
but	O
Dr.	B-pers
W	I-pers
..	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
manuscripts	O
.	O
--	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
offer	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
mention	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
engraving	O
from	O
the	O
portrait	O
&	O
likewise	O
the	O
quarto	O
edition	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
desires	O
her	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
shock	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
behaviour	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
near	O
a	O
month	O
&	O
has	O
never	O
once	O
wrote	O
a	O
single	O
line	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
or	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
well	O
knew	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
pleased	O
wth	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Aufrere	I-pers
's	O
letter	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
particularly	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
deserve	O
her	O
friendship	O
.	O
--	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
mention	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ockendon	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
very	O
pretty	O
things	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
,	O
&	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
amuse	O
you	O
by	O
reading	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
unite	O
in	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Sr.	B-pers
William	I-pers
&	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
Tell	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
D——	I-pers
that	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
&	O
hearing	O
particularly	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
(	O
would	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
you	O
)	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
make	O
me	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
very	O
poorly	O
.	O
adieu	O
dearest	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
your	O
Sincere	O
&	O
obliged	O
friend	O
M	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
compts	O
..	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
yr	O
.	O
self	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickienson	I-pers
