TOKEN	NE
Saturday	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
&	O
called	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dayvy	I-pers
where	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
pains	O
to	O
adjust	O
the	O
picture	O
--	O
he	O
walked	O
wh-	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Limestone	O
Quarry	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
but	O
as	O
Morrison	B-pers
would	O
have	O
it	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
foſsils	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
fine	O
Lime	O
Stone	O
almost	O
black	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Oakford	B-place
found	O
a	O
person	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
News	O
that	O
put	O
us	O
all	O
in	O
high	O
Spirits	O
--	O
Sunday	O
--	O
We	O
all	O
tried	O
to	O
prevail	O
on	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynter	I-pers
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
with	O
us	O
this	O
morng	O
--	O
but	O
nothing	O
can	O
make	O
him	O
talk	O
seriously	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
James	B-pers
administered	O
it	O
&	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
much	O
affected	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
a	O
Meſsenger	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
to	O
bring	O
News	O
papers	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
--	O
which	O
damped	O
our	O
Spirits	O
again	O
tho	O
the	O
Reports	O
from	O
the	O
Allies	O
are	O
very	O
encouraging	O
--	O
Monday	O
--	O
Owing	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paynter	I-pers
s	O
dilatorineſs	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
set	O
off	O
till	O
eleven	O
this	O
morng	O
--	O
James	B-pers
accompanied	O
us	O
to	O
Bampton	B-place
&	O
is	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
Cousin	O
at	O
Oakhampton	B-place
tomorrow	O
&	O
attend	O
him	O
to	O
Cornwal	B-place
as	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
alone	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
seemed	O
much	O
affected	O
at	O
parting	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
felt	O
much	O
obliged	O
by	O
her	O
Civilities	O
&	O
those	O
of	O
every	O
one	O
else	O
--	O
I	O
set	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
down	O
at	O
Tiverton	B-place
&	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Conveyance	O
by	O
Coach	O
before	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
another	O
Post	O
Chaise	O
&	O
came	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
--	O
brought	O
Parkin	B-pers
's	O
&	O
Paynter	B-pers
s	O
trunks	O
wh-	O
me	O
as	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
distreſsed	O
by	O
a	O
mis	O
calculation	O
of	O
a	O
Conveyance	O
from	O
thence	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
drive	O
to	O
Exeter	B-place
--	O
Sir	B-pers
T.	I-pers
Ackland	I-pers
paſsed	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Curricle	O
--	O
his	O
Servt	O
.	O
drove	O
&	O
he	O
was	O
makg	O
Notes	O
to	O
speechify	O
at	O
Exeter	B-place
I	O
suppose	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
wh-	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
drove	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
long	O
hill	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Road	O
from	O
Tiverton	B-place
to	O
South	B-place
Molton	I-place
is	O
rough	O
&	O
stoney	O
,	O
up	O
hill	O
&	O
down	O
--	O
19	O
miles	O
&	O
18	O
hills	O
&	O
all	O
Gentn	O
.	O
grumble	O
at	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
4½	O
hours	O
in	O
going	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
distance	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
paſsed	O
3	O
times	O
thro	O
this	O
beautiful	O
Country	O
&	O
am	O
become	O
pretty	O
well	O
acquaint	O
ed	O
with	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
new	O
Mayor	O
is	O
chosen	O
today	O
&	O
the	O
old	O
gives	O
an	O
Entertainment	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
peep	O
at	O
Exeter	B-place
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
told	O
me	O
to	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
County	O
rates	O
in	O
Devon	B-place
are	O
enormous	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
500	O
L	O
County	O
Bridges	O
&	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
their	O
Repairs	O
&	O
ye-	O
prosecution	O
of	O
felons	O
is	O
never	O
leſs	O
than	O
36-000	O
L	O
&	O
frequently	O
exceeds	O
40-000	O
L	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bridge	O
which	O
divides	O
the	O
Counties	B-place
of	I-place
Devon	I-place
&	O
Cornwal	B-place
that	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
since	O
&	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
funds	O
has	O
been	O
allowed	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
--	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
ye-	O
Deanery	O
of	O
Exeter	B-place
&	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
selling	O
the	O
Trees	O
that	O
ornament	O
that	O
beautiful	O
Walk	O
called	O
Northeny	O
that	O
constitutes	O
a	O
principal	O
feature	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
toward	O
's	O
defraying	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
's	O
Share	O
of	O
this	O
bridge	O
--	O
fortunately	O
this	O
horrible	O
Act	O
of	O
Barbarism	O
is	O
given	O
up	O
--	O
Immediately	O
on	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mail	O
Coach	O
Office	O
--	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
present	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
hour	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
away	O
--	O
The	O
W	O
ea	O
ther	O
is	O
so	O
fine	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
anxious	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
&	O
I	O
understand	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
day	O
allowed	O
to	O
see	O
Mount	B-place
Edgecumbe	I-place
&	O
that	O
day	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
formerly	O
Wed——	O
&	O
Fridays	O
were	O
given	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
sometime	O
&	O
till	O
then	O
will	O
amuse	O
myself	O
by	O
thinking	O
of	O
you	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
has	O
more	O
sense	O
than	O
all	O
her	O
family	O
put	O
together	O
--	O
her	O
manners	O
are	O
not	O
fine	O
&	O
she	O
holds	O
herself	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
She	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
amiable	O
Woman	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
Offers	O
,	O
but	O
rejected	O
them	O
all	O
--	O
I	O
dont	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
her	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
artful	O
longheaded	O
--	O
dirty	O
Scotchman	O
--	O
who	O
has	O
coaxed	O
her	O
from	O
interested	O
Motives	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
natural	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
much	O
secluded	O
from	O
Society	O
,	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
warm	O
Attachment	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
contributed	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
happy	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
off	O
in	O
two	O
hours	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
go	O
all	O
night	O
will	O
not	O
send	O
this	O
from	O
hence	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
pleasanter	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
arrived	O
at	O
Plymouth	B-place
--	O
where	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
finding	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
You	O
--	O
The	O
Beugles	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
playing	O
delightfully	O
before	O
my	O
Window	O
Plymouth	B-place
--	O
Fountain	O
Inn	O
Tuesday	O
--	O
Last	O
night	O
I	O
took	O
Coach	O
at	O
ten	O
OClock	O
&	O
arrived	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
at	O
7	O
--	O
the	O
road	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
hilly	O
I	O
ever	O
travelled	O
The	O
first	O
9	O
miles	O
required	O
full	O
2	O
hours	O
--	O
the	O
Mail	O
is	O
allowed	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
at	O
5	O
it	O
began	O
to	O
rain	O
&	O
has	O
never	O
ceased	O
--	O
I	O
slept	O
frequently	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
on	O
my	O
arrival	O
here	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
dreſsed	O
&	O
made	O
myself	O
comfortable	O
by	O
8	O
OClock	O
&	O
then	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
--	O
The	O
Post	O
Office	O
is	O
not	O
open	O
till	O
ten	O
--	O
Patience	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mount	B-place
Edgecumbe	I-place
&	O
Ld	B-pers
Borringdon	I-pers
s	O
from	O
the	O
Coach	O
&	O
can	O
see	O
Mt	B-place
.	I-place
E	I-place
.	I-place
any	O
day	O
by	O
applying	O
to	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
'm	O
easy	O
on	O
that	O
score	O
--	O
The	O
Land	O
in	O
the	O
Dock	O
belonged	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Aubin	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Crown	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
&	O
a	O
Quit	O
Rent	O
of	O
200	O
L	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
--	O
All	O
the	O
Land	O
at	O
Dock	O
on	O
wch	O
.	O
Houses	O
are	O
built	O
on	O
leases	O
belongs	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
is	O
supposed	O
to	O
derive	O
an	O
income	O
from	O
this	O
property	O
of	O
20-000	O
pr	O
.	O
An	O
.	O
his	O
Mines	O
in	O
Cornwal	B-place
10000	O
more	O
&	O
yet	O
he	O
is	O
poor	O
--	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
natural	O
Children	O
who	O
are	O
very	O
extravagant	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
--	O
no	O
letter	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
wrote	O
on	O
Saturday	O
as	O
I	O
requested	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
here	O
--	O
The	O
Mail	O
to	O
day	O
is	O
not	O
arrived	O
--	O
that	O
can	O
only	O
bring	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
mistake	O
It	O
is	O
too	O
soon	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
the	O
Commiſsioner	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
s	O
Retreat	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Rundell	I-pers
and	O
a	O
retreat	O
it	O
is	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
5	O
Miles	O
from	O
Dock	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Plymouth	B-place
thinking	O
it	O
poſsible	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
docked	O
yr-	O
direction	O
&	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
find	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
there	O
--	O
however	O
there	O
I	O
learnt	O
tidings	O
of	O
this	O
Seclusion	O
&	O
hired	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
&	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
&	O
just	O
concluding	O
my	O
letter	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
in	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
Post	O
--	O
Dont	O
write	O
again	O
as	O
I	O
feel	O
no	O
inclination	O
to	O
prolong	O
my	O
Stay	O
--	O
No	O
words	O
can	O
describe	O
the	O
Beauties	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
this	O
day	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
looking	O
vastly	O
well	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
difference	O
except	O
what	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
Teeth	O
creates	O
--	O
Most	O
Affy	O
Yr	O
JD	B-pers
.	I-pers
Single	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
32	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
