TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dearest	O
I	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
inclosed	O
to	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
,	O
&	O
tho	O
not	O
many	O
memorable	O
Events	O
have	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
Sanity	O
enough	O
to	O
think	O
my	O
Scrawl	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
unwelcome	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
has	O
been	O
chearful	O
and	O
good	O
humored	O
the	O
most	O
ridiculous	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
happened	O
was	O
Mr	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
introduced	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Arnald	I-pers
to	O
Col	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
as	O
the	O
new	O
Cannon	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Idea	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
properly	O
performed	O
without	O
attempting	O
a	O
Salute	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
successful	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
great	O
vehemence	O
denies	O
,	O
&	O
certainly	O
,	O
as	O
appearances	O
sometimes	O
are	O
deceitful	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
insist	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
very	O
near	O
hers	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
what	O
a	O
Sight	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
expired	O
,	O
&	O
was	O
yet	O
frightened	O
to	O
death	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
offending	O
her	O
he	O
declares	O
he	O
will	O
never	O
attempt	O
again	O
&	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
equally	O
afraid	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
enchanted	O
with	O
Harlyford	B-place
which	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
at	O
this	O
Morg	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
quiet	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bludworth	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Princes	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
King	B-pers
is	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Q	I-pers
alone	O
and	O
P	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
translating	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
vastly	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
then	O
know	O
how	O
pleasing	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Prſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mou	B-pers
Mou	I-pers
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
with	O
great	O
Sincerity	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
Affce	O
Chi	B-pers
Chi	I-pers
--	O
Windsor	B-place
10	O
th	O
.	O
Sepbr	O
1779	O
