TOKEN	NE
Burlington	O
Street	O
16	O
th	O
Oct	O
:	O
1788	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
yours	O
by	O
yesterday	O
's	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
trouble	O
you	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
yesterday	O
directed	O
for	O
you	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
in	O
Derbyshire	B-place
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
&	O
deposited	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
Garratt	O
until	O
you	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
If	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
with	O
me	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
send	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Benn	I-pers
to	O
come	O
&	O
remove	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
at	O
present	O
it	O
remains	O
in	O
my	O
paſsage	O
&	O
is	O
so	O
heavy	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Waggon	O
--	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
Letters	O
except	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
the	O
superscription	O
;	O
--	O
This	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s.	O
I	O
am	O
extremely	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
like	O
your	O
situation	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
improved	O
in	O
your	O
Shooting	O
.	O
The	O
Children	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
all	O
at	O
School	O
except	O
Henry	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
Nanny	B-pers
but	O
expect	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
enquire	O
after	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Ladies	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
Ramsgate	B-place
--	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
the	O
Air	O
of	O
Hants	B-place
will	O
continue	O
to	O
improve	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
As	O
I	O
write	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
goodwill	O
to	O
excuse	O
me	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
brief	O
which	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
again	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
--	O
pray	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
very	O
truly	O
Yours	O
J.	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
at	O
--	O
Iremonger	B-pers
s	O
Esq	O
r	O
.	O
Whearwell	B-place
near	O
Andover	B-place
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Octbr	O
16	O
th	O
1788	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
1788	O
