TOKEN	NE
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Friday	O
Night	O
--	O
Tho	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
write	O
yet	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
thought	O
of	O
you	O
my	O
Dst	O
I	O
k	O
now	O
seize	O
the	O
moment	O
whilst	O
Prſs	B-pers
Augusta	I-pers
is	O
writing	O
her	O
German	O
to	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
besides	O
all	O
my	O
other	O
Capacitys	O
Teacher	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
Leſsons	O
&	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizh	I-pers
are	O
always	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
English	O
,	O
they	O
go	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
&	O
desire	O
their	O
Love	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
them	O
Justice	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
wrote	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
their	O
fault	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
but	O
they	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
Our	O
Life	O
has	O
gone	O
on	O
pretty	O
much	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
to	O
morrow	O
is	O
a	O
Hunting	O
day	O
,	O
whether	O
we	O
go	O
you	O
know	O
is	O
always	O
a	O
Secret	O
,	O
pray	O
kiſs	O
Dear	O
Prſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
&	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Meſsage	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
good	O
resolutions	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Tolpey	I-pers
appeared	O
at	O
Chapel	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
with	O
in	O
a	O
Grey	O
Riding	O
Habit	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
describing	O
her	O
Figure	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
my	O
Countenance	O
but	O
Mr	B-pers
Lyte	I-pers
&	O
Col.	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
laughd	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dst	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
I	O
can	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
&	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
very	O
entertaining	O
Letter	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
Affly	O
Yr	O
MCG	B-pers
--	O
Love	O
to	O
Chi	B-pers
Chi	I-pers
--	O
Pray	O
kiss	O
Prſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Kew	B-place
