TOKEN	NE
Friday	O
--	O
16	O
th	O
Janry	O
1784	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
Have	O
Just	O
Recd	O
.	O
the	O
enclosed	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
;	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
I	O
Believe	O
;	O
I	O
find	O
she	O
still	O
wishes	O
,	O
me	O
to	O
own	O
Her	O
situation	O
;	O
as	O
She	O
Has	O
not	O
Informed	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
--	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
Hope	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
Mentioned	O
It	O
;	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
some	O
Knotting	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
,	O
Who	O
will	O
see	O
Her	O
this	O
Evening	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
Happy	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
You	O
any	O
Day	O
--	O
next	O
Week	O
;	O
You	O
Will	O
mention	O
excepting	O
Monday	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Yrs	O
--	O
FHarpur	B-pers
