TOKEN	NE
I	O
send	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
Volume	O
of	O
Boileau	B-pers
I	O
promised	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
Tho	O
'	O
the	O
French	O
think	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
Satire	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
beſt	O
performances	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
read	O
it	O
without	O
finding	O
it	O
tedious	O
,	O
&	O
thinking	O
that	O
moſt	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
are	O
outrés	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
calculated	O
for	O
the	O
meridian	O
of	O
these	O
parts	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
alſo	O
ſend	O
you	O
two	O
Volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Italian	O
Molière	B-pers
;	O
a	O
french	O
&	O
Italian	O
Volume	O
of	O
Gil	O
Blas	O
which	O
have	O
ſtray	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
Town	O
;	O
&	O
a	O
Volume	O
of	O
Montesquieu	B-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
ſake	O
of	O
his	O
Chapter	O
on	O
the	O
Britiſh	O
Conſtitution	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
of	O
his	O
Esprit	O
des	O
Loix	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
occaſion	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
--	O
When	O
At	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
find	O
your	O
Mama	O
&	O
you	O
by	O
yourſelves	O
,	O
I	O
ſhall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
help	O
you	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
pronunciation	O
of	O
the	O
Italian	O
;	O
“	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
London	B-place
(	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
practice	O
)	O
you	O
will	O
ſoon	O
be	O
mistreſs	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
begun	O
with	O
your	O
ſincere	O
&	O
affecte	O
:	O
Friend	O
”	O
--	O
J	B-pers
H	I-pers
