TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
A	I-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Canterbury	B-place
Nov	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
1814	O
My	O
dear	O
&	O
amiable	O
Friend	O
Having	O
yesterday	O
had	O
the	O
inexpreſsible	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
your	O
dear	O
Father	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
united	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
respectable	O
Character	O
&	O
distinguished	O
Family	O
who	O
equally	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
preference	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
&	O
the	O
approbation	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
Parents	O
will	O
I	O
trust	O
contribute	O
to	O
your	O
happineſs	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
will	O
secure	O
his	O
own	O
by	O
being	O
the	O
object	O
of	O
your	O
choice	O
accept	O
my	O
most	O
cordial	O
&	O
affectionate	O
wishes	O
for	O
the	O
attaiment	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
felicity	O
you	O
can	O
desire	O
on	O
the	O
approaching	O
Event	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
particularly	O
interested	O
in	O
--	O
both	O
from	O
the	O
esteem	O
and	O
affection	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
you	O
&	O
my	O
envaluabl	O
my	O
invaluable	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
imperfectly	O
expreſsed	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
the	O
joy	O
&	O
solicitude	O
I	O
feel	O
respecting	O
you	O
on	O
this	O
very	O
interesting	O
occasion	O
but	O
sensible	O
as	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
of	O
my	O
friendship	O
for	O
your	O
Parents	O
&	O
yourself	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
unneceſsary	O
were	O
I	O
to	O
attempt	O
to	O
add	O
more	O
I	O
shall	O
therefore	O
with	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
of	O
my	O
esteem	O
&	O
affection	O
subscribe	O
myself	O
your	O
ever	O
affectionate	O
&	O
most	O
sincere	O
Friend	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
PS	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
underwritten	O
&	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Dr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Inglis	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
met	O
yesterday	O
well	O
in	O
Canterbury	B-place
.	O
My	O
dearest	O
friend	O
By	O
a	O
remarkable	O
coincidence	O
I	O
received	O
dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
kind	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
put	O
one	O
from	O
myself	O
to	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
letter	O
box	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
it	O
has	O
so	O
happened	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
solicitous	O
respecting	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
--	O
I	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
in	O
learning	O
that	O
your	O
excursion	O
to	O
Ramsgate	B-place
which	O
was	O
so	O
conducive	O
to	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
was	O
beneficial	O
to	O
your	O
health	O
.	O
The	O
interesting	O
contents	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
sincerest	O
joy	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
her	O
father	O
I	O
anticipate	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
future	O
happineſs	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
by	O
an	O
alliance	O
so	O
respectable	O
&	O
desirable	O
you	O
will	O
derive	O
all	O
poſsible	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
ensuing	O
happy	O
Event	O
.	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
's	O
residence	O
with	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
delightful	O
circumstance	O
&	O
save	O
the	O
pang	O
of	O
continual	O
absence	O
from	O
a	O
Daughter	O
from	O
her	O
whose	O
merit	O
&	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
render	O
her	O
so	O
justly	O
dear	O
&	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
hitherto	O
so	O
inseparably	O
yours	O
accept	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
Brother	O
the	O
most	O
cordial	O
congratulations	O
I	O
can	O
offer	O
&	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
informed	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Event	O
shall	O
have	O
taken	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
imagine	O
myself	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
participating	O
in	O
your	O
domestic	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
congratulate	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
reconciliation	O
with	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
I	O
feel	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
are	O
interested	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
at	O
ease	O
when	O
divided	O
from	O
a	O
friend	O
so	O
dear	O
&	O
estimable	O
.	O
is	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
still	O
with	O
you	O
remember	O
me	O
With	O
my	O
Love	O
&	O
thanks	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
conclude	O
your	O
ever	O
grateful	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
I	O
see	O
a	O
second	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Memoirs	O
as	O
supposed	O
is	O
come	O
out	O
do	O
read	O
it	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
your	O
opinion	O
of	O
its	O
autheticity	O
&	O
your	O
sentiments	O
the	O
price	O
is	O
7-6	O
d	O
--	O
MiſsMrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
