TOKEN	NE
Bromley	O
June	O
11	O
th	O
1801	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Grenville	I-pers
's	O
returning	O
to	O
Leighton	B-place
of	O
sending	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
two	O
very	O
great	O
events	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
as	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
d	I-pers
.	I-pers
have	O
ever	O
interested	O
yourselves	O
so	O
kindly	O
on	O
our	O
Accounts	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
Katherine	B-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
whom	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
entir	O
ely	O
with	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
My	O
Aunts	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Kindderley	I-pers
&	O
at	O
present	O
no	O
other	O
of	O
our	O
friends	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
disparity	O
of	O
their	O
ages	O
is	O
certainly	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
acted	O
so	O
generous	O
a	O
part	O
(	O
situated	O
as	O
our	O
affairs	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
as	O
you	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
well	O
aſsured	O
of	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
any	O
fortune	O
with	O
her	O
therefore	O
his	O
motive	O
must	O
be	O
real	O
affection	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
she	O
has	O
very	O
good	O
prospect	O
of	O
being	O
perfectly	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
distance	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
from	O
us	O
is	O
very	O
great	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
her	O
only	O
objection	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
she	O
shall	O
never	O
be	O
without	O
one	O
of	O
us	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
wishes	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
like	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
pleasant	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
Katherine	B-pers
is	O
just	O
gone	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
and	O
she	O
is	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Froggatt	I-pers
at	O
Fulmer	B-place
she	O
would	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
herself	O
and	O
had	O
indeed	O
had	O
began	O
a	O
letter	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
hurryed	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
it	O
she	O
will	O
very	O
shortly	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
very	O
communicative	O
--	O
The	O
other	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
we	O
she	O
was	O
invited	O
to	O
tea	O
alone	O
at	O
my	O
Aunt	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
expreſs	O
purpose	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
Aunt	O
Bell	B-pers
who	O
was	O
seated	O
in	O
great	O
form	O
in	O
the	O
parlor	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
agitated	O
but	O
talked	O
of	O
indifferent	O
subjects	O
and	O
told	O
she	O
hoped	O
very	O
soon	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
--	O
we	O
d	O
spent	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Bishop	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
an	O
evening	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
desi	O
re	O
to	O
spend	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
were	O
setting	O
off	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
g	O
d	O
rive	O
in	O
the	O
sociable	O
Mr	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
his	O
intended	O
Lady	O
on	O
horseback	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
n	O
Park	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
thrown	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
covered	O
with	O
blood	O
and	O
perfectly	O
loſſ	O
senseless	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
recover	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
for	O
full	O
3	O
quart	O
z	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
very	O
shortly	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
cut	O
her	O
head	O
&	O
ne	O
ck	O
,	O
hand	O
and	O
,	O
knee	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
no	O
t	O
broke	O
or	O
dislocated	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
scene	O
of	O
confusion	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
every	O
one	O
in	O
fits	O
&	O
c.	O
pray	O
tell	O
Louisa	B-pers
to	O
be	O
Careful	O
how	O
she	O
figures	O
away	O
on	O
horseback	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
this	O
short	O
hasty	O
written	O
letter	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
catch	O
the	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
in	O
good	O
humour	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
and	O
write	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
one	O
with	O
one	O
united	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
yourself	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
Believe	O
me	O
ever	O
My	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yrs	O
sincerely	O
obled	O
&	O
afftly	O
M	B-pers
J	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Dont	O
let	O
Louisa	B-pers
quiz	O
this	O
writing	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
aſſure	O
I	O
can	O
write	O
much	O
better	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
house	O
