TOKEN	NE
Wimpole	O
Street	O
Sunday	O
Even	O
:	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
perseveriance	O
shown	O
me	O
by	O
you	O
in	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
sight	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Goſsiping	O
Old	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Many	O
Daughters	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
to	O
Chapron	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
real	O
cause	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Tuesday	O
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
&	O
having	O
no	O
Carriage	O
&	O
a	O
bad	O
Walker	O
;	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Goodneſs	O
to	O
fix	O
upon	O
any	O
Hour	O
to	O
Morrow	O
between	O
twelve	O
One	O
,	O
&	O
four	O
O'Clock	O
for	O
my	O
having	O
the	O
Honour	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
Various	O
things	O
have	O
happend	O
in	O
my	O
Sisterhood	O
since	O
we	O
met	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
relate	O
&	O
equal	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
relate	O
Pleasant	O
Anecdotes	O
of	O
your	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
very	O
Much	O
your	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
E.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mrs.	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mother	O
to	O
Marchioneſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
&	O
c	O
May	O
or	O
June	O
1795	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
Boulton	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	B-place
