TOKEN	NE
Sayes	O
Farm	O
Sept	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
:	O
Ma	O
Chere	O
Amie	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
dear	O
Caterina	B-pers
's	O
promise	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
you	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
so	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
recieving	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
write	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
intention	O
of	O
complying	O
with	O
my	O
request	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
without	O
some	O
expectation	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cover	O
from	O
our	O
Dearest	O
Anna	B-pers
as	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
recieved	O
one	O
this	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
sincerely	O
wishing	O
my-self	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
ealier	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
enjoyed	O
with	O
you	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasure	O
we	O
could	O
have	O
recieved	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
with	O
a	O
very	O
sincere	O
regret	O
&	O
it	O
was	O
doubly	O
painful	O
,	O
as	O
besides	O
the	O
concern	O
I	O
felt	O
at	O
parting	O
from	O
you	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
but	O
be	O
sensi-ble	O
that	O
losing	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
would	O
make	O
your	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
absence	O
even	O
more	O
tedious	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
hope	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
now	O
will	O
re-unite	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
shall	O
forget	O
the	O
pain	O
we	O
have	O
felt	O
in	O
parting	O
in	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
meeting	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Deputy	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
I	O
dare	O
say	O
fills	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
yor	O
leisure	O
hours	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
play	O
at	O
Cheſs	O
,	O
but	O
Anna	B-pers
can	O
beat	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
-	O
Fours	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
prevail	O
on	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
little	O
excursion	O
you	O
talked	O
of	O
making	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
to	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
not	O
inviting	O
but	O
the	O
country	O
still	O
looks	O
pleasant	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
enquire	O
my	O
Dear	O
Leonidas	B-pers
particularly	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
I	O
heard	O
you	O
were	O
pretty	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
happier	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
without	O
anxiety	O
lest	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
over	O
fatigued	O
you	O
at	O
Hampton-Court	B-place
--	O
This	O
retired	O
place	O
affords	O
little	O
news	O
--	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
this	O
afternoon	O
to	O
Egham	O
Races	O
but	O
prevented	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
regret	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
fond	O
of	O
that	O
amusement	O
&	O
am	O
happier	O
to	O
employ	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
spent	O
there	O
in	O
conversing	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
tell	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
here	O
who	O
painted	O
those	O
views	O
in	O
Otaheité	B-place
which	O
we	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Exhibition	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
remarking	O
it	O
&	O
our	O
surprize	O
at	O
the	O
purple	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
Mountains	O
&	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
satisfy	O
his	O
curiosity	O
&	O
my	O
own	O
by	O
enquiring	O
of	O
Leonidas	B-pers
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
what	O
occasion	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
they	O
are	O
always	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Fern	O
which	O
grows	O
upon	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
of	O
Fern	O
wch	O
:	O
we	O
find	O
upon	O
upon	O
Heaths	O
in	O
England	B-place
,	O
&	O
which	O
also	O
bears	O
a	O
purple	O
flower	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
larger	O
Flower	O
,	O
is	O
fuller	O
of	O
Bloſsoms	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
always	O
in	O
Bloom	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hodges	I-pers
says	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
by	O
his	O
account	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
beautiful	O
&	O
the	O
perpetual	O
spring	O
they	O
enjoy	O
makes	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fruit	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Tree	O
in	O
bloſsom	O
,	O
green	O
,	O
&	O
ripe	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
diverted	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
H——	I-pers
before	O
he	O
left	O
England	B-place
purchased	O
a	O
very	O
elegant	O
white	O
Sattin	O
umbrella	O
with	O
a	O
broad	O
fringe	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
cost	O
him	O
5	O
guineas	O
to	O
preserve	O
his	O
complexion	O
from	O
the	O
Sun	O
--	O
My	O
sister	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
our	O
scheme	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
Suſsex	B-place
Omiah	B-pers
is	O
prevented	O
--	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
foreseen	O
this	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
you	O
--	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
put	O
off	O
--	O
My	O
Sister	O
Mr.	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
insists	O
upon	O
fetching	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
to	O
Maple	B-place
Durham	I-place
--	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
leave	O
of	O
Absence	O
for	O
only	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
refuse	O
a	O
request	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
most	O
certainly	O
return	O
to	O
you	O
next	O
week	O
you	O
my	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
promise	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
interested	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
you	O
do	O
;	O
--	O
continue	O
to	O
love	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
decieve	O
you	O
Adieu	O
Ma	O
Chere	O
Amie	O
Je	O
vous	O
aime	O
en	O
verité	O
Adieu	O
Barnard	B-pers
To	O
--	O
Caterina	B-pers
James	O
Street	O
Buckingham	O
Gate	O
