TOKEN	NE
Horton	B-place
August	O
24	O
th	O
1786	O
Why	O
do	O
I	O
never	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
forgot	O
that	O
I	O
exist	O
,	O
either	O
for	O
myself	O
or	O
you	O
?	O
Have	O
I	O
ceased	O
to	O
be	O
anything	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
have	O
you	O
chose	O
to	O
imagine	O
that	O
you	O
no	O
longer	O
interest	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
answered	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
,	O
immediately	O
--	O
&	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
heard	O
from	O
,	O
nor	O
even	O
of	O
you	O
but	O
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
whom	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
unpleasant	O
circumstances	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
seeing	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
--	O
When	O
first	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
here	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
daily	O
expectation	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
--	O
Indeed	O
nothing	O
could	O
equal	O
my	O
diſsappointment	O
in	O
not	O
finding	O
you	O
at	O
Courteenhall	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
constant	O
ill	O
luck	O
whic	O
h	O
has	O
invariably	O
attended	O
my	O
wishes	O
on	O
this	O
subject	O
--	O
my	O
Brother	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
you	O
well	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
found	O
very	O
low	O
myself	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
comfortable	O
account	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
all	O
comfort	O
with	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
surprised	O
at	O
her	O
having	O
felt	O
your	O
loſs	O
greatly	O
--	O
her	O
Daughter	O
ill	O
too	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
indifferent	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
there	O
tomorr	O
ow	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
procure	O
your	O
direction	O
for	O
this	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
continue	O
my	O
account	O
of	O
myself	O
this	O
summer	O
--	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
we	O
had	O
Company	O
whom	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
provoked	O
and	O
mortified	O
by	O
your	O
silence	O
I	O
then	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
received	O
the	O
news	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
's	O
short	O
illneſs	O
&	O
sudden	O
Death	O
almost	O
in	O
one	O
letter	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
shock	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
both	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
accoun	O
t	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
miserable	O
Family	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
far	O
from	O
recovered	O
--	O
I	O
my	O
first	O
thought	O
was	O
to	O
fly	O
to	O
them	O
--	O
&	O
upon	O
the	O
repeated	O
sollicitations	O
of	O
Ly	B-pers
Lonsdale	I-pers
,	O
Ly	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
himself	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
agreeable	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Richmond	B-place
leaving	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
dear	O
&	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
here	O
--	O
the	O
scene	O
of	O
misery	O
&	O
the	O
various	O
expreſsions	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
were	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
&	O
shall	O
I	O
think	O
never	O
forget	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
s	O
affliction	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
affecti	O
n	O
g	O
&	O
heart	O
rending	O
thi	O
n	O
g	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
--	O
my	O
intention	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
staid	O
4	O
Days	O
&	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
here	O
--	O
but	O
no	O
persuasion	O
could	O
make	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
move	O
--	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
staid	O
three	O
weeks	O
there	O
without	O
ever	O
stirring	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
above	O
three	O
times	O
--	O
I	O
grew	O
so	O
thin	O
,	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
mecconnoiſsable	O
.	O
never	O
slept	O
one	O
night	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
--	O
&	O
as	O
for	O
appetite	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
--	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
weepi	O
n	O
g	O
the	O
whole	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
(	O
her	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
who	O
is	O
exceſsively	O
attached	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
used	O
to	O
sit	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morni	O
n	O
g	O
talking	O
over	O
all	O
the	O
horrid	O
circumstances	O
of	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
Death	O
--	O
with	O
this	O
horrible	O
images	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
sleep	O
they	O
still	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
woke	O
agitated	O
&	O
unrefreshed	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
inst	O
I	O
returned	O
here	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
&	O
their	O
Son	O
&	O
Daughter	O
--	O
during	O
their	O
stay	O
here	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
them	O
a	O
minute	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
comfort	O
&	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
all	O
infinitly	O
better	O
both	O
in	O
Health	O
&	O
spirits	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
(	O
who	O
has	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
&	O
the	O
appearan	O
ce	O
of	O
an	O
unfeeling	O
hard	O
heart	O
)	O
burst	O
into	O
tears	O
when	O
he	O
embraced	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
forget	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
mine	O
!	O
How	O
he	O
is	O
altered	O
--	O
how	O
softened	O
,	O
how	O
improved	O
--	O
never	O
swears	O
never	O
gives	O
way	O
to	O
paſsions	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
for	O
to	O
day	O
's	O
Drawing	O
,	O
but	O
received	O
an	O
expreſs	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
to	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
none	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elisabeth	I-pers
's	O
dangerous	O
illneſs	O
--	O
my	O
Sister	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
&	O
stays	O
three	O
weeks	O
with	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
thank	O
God	O
left	O
to	O
myself	O
&	O
to	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
peace	O
&	O
tranquility	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
--	O
the	O
first	O
use	O
I	O
make	O
of	O
my	O
liberty	O
is	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
very	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
for	O
Godsake	O
writte	O
me	O
fully	O
--	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
most	O
sincerely	O
&	O
tenderly	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
most	O
truly	O
interested	O
about	O
you	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
prevented	O
writing	O
before	O
--	O
my	O
head	O
has	O
been	O
turned	O
&	O
my	O
heart	O
&	O
my	O
spirits	O
oppreſsed	O
--	O
the	O
weather	O
has	O
been	O
miserable	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
here	O
till	O
this	O
Day	O
fortnight	O
&	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
Putney	B-place
Lodge	O
--	O
but	O
direct	O
to	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
--	O
I	O
go	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Races	O
--	O
here	O
Wednesday	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
write	O
soon	O
if	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
my	O
F	O
.	O
&	O
Mother	O
are	O
well	O
--	O
Bell	B-pers
only	O
so	O
so	O
--	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
allud	O
e	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
reestablishment	O
of	O
my	O
Health	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
greatest	O
Physician	O
&	O
Apothecary	O
du	O
canton	O
&	O
all	O
the	O
poor	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
far	O
to	O
be	O
cured	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
employment	O
wth	O
musick	O
&	O
a	O
little	O
reading	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
read	O
more	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
alone	O
adieu	O
--	O
once	O
more	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gunning	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
near	O
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
