TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
17	O
th	O
-	O
April	O
1781	O
11	O
oClock	O
at	O
Night	O
You	O
might	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
have	O
imagin	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
some	O
accounts	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
--	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
respecting	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
were	O
far	O
from	O
Well	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Eveg	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Culling	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
s	O
.	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
you	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
Ill	O
at	O
Chapel	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
till	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
enquiry	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
town	B-place
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
therefore	O
judging	O
from	O
your	O
silence	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
worse	O
than	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
You	O
--	O
you	O
surely	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
withheld	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
were	O
better	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
here	O
about	O
7	O
on	O
Sunday	O
&	O
spent	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
in	O
conversation	O
(	O
Madm	B-pers
Hardenberg	I-pers
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
)	O
Yesterday	O
Morng	O
.	O
Rhea	B-pers
had	O
letters	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
so	O
P	O
ſ	O
's	O
.	O
Royal	O
Sabine——	B-pers
--	O
Eliza	B-pers
&	O
the	B-pers
Genl-	I-pers
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Frytag	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
took	O
a	O
pleasant	O
walk	O
round	O
ye	O
little	O
Park	O
;	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
ye	O
.	O
Seat	O
whereon	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
together	O
&	O
felt	O
a	O
sensible	O
pleasure	O
in	O
the	O
recollection	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
my	O
Astrea	B-pers
Friend	O
we	O
shall	O
this	O
Summer	O
contrive	O
frequent	O
interviews	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
Kind	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
real	O
comfort	O
&	O
pleasure	O
arrising	O
from	O
Virtu	O
ous	O
connections	O
the	O
remembrance	O
of	O
past	O
scenes	O
are	O
never	O
painful	O
--	O
can	O
any	O
thing	O
my	O
love	O
be	O
more	O
pure	O
,	O
more	O
sacred	O
than	O
our	O
connection	O
?	O
Friday	O
Thursd	O
ay	O
19	O
th	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
see	O
my	O
friend	O
by	O
the	O
Crumpled	O
appearance	O
of	O
this	O
paper	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
've	O
worn	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
hardly	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
scribble	O
a	O
dozen	O
lines	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
made	O
happy	O
by	O
your	O
Dr	O
.	O
Letter	O
of	O
yesterday	O
--	O
I	O
endulg	O
'd	O
indulged	O
RH	O
with	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
I	O
mus	O
t	O
send	O
this	O
scrap	O
or	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
hear	O
fr	O
om	O
me	O
before	O
my	O
return	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
an	O
instant	O
to	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
go	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
Saty	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
order	O
some	O
trifle	O
thing	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
eat	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
4	O
oClock	O
.	O
we	O
will	O
then	O
talk	O
over	O
my	O
week	O
's	O
absence	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
once	O
More	O
17	O
April	O
1781	O
