TOKEN	NE
17	O
th	O
-	O
July	O
1780	O
My	O
Dear	O
Dear	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
love	O
me	O
tell	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
causes	O
of	O
your	O
uneasineſs	O
's	O
--	O
for	O
my	O
busy	O
imagination	O
perhaps	O
magnifies	O
your	O
distreſs	O
--	O
&	O
thus	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
only	O
nursing	O
up	O
grief	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
me	O
unhappy	O
,	O
Oh	O
how	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
last	O
nights	O
view	O
was	O
picturesque	O
beyond	O
description	O
--	O
I	O
cld-	O
hardly	O
prevail	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
quit	O
my	O
Window	O
to	O
retire	O
to	O
rest	O
--	O
the	O
Eveg	O
.	O
was	O
perfectly	O
calm	O
,	O
hardly	O
a	O
Breeze	O
to	O
move	O
the	O
surface	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
--	O
at	O
11	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
shining	O
in	O
full	O
splendor	O
--	O
a	O
broad	O
column	O
of	O
light	O
lay	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
ocean	O
--	O
a	O
Veſsel	O
of	O
some	O
size	O
approaching	O
through	O
it	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
Shore	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
light	O
was	O
so	O
unclouded	O
that	O
we	O
plainly	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
every	O
object	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
--	O
at	O
other	O
distances	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
little	O
Veſsels	O
sailing	O
along	O
,	O
nothing	O
cld	O
.	O
be	O
more	O
tranquil	O
&	O
beautiful	O
than	O
the	O
scenery	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
delightful	O
ride	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
afternoon	O
,	O
attend	O
ing	O
ed	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
J——	I-pers
I	O
rode	O
near	O
ten	O
miles	O
.	O
t	O
T	O
his	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
&	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
Sea	O
--	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
enjoy	O
bathin	O
17	O
th	O
.	O
July	O
80	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
heard	O
in	O
confidence	O
a	O
report	O
of	O
our	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
12	O
th	O
-	O
of	O
August	O
--	O
--	O
A	O
--	O
a	O
Ball	O
I	O
hear	O
at	O
St	B-place
James'sLouvre	I-place
&	O
c	O
do	O
try	O
&	O
find	O
out	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Dear	O
Astrea	B-pers
Friend	O
ye	O
.	O
post	O
is	O
going	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
sweet	O
pretty	O
poem	O
from	O
Town	B-place
--	O
pray	O
get	O
it	O
immediately	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
yo	O
.	O
like	O
it	O
“	O
Epistle	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
Death	O
of	O
John	O
Thorton	O
--	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hayley	I-pers
read	O
too	O
his	O
Ode	O
to	O
John	O
Howard	O
--	O
this	O
latter	O
is	O
well	O
written	O
&	O
a	O
Noble	O
Theme	O
--	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
more	O
touching	O
--	O
more	O
immediately	O
from	O
the	O
Heart	O
--	O
we	O
will	O
sometime	O
or	O
other	O
read	O
it	O
together	O
--	O
have	O
You	O
ever	O
read	O
the	O
Lusiad	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
“	O
my	O
beloved	O
”	O
.	O
send	O
me	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
female	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
danger	O
of	O
discovery	O
,	O
our	O
Dict	O
:	O
secures	O
us	O
--	O
send	O
it	O
next	O
post	O
.	O
pray	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
future	O
date	O
your	O
letters	O
