TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
Aprl-	O
15	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
tell	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
that	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
,	O
good	O
,	O
&	O
kind	O
Father	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
Please	O
inform	O
Mr	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
every	O
body	O
&	O
My	O
Father	O
was	O
his	O
Uncle	O
I	O
go	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
to	O
Canterbury	B-place
where	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
franks	O
directed	O
for	O
Col.-	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
you	O
had	O
better	O
use	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
ſafe	O
&	O
the	O
next	O
you	O
get	O
may	O
be	O
properly	O
derected	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
most	O
Affctly-	O
Napier	B-pers
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
Manner	O
