TOKEN	NE
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Octr	O
.	O
1786	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
long	O
Letter	O
that	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
large	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
in	O
kind	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
promise	O
that	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
tir	O
'd	O
before	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
thro	O
'	O
it	O
--	O
however	O
,	O
you	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
patience	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	O
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
ago	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Town	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Days	O
--	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
'till	O
December	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
that	O
I	O
had	O
lately	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
shortly	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
interest	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
her	O
lately	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
mention	O
'd	O
that	O
her	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
--	O
She	O
has	O
three	O
Daughters	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
by	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
that	O
Maria	B-pers
has	O
got	O
a	O
Son	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
permitted	O
to	O
be	O
God-Mother	O
--	O
As	O
you	O
say	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
is	O
an	O
admirer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
myself	O
bound	O
in	O
gratitude	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
part	O
--	O
therefore	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
hazard	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
Bones	O
,	O
by	O
letting	O
him	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
receiving	O
any	O
instructions	O
from	O
so	O
saucy	O
a	O
Lady	O
as	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
his	O
part	O
very	O
handsomely	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
know	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
of	O
Bath	B-place
is	O
dead	O
--	O
though	O
,	O
upon	O
second	O
thoughts	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
)	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
News-Papers	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
much	O
recover	O
'd	O
--	O
travelling	O
he	O
found	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
near	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
London	B-place
--	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Colonel	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Charles	O
Street	O
,	O
Berkeley	O
Square	O
--	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
last	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
--	O
all	O
the	O
little	O
Charles	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
's	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Measles	O
,	O
except	O
Murray	B-pers
--	O
William	B-pers
and	O
Lord	B-pers
wish	O
'd	O
much	O
that	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Westminster	O
School	O
--	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
catch	O
them	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
not	O
only	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
Brothers	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
nursing	O
little	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
--	O
Henry	B-pers
is	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
in	O
leſs	O
than	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
grown	O
and	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
really	O
,	O
as	O
fine	O
a	O
Boy	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
has	O
been	O
extremely	O
ill	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cold	O
which	O
fell	O
violently	O
on	O
her	O
Lungs	O
--	O
she	O
had	O
much	O
fever	O
,	O
kept	O
her	O
Bed	O
some	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
blooded	O
twice	O
in	O
two	O
Days	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
(	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
)	O
pretty	O
well	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
of	O
herself	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
myself	O
have	O
been	O
well	O
,	O
excepting	O
colds	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
now	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
begs	O
his	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
William	B-pers
--	O
he	O
is	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
desire	O
of	O
making	O
him	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
Irish	O
affairs	O
--	O
he	O
knows	O
it	O
but	O
too	O
well	O
--	O
all	O
the	O
intelligence	O
you	O
receiv	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
an	O
amendment	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
returns	O
her	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
with	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Dowager	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
is	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
describe	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
our	O
new	O
House	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
London	B-place
before	O
it	O
is	O
completed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
more	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
in	O
describing	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
--	O
However	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
describe	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
like	O
our	O
Situation	O
extremely	O
--	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
do	O
otherwise	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
's	O
&	O
your	O
affectionate	O
remembrance	O
of	O
him	O
--	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
forget	O
either	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
friend	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
great	O
favourites	O
of	O
his	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
grown	O
and	O
improv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
makes	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
progreſs	O
in	O
Latin	O
--	O
We	O
are	O
now	O
so	O
much	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
than	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Bedford-Square	O
,	O
that	O
'till	O
very	O
lately	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
every	O
Sunday	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Days	O
are	O
now	O
too	O
short	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
Music	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
it	O
(	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
)	O
better	O
and	O
better	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
learnt	O
Italian	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
continue	O
to	O
take	O
Leſsons	O
in	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
remarkable	O
pretty	O
Language	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
certainly	O
,	O
peculiarly	O
adapted	O
to	O
Music	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
walk	O
about	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
in	O
Hyde	B-place
Park	I-place
when	O
the	O
Weather	O
permits	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
ride	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
learnt	O
to	O
drive	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ponies	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
Phaeton	O
,	O
this	O
Summer	O
--	O
she	O
likes	O
driving	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Town	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
hope	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
shortly	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
it	O
must	O
begin	O
to	O
be	O
cold	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
grown	O
so	O
hardy	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
mind	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
stupid	O
Letter	O
enough	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
seldom	O
have	O
much	O
news	O
to	O
tell	O
.	O
Poor	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	I-pers
(	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Amelia	I-pers
's	O
Aunt	O
,	O
)	O
is	O
dying	O
--	O
indeed	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
dead	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Morning	O
's	O
Paper	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
alive	O
last	O
Night	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
loſs	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
charitable	O
,	O
good	O
,	O
Woman	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
't	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Papers	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
recover	O
'd	O
the	O
shock	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Cousin	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Head	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
his	O
last	O
illneſs	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
long	O
,	O
survive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
the	O
attempt	O
of	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pruſsia	I-pers
to	O
aſsaſsinate	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
--	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
piece	O
of	O
Work	O
than	O
enough	O
,	O
made	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
Woman	O
was	O
undoubtedly	O
mad	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Bedlam	B-place
,	O
ever	O
since	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
her	O
mad	O
action	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
(	O
poor	O
Creature	O
!	O
)	O
will	O
continue	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
desires	O
her	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
sure	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
stand	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
any	O
instruction	O
about	O
your	O
Work	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
commend	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
knows	O
what	O
a	O
nice	O
Work-Woman	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Pray	O
give	O
her	O
Compts	O
:	O
and	O
mine	O
to	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
my	O
charming	O
friend	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
only	O
once	O
this	O
season	O
in	O
public	O
,	O
as	O
yet	O
--	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
us	O
the	O
other	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
beautiful	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
rather	O
indispos	O
'd	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
Cold	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
soon	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
perform	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
expect	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
very	O
long	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
that	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
yours	O
sincerely	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Siddons	I-pers
October	O
30	O
th	O
:	O
1786	O
.	O
London	B-place
.	O
