TOKEN	NE
From	O
Miss	B-pers
S.	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
her	O
sister	O
in	O
law	O
Mrs.	B-pers
J	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Jany	O
26	O
.	O
1807	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Sister	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
proposes	O
to	O
send	O
My	O
Brother	O
s	O
cash	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
I	O
have	O
netted	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
casket	O
for	O
your	O
tr	O
easure	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
acceptable	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
its	O
agreeable	O
contents	O
will	O
make	O
ample	O
amends	O
for	O
its	O
numerous	O
deficiencies	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
netted	O
in	O
a	O
smaller	O
scale	O
,	O
2	O
bags	O
for	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
very	O
well	O
lately	O
;	O
&	O
since	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Pit	I-pers
s	O
speeches	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
employd	O
in	O
reading	O
&	O
admiring	O
the	O
astonishing	O
p	O
ow	O
ers	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
coud	O
expreſs	O
my	O
sentiments	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
shoud	O
be	O
as	O
enthusiastic	O
as	O
Mr	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
but	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
content	O
with	O
simply	O
observing	O
I	O
never	O
read	O
any	O
work	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
more	O
pleasure	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
last	O
night	O
every	O
prospect	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
s	O
having	O
a	O
regular	O
&	O
comfortable	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
gout	O
in	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
the	O
inflammation	O
was	O
strong	O
&	O
the	O
swelling	O
had	O
commenced	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
5	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
&	O
from	O
the	O
pain	O
he	O
complaind	O
of	O
,	O
conclud	O
ed	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
however	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
many	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
foot	O
was	O
become	O
easy	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
most	O
violen	O
t	O
&	O
obstinate	O
spasm	O
on	O
the	O
chest	O
took	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
guaiacum	O
&	O
agar	O
&	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
was	O
relieved	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
this	O
circumstance	O
so	O
fully	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
tends	O
strongly	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
spasm	O
is	O
a	O
gouty	O
affection	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
arise	O
from	O
the	O
cause	O
his	O
medical	O
friends	O
sometimes	O
suggest	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
flattering	O
hope	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
indulged	O
myself	O
in	O
repeating	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Tell	O
my	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
that	O
this	O
day	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
forgotten	O
by	O
her	O
affectionate	O
relatives	O
at	O
Birch	B-place
Hall	I-place
.	O
Grand	O
papa	O
tho	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
feel	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
sincere	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
continuance	O
of	O
helth	O
&	O
happineſs	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
sister	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
course	O
anxious	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
interruptions	O
that	O
must	O
naturally	O
arise	O
to	O
any	O
intercourse	O
with	O
that	O
devoted	O
country	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
cause	O
of	O
surprise	O
tho	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
regret	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
fever	O
about	O
the	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
enquire	O
or	O
must	O
I	O
apply	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
written	O
to	O
her	O
lately	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
woud	O
not	O
finally	O
dash	O
all	O
her	O
airy	O
dreams	O
whilst	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
least	O
hope	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
realised	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
the	O
8:8:0	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Brandt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
letter	O
tomorrow	O
(	O
if	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
tolerably	O
well	O
)	O
to	O
Manchester	B-place
when	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Mr	B-pers
Brandt	I-pers
&	O
gather	O
what	O
intelligence	O
I	O
can	O
from	O
him	O
we	O
are	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
for	O
the	O
presentation	O
,	O
&	O
medicine	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
&	O
the	O
farrier	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
valuable	O
animal	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
so	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
changing	O
him	O
is	O
given	O
up	O
.	O
you	O
will	O
thank	O
my	O
Brother	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
vines	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
more	O
productive	O
than	O
their	O
predeceſsors	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
now	O
going	O
to	O
flourish	O
,	O
or	O
paſs	O
the	O
strict	O
bounds	O
of	O
sober	O
truth	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
flowers	O
in	O
my	O
garden	O
about	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
to	O
1	O
5	O
th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
bloom	O
a	O
jonquil	O
roses	O
purple	O
primrose	O
snow	O
drop	O
hepatica	O
aconite	O
oxlip	O
heartsease	O
bearsfoot	O
,	O
yellow	O
&	O
white	O
potentilla	O
Italian	O
cytiſsus	O
Christmas	O
rose	O
daisies	O
periwinkle	O
laurustinus	O
;	O
&	O
in	O
full	O
bud	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
paſsion	O
tree	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
greenhouses	O
,	O
a	O
while	O
either	O
,	O
anemone	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
throstle	O
sing	O
in	O
december	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
sparrow	O
this	O
morning	O
pickd	O
up	O
a	O
feather	O
to	O
line	O
no	O
doubt	O
its	O
nest	O
.	O
M	O
rs	O
:	O
becky	O
presents	O
her	O
respectful	O
duty	O
to	O
her	O
young	O
mistreſs	O
&	O
desires	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
being	O
as	O
broad	O
as	O
long	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
compared	O
to	O
her	O
weighty	O
charms	O
.	O
Mungo	O
is	O
very	O
fat	O
&	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
&	O
angus	O
increases	O
daily	O
in	O
size	O
&	O
good	O
manners	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
longer	O
the	O
Bonaparte	O
of	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
&	O
even	O
sustains	O
courage	O
enables	O
him	O
to	O
br	O
ing	O
the	O
news	O
paper	O
with	O
leſs	O
dismay	O
than	O
formerly	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Mckenner	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
,	O
the	O
good	O
news	O
of	O
to	O
day	O
has	O
raised	O
Mr	B-pers
M	I-pers
above	O
par	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
coud	O
not	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
sorrowful	O
face	O
all	O
tho	O
his	O
wife	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
Great	O
an	O
invalid	O
Mr	B-pers
Streetly	I-pers
looks	O
very	O
delicate	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
declining	O
,	O
Dr	B-pers
C	I-pers
continues	O
in	O
excellent	O
mind	O
&	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
a	O
third	O
cousin	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
4000	O
a	O
year	O
is	O
an	O
undeniable	O
subject	O
on	O
all	O
occasions	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
N	I-pers
&	O
I	O
write	O
notes	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
pretty	O
notes	O
too	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
visit	O
very	O
cordially	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
expect	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
again	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
Blagsey	B-pers
is	O
arrived	O
at	O
his	O
ne	O
plus	O
ultra	O
,	O
his	O
insolence	O
&	O
ingratitude	O
can	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
as	O
I	O
trust	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
final	O
stop	O
to	O
all	O
intercourse	O
of	O
every	O
kind	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
now	O
sorry	O
,	O
altho	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
lest	O
my	O
father	O
might	O
suffer	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
h	O
e	O
s	O
borne	O
this	O
fresh	O
instance	O
of	O
his	O
malignity	O
with	O
tolerable	O
composure	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
disposed	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
happy	O
ecclairciſsement	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
particulars	O
as	O
the	O
detail	O
will	O
be	O
too	O
long	O
for	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
it	O
to	O
distinctly	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
father	O
will	O
not	O
fail	O
in	O
his	O
next	O
letter	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
circumstantial	O
account	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
's	O
paragon	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
better	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
pleasant	O
young	O
woman	O
come	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
neighbourhood	O
with	O
whose	O
mother	O
I	O
was	O
formally	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
she	O
has	O
calld	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
out	O
the	O
ceremony	O
of	O
being	O
first	O
waited	O
upon	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
return	O
her	O
visit	O
when	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
Tell	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
if	O
Mr	B-pers
Pit	I-pers
had	O
not	O
croſsed	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
shoud	O
have	O
finished	O
the	O
trim̄ing	O
