TOKEN	NE
Tewin	B-place
Water	I-place
27	O
th	O
:	O
April	O
1780	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
imagine	O
that	O
your	O
18	O
Pens	O
have	O
been	O
unemployed	O
,	O
rather	O
conceive	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
almost	O
wor'n	O
to	O
the	O
stumps	O
writing	O
to	O
such	O
of	O
my	O
Correspondents	O
as	O
vouchsafe	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
Epistles	O
.	O
Ungrateful	O
Wretch	O
,	O
Naughty	O
Brother	O
&	O
suchlike	O
Courtly	O
Phrases	O
are	O
hardly	O
comprehensible	O
to	O
a	O
Tewin	B-place
Beau	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
convince	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
poſseſsed	O
of	O
some	O
good	O
breeding	O
and	O
pay	O
proper	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
Commands	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
I	O
(	O
now	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
profound	O
Bow	O
&	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
your	O
positive	O
injunctions	O
)	O
wish	O
you	O
Joy	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
you	O
full	O
power	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
many	O
pretty	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
heighth	O
of	O
your	O
condescension	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
neceſsary	O
.	O
Turn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Page	O
&	O
you	O
will	O
discover	O
in	O
pretty	O
legible	O
Characters	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
now	O
reside	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
whence	O
you	O
shall	O
receive	O
my	O
opinion	O
fairly	O
upon	O
such	O
questions	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
chuse	O
to	O
ask	O
.	O
The	O
Dowager	O
returns	O
you	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
Stormont	O
information	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
who	O
have	O
more	O
curiosity	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
will	O
be	O
forthcoming	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Day	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
Almanack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
fixed	O
upon	O
to	O
represent	O
the	O
K	B-pers
&	O
Q	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
puzzling	O
my	O
brains	O
to	O
discover	O
what	O
weighty	O
matters	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
consulted	O
upon	O
and	O
after	O
mature	O
deliberation	O
have	O
resolved	O
that	O
the	O
little	O
God	O
Cupid	O
has	O
been	O
dealing	O
about	O
his	O
Darts	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
But	O
who	O
the	O
Adonis	O
can	O
be	O
,	O
is	O
far	O
beyond	O
my	O
dull	O
Genius	O
to	O
discover	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
3	O
personages	O
have	O
however	O
presented	O
themselves	O
to	O
my	O
imagination	O
viz	O
.	O
R——t	B-pers
G——v——le	I-pers
&	O
J——k	B-pers
H——e	I-pers
.	O
Miranda	B-pers
can	O
easily	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
Blanks	O
.	O
Had	O
your	O
Sylph	O
been	O
a	O
Widower	O
perhaps	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
Your	O
Books	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
prodigious	O
consolation	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
consider	O
myself	O
as	O
really	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Value	O
my	O
condescension	O
&	O
profit	O
by	O
the	O
Example	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
expect	O
a	O
packet	O
from	O
you	O
by	O
Saturday	O
Nights	O
Post	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
receive	O
on	O
Sunday	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Beleive	O
me	O
your	O
Affece	O
.	O
Brother	O
Edwin	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
