TOKEN	NE
Ipswich	B-place
November	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1770	O
.	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
London	B-place
where	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
paſs	O
a	O
week	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
intirely	O
forgot	O
by	O
the	O
few	O
friends	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
paſs	O
'd	O
my	O
time	O
chiefly	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
have	O
undertaken	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
trouble	O
about	O
residence	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
&	O
as	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hillsborough	I-pers
is	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
feel	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
easier	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
.	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
some	O
days	O
ago	O
from	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
who	O
is	O
at	O
Ghent	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
proposes	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
winter	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
on	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Aix	B-place
la	I-place
Chapelle	I-place
,	O
&	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
her	O
disorder	O
ending	O
in	O
a	O
jaund	O
ice	O
which	O
detain	O
'd	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
travelling	O
season	O
was	O
past	O
,	O
she	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
continue	O
where	O
she	O
is	O
till	O
next	O
Spring	O
.	O
Her	O
house	O
in	O
London	B-place
is	O
coverd	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
on	O
slowly	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Great	O
undertaking	O
&	O
above	O
her	O
abilities	O
to	O
push	O
on	O
with	O
more	O
expedition	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
Street	O
behind	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
return	O
here	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
who	O
gives	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
our	O
friends	O
at	O
Petersburgh	B-place
,	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
lately	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
at	O
Naples	B-place
who	O
has	O
obtain	O
'd	O
leave	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
England	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
next	O
Spring	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Vienna	B-place
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
the	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
a	O
personal	O
liking	O
to	O
him	O
&	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
will	O
certainly	O
go	O
Ambaſsador	O
when	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
is	O
weary	O
of	O
that	O
Office	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Patoun	I-pers
says	O
my	O
Brother	O
is	O
become	O
extremely	O
grave	O
&	O
that	O
the	O
Climate	O
of	O
Naples	B-place
has	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
and	O
yellow	O
appearance	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
astonish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
progreſs	O
Patoun	O
has	O
made	O
in	O
painting	O
he	O
has	O
totally	O
attach	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
painting	O
in	O
oil	O
colours	O
&	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
performances	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
deed	O
excellent	O
he	O
is	O
thought	O
to	O
understand	O
the	O
art	O
of	O
colouring	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
living	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
discoverd	O
many	O
valuable	O
secrets	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
very	O
much	O
with	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
who	O
has	O
settled	O
200	O
£	O
a	O
year	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
applied	O
himself	O
earlier	O
to	O
drawing	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
excell	O
'd	O
any	O
Painter	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
present	O
I	O
observe	O
defects	O
in	O
his	O
pictures	O
in	O
that	O
particular	O
&	O
chiefly	O
in	O
the	O
extremities	O
of	O
his	O
figures	O
.	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
is	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
has	O
many	O
excellent	O
qualities	O
,	O
his	O
figure	O
is	O
perfectly	O
good	O
as	O
one	O
very	O
rarely	O
meets	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
better	O
made	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
his	O
next	O
Brother	O
is	O
expected	O
home	O
this	O
month	O
from	O
Germany	B-place
,	O
his	O
appearance	O
is	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
allow	O
'd	O
on	O
all	O
hands	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
most	O
remarkably	O
good	O
understanding	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
the	O
third	O
Son	O
,	O
first	O
Cornet	O
in	O
Mordaunt	B-pers
's	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Dresden	B-place
&	O
has	O
a	O
particular	O
turn	O
for	O
military	O
knowle	O
d	O
ge	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
tall	O
&	O
is	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
&	O
striking	O
f	O
igure	O
&	O
has	O
excellent	O
dispos	O
itions	O
so	O
tha	O
t	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
thinks	O
himself	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
really	O
is	O
,	O
very	O
fortunate	O
in	O
his	O
Children	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Ldy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Louisa	I-pers
since	O
her	O
marriage	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
with	O
L.	B-pers
W——k	I-pers
who	O
allows	O
them	O
besides	O
,	O
400	O
£	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
w	O
h	O
ich	O
is	O
the	O
interest	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
ago	O
completd	O
all	O
my	O
operations	O
here	O
,	O
&	O
hav	O
e	O
very	O
comfortable	O
reside	O
nc	O
e	O
--	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
age	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
he	O
ard	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happ	O
y	O
to	O
be	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
from	O
the	O
gout	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
continue	O
to	O
like	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
to	O
be	O
affectionately	O
rememberd	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
Niece	O
as	O
does	O
also	O
you	O
r	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
Betty	B-pers
turn	O
out	O
a	O
fine	O
girl	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
lately	O
inoculated	O
our	O
with	O
great	O
succeſs	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
Dublin	B-place
for	O
my	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Welldone	I-pers
,	O
a	O
very	O
t	O
ru	O
sty	O
Person	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
your	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
past	O
till	O
I	O
can	O
n	O
instructions	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
Dear	O
Brother	O
Yours	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
at	O
Northampton	B-place
Letters	O
from	O
B	O
Letters	O
to	O
Papa	O
at	O
Ipswich	B-place
From	O
Mr	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
Charles	B-pers
at	O
Northampton	B-place
Nov	O
1770	O
