TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Mr	B-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
my	O
Sincere	O
thanks	O
for	O
all	O
yr	O
kind	O
attentions	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Scene	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
.	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
fatal	O
Strokes	O
deprived	O
me	O
not	O
only	O
of	O
an	O
Excellent	O
Parent	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
who	O
I	O
Tenderly	O
Loved	O
.	O
as	O
a	O
Companion	O
&	O
as	O
a	O
Friend	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
yet	O
seen	O
but	O
three	O
old	O
friends	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
place	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
Claſs	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
esteem	O
my	O
self	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
&	O
see	O
us	O
,	O
Either	O
this	O
Evening	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
&	O
so	O
would	O
Dr	B-pers
de	I-pers
Salis	I-pers
.	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Good	O
fortune	O
to	O
know	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
yrs	O
Afftely	O
DBloſset	B-pers
Dover	O
Street	O
,	O
March	O
25	O
th	O
-	O
1797	O
Poor	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bloſset	I-pers
died	O
Wedn	O
night	O
12	O
oClock	O
15	O
March	O
1797	O
was	O
buried	O
yesterday	O
24	O
th	O
March	O
1797	O
London	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Lower	O
Brook	O
Street	O
