TOKEN	NE
Wherwell	B-place
--	O
Nov	O
--	O
18	O
--	O
1789	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
particularly	O
desired	O
by	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
to	O
expreſs	O
their	O
sincerest	O
heart-felt	O
Thanks	O
to	O
our	O
good	O
Friends	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
their	O
solicitude	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
kind	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
sending	O
the	O
Recipe	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
have	O
experienced	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
happily	O
efficacious	O
.	O
--	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
inclined	O
to	O
have	O
Faith	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
tried	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
continued	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
your	O
Letters	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
with	O
any	O
present	O
benefit	O
yet	O
.	O
Indeed	O
within	O
this	O
last	O
fortnight	O
my	O
Father	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
worse	O
again	O
,	O
his	O
Thigh	O
is	O
swollen	O
to	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
Two	O
,	O
&	O
this	O
came	O
on	O
suddenly	O
even	O
while	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
continued	O
practice	O
of	O
a	O
recumbent	O
Posture	O
,	O
which	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
advised	O
never	O
to	O
vary	O
except	O
at	O
his	O
meals	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
dejected	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
degree	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
of	O
the	O
accident	O
been	O
persuaded	O
that	O
at	O
his	O
time	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
this	O
confinement	O
must	O
terminate	O
fatally	O
.	O
Yet	O
no	O
Disorder	O
whatever	O
ensues	O
,	O
his	O
appetite	O
remains	O
good	O
,	O
his	O
Rhumatic	O
Pains	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
leſsened	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
times	O
have	O
totally	O
ceased	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
size	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
reduced	O
,	O
&	O
his	O
Countenance	O
fallen	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
He	O
certainly	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
melancholy	O
affecting	O
state	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
immediately	O
alarming	O
;	O
and	O
every	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
consulted	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
advice	O
the	O
Country	O
affords	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
fresh	O
man	O
of	O
Eminence	O
very	O
lately	O
,	O
)	O
all	O
declare	O
,	O
seperately	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
decisive	O
unanimous	O
opinion	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
lenth	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
He	O
will	O
recover	O
.	O
They	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
have	O
ever	O
expreſsed	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
very	O
much	O
wishes	O
on	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
s	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
He	O
could	O
be	O
removed	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
that	O
She	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
warmer	O
House	O
&	O
amongst	O
her	O
Friends	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
at	O
present	O
see	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
practicable	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
scarcely	O
poſsible	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
fear	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
same	O
Posture	O
for	O
even	O
one	O
Stage	O
.	O
Poor	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
as	O
You	O
will	O
naturally	O
imagine	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
add	O
to	O
our	O
Grievances	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
complaint	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
for	O
several	O
months	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
lately	O
increased	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
troublesome	O
to	O
he	O
r	O
,	O
&	O
incapacitates	O
her	O
for	O
any	O
employment	O
,	O
&	O
does	O
not	O
yield	O
to	O
any	O
Remedy	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
advised	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
to	O
Both	O
,	O
&	O
do	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
alleviate	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
afflicted	O
House	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
lively	O
&	O
well	O
,	O
drinks	O
Aſses-milk	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
leſs	O
Thin	O
than	O
She	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
would	O
willingly	O
accept	O
her	O
challenge	O
for	O
a	O
Game	O
of	O
Play	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
within	O
distance	O
.	O
Think	O
of	O
your	O
fine	O
Friend	O
Miſs	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
having	O
staid	O
at	O
Lady	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
's	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
been	O
introduced	O
by	O
Her	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
at	O
Warwick	O
Castle	O
.	O
Cosi	O
va	O
il	O
Mondo	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
enclose	O
you	O
some	O
lines	O
which	O
poſsibly	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Lethr-	O
goes	O
between	O
this	O
&	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
direct	O
any	O
thing	O
under	O
Cover	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
unleſs	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
double	O
or	O
treble	O
enclosures	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
an	O
addreſs	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Seymour	O
Place	O
will	O
always	O
be	O
forwarded	O
wherever	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
if	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
Brother	O
&	O
all	O
this	O
House	O
unite	O
in	O
affectionate	O
compliments	O
to	O
Mr-	B-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
I	O
remain	O
with	O
great	O
Truth	O
their	O
Affectionate	O
&	O
Much	O
obliged	O
Friend	O
&	O
Servant	O
E.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
