TOKEN	NE
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
March	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
Note	O
my	O
dear	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
some	O
chance	O
of	O
a	O
reply	O
--	O
I	O
want	O
much	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
after	O
all	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
have	O
suffered	O
during	O
our	O
most	O
beloved	O
&	O
excellent	O
King	B-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
and	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
s	O
poignant	O
affliction	O
wch	O
.	O
must	O
have	O
affected	O
the	O
most	O
insensible	O
but	O
deeply	O
wounded	O
such	O
a	O
heart	O
as	O
yours	O
--	O
God	O
be	O
praised	O
our	O
grief	O
sadneſs	O
is	O
turned	O
to	O
joy	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
trust	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
will	O
consider	O
himself	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
preserve	O
a	O
life	O
of	O
such	O
infinite	O
value	O
&	O
consequence	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
one	O
good	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
overflowing	O
happineſs	O
our	O
amiable	O
&	O
exemplary	O
Queen	B-pers
and	O
the	O
Princeſses	O
must	O
feel	O
--	O
May	O
they	O
never	O
again	O
experience	O
the	O
anguish	O
of	O
mind	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
!	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
was	O
ever	O
deserving	O
of	O
the	O
highest	O
respect	O
attachment	O
&	O
admiration	O
,	O
--	O
she	O
must	O
now	O
not	O
only	O
be	O
admired	O
respected	O
&	O
loved	O
but	O
revered	O
as	O
a	O
shining	O
pattern	O
of	O
Christian	O
piety	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
else	O
than	O
a	O
firm	O
faith	O
,	O
&	O
reliance	O
on	O
he	O
Supreme	O
Being	O
could	O
have	O
supported	O
her	O
to	O
act	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
she	O
has	O
d	O
one	O
id	O
when	O
under	O
the	O
heavy	O
preſsure	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
affliction	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
with	O
a	O
particular	O
acct-	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
&	O
am	O
extremely	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
has	O
so	O
fair	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
comfort	O
&	O
happineſs	O
;	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
You	O
hear	O
often	O
frequently	O
from	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
needleſs	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
any	O
intelligence	O
respecting	O
her	O
.	O
If	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
pray	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
kindly	O
to	O
her	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
fortunate	O
circumstance	O
that	O
our	O
beloved	O
dearest	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
did	O
not	O
live	O
till	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
illneſs	O
she	O
certainly	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
heart	O
long	O
before	O
it	O
pleased	O
God	O
he	O
should	O
recover	O
.	O
If	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Schwellenberg	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
pray	O
ask	O
her	O
Mrs	B-pers
S	I-pers
if	O
she	O
has	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
one	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
entrusted	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
hand	O
ye	O
.	O
begin̅ing	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
suffer	O
so	O
terribly	O
cruelly	O
in	O
her	O
health	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Yr	O
.	O
father	O
is	O
well	O
--	O
dont	O
fail	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
very	O
cordially	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
love	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
wth	O
.	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
friendly	O
&	O
kind	O
answer	O
reply	O
to	O
my	O
letter	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
yesterday	O
--	O
If	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
is	O
at	O
W——	B-place
the	O
worthy	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
is	O
wth	O
.	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
&	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
favor	O
to	O
present	O
our	O
most	O
affectionate	O
regards	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
like	O
Mr.	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
?	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
deserving	O
respect	O
&	O
love	O
--	O
how	O
rich	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
both	O
him	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
insists	O
upon	O
my	O
sending	O
his	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
as	O
is	O
our	O
little	O
Darling	O
--	O
whom	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
sake	O
--	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
so	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yours	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
most	O
Affly	O
&	O
faithfly	O
Yours	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
inform	O
me	O
if	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
are	O
at	O
W——	B-place
tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
F	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
last	O
summer	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
disappointed	O
not	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
recd	O
.	O
an	O
ansr-	O
How	O
is	O
Mrs.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
?	O
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
de	I-pers
Luc	I-pers
that	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
ye	O
.	O
sincerest	O
regard	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
do	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
favor	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Schwellenberg	I-pers
after	O
Genl	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freytag	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
