TOKEN	NE
I	O
return	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
my	O
very	O
affectionat	O
thanks	O
for	O
her	O
obliging	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
aſsured	O
that	O
nothing	O
but	O
haveing	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
Confined	O
with	O
bad	O
health	O
this	O
Spring	O
,	O
could	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
trying	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
often	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Cultivateing	O
every	O
opportunity	O
of	O
waiting	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
but	O
when	O
one	O
is	O
ill	O
one	O
has	O
no	O
spirits	O
to	O
doe	O
either	O
what	O
is	O
right	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
one	O
wishes	O
,	O
I	O
now	O
lamented	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
doe	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
at	O
heart	O
paying	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
my	B-pers
King	I-pers
upon	O
his	O
Birth	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nursed	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
great	O
Care	O
and	O
have	O
realy	O
my	O
Cloths	O
ready	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
goe	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
fatigue	O
What	O
makes	O
me	O
regrate	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
young	O
Royall	O
family	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
realy	O
set	O
my	O
heart	O
upon	O
seeing	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
that	O
happyneſs	O
and	O
pleasure	O
this	O
two	O
year	O
,	O
how	O
ever	O
I	O
must	O
hope	O
the	O
best	O
an	O
other	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
health	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
indeavour	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Duty	O
upon	O
a	O
quiet	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
there	B-pers
Majestys	I-pers
befor	O
I	O
leave	O
town	B-place
,	O
I	O
bliſs	O
good	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
better	O
tho	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
perfectly	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
aſsured	O
of	O
the	O
affectionat	O
regard	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
your	O
much	O
obliged	O
and	O
fathfull	O
Servt	O
Cath	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Maddox	O
Street	O
May	O
30	O
th	O
1781	O
I	O
will	O
indeavour	O
if	O
posible	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
out	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
morning	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
every	O
happineſs	O
