TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
it	O
gave	O
me	O
very	O
Sincere	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
befor	O
I	O
left	O
London	B-place
that	O
you	O
was	O
got	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
continued	O
so	O
all	O
this	O
very	O
fine	O
summer	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
thought	O
of	O
makeing	O
my	O
inquiries	O
after	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
certainly	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
befor	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
Charming	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Archer	I-pers
and	O
I	O
amuses	O
our	O
selves	O
very	O
agreeably	O
with	O
work	O
reading	O
and	O
most	O
delightfull	O
airrings	O
yet	O
it	O
affords	O
very	O
few	O
incidents	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
letter	O
amuseing	O
or	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
wish	O
to	O
intertain	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
often	O
deny	O
my	O
self	O
what	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
pleasures	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
writing	O
them	O
or	O
hearing	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
now	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
giveing	O
you	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
this	O
seing	O
in	O
the	O
news	O
papers	O
,	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfrede	I-pers
has	O
been	O
danger	O
ously	O
ill	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
god	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
his	O
Royall	O
Highneſs	O
is	O
better	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
soon	O
get	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
being	O
anxious	O
to	O
hear	O
our	O
most	O
exelent	O
and	O
Ami	O
a	O
ble	O
Queen	B-pers
has	O
not	O
suffered	O
from	O
her	O
Concern	O
,	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
has	O
a	O
great	O
dell	O
of	O
fortitude	O
but	O
her	O
Exelent	O
heart	O
would	O
feel	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
so	O
charmine	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
writ	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
greater	O
enthusiast	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
Concerns	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
my	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
I	O
hope	O
all	O
the	O
Royall	O
family	O
are	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
rejoice	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
writ	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
is	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlote	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
returned	O
or	O
is	O
her	O
son	O
like	O
to	O
recover	O
poor	O
woman	O
She	O
is	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
pittyed	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
writs	O
me	O
Mr	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mrs	I-pers
Graham	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
are	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
winter	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
of	O
france	B-place
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
back	O
to	O
Lisbon	B-place
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
seems	O
very	O
happy	O
with	O
nursing	O
her	O
son	O
Charles	B-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
exemple	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
fine	O
Ladys	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
few	O
so	O
handsom	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
few	O
things	O
would	O
hurt	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
Children	O
was	O
not	O
behave	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
very	O
highest	O
attachment	O
for	O
there	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
all	O
realy	O
exemplary	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
thy	O
will	O
ever	O
Continue	O
so	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Hume	I-pers
very	O
lately	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
musick	O
at	O
Salisbury	B-place
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
very	O
superb	O
intertainment	O
at	O
Fonthill	B-place
,	O
upon	O
your	O
Cousins	O
Mr	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
s	O
birth	O
day	O
upon	O
his	O
Comming	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
paragraph	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
to	O
inclose	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
very	O
superb	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dar	O
say	O
all	O
the	O
fine	O
young	O
Ladys	O
that	O
wear	O
there	O
,	O
wear	O
in	O
full	O
expectation	O
of	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prise	O
,	O
now	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
doe	O
me	O
the	O
favour	O
to	O
writ	O
me	O
soon	O
and	O
beleive	O
me	O
with	O
very	O
sincere	O
regard	O
and	O
esteem	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
most	O
affectionat	O
and	O
much	O
obliged	O
Cath	B-pers
:	I-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
Hale	B-place
by	O
Downton	B-place
Wilts	B-place
Octr	O
1	O
st	O
1781	O
