TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
Evening	O
14	O
th	O
August	O
1783	O
A	O
Thousand	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
niece	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
eagerneſs	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
St	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
tired	O
to	O
death	O
&	O
very	O
hungry	O
--	O
so	O
shall	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
meet	O
you	O
any	O
day	O
you	O
please	O
at	O
my	O
Brother	O
Frederick	B-pers
s	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hotel	O
King	O
Street	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
go	O
to	O
Scotland	B-place
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
thes	O
'	O
e	O
ten	O
days	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
--	O
your	O
tired	O
hungry	O
but	O
affectionate	O
Uncle	O
Wm	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
let	O
my	O
Br	O
.	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
if	O
not	O
inconvenient	O
but	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
put	O
yourself	O
to	O
inconveni	O
ence	O
Thursday	O
past	O
5	O
&	O
no	O
dinner	O
yet	O
To	O
The	B-pers
Honble	I-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
