TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
morning	O
received	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
yours	O
of	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
with	O
the	O
enclosed	O
Bill	O
for	O
One	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
on	O
Meſs	O
rs	O
.	O
Jones	O
&	O
Co.	O
Bankers	O
in	O
London	B-place
&	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
desire	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
accepted	O
&	O
according	O
to	O
form	O
,	O
they	O
avail	O
themselves	O
of	O
the	O
Days	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
however	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
cash	O
in	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
comes	O
in	O
perfect	O
good	O
time	O
as	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
informs	O
me	O
the	O
busineſs	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Secretary	O
at	O
War	O
,	O
till	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
your	O
part	O
&	O
the	O
confidence	O
you	O
repose	O
in	O
me	O
adds	O
greatly	O
to	O
the	O
obligation	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
now	O
perfectly	O
&	O
if	O
I	O
dont	O
forget	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
ever	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
manly	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
singular	O
favor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
is	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
suppose	O
,	O
in	O
no	O
small	O
joy	O
&	O
knows	O
the	O
transaction	O
.	O
Our	O
united	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
remain	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
most	O
Obliged	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Oxford	O
Street	O
249	O
.	O
October	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
Park	O
Gate	O
near	O
Chester	B-place
