TOKEN	NE
Sunday	O
Morning	O
April	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
1786	O
My	O
dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
hope	O
you	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
the	O
scrawl	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
compleatly	O
tired	O
&	O
ill	O
that	O
instead	O
of	O
writing	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
prefer	O
'd	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
--	O
but	O
dear	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
&	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
four	O
&	O
twenty	O
pages	O
allready	O
written	O
to	O
your	O
Cara	O
Sposa	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
that	O
volume	O
large	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
intends	O
paying	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
she	O
said	O
yesterday	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
beg	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
reason	O
,	O
the	O
answer	O
was	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
convenient	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
notion	O
it	O
is	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Bell	B-pers
who	O
is	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
well	O
all	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
better	O
now	O
&	O
her	O
spirits	O
are	O
rather	O
better	O
.	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
is	O
such	O
a	O
sweet	O
place	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
could	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
enjoy	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
spot	O
nor	O
place	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
constantly	O
remind	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
dear	O
improver	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
fancy	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
hear	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
walk	O
,	O
I	O
miſs	O
him	O
there	O
far	O
more	O
than	O
here	O
,	O
Oh	O
my	O
dear	O
brother	O
it	O
he	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
loſs	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
a	O
loſs	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
affects	O
me	O
more	O
now	O
than	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
lost	O
that	O
best	O
of	O
friends	O
of	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
in	O
hearing	O
that	O
your	O
good	O
Father	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
uneasy	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
Town	B-place
as	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
worse	O
than	O
he	O
wrote	O
you	O
word	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
feel	O
no	O
more	O
from	O
the	O
ugly	O
strain	O
that	O
you	O
complain	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
our	O
guest	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
miſs	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
every	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
;	O
Mr-	B-pers
John	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
whom	O
you	O
saw	O
is	O
married	O
&	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
improv	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
looks	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
an	O
agreeable	O
man	O
,	O
rather	O
graver	O
than	O
you	O
are	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
too	O
grave	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
though	O
without	O
flattery	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
quite	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
a	O
certain	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
will	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
advice	O
on	O
a	O
certain	O
subject	O
,	O
their	O
is	O
no	O
ones	O
advice	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
take	O
or	O
be	O
more	O
thankful	O
for	O
than	O
your	O
's	O
&	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miſs	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
of	O
your	O
esteem	O
&	O
love	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Adieu	O
I	O
must	O
drop	O
for	O
church	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
as	O
if	O
their	O
was	O
thunder	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
rain	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
acceptable	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
very	O
backward	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
her	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
£100	O
at	O
her	O
death	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
I	O
think	O
by	O
my	O
conclusion	O
yesterday	O
you	O
will	O
perceive	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
spirits	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
better	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
tea	O
at	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
..	I-pers
s	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
painted	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
which	O
Sr	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
Kneller	I-pers
has	O
lately	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Queensbury	I-pers
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
painted	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
92	O
when	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
about	O
19	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
in	O
Armour	O
very	O
handsome	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
small	O
resemblance	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H——	I-pers
has	O
in	O
his	O
poſseſsion	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
which	O
he	O
has	O
promised	O
to	O
the	B-pers
late	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
for	O
a	O
companion	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
painted	O
by	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
H——	I-pers
likewise	O
the	O
colours	O
are	O
still	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
has	O
just	O
purchased	O
a	O
pr-	O
of	O
ponies	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
black	O
&	O
very	O
handsome	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
breaking	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
happy	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
driving	O
them	O
this	O
summer	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
look	O
better	O
&	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
desires	O
her	O
affectionate	O
love	O
to	O
her	O
dear	O
Sr.	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
&	O
her	O
saucy	O
husband	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
with	O
whom	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
slight	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
my	O
publication	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
en	O
train	O
,	O
Miranda	B-pers
undertakes	O
all	O
the	O
trouble	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
detain	O
us	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
in	O
Town	B-place
than	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
On	O
thursday	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
stag	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
on	O
Ascot	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
was	O
there	O
&	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
;	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
stag	O
hounds	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
&	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
monday	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
therefore	O
made	O
his	O
Apologies	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Hinchinbroke	I-pers
&	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
joy	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
a	O
fever	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
stroke	O
was	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
answer	O
,	O
very	O
comforting	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
think	O
.	O
--	O
Pray	O
tell	O
his	B-pers
majesty	I-pers
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D——	I-pers
is	O
dead	O
&	O
has	O
left	O
debts	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
seven	O
hundred	O
pound	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Bloodworth	I-pers
buried	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
expence	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
since	O
her	O
death	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
hypocrite	O
who	O
during	O
her	O
life	O
time	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
charitable	O
&	O
religious	O
.	O
ye-	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
desires	O
her	O
best	O
compts	O
..	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
--	O
When	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
marriage	O
was	O
mention	O
'd	O
before	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
she	O
said	O
O-	O
.	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
many	O
such	O
wives	O
as	O
George	B-pers
he	O
had	O
his	O
failings	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
heart	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
reports	O
out	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
F——t	I-pers
I	O
just	O
left	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
F	I-pers
's	O
a	O
quater	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
cards	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
playing	O
till	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
tired	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
really	O
been	O
at	O
cards	O
with	O
the	O
P——	O
the	O
whole	O
evening	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
now	O
conclude	O
this	O
dull	O
&	O
tedious	O
scrawl	O
with	O
aſsuring	O
my	O
brother	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
great	O
truth	O
his	O
ever	O
obliged	O
friend	O
&	O
sister	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
V	I-pers
:	I-pers
My	O
affectionate	O
&	O
kindest	O
love	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
M	B-pers
..	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
