TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
have	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
moving	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
informing	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
s	O
Death	O
,	O
&	O
expreſsing	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
grateful	O
terms	O
his	O
Sense	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
s	O
Gracious	O
Goodness	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
adds	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
Improper	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Corpse	O
in	O
the	O
Palace	O
any	O
longer	O
than	O
is	O
absolutely	O
neceſsary	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Laſps	O
.	O
directions	O
when	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
removed	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
desire	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hagerdorn	I-pers
to	O
shew	O
this	O
to	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
tonight	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
receive	O
her	O
Orders	O
concerning	O
the	O
Answer	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
;	O
as	O
her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
probably	O
goes	O
to	O
Kew	B-place
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
speaking	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Ever	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
¼	O
past	O
Ten	O
We	O
have	O
recd	O
.	O
a	O
sad	O
Account	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
