TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
announce	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
glad	O
tidings	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
having	O
been	O
this	O
morning	O
safely	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
&	O
stout	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
its	O
dear	O
mother	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
add	O
,	O
are	O
at	O
present	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
We	O
could	O
wish	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
very	O
faithful	O
&	O
Obedient	O
Humb	O
le	O
Servant	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
Monday	O
Decr	O
.	O
1	O
st	O
:	O
London	B-place
December	O
One	O
1800	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Bedfordshire	B-place
free	O
RFGreville	B-pers
