TOKEN	NE
4	O
Sunning	B-place
Hill	I-place
Augst	O
..	O
12	O
th	O
..	O
1782	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Devaynes	I-pers
is	O
just	O
arrived	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
has	O
deliver	O
'd	O
your	O
meſsage	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
before	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
with	O
pleasure	O
to	O
have	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
father	O
s	O
health	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
better	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
few	O
days	O
the	O
waters	O
have	O
not	O
agreed	O
quite	O
so	O
well	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
intends	O
leaving	O
off	O
the	O
waters	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
&	O
Katherine	B-pers
din	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
yesterday	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
think	O
be	O
much	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
Katherine	B-pers
she	O
is	O
so	O
very	O
much	O
improved	O
,	O
your	O
little	O
goddaughter	O
is	O
grown	O
really	O
beautiful	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
endow	O
'd	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
virtues	O
of	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
&	O
god	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
then	O
be	O
as	O
amiable	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
likely	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
pretty	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
much	O
disappointed	O
in	O
not	O
seeing	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
you	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Sunning	B-place
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
prevented	O
by	O
illneſs	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
wish	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
ever	O
you	O
can	O
come	O
,	O
write	O
us	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
receive	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
&	O
mother	O
desire	O
their	O
Love	O
.	O
I	O
remain	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
your	O
ever	O
obiged	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
