TOKEN	NE
Kew	B-place
House	I-place
Saturday	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
inclose	O
a	O
Letter	O
without	O
writing	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
lines	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
for	O
your	O
welcome	O
Epistle	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
begun	O
to	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
much	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
--	O
Their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
came	O
home	O
yesterdy	O
Evg	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sincerely	O
glad	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
my	O
Friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Cowper	I-pers
,	O
which	O
visit	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
aprehensive	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
Rupert	B-pers
says	O
we	O
all	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
next	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
every	O
Friday	O
,	O
&	O
return	O
here	O
every	O
Wedy	O
the	O
little	O
Princes	O
likewise	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
for	O
certain	O
by	O
Thursday	O
&	O
will	O
in	O
my	O
Letter	O
to	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
mention	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
you	O
spend	O
yr-	O
time	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
your	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
&	O
feel	O
very	O
sincerely	O
all	O
the	O
kind	O
things	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
Selfish	O
,	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
think	O
&	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
Friends	O
are	O
happy	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
now	O
as	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
are	O
here	O
additional	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
a	O
Patrole	O
of	O
Dragoons	O
,	O
however	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
quiet	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
shall	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
recd	O
the	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
&	O
a	O
Locket	O
safe	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
last	O
Saturday	O
by	O
the	O
Lewes	O
Coach	O
--	O
Pray	O
give	O
my	O
Affte	O
Duty	O
to	O
Dear	O
Prſs	B-pers
Elizth	I-pers
,	O
her	O
three	O
Sisters	O
are	O
at	O
Dinner	O
with	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Elder	O
Princes	O
,	O
Prſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
however	O
has	O
dined	O
,	O
but	O
sits	O
by	O
,	O
&	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
charming	O
than	O
her	O
whole	O
Behaviour	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
Love	O
to	O
Dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Affly	O
Yr-	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
be	O
careful	O
about	O
your	O
Letters	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
shew	O
yours	O
but	O
I	O
burnt	O
it	O
purposely	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
therefore	O
what	O
you	O
wish	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
write	O
upon	O
a	O
Separate	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
July	O
1	O
st	O
1780	O
