TOKEN	NE
South	O
Audley	O
Street	O
--	O
Sunday	O
7	O
th	O
May	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
are	O
thanki	O
n	O
g	O
God	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
return	O
!	O
he	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
,	O
looking	O
comfortable	O
&	O
occupied	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
told	O
you	O
about	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
probably	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
looked	O
ill	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
a	O
moment	O
for	O
writing	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
thanked	O
you	O
e	O
're	O
now	O
for	O
your	O
dear	O
tho	O
'	O
short	O
little	O
note	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
Ld	B-pers
Ilchester	I-pers
s	O
merely	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
to	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
Friends	O
,	O
whose	O
kind	O
congratulations	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
answered	O
--	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Digby	I-pers
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
resist	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
leisure	O
,	O
which	O
otherwise	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
find	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
most	O
happy	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
Louisa	B-pers
improving	O
in	O
Health	O
&	O
strength	O
&	O
perfections	O
,	O
&	O
of	O
course	O
that	O
your	O
comforts	O
were	O
daily	O
increasi	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
too	O
a	O
new	O
interest	O
in	O
Taxal	B-place
&	O
of	O
course	O
new	O
amusement	O
s	O
&	O
occupation	O
in	O
the	O
alterations	O
&	O
improvements	O
you	O
are	O
maki	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
London	B-place
this	O
year	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
tells	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
wonder	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
dislik	O
e	O
quitting	O
a	O
beautiful	O
spot	O
in	O
this	O
delightful	O
season	O
where	O
every	O
source	O
of	O
happineſs	O
is	O
united	O
in	O
your	O
husband	O
&	O
your	O
Child	O
!	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
happy	O
too	O
here	O
I	O
find	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
feel	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
more	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
dinners	O
of	O
ceremony	O
are	O
over	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
more	O
regular	O
plan	O
of	O
comfort	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
hitherto	O
enjoyed	O
it	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
hardly	O
in	O
publick	O
at	O
all	O
&	O
but	O
at	O
one	O
play	O
&	O
one	O
Opera	O
since	O
I	O
married	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entered	O
into	O
so	O
numerous	O
a	O
family	O
,	O
all	O
so	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
great	O
difficulty	O
I	O
find	O
means	O
to	O
divide	O
myself	O
amongst	O
them	O
without	O
neglecting	O
my	O
old	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
rise	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
breakfast	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
9	O
--	O
then	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
stays	O
talking	O
till	O
perhaps	O
near	O
12	O
--	O
then	O
my	O
little	O
Girls	O
leſsons	O
,	O
with	O
sometim	O
es	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
sometimes	O
some	O
neceſsary	O
visits	O
&	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
Mr	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
or	O
Brown	B-pers
for	O
myself	O
bring	O
me	O
to	O
4	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
dreſs	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
plainly	O
see	O
leave	O
me	O
little	O
time	O
for	O
writing	O
or	O
reading	O
both	O
of	O
which	O
talents	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
in	O
some	O
danger	O
of	O
forgetting	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
hitherto	O
generally	O
dined	O
out	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
have	O
begun	O
to	O
give	O
dinners	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
return	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
over	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
begin	O
to	O
enjoy	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
stomack	O
--	O
&	O
am	O
every	O
now	O
&	O
then	O
very	O
bad	O
--	O
then	O
better	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
to	O
day	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
day	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
Farquar	B-pers
's	O
care	O
to	O
please	O
Mr	B-pers
D——	I-pers
&	O
my	O
Father	O
&	O
am	O
taking	O
Hemlock	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
nonsense	O
,	O
&	O
God	O
alone	O
can	O
do	O
me	O
good	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
he	O
will	O
soon	O
--	O
my	O
Brother	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
from	O
a	O
hurt	O
he	O
received	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
from	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
is	O
recoveri	O
n	O
g	O
thank	O
God	O
very	O
fast	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
de	O
temps	O
en	O
temps	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
one	O
can	O
ex	O
pec	O
t	O
from	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
&	O
the	O
mistre	O
ſs	O
of	O
a	O
family	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
more	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
Most	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
affec	O
:	O
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
D	I-pers
C.	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
Miss	B-pers
C.M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
married	O
Colonel	B-pers
the	I-pers
Honble	I-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
of	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
brother	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
first	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
Digby	I-pers
--	O
in	O
1790	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
