TOKEN	NE
Harleyford	B-place
Friday	O
Night	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Feilding	I-pers
s	O
return	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
back	O
the	O
pretty	O
Entertaining	O
Manuscript	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
entrust	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
suffer	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Leaves	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
wet	O
in	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
that	O
rainy	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dried	O
them	O
very	O
carefully	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
they	O
have	O
suffer	O
'd	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
poſsible	O
.	O
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Duty	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Houſe	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
tomorrow	O
will	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
there	O
&	O
particularly	O
of	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
of	O
answering	O
P.	B-pers
Ernest	I-pers
s	O
Letter	O
&	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
thank	O
H.R.H	B-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
new	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
my	O
health	O
,	O
so	O
will	O
only	O
add	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
's	O
kind	O
Compliments	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
she	O
reproaches	O
me	O
with	O
having	O
omitted	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
shared	O
in	O
the	O
Amusement	O
of	O
the	O
pretty	O
Manuscript	O
I	O
am	O
ever	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamn	I-pers
Most	O
Affly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
CFinch	B-pers
Remember	O
me	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
