TOKEN	NE
Wandsworth	O
hill	O
Sepr	O
.	O
4	O
th	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
should	O
think	O
me	O
so	O
negligent	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
omitted	O
answ'ring	O
your	O
kind	O
Letter	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
last	O
would	O
have	O
reached	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
Windsor	B-place
or	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
directed	O
it	O
there	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
&	O
the	O
Child	O
continue	O
perfectly	O
well	O
she	O
wished	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
more	O
prudent	O
to	O
check	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
&	O
insisted	O
upon	O
being	O
her	O
Secretary	O
--	O
she	O
complains	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
arbitrary	O
and	O
desires	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wont	O
let	O
her	O
speak	O
for	O
herself	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
happy	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
your	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
's	O
Christening	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
hopes	O
you	O
will	O
if	O
poſsible	O
contrive	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
thinks	O
of	O
having	O
the	O
ceremony	O
performed	O
on	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
but	O
if	O
Saturday	O
should	O
be	O
more	O
convenient	O
&	O
agreeable	O
to	O
you	O
she	O
will	O
very	O
willingly	O
change	O
the	O
day	O
--	O
she	O
begs	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
her	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
desire	O
he	O
will	O
keep	O
himself	O
unengaged	O
for	O
that	O
occasion	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
's	O
Coq	O
de	O
perle	O
necklace	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
Mr.	B-pers
Duval	I-pers
's	O
hands	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
interrupted	O
and	O
must	O
therefore	O
conclude	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
yr	O
.	O
very	O
affecte-	O
&	O
c	O
Elizath	B-pers
.	I-pers
M.	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
Papa	O
desires	O
his	O
best	O
Compts-	O
&	O
joins	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
hoping	O
you	O
will	O
favor	O
us	O
with	O
yr	O
.	O
Company	O
