TOKEN	NE
St.	B-place
Georges	I-place
Bermuda	B-place
Decr	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
1790	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
in	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ds	I-pers
.	I-pers
improvement	O
in	O
health	O
--	O
pray	O
acquaint	O
him	O
of	O
of	O
that	O
&	O
the	O
&	O
era	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
reflect	O
upon	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
so	O
distant	O
from	O
many	O
whom	O
I	O
revere	O
,	O
esteem	O
,	O
or	O
love	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
impulse	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
regret	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
correct	O
this	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
poſſible	O
,	O
by	O
recollecting	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
entirely	O
forgotten	O
by	O
these	O
estimable	O
friends	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
general	O
distance	O
produces	O
indifference	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
secondly	O
,	O
some	O
thing	O
very	O
like	O
oblivion	O
--	O
now	O
since	O
I	O
derive	O
so	O
much	O
pleasure	O
from	O
the	O
communication	O
of	O
friends	O
,	O
how	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
expreſs	O
my	O
thankfullneſs	O
?	O
In	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
in	O
my	O
situation	O
poſſible	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
by	O
setting	O
out	O
on	O
my	O
journey	O
towards	O
them	O
(	O
by	O
letter	O
)	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
minnikin	O
character	O
as	O
shews	O
my	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
long	O
talk	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
a	O
reply	O
twice	O
as	O
long	O
--	O
and	O
indeed	O
all	O
things	O
duely	O
considerd	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
that	O
expectation	O
--	O
My	O
European	O
friends	O
are	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
thousand	O
topics	O
of	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
anecdote	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
interesting	O
to	O
one	O
so	O
remote	O
from	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
The	O
World	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
You	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
unfashionable	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
so	O
vain	O
as	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
antiquated	O
term	O
which	O
implies	O
something	O
nearer	O
than	O
common	O
acquaintance	O
or	O
even	O
friendship	O
,	O
You	O
my	O
dear	O
Coz	O
(	O
note	O
the	O
familiarity	O
)	O
have	O
well	O
understood	O
how	O
great	O
the	O
pleasure	O
must	O
be	O
which	O
I	O
derive	O
from	O
so	O
chearful	O
and	O
pleasant	O
a	O
letter	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
honord	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
However	O
proud	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
(	O
as	O
a	O
Hamilton	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
that	O
persuasion	O
of	O
your	O
excellent	O
understanding	O
that	O
titles	O
Wealth	O
and	O
all	O
exterior	O
loses	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
set	O
in	O
contrast	O
with	O
honor	O
,	O
honest	O
pride	O
,	O
veracity	O
generosity	O
humanity	O
and	O
those	O
leſs	O
brilliant	O
but	O
more	O
amiable	O
qualifications	O
of	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
un	O
...	O
common	O
acquaintances	O
and	O
friends	O
are	O
poſſeſsd	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
for	O
your	O
flattery	O
in	O
writing	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
and	O
that	O
your	O
letter	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
short	O
one	O
)	O
--	O
This	O
kindneſs	O
was	O
the	O
leſs	O
expected	O
,	O
as	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
England	B-place
(	O
however	O
my	O
health	O
might	O
be	O
)	O
my	O
Spirits	O
were	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
up	O
to	O
their	O
usual	O
level	O
--	O
Under	O
such	O
circumstances	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
natural	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
appear	O
indifferent	O
where	O
indifference	O
could	O
not	O
or	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
find	O
admittance	O
.	O
I	O
well	O
recollect	O
a	O
coldneſs	O
of	O
manner	O
and	O
an	O
indifference	O
to	O
the	O
subjects	O
of	O
conversation	O
which	O
might	O
well	O
wear	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
apathy	O
or	O
superciliousneſs	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
however	O
at	O
bottom	O
--	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
at	O
the	O
sollicitation	O
of	O
M	O
.	O
I	O
carryed	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
London	B-place
real	O
affection	O
and	O
a	O
wish	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
loving	O
and	O
estimable	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
that	O
the	O
incertainty	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
joined	O
to	O
the	O
embarrassment	O
of	O
my	O
circumstances	O
laid	O
so	O
many	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
upon	O
a	O
heart	O
naturally	O
light	O
and	O
inconsiderate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
grave	O
look	O
and	O
frequent	O
absenses	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
air	O
of	O
indifference	O
which	O
were	O
totally	O
foreign	O
to	O
my	O
natural	O
diſposition	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
habitual	O
careleſsneſs	O
which	O
my	O
old	O
friends	O
and	O
acquaintances	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
embroidery	O
of	O
my	O
constitution	O
.	O
I	O
pray	O
you	O
gentle	O
Cox	O
pardon	O
that	O
apparent	O
coldneſs	O
and	O
visiting	O
manner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
frequently	O
snubbed	O
myself	O
,	O
while	O
your	O
courteousneſs	O
and	O
prevenance	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
more	O
frequent	O
and	O
leſs	O
constrained	O
intercourse	O
--	O
I	O
owe	O
to	O
your	O
kindneſs	O
this	O
confeſſion	O
and	O
now	O
having	O
bent	O
the	O
knee	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
teize	O
you	O
no	O
longer	O
with	O
peccavis	O
Of	O
Lady	B-pers
D.	I-pers
Vesie	I-pers
an	O
able	O
panegyrist	O
would	O
be	O
posed	O
to	O
pronounce	O
all	O
her	O
various	O
merits	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
content	O
myself	O
with	O
telling	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
poſſeſsion	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Treasure	O
ought	O
to	O
endeavor	O
by	O
every	O
poſſible	O
attention	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
understand	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
value	O
he	O
set	O
upon	O
so	O
inestimable	O
a	O
prize	O
in	O
the	O
matrimonial	O
lottery	O
--	O
She	O
can	O
not	O
hide	O
her	O
Talents	O
in	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
diffidence	O
constantly	O
throws	O
a	O
veil	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
masculine	O
mind	O
and	O
understanding	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
truly	O
femine	O
and	O
most	O
delicately	O
so	O
without	O
parade	O
or	O
affectation	O
--	O
She	O
knows	O
too	O
well	O
what	O
beauty	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
blind	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
gesture	O
escapes	O
her	O
that	O
can	O
betray	O
her	O
consciousneſs	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
happyneſs	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
is	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
fill	O
her	O
eyes	O
with	O
tears	O
than	O
any	O
distreſs	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
--	O
you	O
may	O
discover	O
a	O
beautiful	O
soul	O
thro	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
such	O
eyes	O
!	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
never	O
dared	O
to	O
consider	O
the	O
lustre	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
offending	O
--	O
If	O
Women	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
placed	O
on	O
seats	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
their	O
perfections	O
she	O
should	O
undoubtedly	O
hold	O
her	O
place	O
among	O
the	O
highest	O
--	O
This	O
Thought	O
reminds	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Painters	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
Model	O
I	O
would	O
frame	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Females	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
known	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
and	O
who	O
have	O
honord	O
me	O
with	O
some	O
tokens	O
of	O
their	O
condescension	O
or	O
what	O
other	O
term	O
shall	O
I	O
use	O
,	O
goodwill	O
,	O
will	O
that	O
do	O
?	O
you	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
so	O
judge	O
--	O
I	O
detest	O
those	O
men	O
who	O
are	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
specks	O
on	O
snow	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
use	O
the	O
Seamans	O
phrase	O
,	O
&	O
bl-st	O
their	O
eyes	O
--	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
answer	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——	I-pers
s	O
Quære	O
--	O
now	O
I	O
will	O
turn	O
to	O
a	O
subject	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
familiar	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
dear	O
delightful	O
creature	O
myself	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
happy	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
as	O
Horace	B-pers
says	O
uti	O
conviva	O
satir	O
Horace	O
,	O
Satires	O
1	O
:	O
i	O
,	O
94	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
know	O
well	O
enough	O
--	O
yet	O
you	O
will	O
turn	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D——n	I-pers
,	O
pray	O
what	O
does	O
this	O
man	O
mean	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
his	O
politeneſs	O
,	O
does	O
he	O
take	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
she	O
Pedant	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
aſſure	O
you	O
my	O
amiable	O
Coz	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
flattering	O
circumstance	O
of	O
receiving	O
letters	O
from	O
kind	O
absentees	O
makes	O
the	O
chief	O
gratification	O
and	O
solamen	O
of	O
my	O
present	O
situation	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
circumstantially	O
how	O
my	O
time	O
paſses	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
not	O
to	O
indulge	O
too	O
far	O
the	O
loquacity	O
of	O
my	O
pen	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
long	O
small	O
letters	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
affectionate	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
employ	O
the	O
term	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
hand	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
should	O
paſs	O
for	O
a	O
puppy	O
,	O
what	O
care	O
I	O
?	O
However	O
before	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
scribble	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
congratulate	O
you	O
both	O
on	O
that	O
delightfull	O
independance	O
you	O
so	O
exultingly	O
describe	O
may	O
you	O
long	O
enjoy	O
it	O
in	O
perfection	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
my	O
sacred	O
word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
eyewitneſs	O
of	O
your	O
happyneſs	O
if	O
Lady	O
Fortune	O
ever	O
indulges	O
my	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
England	B-place
again	O
where	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
friends	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
--	O
The	O
kind	O
terms	O
of	O
your	O
letter	O
engage	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
unreserved	O
communication	O
has	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Stratford	I-pers
s	O
sister	O
,	O
alias	O
her	O
Mother	O
s	O
daughter	O
profited	O
by	O
the	O
private	O
Theatricals	O
which	O
were	O
so	O
public	O
--	O
is	O
her	O
father	O
yet	O
disgusted	O
with	O
his	O
new	O
house	O
or	O
his	O
old	O
...	O
lady	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
so	O
venemously	O
cruel	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
you	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
such	O
a	O
sentence	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
proof	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
entrust	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
character	O
--	O
I	O
once	O
at	O
Oxford	O
met	O
a	O
little	O
starched	O
Cousin	O
,	O
late	O
a	O
fellow	O
of	O
C	O
.	O
C	O
.	O
now	O
Dean	O
of	O
Tuam	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
after	O
dinner	O
pour	O
m'egayer	O
I	O
ridiculed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
old	O
card	O
playing	O
everlasting	O
Aunts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
University	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
grave	O
face	O
&	O
monitory	O
tone	O
of	O
Voice	O
cried	O
oh	O
Couzen	O
!	O
we	O
should	O
never	O
laugh	O
at	O
our	O
Relations	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
think	O
our	O
relations	O
are	O
as	O
fair	O
game	O
as	O
heart	O
can	O
wish	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
is	O
my	O
relation	O
and	O
I	O
bleſs	O
my	O
stars	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
number	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
whom	O
I	O
love	O
pretty	O
intensely	O
--	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
relations	O
who	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
friends	O
,	O
tried	O
ones	O
,	O
refined	O
in	O
that	O
unerring	O
crucible	O
,	O
the	O
test	O
of	O
all	O
profeſſions	O
and	O
promises	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
parting	O
with	O
their	O
money	O
--	O
I	O
require	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
alterations	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
in	O
house	O
garden	O
or	O
farm	O
,	O
if	O
the	B-pers
elder	I-pers
Mr.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
since	O
your	O
setting	O
up	O
for	O
yourselves	O
--	O
have	O
your	O
Neighbours	O
a	O
de	O
V	O
.	O
among	O
them	O
?	O
rejoyce	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Villiers	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
at	O
heart	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
sterling	O
merit	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
match	O
for	O
her	O
--	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
my	O
clever	O
Cousin	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irish	O
Patriot	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
improvement	O
in	O
commerce	O
,	O
science	O
,	O
manners	O
,	O
that	O
wild	O
is	O
becoming	O
tame	O
,	O
that	O
vanity	O
is	O
becoming	O
pride	O
,	O
ostentation	O
hospitallity	O
,	O
and	O
hospitallity	O
improved	O
from	O
making	O
folk	O
deadly	O
drunk	O
,	O
into	O
making	O
them	O
sociably	O
reasonably	O
happy	O
--	O
But	O
England	B-place
is	O
my	O
Foster	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
owe	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
if	O
during	O
my	O
remainder	O
of	O
life	O
rebellion	O
took	O
place	O
in	O
Shamrockshire	B-place
,	O
I	O
should	O
coot	O
paddy	O
's	O
troat	O
to	O
larn	O
him	O
better	O
manners	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
de	I-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
making	O
love	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
the	O
Boar	O
in	O
silence	O
creeping	O
Alexander	O
Pope	O
,	O
A	O
Love	O
Song	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Modern	O
Taste	O
(	O
1733	O
)	O
.	O
--	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
certainly	O
recover	O
--	O
young	O
M	B-pers
:	I-pers
writes	O
me	O
long	O
letters	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
love	O
the	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
could	O
approve	O
for	O
her	O
help	O
mate	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Catholic	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
kiſs	O
the	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
's	O
for	O
a	O
dispensation	O
,	O
so	O
well	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
In	O
a	O
conversation	O
where	O
the	O
personae	O
dramatis	O
were	O
Lydia	B-pers
Whyte	I-pers
Colol	B-pers
.	I-pers
Phipps	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Junior	I-pers
and	O
your	O
humble	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
Spinster	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
had	O
more	O
solidity	O
with	O
connaiſsance	O
de	O
cause	O
than	O
we	O
other	O
three	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
withal	O
a	O
loving	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
far	O
from	O
selfish	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
sort	O
of	O
thing	O
which	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
husband	O
and	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
personals	O
which	O
give	O
a	O
zest	O
to	O
existence	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
us	O
more	O
devout	O
than	O
Hell	O
and	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
pitch	O
for	O
his	O
pasture	O
Worms	O
despair	O
&	O
darkneſs	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
A	O
beautiful	O
Woman	O
,	O
a	O
rose	O
or	O
any	O
sweet	O
,	O
the	O
Ocean	O
,	O
sky	O
,	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
a	O
Cathedral	O
,	O
an	O
Organ	O
and	O
Psalm	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Jordan	I-pers
in	O
Viola	O
,	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Milnes	I-pers
tho	O
in	O
full	O
dreſs	O
,	O
an	O
Orchard	O
in	O
full	O
bearing	O
,	O
forgiveness	O
with	O
tears	O
,	O
the	O
glorious	O
Sun	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
sparks	O
from	O
the	O
Powerful	O
king	O
whose	O
light	O
we	O
dare	O
not	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
emanations	O
which	O
our	O
senses	O
qualify	O
us	O
to	O
admire	O
,	O
&	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
we	O
communicate	O
adoration	O
without	O
a	O
direct	O
addreſs	O
--	O
What	O
think	O
you	O
--	O
Our	O
Parson	O
here	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
stupid	O
fellow	O
,	O
prays	O
for	O
rain	O
--	O
I	O
might	O
just	O
as	O
well	O
pray	O
for	O
L.	B-pers
de	I-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
my	O
adorables	O
who	O
are	O
actually	O
in	O
poſſeſſion	O
of	O
the	O
rightful	O
owners	O
--	O
This	O
is	O
fine	O
language	O
from	O
a	O
Greybeard	O
.	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Clock	O
chinks	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
saw	O
built	O
on	O
experiance	O
--	O
you	O
postage	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
transfer	O
you	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
roses	O
and	O
July	O
flowers	O
and	O
sweetpeas	O
all	O
a	O
blowse	O
of	O
sweets	O
,	O
not	O
such	O
northerly	O
puling	O
things	O
,	O
fosterd	O
like	O
spoiled	O
children	O
as	O
you	O
Derbyshire	B-place
folk	O
will	O
just	O
have	O
a	O
peep	O
at	O
about	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
with	O
in	O
September	O
--	O
We	O
Mudians	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
confusion	O
of	O
Flowers	O
and	O
Verdure	O
all	O
the	O
year	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
almost	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
judge	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
losing	O
my	O
hair	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
gout	O
&	O
am	O
more	O
wrinkled	O
than	O
the	O
most	O
scientific	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Witch	O
of	O
Endor	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
bold	O
as	O
Kicksy	O
and	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
dread	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
swagger	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
and	O
cry	O
out	O
like	O
him	O
who	O
's	O
afraid	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
PORTSMOUTH	B-place
SHIP-LRE	I-place
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
