TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
,	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1807	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
-	O
Instant	O
has	O
remained	O
unanswered	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
say	O
anything	O
about	O
my	O
Appointment	O
,	O
as	O
His	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
's	O
High	O
Commissioner	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
Lord	B-pers
Hawkesbury	I-pers
Letter	O
Announcing	O
its	O
having	O
taken	O
place	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
must	O
hunt	O
about	O
for	O
my	O
Purse	O
Bearer	O
,	O
my	O
Aſsisting	O
Minister	O
,	O
my	O
two	O
Pages	O
,	O
my	O
four	O
Ushers	O
,	O
my	O
Eight	O
Footmen	O
,	O
my	O
Two	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
Macers	O
,	O
Confectioner	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
desire	O
You	O
may	O
feel	O
the	O
full	O
force	O
of	O
the	O
Obligation	O
You	O
are	O
under	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
sparing	O
this	O
precious	O
moment	O
,	O
which	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
employed	O
in	O
making	O
my	O
Arrangements	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Contracts	O
with	O
Tavern	O
Keepers	O
,	O
&	O
Wine	O
Merchants	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
order	O
Wines	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Gin	O
,	O
Rum	O
,	O
&	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Divines	O
not	O
being	O
much	O
accustomed	O
to	O
drink	O
Claret	O
,	O
on	O
other	O
occasions	O
,	O
feel	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
to	O
qualify	O
that	O
Liquo	O
r	O
by	O
fortifying	O
their	O
Stomachs	O
with	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
have	O
some	O
squabbling	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
aſsembly	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Clerkship	O
Vacant	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
£80	O
,	O
or	O
£90	O
pr	O
Ann	O
.	O
has	O
been	O
considered	O
so	O
consequential	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
late	O
Ministry	O
have	O
left	O
no	O
stone	O
unturned	O
,	O
to	O
procure	O
Members	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
inclined	O
to	O
support	O
their	O
favourite	O
Candidate	O
.	O
The	O
friends	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Ministry	O
have	O
been	O
equally	O
active	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
have	O
secured	O
the	O
point	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
no	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
busineſs	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
ask	O
much	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
appointment	O
of	O
Procurator	O
was	O
Vacant	O
last	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Election	O
was	O
carried	O
against	O
the	O
Candidate	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Ministers	O
,	O
by	O
three	O
to	O
one	O
.	O
From	O
this	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
understand	O
that	O
“	O
All	O
the	O
Talents	O
”	O
had	O
not	O
won	O
the	O
affections	O
of	O
the	O
Scottish	O
Clergy	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Grenville	I-pers
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
sensible	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
honest	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
readily	O
have	O
pinned	O
all	O
my	O
political	O
faith	O
on	O
his	O
Opinion	O
.	O
His	O
conduct	O
,	O
when	O
last	O
out	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
last	O
in	O
Office	O
,	O
almost	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
disgust	O
at	O
Politics	O
altogether	O
,	O
as	O
Sincerity	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
neceſsary	O
Virtue	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Science	O
.	O
His	O
worthy	O
Nephews	O
are	O
chuckle	O
heads	O
.	O
Your	O
young	O
Chief	O
,	O
the	B-pers
Marquis	I-pers
of	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
deserves	O
the	O
Grand	O
Knout	O
&	O
a	O
Trip	O
to	O
Siberia	B-place
,	O
for	O
his	O
folly	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
written	O
wickedness	O
)	O
for	O
exposing	O
the	O
confidential	O
communication	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Merchants	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Ruſsian	O
Government	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
My	O
Purse	O
Bearer	O
is	O
just	O
announced	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
conclude	O
,	O
wishing	O
You	O
and	O
Yours	O
every	O
poſsible	O
benefit	O
from	O
your	O
Jaunt	O
to	O
Cheltenham	B-place
With	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
You	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
ever	O
am	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
Affecte	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
