TOKEN	NE
Wilton	O
Lodge	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
Octr-	O
1794	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Having	O
escaped	O
from	O
my	O
Troops	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Inst-	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
presented	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Son	O
,	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
remarkable	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
expeditious	O
labour	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
hitherto	O
been	O
unusual	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
venture	O
,	O
I	O
direct	O
this	O
to	O
Birch	O
Hall	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
promise	O
given	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
from	O
certain	O
Wanderers	O
on	O
their	O
return	O
there	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
written	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
scolded	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
feel	O
so	O
happy	O
at	O
Maria	B-pers
's	O
situation	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
good	O
humour	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
myself	O
.	O
Our	O
Uncle	O
Sir	B-pers
Thos	I-pers
.	I-pers
Clavering	I-pers
died	O
last	O
week	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
executed	O
a	O
deed	O
bequeathing	O
to	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
,	O
£1500	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
new	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
my	O
Legacy	O
's	O
,	O
left	O
us	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
remembrances	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
affection	O
for	O
Me	O
,	O
never	O
think	O
of	O
putting	O
down	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
your	O
Will	O
.	O
All	O
my	O
good	O
fortune	O
came	O
to	O
Me	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
further	O
to	O
expect	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
many	O
kiſses	O
as	O
You	O
please	O
to	O
my	O
Pet	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
pray	O
dont	O
forget	O
my	O
civilities	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Your	O
faithful	O
friend	O
and	O
Affect	O
.	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
24	O
Octber	O
1794	O
Birth	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
Manchesterxx	B-place
xx	I-place
xx	I-place
By	O
Carlisle	O
