TOKEN	NE
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
renew	O
my	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
continues	O
well	O
--	O
Pray	O
,	O
how	O
soon	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
is	O
all	O
impatience	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
Stranger	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Glover	I-pers
--	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Excursion	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
hope	O
so	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
but	O
indifferent	O
lately	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Music	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
our	O
Liking	O
does	O
not	O
diminish	O
--	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
croſs	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
among	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Father	O
told	O
you	O
what	O
a	O
Giant	O
Robert	B-pers
was	O
grown	O
--	O
he	O
comes	O
home	O
every	O
Sunday	O
,	O
now	O
that	O
the	O
Days	O
are	O
long	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Kensington	B-place
after	O
Dinner	O
--	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
imagine	O
,	O
he	O
perfectly	O
approves	O
of	O
our	O
Situation	O
.	O
You	O
wish	O
for	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
our	O
House	O
--	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
--	O
The	O
Front	O
50	O
Feet	O
,	O
looking	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
Court	O
,	O
parted	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
an	O
Iron	O
Rail	O
.	O
The	O
Hall	O
22-	O
by	O
15-	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fire-Place	O
:	O
shut	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
and	O
best	O
Stair-Case	O
with	O
a	O
Door	O
leading	O
to	O
each	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
you	O
turn	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
,	O
which	O
brings	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Dining-Parlour	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
South	O
;	O
with	O
three	O
Windows	O
--	O
the	O
Chimney	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
--	O
The	O
Dimensions	O
,	O
30-	O
by	O
22-	O
and	O
14	O
Feet	O
high	O
.	O
A	O
Door	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
leads	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
Back-Parlour	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Bow-Window	O
--	O
25-	O
by	O
21-	O
14	O
Feet	O
high	O
.	O
A	O
Door	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
leads	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
Dreſsing-Room	O
--	O
&	O
c.	O
--	O
You	O
go	O
up	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
winding	O
one	O
,	O
nor	O
lighted	O
by	O
a	O
Sky-Light	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
straight	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
lighted	O
by	O
a	O
large	O
Window	O
--	O
this	O
Stair-Case	O
goes	O
no	O
higher	O
than	O
the	O
Drawing-Room	O
Floor	O
.	O
You	O
now	O
come	O
into	O
an	O
Anti-Room	O
,	O
22	O
by	O
15-	O
and	O
16	O
Feet	O
high	O
;	O
with	O
two	O
Windows	O
looking	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
--	O
consequently	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
folding	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
this	O
AntiRoom	O
,	O
lets	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
30	O
by	O
22	O
16	O
feet	O
high	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
folding	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
this	O
Room	O
,	O
lets	O
you	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Drawing-Room	O
,	O
25	O
by	O
21-	O
16	O
Feet	O
high	O
--	O
with	O
a	O
Bow.-Window	O
.	O
You	O
go	O
up	O
a	O
back	O
Stair-Case	O
to	O
the	O
Attics	O
--	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
Rooms	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
backwards	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
of	O
Garrets	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Kitchen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
excellent	O
Offices	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
a	O
capital	O
House-Keepers	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Size	O
as	O
the	O
Back-Parlour	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Servants'-Hall	O
,	O
Butler	O
's	O
Pantry	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cellar	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
Justice	O
to	O
the	O
cheap	O
Claret	O
we	O
are	O
told	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
have	O
.	O
Add	O
to	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
magnificent	O
View	O
that	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
conceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
Kensington	B-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surry	B-place
Hills	I-place
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
my	O
Father	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
judicious	O
in	O
the	O
choice	O
of	O
his	O
Situation	O
--	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
calculated	O
for	O
comfortable	O
habitation	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
most	O
elegant	O
,	O
and	O
Gentleman-like	O
Appearance	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
best	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
(	O
30	O
feet	O
by	O
22-	O
and	O
16	O
feet	O
high	O
,	O
)	O
has	O
three	O
Windows	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chimney	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
tir	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
long	O
account	O
,	O
remember	O
you	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Pray	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
beg	O
likewise	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
time	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
distant	O
when	O
you	O
will	O
introduce	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
to	O
us	O
--	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
remain	O
,	O
with	O
best	O
Wishes	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
Cousin	O
,	O
yours	O
sincerely	O
--	O
J	B-pers
:	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
London	B-place
March	O
20	O
th	O
:	O
1787	O
.	O
