TOKEN	NE
4	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
Charing	B-place
Croſs	I-place
11	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1802	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
your	O
Letter	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
as	O
concerned	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
rejoiced	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Clishmaclaver	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
bothered	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Having	O
generously	O
bestowed	O
a	O
Wafer	O
&	O
some	O
Spittle	O
upon	O
the	O
despatch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
consigned	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Order	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
twopenny	O
Post	O
.	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
War	O
.	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
looks	O
Cool	O
,	O
and	O
Well	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
doing	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
purpose	O
going	O
to	O
sleep	O
immediately	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
trust	O
my	O
Dreams	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
disturbed	O
with	O
the	O
horrid	O
Idea	O
,	O
of	O
hearing	O
the	O
Clack	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
all	O
with	O
You	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
&	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
London	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
March	O
1802	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Post	O
Office	O
Northampton	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
