TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
Monday	O
night	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
May	O
177	O
3	O
You	O
See	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
that	O
its	O
as	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
content	O
without	O
writing	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
its	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
refrain	O
being	O
ſome	O
times	O
ſaucy	O
so	O
allowing	O
both	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
and	O
just	O
I	O
'	O
ll	O
shall	O
begin	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
news	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Dutcheſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gloucester	I-pers
brought	O
to	O
Bed	O
of	O
a	O
daughter	O
,	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Snuff	O
in	O
my	O
poſseſsion	O
,	O
Cloe	O
's	O
Collar	O
ordered	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
sups	O
abroad	O
but	O
her	O
letter	O
is	O
at	O
Mr	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
's	O
(	O
almost	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
leave	O
town	B-place
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
or	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
at	O
furthest	O
tho	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
no	O
body	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
I	O
likeways	O
call	O
'd	O
abt	O
your	O
two	O
odd	O
Vol	O
.	O
of	O
Les	O
vie	O
de	O
Peintres	O
which	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dunoyer	I-pers
has	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
got	O
tho	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
ſeeking	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
town	O
but	O
has	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
abroard	O
for	O
them	O
but	O
gives	O
me	O
but	O
little	O
encouragement	O
to	O
expect	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
but	O
My	O
dearest	O
Ward	O
will	O
find	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
please	O
her	O
&	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Will	O
for	O
the	O
Deed	O
should	O
Madame	B-pers
Danoyer	I-pers
not	O
succeed	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
white	O
Hart	O
St	B-place
Albans	I-place
where	O
ye	O
Landlady	O
enquired	O
greatly	O
after	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Keynes	I-pers
(	O
apropos	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
her	O
)	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
her	O
dear	O
amiable	O
sweet	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
(	O
her	O
very	O
words	O
upon	O
Honor	O
)	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
know	O
me	O
but	O
took	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
Uncle	O
of	O
yours	O
by	O
my	O
likeneſs	O
to	O
the	B-pers
Hamiltons	I-pers
(	O
what	O
a	O
flattering	O
Speech	O
for	O
me	O
)	O
&	O
was	O
so	O
fond	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Kitten	O
was	O
quite	O
wrong	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
fault	O
however	O
we	O
agreed	O
so	O
very	O
well	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
still	O
had	O
not	O
John	B-pers
acquainted	O
me	O
the	O
Chaise	O
was	O
ready	O
at	O
ye	O
door	O
however	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
converſation	O
about	O
you	O
in	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
s	O
praises	O
is	O
an	O
entertainment	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
weary	O
of	O
hearing	O
,	O
tho	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
fatigued	O
with	O
the	O
tongue	O
of	O
a	O
talkative	O
landlady	O
,	O
so	O
mine	O
Good	O
Hostess	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
may	O
prate	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
pleaſes	O
providing	O
her	O
converſation	O
runs	O
of	O
a	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
who	O
does	O
me	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
calling	O
her	O
Guardian	O
how	O
that	O
flatters	O
me	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expreſs	O
'd	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
Man	O
--	O
Woman	O
&	O
Child	O
is	O
fond	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
Ward	O
even	O
the	O
bowels	O
of	O
an	O
overgrown	O
fatt	O
LandLady	O
of	O
St	B-place
Albans	I-place
yearns	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
til	O
she	O
finds	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
well	O
,	O
O	O
what	O
powers	O
goodneſs	O
and	O
Amiableneſs	O
has	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
known	O
where	O
My	O
dear	O
Ward	O
makes	O
her	O
appearance	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
drop	O
the	O
subject	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
may	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
Col	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bland	I-pers
s	O
way	O
of	O
Complimenting	O
which	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
thinks	O
of	O
me	O
I	O
shall	O
bring	O
Mr	B-pers
T	I-pers
in	O
with	O
his	O
abſurd	O
,	O
ridiculous	O
,	O
Nonſenſical	O
Stuff	O
pho	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
wt	O
a	O
stamp	O
of	O
ye	O
Foot	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
honor	O
seriously	O
I	O
never	O
paid	O
you	O
a	O
Compt	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
nor	O
never	O
deſigns	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'	O
ll	O
at	O
least	O
allow	O
me	O
one	O
virtue	O
(	O
sincerity	O
)	O
to	O
counterballence	O
my	O
many	O
fold	O
vices	O
,	O
if	O
its	O
poſsible	O
many	O
can	O
be	O
lodged	O
where	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
you	O
regard	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
friendſhip	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Girl	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
return	O
her	O
my	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
Civilities	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
shew	O
me	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
repay	O
so	O
properly	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
whither	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
this	O
letter	O
a	O
Compt	O
or	O
not	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
conſidering	O
the	O
journey	O
and	O
my	O
running	O
about	O
for	O
four	O
hours	O
constantly	O
on	O
my	O
feet	O
since	O
being	O
in	O
town	B-place
that	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
fatigued	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
neither	O
expect	O
or	O
deſire	O
an	O
Anſwer	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
not	O
expect	O
one	O
because	O
I	O
dont	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
derection	O
,	O
not	O
deſire	O
one	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
wt	O
you	O
before	O
it	O
could	O
come	O
so	O
believe	O
me	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
yours	O
most	O
affctly	O
.	O
N——r	B-pers
