TOKEN	NE
Mr.	B-pers
Farhill	I-pers
&	O
Bishop	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
Exeter	O
22	O
d	O
Janry-	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
finished	O
Julia	O
de	O
Roubigné	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
delighted	O
with	O
it	O
beyond	O
measure	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
volume	O
is	O
I	O
think	O
far	O
preferable	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
this	O
may	O
however	O
arise	O
from	O
my	O
Love	O
of	O
Episode	O
:	O
the	O
Incidents	O
however	O
are	O
more	O
numerous	O
&	O
more	O
interesting	O
--	O
I	O
coud	O
scarcely	O
help	O
giving	O
a	O
Tear	O
to	O
Yambu	O
&	O
the	O
Catastrophe	O
made	O
my	O
heart	O
palpitate	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Tragedy	O
.	O
The	O
end	O
Conclusion	O
is	O
a	O
natural	O
one	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
delightful	O
Novel	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
your	O
Watch	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
coud	O
not	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
leſs	O
than	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
you	O
wanted	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
his	O
Reply	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Impatience	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
prevented	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
having	O
good	O
watches	O
:	O
He	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
exception	O
to	O
the	O
general	O
Rule	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
woud	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
nothing	O
I	O
mean	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
tomorrow	O
morn	O
.	O
Adieu	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
sincerely	O
your	O
's	O
I	O
aſsist	O
the	O
Philosopher	O
in	O
his	O
most	O
abstruse	O
Studies	O
&	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
every	O
place	O
of	O
public	O
amusement	O
and	O
diſsipation	O
.	O
The	O
Charms	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
Fashion	O
are	O
heightened	O
by	O
my	O
presence	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
advantage	O
a	O
nd	O
comfort	O
to	O
the	O
lowest	O
orders	O
.	O
of	O
m	O
ankind	O
.	O
My	O
Existence	O
is	O
in	O
gener	O
a	O
l	O
short	O
duration	O
&	O
my	O
decay	O
profor	O
m	O
l	O
to	O
the	O
Benefit	O
which	O
others	O
received	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
With	O
me	O
the	O
Statesman	O
consults	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
his	O
Country	O
&	O
the	O
Divine	O
for	O
the	O
honor	O
of	O
Religion	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
who	O
am	O
in	O
every	O
Scene	O
of	O
nocturnal	O
Riot	O
and	O
Debauchery	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
this	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
frequently	O
admitted	O
even	O
to	O
your	O
Private	O
Parties	O
&	O
I	O
may	O
without	O
vanity	O
aſsert	O
that	O
whenever	O
I	O
leave	O
them	O
your	O
Smiles	O
immediately	O
disappear	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Queen	O
's	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
