TOKEN	NE
March	O
21	O
st	O
:	O
1806	O
my	O
Eye	O
s	O
being	O
still	O
weak	O
and	O
my	O
occupations	O
so	O
various	O
,	O
on	O
acct	O
.	O
of	O
our	O
late	O
recent	O
sad	O
Loſs	O
of	O
a	O
f	O
our	O
good	O
&	O
excellent	O
Wainwright	B-pers
;	O
&	O
a	O
new	O
Sert	O
..	O
coming	O
;	O
&	O
my	O
dear	O
Husband	O
's	O
spirits	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
being	O
good	O
&	O
strong	O
enough	O
at	O
present	O
for	O
any	O
Exertion	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
can	O
send	O
you	O
only	O
a	O
hasty	O
Scrap	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
2	O
Vols	O
of	O
Books	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
small	O
Parcel	O
for	O
yr	O
Louisa	B-pers
--	O
(	O
the	O
Legaſcies	O
of	O
our	O
beloved	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Coach	O
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
not	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
conversing	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
painful	O
subject	O
you	O
have	O
mentiond	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
I	O
bleſs	O
God	O
tolerably	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
joins	O
me	O
in	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
your	O
dear	O
Daughter	O
--	O
Believe	O
me	O
Your	O
's	O
Sincerely	O
PCremorne	B-pers
