TOKEN	NE
Buxton	B-place
June	O
23	O
d	O
1773	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
time	O
to	O
acquaint	O
my	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
ever	O
ſince	O
e	O
I	O
wrote	O
her	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
propose	O
taking	O
the	O
Air	O
to	O
morrow	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
&	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
the	B-place
Abbey	I-place
on	O
Sunday	O
so	O
dont	O
expect	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
me	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Scotland	B-place
but	O
ye	O
Doctor	O
says	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
danger	O
in	O
my	O
going	O
so	O
conſidering	O
this	O
terrible	O
place	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
stay	O
a	O
moment	O
I	O
can	O
set	O
off	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
gone	O
for	O
London	B-place
I	O
hope	O
its	O
in	O
yr	O
way	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
as	O
you	O
dont	O
say	O
any	O
reason	O
for	O
so	O
sudden	O
jaunt	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
m	O
e	O
yrs	O
most	O
sincerely	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
adieu	O
