TOKEN	NE
38	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1803	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
Letter	O
today	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
learn	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
about	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
I	O
first	O
tried	O
the	O
Atholls	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
bye	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Drummond	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
Son	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
doing	O
well	O
)	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cathcarts	O
,	O
&	O
finding	O
my	O
Lady	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
buried	O
early	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
as	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
directions	O
himself	O
that	O
everything	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
wished	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
attended	O
to	O
.	O
His	O
welch	O
Estate	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
his	O
Heirs	O
Male	O
;	O
then	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
including	O
Lord	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
&	O
Archy	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Entail	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
has	O
debt	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
burdened	O
with	O
a	O
Jointure	O
of	O
£800	O
a	O
Year	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
Legacies	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
delicate	O
to	O
ask	O
.	O
The	O
Newspapers	O
,	O
will	O
probably	O
very	O
soon	O
tell	O
you	O
whether	O
he	O
remains	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Lady	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
A	O
change	O
of	O
Ministry	O
is	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
fixed	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
to	O
resume	O
his	O
old	O
situation	O
;	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
Melville	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
;	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
to	O
succeed	O
Lord	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
.	O
How	O
the	O
latter	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Best	O
Love	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
married	O
the	O
Nail	O
nibbling	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
,	O
has	O
left	O
his	O
name	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Twelfth	O
April	O
1803	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
Napier	B-pers
.	O
