TOKEN	NE
Burlington	O
Street	O
June	O
6	O
th	O
:	O
1794	O
Dear	O
ſir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
trouble	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
concerning	O
the	O
poor	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
's	O
picture	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
received	O
--	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
enclosed	O
a	O
draft	O
on	O
my	O
Banker	O
at	O
three	O
days	O
sight	O
for	O
£4:20	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
oblig	O
ed	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
--	O
From	O
your	O
Account	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
Loyal	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
;	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
every	O
person	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
trust	O
the	O
vigilance	O
of	O
Ministers	O
will	O
effectually	O
frustrate	O
the	O
rascally	O
designs	O
of	O
the	O
Jacobins	O
.	O
--	O
No	O
man	O
more	O
sincerely	O
wishes	O
for	O
a	O
Peace	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
unleſs	O
we	O
can	O
have	O
one	O
on	O
safe	O
terms	O
I	O
am	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
think	O
a	O
continuance	O
of	O
War	O
neceſsary	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
remain	O
Dear	O
ſir	O
your	O
obliged	O
&	O
obedient	O
Sert	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
82	O
92	O
10	O
93	O
9	O
5	O
4	O
95	O
3Ro	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
Portland	O
Place	O
Bath	B-place
Jackson	B-pers
Novbr	O
.	O
6	O
1794	O
