TOKEN	NE
Liverpool	B-place
,	O
15	O
th	O
.	O
March	O
1795	O
.	O
Far	O
be	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
to	O
deny	O
your	O
Witchlike	O
powers	O
.	O
By	O
descent	O
,	O
you	O
certainly	O
may	O
inherit	O
the	O
Gift	O
of	O
second	O
sight	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
Marriage	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
obtained	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
such	O
wonderful	O
qualities	O
as	O
your	O
Husband	O
may	O
poſseſs	O
,	O
in	O
right	O
of	O
the	O
Witches	O
of	O
Lancashire	B-place
.	O
Your	O
very	O
letter	O
to	O
Me	O
proves	O
your	O
dealings	O
with	O
secret	O
Intelligencers	O
,	O
otherwise	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
arrive	O
at	O
Liverpool	B-place
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
?	O
True	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
was	O
my	O
Intention	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
all	O
Wits	O
are	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
mighty	O
short	O
Memories	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
can	O
doubt	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
number	O
?	O
You	O
ought	O
therefore	O
to	O
have	O
forgotten	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
placing	O
my	O
Son	O
at	O
School	O
,	O
the	O
Snow	O
begun	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
quantities	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
January	O
till	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
Roads	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
have	O
been	O
totally	O
impaſsable	O
,	O
T	O
for	O
Carriages	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
Rib	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
close	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Happily	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
so	O
fashionable	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
tired	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
our	O
solitude	O
consequently	O
proved	O
no	O
punishment	O
.	O
The	O
vile	O
tenth	O
of	O
March	O
imperceptibly	O
drew	O
upon	O
Us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
eighth	O
,	O
obliged	O
us	O
to	O
separate	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
remain	O
here	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
on	O
leaving	O
this	O
,	O
is	O
still	O
kept	O
secret	O
from	O
Me	O
.	O
I	O
dread	O
a	O
Camp	O
,	O
for	O
many	O
reasons	O
.	O
I	O
hate	O
sleeping	O
under	O
Canvas	O
,	O
&	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
expence	O
will	O
ruin	O
my	O
Subalterns	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
nothing	O
but	O
their	O
pay	O
to	O
live	O
on	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
my	O
thoughts	O
are	O
principally	O
occupied	O
in	O
calculating	O
when	O
I	O
may	O
probably	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
ingenuity	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
effected	O
earlier	O
than	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
Major	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
wishes	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
for	O
Six	O
Months	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
entitled	O
to	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
constantly	O
at	O
Quarters	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
Should	O
You	O
wander	O
into	O
Scotland	B-place
this	O
Summer	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
will	O
be	O
most	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
regret	O
the	O
impossibility	O
of	O
my	O
making	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
,	O
and	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
lamenting	O
my	O
Absence	O
,	O
in	O
Heroics	O
.	O
You	O
ask	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
opinion	O
about	O
Invasions	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
the	O
French	O
will	O
attempt	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
,	O
though	O
my	O
alarm	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
absurd	O
proceeding	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
great	O
.	O
The	O
pretty	O
Kettle	O
of	O
Fish	O
cooked	O
lately	O
in	O
Ireland	B-place
,	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
matter	O
of	O
more	O
serious	O
concern	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
,	O
of	O
somebody	O
,	O
ought	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
not	O
times	O
for	O
half	O
measures	O
.	O
Either	O
the	O
late	O
chief	O
Governour	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
present	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
have	O
acted	O
nefariously	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sincerely	O
hope	O
,	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
wrong	O
,	O
will	O
meet	O
with	O
severe	O
chastisement	O
.	O
My	O
sentiments	O
,	O
though	O
very	O
favourable	O
to	O
the	O
Roman	O
Catholics	O
,	O
are	O
perfectly	O
hostile	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
called	O
their	O
emancipation	O
,	O
&	O
restoration	O
to	O
the	O
bosom	O
of	O
their	O
Country	O
.	O
They	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
footing	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
their	O
Religion	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
no	O
other	O
.	O
Persecution	O
for	O
modes	O
of	O
Worship	O
,	O
I	O
detest	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
sufficient	O
degree	O
of	O
cordiality	O
does	O
not	O
exist	O
between	O
the	O
Irish	O
Protestants	O
&	O
Catholics	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
muc	O
h	O
the	O
late	O
manœuvres	O
will	O
not	O
lead	O
t	O
o	O
an	O
increase	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
,	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
Self	O
,	O
escaped	O
the	O
influenza	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
it	O
has	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
left	O
Birchhall	O
.	O
Make	O
my	O
best	O
wishes	O
acceptable	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Kiſs	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
too	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
like	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
dont	O
chuse	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
pray	O
bid	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Ever	O
with	O
sincere	O
affection	O
&	O
regard	O
,	O
Your	O
very	O
faithful	O
friend	O
and	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
The	O
Phœnix	O
You	O
want	O
for	O
a	O
Governeſs	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
banks	O
of	O
the	O
Teviot	O
--	O
Mrs=	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Birch	O
Hall	O
LIVERPOOL	B-place
Ld	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
1795	O
