TOKEN	NE
28	O
,	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
Albans	O
Street	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
June	O
1800	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
You	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
perfect	O
peace	O
with	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Mankind	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
score	O
of	O
Letter	O
Writing	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
sorry	O
that	O
your	O
Conscience	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
troublesome	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
You	O
write	O
to	O
Me	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
longer	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
put	O
this	O
aſsertion	O
beyond	O
all	O
doubt	O
.	O
My	O
plan	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
paſsed	O
a	O
Night	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
Arch	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
,	O
if	O
poſsible	O
,	O
o	O
i	O
n	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
determined	O
to	O
inform	O
neither	O
of	O
You	O
of	O
my	O
intention	O
,	O
until	O
l	O
the	O
fulfilling	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
certain	O
.	O
That	O
depends	O
on	O
the	O
Motions	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Minister	O
told	O
me	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prorogation	O
would	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
Inst	O
.	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
the	O
busineſs	O
now	O
remaining	O
to	O
be	O
concluded	O
convinces	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
dismiſsed	O
before	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
right	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
utterly	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
Me	O
to	O
halt	O
one	O
moment	O
on	O
my	O
Northern	O
Journey	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
s	O
holidays	O
begin	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
He	O
waits	O
for	O
my	O
taking	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
moment	O
to	O
carry	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
announced	O
to	O
Me	O
,	O
his	O
desire	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
I	O
wondered	O
at	O
his	O
choice	O
,	O
but	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
arranged	O
with	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
John	I-pers
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
next	O
Spring	O
.	O
Ten	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
Mr-	B-pers
Dundas	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
Voluntary	O
offer	O
of	O
sending	O
my	O
Son	O
to	O
India	B-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
view	O
of	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
repairing	O
the	O
worn	O
out	O
Fortune	O
of	O
our	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
full	O
force	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
goodneſs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
acceptance	O
,	O
must	O
depend	O
on	O
my	O
Son	O
himself	O
.	O
To	O
counsel	O
and	O
advise	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
be	O
ready	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
thwart	O
natural	O
genius	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
force	O
my	O
Children	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
a	O
line	O
of	O
Profeſsion	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
feel	O
inclined	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
bring	O
myself	O
.	O
Dundas	B-pers
has	O
behaved	O
like	O
a	O
true	O
friend	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
“	O
if	O
your	O
eldest	O
“	O
Son	O
wo	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
India	B-place
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
“	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
younger	O
Sons	O
who	O
may	O
“	O
like	O
it	O
better	O
--	O
”	O
This	O
is	O
very	O
flattering	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
my	O
second	O
Son	O
is	O
only	O
Seven	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
to	O
William	B-pers
mentioning	O
the	O
Offer	O
;	O
desiring	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
positively	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
Navy	O
for	O
his	O
profeſsion	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
going	O
to	O
India	B-place
,	O
he	O
may	O
sooner	O
become	O
an	O
Independant	O
Man	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
trusting	O
to	O
the	O
chance	O
of	O
Prize	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
preſsed	O
him	O
to	O
decide	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
begged	O
to	O
know	O
his	O
present	O
Sentiments	O
,	O
without	O
disguise	O
.	O
My	O
wish	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
friend	O
of	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
not	O
their	O
dread	O
.	O
William	B-pers
's	O
answer	O
may	O
poſsibly	O
arrive	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
My	O
anxiety	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
You	O
to	O
gueſs	O
at	O
.	O
My	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
Spring	O
,	O
was	O
entirely	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Important	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
Union	O
with	O
the	O
Ireland	B-place
.	O
The	O
doing	O
so	O
was	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
convenient	O
,	O
my	O
Income	O
being	O
leſsened	O
upwards	O
of	O
£300	O
pr-	O
An	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Regiment	O
I	O
served	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
Lt	O
Colonel	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
did	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
vented	O
my	O
Spite	O
on	O
You	O
Ladies	O
,	O
by	O
voting	O
for	O
(	O
what	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
)	O
the	O
Adultery	O
Bill	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
your	O
sentiments	O
on	O
that	O
subject	O
.	O
In	O
opposition	O
to	O
mine	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
love	O
and	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pet	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
forget	O
my	O
Civilities	O
to	O
my	O
Countrywoman	O
.	O
Adieu	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Ever	O
Your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
How	O
You	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
gueſs	O
.	O
London	B-place
,	O
Tenth	O
June	O
1800	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Napier	B-pers
