TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dear	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
must	O
say	O
I	O
love	O
my	O
good	O
Child	O
;	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
remember	O
you	O
are	O
engag	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
xmas	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
feal	O
a	O
little	O
offended	O
in	O
not	O
seeing	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
--	O
your	O
good	O
Father	O
will	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
as	O
well	O
this	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
he	O
looks	O
well	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
bowel	O
complaint	O
,	O
which	O
lasted	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
now	O
better	O
but	O
very	O
low	O
;	O
our	O
friend	O
Ann	B-pers
wants	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
Frank	O
.	O
--	O
Adieu	O
--	O
E	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
Albemarle	O
Street	O
Decr	O
:	O
15	O
th	O
:	O
1783	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
sends	O
her	O
Compts	O
:	O
Garte	O
Glover	B-pers
Bulstrode	O
Park	O
Bucks	B-place
