TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
In	O
my	O
extreme	O
distreſs	O
on	O
the	O
afflicting	O
information	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
received	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
communicate	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
instructions	O
that	O
are	O
requisite	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
my	O
mind	O
is	O
so	O
totally	O
distracted	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
enter	O
upon	O
one	O
subject	O
only	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
deferr	O
'd	O
&	O
that	O
is	O
respecting	O
my	O
dear	O
daughter	O
's	O
funeral	O
.	O
I	O
approve	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
's	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
with	O
caution	O
not	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
unneceſsary	O
expence	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Paddington	I-place
where	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
employd	O
him	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
acquitted	O
himself	O
with	O
great	O
propriety	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
preserve	O
a	O
continuance	O
of	O
my	O
regard	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
my	O
conduct	O
towards	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
as	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
further	O
intercourse	O
between	O
us	O
I	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
desire	O
to	O
act	O
with	O
rancour	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
add	O
no	O
more	O
at	O
present	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
line	O
of	O
grateful	O
acknowledgements	O
to	O
the	O
worthy	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
all	O
other	O
objects	O
tho	O
'	O
deferr	O
'd	O
,	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
neglected	O
.	O
Ever	O
yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Bath	B-place
June	O
12	O
th	O
.	O
1810	O
.	O
Pray	O
supply	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
without	O
reserve	O
with	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
may	O
want	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.49	O
Welbeck	O
Street	O
London	B-place
Mr	B-pers
F	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
