TOKEN	NE
Windsor	O
Castle	O
Monday	O
Decbr	O
31	O
1811	O
Having	O
got	O
a	O
Franke	O
from	O
my	O
Youngest	O
Son	O
I	O
return	O
with	O
many	O
,	O
many	O
thanks	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dearst	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
the	O
valuable	O
Portrait	O
,	O
admired	O
it	O
much	O
as	O
did	O
Dear	B-pers
Pſs	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
H	O
R	O
H	O
has	O
now	O
got	O
safe	O
in	O
her	O
tower	O
the	O
Extracts	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
much	O
pleased	O
with	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
from	O
illneſs	O
&	O
the	O
constant	O
interuption	O
that	O
occaſsions	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
read	O
many	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
tho	O
'	O
much	O
recovered	O
from	O
Her	O
Fever	O
,	O
Miss	O
now	O
suffers	O
from	O
a	O
very	O
Stiff	O
Neck	O
,	O
&	O
can	O
scarcely	O
move	O
Her	O
Head	O
--	O
You	O
will	O
receive	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
a	O
New	O
Year	O
,	O
&	O
most	O
sincerly	O
do	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
your	O
Truly	O
amiable	O
daughter	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
Happineſs	O
during	O
that	O
&	O
many	O
succeeding	O
years	O
as	O
this	O
uncertain	O
World	O
can	O
give	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gomm	I-pers
will	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
--	O
as	O
to	O
myself	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
may	O
meet	O
&	O
that	O
my	O
Flirtation	O
with	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
will	O
be	O
renewed	O
--	O
God	O
Bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
Yr	O
Affly	O
MCGoldsworthy	B-pers
