TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dearest	O
Love	O
--	O
!	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Louvre	B-place
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
your	O
note	O
--	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
disappointed	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
to	O
day	O
&	O
yet	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
probability	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
night	O
in	O
waiting	O
below	O
--	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
3	O
handed	O
cribbage	O
--	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
undreſsing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
--	O
Rheathe	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
was	O
more	O
than	O
usually	O
Kind	O
&	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
conversation	O
--	O
quite	O
friendly	O
--	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
every	O
thing	O
yt	O
.	O
gives	O
Miranda	B-pers
satisfaction	O
affords	O
pleasure	O
to	O
her	O
Astrea	B-pers
--	O
The	O
Country	O
you	O
describe	O
is	O
charming	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
sensations	O
--	O
&	O
admired	O
it	O
equally	O
wth	O
.	O
you	O
--	O
Tomorrow	O
I	O
write	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
time	O
O	O
how	O
I	O
anticipate	O
Monday	O
--	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
day	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
--	O
No	O
news	O
from	O
——	B-pers
to	O
day	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
tomorrow	O
Morng	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
conclude	O
she	O
h	O
as	O
taken	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
word	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
S——	I-pers
continues	O
to	O
torment	O
me	O
--	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
,	O
yesterday	O
whi	O
ch	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
December	O
Honble	B-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Melsom	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
Free	O
James	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
