TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
heard	O
from	O
my	O
Mother	O
She	O
Says	O
she	O
mends	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
her	O
Cough	O
Appetite	O
&	O
Sleep	O
--	O
But	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
rather	O
deafer	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
London	B-place
--	O
she	O
means	O
however	O
to	O
have	O
patience	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
N	I-pers
:	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
wishes	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
only	O
&	O
try	O
ye	O
Country	O
Air	O
l	O
onger	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
a	O
fair	O
Chance	O
.	O
The	O
Above	O
my	O
dr	O
Miſs	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
what	O
I	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
--	O
that	O
You	O
may	O
hear	O
how	O
she	O
is	O
&	O
likewise	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
repeat	O
it	O
at	O
ye	O
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
--	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
what	O
however	O
does	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
further	O
Comfort	O
but	O
wd-	O
do	O
no	O
t	O
good	O
to	O
repeat	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
seem	O
more	O
than	O
it	O
really	O
is	O
--	O
that	O
by	O
ye	O
general	O
Tenor	O
of	O
her	O
Letter	O
&	O
manners	O
of	O
writing	O
--	O
I	O
shd-	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
rather	O
better	O
Spirits	O
--	O
Which	O
makes	O
me	O
think	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
vastly	O
better	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
ye	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
Expreſsly	O
that	O
her	O
Ears	O
&	O
head	O
are	O
really	O
worse	O
--	O
&	O
more	O
inconvenient	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
--	O
&	O
unfit	O
her	O
now	O
for	O
Society	O
--	O
As	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
wd-	O
be	O
anxious	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
her	O
Attendance	O
I	O
shd	O
be	O
wretch	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
Harleyford	B-place
cd	O
.	O
imply	O
her	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
sooner	O
than	O
she	O
can	O
--	O
Adieu	O
I	O
have	O
writ	O
nonsense	O
but	O
ever	O
always	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
)	O
yrs	O
affy	O
H	B-pers
F	I-pers
H.	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
