TOKEN	NE
My	O
Dearest	O
Love	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
keep	O
my	O
promise	O
&	O
write	O
to	O
day	O
tho	O
it	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
some	O
ounces	O
--	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
warm	O
--	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
London	B-place
is	O
&	O
how	O
difficult	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
command	O
time	O
--	O
Monday	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
filled	O
my	O
scanty	O
paper	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
I	O
wished	O
the	O
dinner	O
&	O
paper	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
devil	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
humour	O
to	O
write	O
&	O
sometimes	O
If	O
I	O
dont	O
write	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
things	O
they	O
escape	O
my	O
memory	O
--	O
After	O
dinner	O
at	O
6	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
AMaria	B-pers
left	O
us	O
in	O
Oxford	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
&	O
returned	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
palace	O
thrō	O
the	O
Courts	O
&	O
up	O
the	O
park	O
to	O
the	O
Queens	O
house	O
then	O
thrō	O
the	O
Horse	O
Gards	O
into	O
Whitehal	O
we	O
called	O
&	O
drank	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
who	O
walked	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
palace	O
--	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Cr	O
.	O
was	O
sleepy	O
&	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Emma	B-pers
&	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
her	O
&	O
her	O
Mother	O
--	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
“	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
down	O
such	O
a	O
plan	O
for	O
her	O
conduct	O
on	O
her	O
return	O
to	O
Naples	B-place
as	O
She	O
was	O
was	O
satisfied	O
wd	O
.	O
ensure	O
to	O
her	O
universal	O
respect	O
&	O
the	O
approbation	O
of	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
--	O
She	O
knows	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
happy	O
--	O
that	O
gratitude	O
,	O
duty	O
,	O
inclination	O
&	O
every	O
consideration	O
would	O
compel	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
please	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
she	O
shd	O
.	O
do	O
it	O
--	O
”	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Eyes	O
of	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
their	O
determination	O
as	O
I	O
ardently	O
wished	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
might	O
be	O
perfectly	O
happy	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
cd	O
.	O
see	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
easy	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
in	O
him	O
that	O
warmth	O
of	O
attachment	O
which	O
he	O
entertained	O
for	O
her	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
always	O
find	O
Emma	B-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
same	O
--	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
She	O
enquired	O
how	O
we	O
had	O
gone	O
on	O
about	O
the	O
ECr.-	B-pers
Settlemt	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
She	O
(	O
&	O
every	O
body	O
)	O
expreſs	O
the	O
greatest	O
astonishment	O
at	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
conduct	O
in	O
choosing	O
ye-	O
Cr	O
.	O
Emma	B-pers
's	O
Mother	O
(	O
who	O
seems	O
a	O
shrewd	O
sensible	O
woman	O
)	O
said	O
“	O
Lord	O
Sir	O
--	O
yesterday	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
devoured	O
him	O
--	O
she	O
surely	O
doats	O
upon	O
him	O
”	O
--	O
Eliz	B-pers
:	I-pers
is	O
thought	O
by	O
most	O
people	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
pretty	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
speakg	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
Emma	B-pers
&	O
said	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
admired	O
him	O
&	O
added	O
that	O
I	O
loved	O
him	O
--	O
She	O
aſsured	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Love	O
lost	O
--	O
for	O
that	O
He	O
liked	O
me	O
as	O
well	O
--	O
she	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
afft	O
:	O
Letter	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
Windsor	B-place
--	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
joked	O
him	O
about	O
Em	B-pers
..	I-pers
at	O
a	O
distance	O
&	O
gave	O
a	O
hint	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
religious	O
as	O
when	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
late	O
Ly	B-pers
H——	I-pers
He	O
has	O
got	O
leave	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
Windsor	O
Uniform	O
the	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
Nobody	O
had	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
--	O
(	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
thought	O
he	O
shd	O
.	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
another	O
Uniform	O
)	O
--	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
La	O
Signora	O
had	O
followed	O
her	O
husband	O
&	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
oysters	O
which	O
I	O
eat	O
&	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
written	O
a	O
long	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
Love	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
locked	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
&	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
undreſsed	O
I	O
heard	O
Sr.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
say	O
what	O
is	O
he	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
so	O
soon	O
--	O
I	O
threw	O
on	O
my	O
Clothes	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
&	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
laugh	O
at	O
the	O
Dear	O
Creature	O
's	O
expence	O
--	O
Sir	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
this	O
morng	O
)	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
shd	O
be	O
home	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
engagements	O
--	O
he	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
--	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thing	O
better	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Dft	O
.	O
on	O
Hammersley	B-pers
for	O
the	O
1000	O
£	O
as	O
Sr.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
made	O
a	O
demur	O
about	O
the	O
Bond	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
Tuesday	O
30	O
th	O
--	O
at	O
9	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
staid	O
there	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
yr-	O
L	O
.	O
relating	O
to	O
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
told	O
his	O
M	O
.	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
loved	O
her	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
his	O
favor	O
--	O
fixed	O
wh-	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
at	O
12	O
&	O
went	O
away	O
--	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
reason	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Emma	B-pers
last	O
night	O
was	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
introduce	O
AMaria	B-pers
to	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
hear	O
her	O
sing	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
appointed	O
AM	B-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
come	O
at	O
10	O
--	O
the	O
hour	O
Emma	B-pers
had	O
fixed	O
for	O
her	O
Masters	O
to	O
attend	O
--	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
AM	B-pers
--	O
we	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Emma	B-pers
who	O
recd	O
.	O
AM	B-pers
.	I-pers
very	O
kindly	O
--	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
contain	O
her	O
astonishment	O
at	O
the	O
simplicity	O
of	O
Em	B-pers
.	I-pers
dreſs	O
--	O
Emma	B-pers
sang	O
enchantingly	O
--	O
and	O
Nanny	B-pers
was	O
quite	O
overcome	O
&	O
diſsolved	O
in	O
tears	O
at	O
the	O
duet	O
of	O
Nina	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
affected	O
too	O
--	O
Emma	B-pers
thanked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
compts	O
.	O
that	O
was	O
paid	O
her	O
--	O
then	O
she	O
sang	O
some	O
lively	O
ones	O
in	O
a	O
masterly	O
stile	O
--	O
her	O
Master	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
voice	O
--	O
but	O
great	O
taste	O
indeed	O
--	O
at	O
12	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
Dft	O
.	O
Emma	B-pers
told	O
Nanny	B-pers
that	O
one	O
day	O
this	O
week	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
sing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
&	O
shew	O
the	O
Attitudes	O
&	O
desired	O
her	O
company	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
at	O
3	O
--	O
&	O
then	O
we	O
attend	O
her	O
to	O
Romney	B-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
's	O
&	O
got	O
the	O
Dft	O
.	O
--	O
he	O
began	O
a	O
conversation	O
about	O
R——	B-pers
his	O
aversion	O
to	O
him	O
is	O
founded	O
principally	O
on	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
want	O
of	O
Veracity	O
--	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
motion	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
preſsed	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
sometg	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
stay	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
wch	O
.	O
obliged	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
had	O
written	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
might	O
go	O
to	O
Litchfield	B-place
Races	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
very	O
improper	O
&	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
he	O
desired	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
would	O
write	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
to	O
put	O
of	O
his	O
Visit	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Races	O
--	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
your	O
attachment	O
to	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
after	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
hammering	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
faint	O
proposal	O
,	O
expressing	O
a	O
wish	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
comes	O
of	O
Age	O
&	O
that	O
we	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
liberally	O
rewarded	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
ansr-	O
&	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Conversation	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
town	B-place
--	O
I	O
shd	O
.	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
&	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
lead	O
you	O
into	O
any	O
Scrape	O
for	O
any	O
Consideration	O
whatever	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
invitation	O
to	O
Dinner	O
at	O
4	O
OClock	O
&	O
fm	O
.	O
Sr.	B-pers
Rt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
at	O
5	O
--	O
Give	O
my	O
best	O
Love	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
&	O
tell	O
her	O
how	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
she	O
means	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
only	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Wife	O
In	O
great	O
haste	O
--	O
but	O
ever	O
tenderly	O
&	O
Affy	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
J.D	B-pers
--	O
AMaria	B-pers
is	O
gone	O
with	O
Eliz	B-pers
to	O
a	O
dentist	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
teeth	O
cleaned	O
I	O
have	O
ten	O
thousand	O
things	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
moment	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
adieu	O
adieu	O
Kiſs	O
the	O
dear	O
pledge	O
of	O
our	O
Love	O
&	O
remember	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
every	O
Body	O
Single	O
Sheet	O
X	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
frith	I-place
Derbye-	B-place
