TOKEN	NE
Edinburgh	B-place
June	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
I	O
am	O
this	O
moment	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
in	O
two	O
day	O
from	O
Buxton	B-place
&	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
feel	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
tired	O
,	O
otherwise	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
ſome	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
three	O
youngest	O
Girls	O
well	O
&	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
are	O
wt	O
Ld	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
where	O
I	O
propose	O
going	O
to	O
morrow	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
happy	O
with	O
yours	O
from	O
London	B-place
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
C	O
hai	O
se	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
&	O
for	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
motto	O
as	O
you	O
ordered	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
certainty	O
like	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
dear	O
Ward	O
in	O
my	O
memory	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
ſurprised	O
you	O
are	O
returned	O
to	O
North	B-place
:	I-place
as	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
on	O
yr	O
way	O
to	O
margate	B-place
&	O
your	O
not	O
saying	O
any	O
particular	O
buſineſs	O
carried	O
you	O
up	O
I	O
t	O
ook	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
your	O
sea	O
bathing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
have	O
all	O
these	O
particulars	O
clear	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
your	O
next	O
.	O
your	O
presentiment	O
never	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Girl	O
surer	O
than	O
of	O
my	O
ilneſs	O
,	O
the	O
G	O
ye	O
Gout	O
took	O
poſseſsion	O
off	O
my	O
Lungs	O
,	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Bowells	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
ſuch	O
a	O
lodgement	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
been	O
worsted	O
however	O
thank	O
God	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
&	O
my	O
Legs	O
being	O
blistered	O
immediately	O
removed	O
my	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
other	O
quarters	O
not	O
so	O
eaſily	O
ascertained	O
however	O
my	O
Legs	O
are	O
so	O
sore	O
yet	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
move	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
ſoon	O
off	O
--	O
Remember	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
manner	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
ſincerely	O
My	O
Dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
's	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
,	O
ye	O
Post	O
just	O
going	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
travelled	O
all	O
night	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
aſsured	O
no	O
other	O
Lady	O
but	O
yrself	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
night	O
My	O
Compts	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
&	O
c	O
Adieu	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
