TOKEN	NE
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
Deal	B-place
Kent	B-place
May	O
26	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
am	O
induced	O
to	O
trouble	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
the	O
solicitude	O
I	O
feel	O
respecting	O
your	O
health	O
&	O
that	O
of	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
&	O
all	O
your	O
Family	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
indeed	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
immediately	O
from	O
our	O
dear	O
Louisa	B-pers
this	O
would	O
occasion	O
me	O
much	O
chagrin	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
know	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
declaration	O
that	O
writing	O
letters	O
is	O
irksome	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
were	O
I	O
not	O
also	O
convinced	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
some	O
attachment	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
uncomfortable	O
silence	O
at	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
offended	O
for	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
has	O
aſsigned	O
&	O
which	O
circumstance	O
occasioned	O
me	O
much	O
uneasineſs	O
on	O
a	O
from	O
a	O
similar	O
cause	O
respecting	O
my	O
late	O
&	O
lost	O
most	O
dear	O
Friend	O
tell	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
that	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
&	O
herself	O
were	O
well	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Luxmoore	I-pers
who	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
I	O
believe	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cockerel	I-pers
's	O
aſsembly	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
one	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
obtaining	O
from	O
you	O
when	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
was	O
recovering	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
lazy	O
&	O
should	O
answer	O
this	O
pray	O
mention	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
uncomfortable	O
circumstance	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
letter	O
lost	O
though	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
secretes	O
or	O
intelligence	O
of	O
great	O
importance	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
case	O
respecting	O
that	O
Epistle	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
&	O
yours	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
the	O
fine	O
&	O
promising	O
spring	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
favoured	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
generally	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
much	O
occupied	O
by	O
Music	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
so	O
much	O
exercice	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
delightful	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
very	O
quiet	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
kind	O
invitation	O
to	O
paſs	O
the	O
spring	O
with	O
my	O
old	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
but	O
I	O
feared	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
too	O
great	O
an	O
exertion	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
malgre	O
my	O
inclination	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
sacrifice	O
I	O
regretted	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
enabled	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
Family	O
&	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
friends	O
I	O
am	O
sincerely	O
attached	O
to	O
&	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
ease	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
S	I-pers
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
pleased	O
in	O
knowing	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
times	O
happy	O
in	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
my	O
other	O
friends	O
I	O
have	O
hopes	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
Autumn	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to-morrow	O
to	O
remove	O
to	O
other	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Deal	B-place
to	O
be	O
nearer	O
the	O
Sea	O
from	O
which	O
health	O
derives	O
benefit	O
&	O
the	O
Landlady	O
who	O
is	O
particularly	O
obliging	O
&	O
goodhumoured	O
has	O
promised	O
to	O
show	O
every	O
attention	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
,	O
should	O
I	O
leave	O
her	O
you	O
perhaps	O
should	O
this	O
take	O
place	O
will	O
have	O
left	O
Devonshire	O
Place	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
pursue	O
your	O
musical	O
studies	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
delightful	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
Baſs	O
an	O
Instrument	O
I	O
much	O
admire	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
hear	O
some	O
of	O
Geminiani	B-pers
's	O
Solos	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
accompanied	O
by	O
a	O
Thorough	O
Baſs	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sweetneſs	O
in	O
the	O
modulation	O
which	O
surpaſses	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
on	O
instruments	O
excepting	O
Handel	B-pers
's	O
airs	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
Niece	O
Mary	B-pers
has	O
left	O
Colchester	B-place
she	O
has	O
lost	O
her	O
sister	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boggis	I-pers
who	O
lately	O
died	O
&	O
left	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
8	O
months	O
old	O
very	O
sickly	O
&	O
of	O
which	O
my	O
Niece	O
has	O
undertaken	O
the	O
care	O
hoping	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
divine	O
bleſsing	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
enabled	O
to	O
raise	O
this	O
poor	O
Child	O
Colonel	B-pers
Boggis	I-pers
the	O
Father	O
has	O
also	O
also	O
left	O
Colchester	B-place
on	O
this	O
melancholy	O
Event	O
my	O
Niece	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
pretty	O
House	O
Garden	O
&	O
Field	O
within	O
a	O
mile	O
of	O
Stamford	B-place
Lincolnshire	I-place
where	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
arriv	O
ed	O
she	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
this	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
's	O
solicitude	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
two	O
Daughters	O
near	O
him	O
the	O
eldest	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Town	B-place
on	O
a	O
visit	O
&	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
is	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
beautiful	O
she	O
is	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Girl	O
with	O
an	O
admirable	O
profile	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
late	O
dear	O
Mother	O
was	O
superior	O
considering	O
the	O
figure	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
S	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Palombi	I-pers
were	O
well	O
&	O
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
&	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
living	O
&	O
do	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
desires	O
her	O
Comp	O
.	O
--	O
give	O
my	O
Love	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
&	O
best	O
Comps	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
x	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
room	O
I	O
must	O
here	O
conclude	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
&	O
Brother	O
your	O
affectionate	O
&	O
obliged	O
Friend	O
A	B-pers
M	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
x	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
:	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
Cavendish	O
Square	O
London	B-place
