TOKEN	NE
As	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
Wish	O
to	O
see	O
Caroline	B-pers
I	O
send	O
the	O
Carriage	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
Hope	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Here	O
;	O
am	O
Sorry	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
Dine	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
It	O
Is	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
bring	O
Louisa	B-pers
&	O
your	O
Maid	O
;	O
&	O
they	O
can	O
Dine	O
w	O
.	O
Caroline	B-pers
,	O
&	O
you	O
May	O
Stay	O
till	O
/3/	O
o'clock	O
;	O
or	O
later	O
;	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
;	O
than	O
Making	O
the	O
Servants	O
&	O
Horses	O
wait	O
so	O
long	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
;	O
--	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
ask	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
Sr.	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
May	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
can	O
Answer	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
We	O
Shall	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
His	O
Way	O
--	O
dont	O
think	O
of	O
your	O
Dreſs	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
See	O
any	O
Company	O
,	O
ever	O
Yours	O
Most	O
Affecly	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
August	O
26	O
th	O
..	O
1788	O
frm	B-place
.	I-place
Putney	I-place
Park	I-place
