TOKEN	NE
on	O
Monday	O
Bell	B-pers
&	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
to	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
&	O
George	B-pers
will	O
remain	O
here	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
12	O
th	O
&	O
then	O
meet	O
us	O
in	O
London	B-place
the	O
House	O
will	O
scarcely	O
be	O
finished	O
before	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
plaistering	O
&	O
painting	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
begun	O
upon	O
till	O
next	O
Monday	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
here	O
now	O
you	O
would	O
think	O
us	O
very	O
comfortable	O
A	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
at	O
last	O
hit	O
upon	O
the	O
only	O
plan	O
that	O
can	O
make	O
us	O
so	O
in	O
cold	O
weather	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
Drawingroom	O
entirely	O
,	O
&	O
are	O
settled	O
in	O
the	O
Saloon	O
with	O
two	O
fires	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
screen	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
room	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
&	O
sit	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
--	O
we	O
are	O
now	O
totally	O
separated	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
writing	O
here	O
very	O
comfortably	O
&	O
uninterrupted	O
by	O
the	O
conversation	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
left	O
to	O
their	O
wine	O
&	O
their	O
conversation	O
at	O
the	O
opposite	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
--	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
be	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
more	O
in	O
detail	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
journey	O
,	O
Louisa	B-pers
,	O
your	O
own	O
health	O
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
&	O
of	O
the	O
State	O
of	O
things	O
at	O
Taxal	B-place
,	O
not	O
omitting	O
what	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
probabilities	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
Breast	O
&	O
am	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
Bark	O
wth	O
5	O
Gr	O
.	O
of	O
long	O
Pepper	O
every	O
day	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
to	O
come	O
without	O
ever	O
omitting	O
it	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
we	O
all	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
remembered	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
--	O
&	O
Bell	B-pers
begs	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
pray	O
direct	O
your	O
next	O
to	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
--	O
adieu	O
ever	O
y	O
affecly	O
&	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
C.M	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
24	O
th	O
:	O
1788	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
