TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
It	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
great	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
Miſs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
accept	O
my	O
best	O
congratulations	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Willm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
is	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
personally	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
hear	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
favorable	O
from	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
&	O
trust	O
that	O
the	O
comfort	O
of	O
seeing	O
your	O
Daughter	O
so	O
satisfactorily	O
settled	O
will	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
loſs	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
favorite	O
of	O
mine	O
&	O
I	O
feel	O
truly	O
interested	O
in	O
her	O
Welfare	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
best	O
Complimens	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
Sr.	B-pers
Willm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
and	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
in	O
person	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
mentioned	O
sometime	O
ago	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
unwell	O
&	O
this	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
weather	O
for	O
Invalids	O
I	O
hope	O
however	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
favorable	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Health	O
.	O
my	O
Daughters	O
join	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
begging	O
you	O
to	O
accept	O
their	O
best	O
wishes	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
very	O
sincerely	O
yours	O
H	B-pers
:	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
--	O
Jany	O
.	O
.	O
30	O
th	O
.	O
1815	O
.	O
Milbrook	O
Place	O
Southampton	B-place
--	O
