TOKEN	NE
Farmborough	O
Place	O
September	O
24	O
th	O
-	O
My	O
dear	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
hasten	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
delighted	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
your	O
dear	O
lette	O
r	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
2	O
1	O
st	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
--	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
since	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
immediatly	O
answered	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
constant	O
expectation	O
of	O
heari	O
n	O
g	O
from	O
you	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
I	O
last	O
wrote	O
but	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
either	O
your	O
situation	O
or	O
your	O
avocations	O
preven	O
ted	O
you	O
writi	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
too	O
much	O
confidence	O
in	O
the	O
affection	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
either	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
vanity	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
suppose	O
any	O
reason	O
for	O
their	O
silence	O
rather	O
than	O
alteration	O
,	O
of	O
in	O
their	O
sentiments	O
towards	O
me	O
aſsured	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
continuation	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sati	O
s	O
fied	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
write	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
more	O
frequently	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
the	O
happier	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
one	O
,	O
whose	O
esteem	O
,	O
tenderneſs	O
&	O
sincer	O
e	O
attachment	O
will	O
last	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
you	O
remain	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
long	O
the	O
happineſs	O
of	O
knowing	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
written	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
desired	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
folio	O
sheet	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
allotted	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
I	O
believe	O
as	O
much	O
here	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
on	O
your	O
long	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
get	O
to	O
Horton	B-place
which	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
account	O
for	O
myself	O
since	O
I	O
last	O
wrote	O
&	O
having	O
brought	O
my	O
journal	O
down	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
will	O
continue	O
it	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
Health	O
&	O
occupations	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
--	O
I	O
left	O
Horton	B-place
as	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
mentioned	O
my	O
intention	O
of	O
doing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
tormented	O
with	O
the	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
jaw	O
&	O
toothache	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Races	O
--	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
Plate	O
at	O
the	O
Hospital	O
Church	O
,	O
caught	O
cold	O
by	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
--	O
increased	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Stand	O
on	O
the	O
course	O
,	O
&	O
again	O
after	O
the	O
Ball	O
,	O
by	O
hurryi	O
n	O
g	O
away	O
in	O
compaſsion	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
cool	O
--	O
I	O
slept	O
at	O
Delapré	B-place
&	O
returned	O
home	O
next	O
Day	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Drawingrooms	O
of	O
course	O
&	O
in	O
the	O
Eveni	O
n	O
g	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Putney	O
Lane	O
which	O
I	O
daresay	O
you	O
know	O
from	O
its	O
vicinity	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
's	O
--	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Poeſs	I-pers
&	O
now	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
--	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
pretty	O
--	O
chearful	O
,	O
small	O
,	O
comfortable	O
and	O
retired	O
--	O
here	O
I	O
remained	O
till	O
last	O
Thursday	O
--	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
suffer	O
with	O
my	O
toothache	O
--	O
Ld	B-pers
Car	I-pers
:	I-pers
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
Spence	B-pers
I	O
did	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
draw	O
my	O
tooth	O
--	O
I	O
now	O
expected	O
ease	O
--	O
but	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
mortification	O
,	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
fit	O
of	O
pain	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
left	O
London	B-place
,	O
that	O
the	O
wrong	O
tooth	O
was	O
drawn	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
suffer	O
two	O
Days	O
longer	O
because	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
was	O
Sunday	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
Monday	O
had	O
the	O
right	O
tooth	O
taken	O
out	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
pain	O
flyi	O
n	O
g	O
about	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
&	O
am	O
far	O
from	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
well	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
complaint	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
feverish	O
&	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
Ghost	O
--	O
I	O
take	O
James	O
's	O
Powders	O
at	O
night	O
&	O
Saline	O
Draughts	O
all	O
day	O
--	O
Robert	B-pers
James	I-pers
who	O
when	O
he	O
chooses	O
(	O
which	O
indeed	O
he	O
often	O
does	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
was	O
remarquably	O
so	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
remaind	O
with	O
us	O
--	O
he	O
carried	O
Lord	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
to	O
Eton	B-place
some	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Putney	B-place
&	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
Castle	B-place
Howard	I-place
--	O
Lord	B-pers
Morpeth	I-pers
&	O
Ly	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
went	O
to	O
Trentham	B-place
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
weeks	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
promised	O
Ly	B-pers
Caroline	I-pers
a	O
visit	O
there	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
yet	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
never	O
before	O
now	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
v	O
astly	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
friendly	O
kind	O
people	O
that	O
ever	O
existed	O
,	O
&	O
have	O
always	O
shew	O
me	O
so	O
muc	O
h	O
friendship	O
,	O
&	O
done	O
me	O
so	O
many	O
offices	O
of	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
particularly	O
during	O
my	O
illneſs	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
most	O
ungrateful	O
indeed	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
take	O
every	O
opportunity	O
of	O
shewing	O
my	O
sense	O
of	O
their	O
goodneſs	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
Saturday	O
&	O
I	O
shall	O
stay	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
intend	O
goi	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
St	B-place
Leonards	I-place
till	O
the	O
next	O
Drawingroom	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
&	O
Lord	B-pers
are	O
there	O
--	O
Ly	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
&	O
Del	B-pers
Campo	I-pers
--	O
both	O
these	O
last	O
are	O
very	O
pleasant	O
and	O
agreeable	O
People	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
different	O
ways	O
--	O
the	O
form	O
er	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Minister	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
pleasant	O
and	O
very	O
musical	O
--	O
the	O
latter	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
admired	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
Character	O
--	O
my	O
admiration	O
is	O
not	O
leſsened	O
since	O
I	O
am	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
private	O
life	O
&	O
society	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
something	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Friday	O
I	O
suppose	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Siddons	I-pers
Birthday	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
next	O
--	O
Pſs	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
indifferent	O
again	O
--	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
is	O
I	O
fear	O
dying	O
at	O
Nice	B-place
--	O
now	O
for	O
my	O
future	O
Plans	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
catch	O
you	O
in	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
if	O
the	O
thing	O
is	O
poſsible	O
--	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
doubt	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
go	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
--	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
of	O
October	O
return	O
there	O
for	O
another	O
fortnight	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
either	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
the	O
last	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
determind	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
your	O
intention	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Dallington	B-place
duri	O
n	O
g	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Month	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
determine	O
it	O
--	O
so	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
--	O
My	O
Father	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
&	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
in	O
February	O
--	O
so	O
after	O
November	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
Northamtonshire	B-place
till	O
87	O
--	O
God	O
Grant	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
meet	O
!	O
Indeed	O
I	O
feel	O
our	O
separation	O
cruelly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
your	O
happineſs	O
which	O
always	O
occurrs	O
when	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
prevents	O
forbids	O
me	O
to	O
mur	O
mur	O
or	O
repine	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
happy	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
near	O
me	O
it	O
would	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
be	O
better	O
on	O
many	O
accoun	O
ts	O
but	O
whilst	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
--	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
contented	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
sincerely	O
enter	O
into	O
your	O
feeli	O
n	O
gs	O
&	O
regretts	O
about	O
Bell	B-pers
!	O
how	O
well	O
I	O
rememb	O
er	O
her	O
--	O
what	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
you	O
!	O
to	O
her	O
Sisters	O
!	O
but	O
an	O
irreparable	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
Children	O
!	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
fatal	O
year	O
or	O
rather	O
Summer	O
to	O
Ladies	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
what	O
a	O
loſs	O
to	O
everybody	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
--	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
&	O
Duke	B-pers
,	O
irrecoverable	O
!	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Montrose	I-pers
was	O
dying	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Harriet	I-pers
Elliott	I-pers
does	O
perfectly	O
well	O
tho	O
'	O
--	O
thank	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
for	O
the	O
Verses	O
--	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
sacred	O
--	O
May	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
quite	O
like	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
them	O
confused	O
&	O
without	O
any	O
distinct	O
visible	O
meani	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
poor	O
Ly	B-pers
Ayoph	I-pers
has	O
been	O
extremely	O
ill	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
accou	O
nt	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
much	O
wish	O
it	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
corresponden	O
ce	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
mutual	O
Friend	O
Col	B-pers
:	I-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
from	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
&	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
writte	O
n	O
12	O
pages	O
--	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
barbarous	O
to	O
send	O
leſs	O
to	O
India	B-place
,	O
esp	O
when	O
one	O
writes	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
two	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
dear	O
Friend	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
may	O
every	O
happineſs	O
attend	O
your	O
steps	O
!	O
your	O
unalterable	O
&	O
affect	O
:	O
Mr	B-pers
Young	I-pers
CMG	B-pers
has	O
lately	O
been	O
here	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
perfectly	O
well	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
?	O
She	O
left	O
us	O
this	O
mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
a	O
remarquable	O
sensible	O
Woman	O
--	O
remember	O
me	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
--	O
To	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Seper	O
.	O
1786	O
