TOKEN	NE
March	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
1787	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
impatient	O
&	O
anxious	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
you	O
&	O
your	O
little	O
love	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
unreasonable	O
to	O
expect	O
you	O
to	O
write	O
sooner	O
than	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
aware	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
demands	O
your	O
Friends	O
make	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
rejoice	O
so	O
sincerely	O
in	O
your	O
happineſs	O
!	O
do	O
you	O
ever	O
sleep	O
?	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Months	O
at	O
least	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
delightful	O
&	O
dear	O
an	O
object	O
to	O
occupy	O
my	O
thoughts	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
mortified	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
nurse	O
it	O
yourself	O
--	O
how	O
did	O
this	O
happen	O
?	O
Bell	B-pers
never	O
mentioned	O
this	O
circumstance	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
indeed	O
any	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
Daug	O
hter	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
you	O
continue	O
perfectly	O
so	O
I	O
hope	O
&	O
your	O
little	O
Girl	O
--	O
what	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
&	O
who	O
stood	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
better	O
--	O
&	O
how	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
continue	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
--	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
be	O
answered	O
on	O
all	O
these	O
points	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
it	O
much	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
doubt	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
wonder	O
at	O
my	O
having	O
allowed	O
three	O
weeks	O
to	O
ellapse	O
without	O
answeri	O
n	O
g	O
your	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
account	O
for	O
this	O
silence	O
satisfactorily	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
nor	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
feel	O
how	O
incapa	O
ble	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
this	O
Month	O
past	O
of	O
writi	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
any	O
bei	O
n	O
g	O
or	O
of	O
doi	O
n	O
g	O
anything	O
else	O
that	O
afforded	O
a	O
minutes	O
pleasure	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
or	O
that	O
left	O
one	O
pleasi	O
n	O
g	O
idea	O
or	O
reflection	O
behind	O
it	O
--	O
since	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
left	O
a	O
minute	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
regret	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
employed	O
the	O
hours	O
I	O
spend	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
manner	O
,	O
the	O
constant	O
diſsipation	O
of	O
the	O
mind	O
,	O
&	O
impoſsibility	O
of	O
application	O
to	O
anythi	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
dangerous	O
--	O
inshort	O
it	O
has	O
broke	O
into	O
all	O
my	O
plans	O
of	O
occupation	O
&	O
has	O
unhinged	O
me	O
quite	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
desœuvre	O
ed	O
diſsipated	O
,	O
without	O
an	O
object	O
or	O
a	O
pursuit	O
which	O
is	O
worse	O
than	O
death	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
produces	O
disgust	O
,	O
disatisfaction	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
total	O
incapacity	O
of	O
exertion	O
there	O
lye	O
my	O
Memoirs	O
,	O
my	O
Euclid	O
&	O
c	O
there	O
my	O
paper	O
pen	O
&	O
ink	O
--	O
here	O
I	O
sit	O
&	O
talk	O
or	O
listen	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
&	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
dreſs	O
&	O
ennuyer	O
myself	O
duri	O
n	O
g	O
a	O
long	O
long	O
Eveni	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
week	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
4	O
times	O
without	O
her	O
--	O
this	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
situation	O
&	O
journal	O
for	O
this	O
month	O
past	O
--	O
&	O
a	O
most	O
dreadful	O
&	O
uncomfortable	O
one	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
--	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
acustomed	O
to	O
my	O
changes	O
&	O
inconsistences	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Fits	O
&	O
Starts	O
&	O
will	O
therefore	O
pity	O
&	O
not	O
blame	O
me	O
--	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
--	O
dependant	O
on	O
circumstances	O
,	O
on	O
humours	O
,	O
on	O
Events	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
my	O
principles	O
or	O
my	O
opinions	O
but	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
my	O
comfort	O
&	O
my	O
bien	O
etre	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
elasticity	O
spring	O
,	O
eager	O
,	O
occupied	O
,	O
happy	O
--	O
since	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
describi	O
n	O
g	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
begin	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
to	O
emerge	O
from	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
first	O
proof	O
symptom	O
I	O
have	O
perceived	O
of	O
my	O
approachi	O
n	O
g	O
change	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
ability	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
The	O
Weather	O
is	O
heavenly	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
Easter	O
week	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
--	O
to	O
Richmond	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
the	O
liberty	O
&	O
the	O
quiet	O
will	O
restore	O
my	O
health	O
&	O
spirits	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
particular	O
complaint	O
,	O
I	O
feel	O
oppreſsed	O
,	O
heavy	O
,	O
stupid	O
,	O
inshort	O
the	O
disorder	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
of	O
havi	O
n	O
g	O
been	O
immured	O
here	O
for	O
Month	O
s	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
scarce	O
ever	O
in	O
publick	O
however	O
,	O
except	O
with	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
suspected	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
--	O
I	O
dine	O
every	O
day	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
--	O
by	O
the	O
by	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
perfectly	O
well	O
--	O
&	O
Is	B-pers
behaves	O
extremely	O
so	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
twice	O
--	O
we	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
one	O
Mor	O
n	O
i	O
n	O
g	O
,	O
&	O
met	O
her	O
another	O
--	O
she	O
looks	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
says	O
Miſs	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
is	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
&	O
I	O
have	O
entirely	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
--	O
we	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
quarel	O
or	O
t	O
he	O
appearance	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
never	O
asks	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
&	O
we	O
do	O
but	O
just	O
speak	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
odd	O
n'estce	O
pas	O
after	O
all	O
we	O
remember	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
is	O
presented	O
&	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
but	O
not	O
liked	O
,	O
&	O
a	O
true	O
Miſs	O
--	O
my	O
dear	O
frie	O
nd	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
everythi	O
n	O
g	O
you	O
think	O
&	O
do	O
--	O
&	O
do	O
not	O
spare	O
my	O
money	O
--	O
could	O
you	O
imagine	O
I	O
could	O
grudge	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
direct	O
under	O
cover	O
to	O
S.G.E	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
will	O
endeav	O
our	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
franked	O
to	O
you	O
either	O
to	O
day	O
or	O
Monday	O
--	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
scrawl	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
finish	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Sister	O
returns	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
visits	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
filled	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
complaints	O
,	O
caprices	O
&	O
contrarietys	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
thinki	O
n	O
g	O
it	O
almost	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
trespaſs	O
upon	O
even	O
your	O
indulgence	O
--	O
I	O
conclude	O
with	O
the	O
aſsurance	O
of	O
my	O
sincere	O
&	O
tender	O
affection	O
for	O
you	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
yours	O
ever	O
CMGunning	B-pers
.	O
my	O
kind	O
Compts	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
London	B-place
March	O
twenty	O
fourth	O
1787	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Abbey	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
Free	O
Geo	B-pers
:	I-pers
Fitzroy	I-pers
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miſs	I-pers
Gung	I-pers
.	I-pers
March	O
1787	O
