TOKEN	NE
Edinr-	B-place
1	O
st	O
.	O
Novr-	O
1779	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
received	O
your	O
Epistle	O
,	O
&	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
intolerable	O
bad	O
humour	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
Sore	O
throat	O
&	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
resist	O
a	O
secret	O
impulse	O
I	O
feel	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
imputed	O
your	O
Silence	O
to	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Reasons	O
you	O
are	O
pleased	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
your	O
Vanity	O
has	O
every	O
reason	O
to	O
be	O
mortified	O
--	O
Distreſses	O
have	O
been	O
multiplied	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
not	O
making	O
me	O
feel	O
them	O
--	O
An	O
Uncle	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
I	O
doated	O
upon	O
Dead	O
;	O
disappointed	O
in	O
a	O
Company	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Northk-	I-pers
so	O
dreadfully	O
burnt	O
(	O
by	O
her	O
head	O
dreſs	O
taking	O
fire	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
these	O
three	O
Weeks	O
&	O
unable	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Hopetoun	I-pers
(	O
my	O
Other	O
Counsellor	O
)	O
is	O
likewise	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
invisible	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
contrive	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
South	O
this	O
Winter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
to	O
finish	O
the	O
matter	O
one	O
Way	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
by	O
applying	O
personally	O
to	O
Ms-	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
temper	O
,	O
that	O
should	O
I	O
make	O
proposals	O
&	O
not	O
be	O
accepted	O
of	O
,	O
her	O
mauvaise	O
honte	O
is	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
besides	O
a	O
thousand	O
other	O
Substantial	O
reasons	O
,	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
trusted	O
upon	O
paper	O
,	O
determines	O
me	O
to	O
postpone	O
all	O
further	O
proceedings	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
certain	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Motions	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
giddy	O
&	O
sprain	O
your	O
hands	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
treat	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
perfectly	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
your	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
credit	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
introduction	O
to	O
character	O
of	O
His	B-pers
H.	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
to	O
being	O
born	O
a	O
Prince	O
That	O
exceſs	O
of	O
diſsimulation	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
surrounded	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
Kingcraft	O
neceſsary	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
&	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
must	O
des	O
troy	O
the	O
seeds	O
of	O
many	O
Virtues	O
&	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
which	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
are	O
born	O
with	O
--	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
a	O
bad	O
Courtier	O
,	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
flatter	O
the	O
actions	O
of	O
a	O
Prince	O
,	O
when	O
incompatible	O
with	O
the	O
Virtues	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
surrounded	O
with	O
honest	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
chance	O
is	O
wonderfully	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
an	O
Anti-Courtier	O
,	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
loyal	O
Subject	O
,	O
&	O
would	O
with	O
pleasure	O
furnish	O
the	O
last	O
shilling	O
of	O
my	O
fortune	O
&	O
last	O
drop	O
of	O
my	O
blood	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
welfare	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
gracious	O
Prince	O
that	O
ever	O
poſseſsed	O
the	O
throne	O
of	O
this	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
P——t	O
of	O
Ireland	B-place
are	O
ungenerous	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
unjust	O
.	O
Their	O
demand	O
of	O
a	O
free	O
trade	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
We	O
dare	O
not	O
irritate	O
them	O
&	O
when	O
they	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
puts	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
patience	O
.	O
God	O
grant	O
more	O
fortunate	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
we	O
never	O
had	O
more	O
need	O
of	O
them	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
with	O
Ld-	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
promotion	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
busineſs	O
&	O
I	O
really	O
beleive	O
capable	O
of	O
filling	O
the	O
office	O
with	O
Credit	O
&	O
Reputation	O
,	O
Your	O
intelligence	O
about	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
I	O
suspect	O
to	O
be	O
premature	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
departure	O
is	O
quite	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
still	O
have	O
compaſsion	O
for	O
poor	O
J.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
his	O
name	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
mentioned	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Your	O
Affectionate	O
Brother	O
N——	B-pers
P.S	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
or	O
Kew	B-place
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
communicate	O
