TOKEN	NE
I	O
fear	O
greatly	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
may	O
think	O
me	O
unkind	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
answerd	O
her	O
Last	O
Letter	O
but	O
alas	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
my	O
Apology	O
is	O
too	O
good	O
&	O
were	O
I	O
leſs	O
Anxious	O
to	O
asure	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
Regard	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
even	O
yet	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
yours	O
came	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
was	O
very	O
Ill	O
--	O
there	O
folowd	O
the	O
fatal	O
Acts	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
than	O
Mr	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
grew	O
Worse	O
&	O
at	O
this	O
Moment	O
I	O
write	O
from	O
his	O
bed	O
side	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
attended	O
by	O
two	O
Physicians	O
who	O
dont	O
even	O
flatter	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
soon	O
get	O
well	O
it	O
all	O
proceeds	O
from	O
an	O
unformd	O
Gout	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
exhausted	O
wt	O
fatigue	O
&	O
want	O
of	O
Sleep	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Anxiety	O
of	O
Mind	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
hold	O
my	O
Pen	O
--	O
be	O
asured	O
we	O
both	O
feell	O
for	O
yr	O
Mamma	O
&	O
you	O
deeply	O
--	O
do	O
write	O
soon	O
how	O
all	O
goes	O
on	O
--	O
I	O
suspect	O
you	O
must	O
prepare	O
for	O
the	O
Worst	O
on	O
Mr	B-pers
F	I-pers
:	I-pers
H——n	I-pers
s	O
part	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
hurt	O
however	O
much	O
he	O
may	O
perplex	O
you	O
--	O
I	O
heartily	O
wish	O
--	O
all	O
were	O
well	O
setled	O
&	O
you	O
at	O
home	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ruſsia	B-place
since	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
fatal	O
News	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
s	O
death	O
--	O
Anxiously	O
do	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
hear	O
again	O
--	O
our	O
best	O
Wishes	O
&	O
compts	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
Adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
Sincearly	O
Yours	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
M	B-pers
A	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
Abbey	B-place
Decr	O
28	O
th	O
1771	O
