TOKEN	NE
23	O
d	O
.	O
Feby-	O
1786	O
--	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
wrote	O
my	O
hasty	O
Letter	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
Wife	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
posted	O
away	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
&	O
our	O
Sister	O
--	O
I	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
M——	I-pers
to	O
write	O
a	O
few	O
Lines	O
,	O
and	O
A	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
very	O
luckily	O
had	O
her	O
Cargo	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
V——	I-pers
was	O
not	O
pleased	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
dined	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
stayed	O
an	O
hour	O
drank	O
your	O
dear	O
health	O
&	O
then	O
returned	O
home	O
to	O
dreſs	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
before	O
--	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
who	O
was	O
charming	O
well	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
.	O
“	O
pray	O
tell	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
that	O
I	O
do	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
my	O
spirits	O
--	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
even	O
play	O
with	O
a	O
Kitten	O
”	O
--	O
a	O
pretty	O
thing	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Wallingford	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
her	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
interrupted	O
our	O
tête	O
a	O
tête	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
Sir	B-pers
Robt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
playing	O
at	O
Cheſs	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sackville	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
s	O
--	O
I	O
soon	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
here	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Revely	I-pers
,	O
playing	O
at	O
vingt	O
et	O
une	O
--	O
they	O
stayed	O
a	O
little	O
Supper	O
--	O
abt	O
.	O
10-	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
yours	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
.	O
with	O
the	O
enclosures	O
--	O
after	O
the	O
departure	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Letters	O
to	O
ye-	O
Glovers	O
--	O
who	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
admire	O
d	O
yr-	O
L	O
.	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
G	I-pers
will	O
write	O
for	O
herself	O
--	O
to	O
you	O
23	O
--	O
this	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
s	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
our	O
Acct	O
.	O
&	O
to	O
settle	O
with	O
him	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Pitos	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
barrel	O
of	O
oysters	O
for	O
our	O
good	O
father	O
--	O
&	O
--	O
I	O
also	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Comptrollers	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
the	O
Negligence	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Offices	O
in	O
forwarding	O
ye-	O
Derbyshire	B-place
Letters	O
so	O
improperly	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
--	O
and	O
to	O
state	O
ye-	O
Grievance	O
wch	O
.	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
do	O
--	O
I	O
returned	O
thrō	O
.	O
the	O
Strand	O
--	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
who	O
sends	O
her	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
Florio	O
--	O
then	O
I	O
executed	O
yr-	O
Commiſsion	O
at	O
Sanguines	O
--	O
&	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
met	O
Sir	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Herries	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
&	O
gone	O
out	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walkinshaw	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
frank	O
for	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
&	O
has	O
just	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
lost	O
the	O
directions	O
--	O
therefore	O
this	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
Whilst	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
or	O
if	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
½	O
an	O
hour	O
--	O
I	O
shall	O
wait	O
upon	O
her	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
5	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Portland	O
Place	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
--	O
her	O
Cap	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
Dreſs	O
--	O
she	O
looked	O
beautiful	O
indeed	O
--	O
her	O
eldest	O
Son	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Boy	O
--	O
the	O
others	O
are	O
recovering	O
finely	O
Henry	B-pers
is	O
also	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
favorite	O
as	O
ever	O
--	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
healthy	O
Child	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
beautiful	O
as	O
George	B-pers
--	O
Ly-	B-pers
S.——	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
&	O
in	O
spirits	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
Ld	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Lady	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cathcart	I-pers
came	O
--	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
at	O
several	O
houses	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
town	B-place
--	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
C——	I-pers
is	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
Relations	O
in	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
trace	O
the	O
least	O
likeneſs	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
Wife	O
--	O
½	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
the	O
Ladies	O
went	O
to	O
Dr	O
Lady	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
's	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
&	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W——	I-pers
's	O
Gl	B-pers
--	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
--	O
made	O
enquiries	O
after	O
you	O
&	O
desired	O
his	O
Comps	O
.	O
--	O
Col.	B-pers
Greville	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Harpur	I-pers
were	O
also	O
there	O
--	O
the	O
Col	O
.	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
&	O
in	O
a	O
pleasant	O
manner	O
made	O
an	O
apology	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
waited	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
so	O
much	O
engaged	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
mentioned	O
the	O
plan	O
of	O
my	O
Residence	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
calling	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
wd	O
.	O
have	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
so	O
intensely	O
cold	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
pitied	O
the	O
poor	O
Coachman	O
--	O
or	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
several	O
Visits	O
--	O
24	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Antrobus	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
were	O
setting	O
out	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
A——	I-pers
was	O
so	O
impertinent	O
as	O
to	O
desire	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
present	O
his	O
Love	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
abt	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
,	O
I	O
unwillingly	O
excused	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
luckily	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
engaged	O
tomorrow	O
--	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
party	O
wd	O
.	O
be	O
Lady	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Iremonger	I-pers
.	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
shall	O
try	O
hard	O
to	O
rival	O
you	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ireer.——	I-pers
and	O
engaged	O
myself	O
--	O
whenever	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
dine	O
in	O
this	O
Society	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
's	O
Eyes	O
sparkle	O
she	O
shakes	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
&	O
seems	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
favor	O
instead	O
of	O
conferring	O
one	O
--	O
I	O
calld	O
upon	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
who	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
headach	O
,	O
wch	O
.	O
did	O
not	O
prevent	O
her	O
being	O
extremely	O
agreeable	O
--	O
we	O
talked	O
of	O
our	O
dear	O
freinds	O
at	O
Courteen	O
Hall	O
and	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
anecdote	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Wal——g——mWalsingham	I-pers
--	O
wch	O
.	O
afforded	O
us	O
a	O
hearty	O
laugh	O
--	O
I	O
took	O
leave	O
in	O
form	O
--	O
tho	O
Soon	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
again	O
--	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarkes	I-pers
where	O
I	O
found	O
Miſs	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
we	O
drank	O
some	O
Chocolate	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Lincoln	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
fields	I-place
--	O
going	O
up	O
Long	B-place
Acre	I-place
my	O
Eyes	O
were	O
attracted	O
by	O
some	O
very	O
elegant	O
Carriages	O
wch	O
.	O
were	O
built	O
upon	O
a	O
new	O
Construction	O
&	O
intended	O
for	O
exportation	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
well	O
worth	O
seeing	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
civil	O
speeches	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
s	O
and	O
left	O
3	O
Cards	O
.	O
Lord	B-pers
Mans	I-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Ruſsel	O
Street	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
told	O
me	O
a	O
curious	O
Anecdote	O
or	O
rather	O
an	O
Acct-	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Czar	O
by	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
Count	B-pers
Orlow	I-pers
--	I-pers
desires	O
his	O
best	O
Comps	O
.	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
B——	I-pers
--	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bedford	O
Square	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
were	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Conversation	O
abt	O
.	O
the	O
musical	O
powers	O
of	O
our	O
Cousin	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
a	O
great	O
singer	O
was	O
to	O
practise	O
this	O
Evg	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
as	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
sing	O
a	O
Duet	O
on	O
friday	O
next	O
--	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
&	O
stay	O
the	O
Evg	O
,	O
I	O
apologized	O
--	O
&	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
hearing	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
sing	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
town	B-place
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
desired	O
I	O
wd	O
.	O
come	O
at	O
8.	O
and	O
beged	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
&	O
wrap	O
myself	O
up	O
warm	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
take	O
cold	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
exactly	O
as	O
I	O
then	O
was	O
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
said	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
without	O
Boots	O
,	O
he	O
shud	O
show	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
dreſsing	O
room	O
--	O
&	O
oblige	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
his	O
--	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
&	O
very	O
friendly	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
found	O
yr	O
.	O
dear	O
Letter	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
s	O
kind	O
favor	O
--	O
immediately	O
after	O
dinner	O
yr-	O
little	O
maid	O
came	O
&	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
--	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
cd	O
.	O
part	O
for	O
the	O
one	O
you	O
have	O
or	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
for	O
her	O
She	O
might	O
come	O
down	O
at	O
present	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
no	O
expences	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
her	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
who	O
seems	O
very	O
well	O
--	O
that	O
Creature	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
is	O
arrived	O
&	O
as	O
wild	O
as	O
an	O
untamed	O
Colt	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
engaged	O
myself	O
for	O
Sunday	O
--	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Uncle	O
s	O
--	O
I	O
really	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
Duet	O
sung	O
so	O
well	O
before	O
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
obliged	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
favourite	O
Song	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
H——	I-pers
came	O
in	O
--	O
Mr	B-pers
C.	I-pers
Greville	I-pers
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
introduced	O
to	O
him	O
--	O
when	O
the	O
Rehearsal	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
do	O
me	O
the	O
favor	O
to	O
frank	O
2	O
Covers	O
for	O
me	O
wch	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
obligingly	O
.	O
and	O
whilst	O
