TOKEN	NE
Kinsale	B-place
,	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
Febry-	O
1787	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
Maria	B-pers
&	O
I	O
very	O
heartily	O
rejoice	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
's	O
safety	O
&	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
your	O
Daughter	O
,	O
&	O
sincerely	O
pray	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
both	O
be	O
long	O
preserved	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
be	O
impatient	O
'till	O
we	O
hear	O
how	O
Nursing	O
agrees	O
with	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
am	O
confident	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
making	O
the	O
attempt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
succeed	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
tried	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
first	O
Child	O
but	O
to	O
her	O
very	O
great	O
mortification	O
She	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
relinquish	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Mrs-	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
must	O
guard	O
against	O
being	O
too	O
anxious	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
advice	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
all	O
management	O
of	O
her	O
daughter	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
will	O
grow	O
as	O
saucy	O
as	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
detested	O
by	O
everybody	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
your	O
intended	O
Challenge	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
humbly	O
be	O
of	O
opinion	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
most	O
prudent	O
for	O
You	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
idea	O
.	O
If	O
my	O
proofs	O
of	O
your	O
Jerryism	O
were	O
before	O
defective	O
,	O
your	O
letter	O
has	O
furnished	O
me	O
with	O
incontestable	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
my	O
aſsertion	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
You	O
allow	O
that	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
letters	O
are	O
sacred	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
communicates	O
what	O
paragraphs	O
she	O
pleases	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
Jerryism	O
?	O
Secondly	O
,	O
Your	O
Wife	O
has	O
forced	O
&	O
commanded	O
You	O
to	O
copy	O
her	O
handwriting	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
progreſs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
bring	O
myself	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
your	O
letter	O
was	O
not	O
written	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
now	O
confeſs	O
yourself	O
to	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Jerry	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
conclude	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
obstinate	O
of	O
the	O
Jeremiah	O
tribe	O
&	O
leave	O
You	O
to	O
chaunt	O
your	O
own	O
Lamentations	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
,	O
'till	O
they	O
at	O
length	O
get	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
your	O
high	O
Spirits	O
&	O
reduce	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
a	O
tame	O
Sparrow	O
to	O
hop	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
Spousy	O
's	O
call	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
waters	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
effect	O
you	O
expected	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
yet	O
made	O
trial	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
bilious	O
from	O
my	O
earliest	O
years	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
quartered	O
here	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Lady	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
simple	O
recipe	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
great	O
benefit	O
from	O
viz	O
.	O
Half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Aloes	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
of	O
Castile	O
Soap	O
.	O
Pound	O
them	O
separately	O
,	O
then	O
pound	O
them	O
well	O
together	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
maſs	O
into	O
Pills	O
.	O
One	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
at	O
Bed	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
with	O
one	O
&	O
have	O
never	O
taken	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Whenever	O
I	O
feel	O
myself	O
heated	O
and	O
costive	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
my	O
Pill	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
operates	O
.	O
The	O
orders	O
for	O
our	O
Embarkation	O
are	O
at	O
length	O
arrived	O
.	O
Colonel	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
Canada	B-place
with	O
the	O
Regt-	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Britain	B-place
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
My	O
Lawsuit	O
will	O
I	O
fear	O
detain	O
me	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
,	O
much	O
against	O
my	O
inclination	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
been	O
tired	O
of	O
living	O
in	O
this	O
very	O
unsettled	O
Country	O
Kingdom	O
--	O
Maria	B-pers
joins	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
affectionate	O
wish	O
to	O
You	O
&	O
Yours	O
.	O
Ever	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Yours	O
very	O
faithfully	O
Napier	B-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esqr	I-pers
.	I-pers
N	O
o	O
2	O
Abbey	O
Street	O
KINSALE	B-place
Lord	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
Febry	O
1787	O
