TOKEN	NE
Madam	O
I	O
have	O
recd	O
the	O
favor	O
of	O
your	O
Letters	O
of	O
Wednesday	O
&	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
last	O
night	O
I	O
also	O
recd	O
one	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
D'Salis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
mentions	O
her	O
Intention	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
Kindly	O
offers	O
to	O
bring	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Chaise	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
communicate	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
Day	O
&	O
Have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
attend	O
Mrs	B-pers
D'Salis	I-pers
With	O
respect	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
mention	O
as	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
--	O
Upon	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
he	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
&	O
offered	O
to	O
attend	O
his	O
funeral	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
agreeable	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Roſs	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
s	O
Clerk	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Music	O
Master	O
&	O
had	O
taught	O
the	O
young	O
Ladies	O
;	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
e	O
funeral	O
&	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
occasionally	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
&	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
respectable	O
in	O
his	O
Profeſsion	O
;	O
he	O
furnishes	O
them	O
with	O
Music	O
&	O
instructs	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
understand	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
do	O
out	O
of	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
witht	O
any	O
Gratuity	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
Partiality	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	O
but	O
have	O
very	O
recently	O
heard	O
it	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
preferrence	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
part	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
however	O
take	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
mentioning	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
witht	O
mentioning	O
your	O
name	O
or	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
abt	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
may	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
respectable	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
Profeſsion	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
learn	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dont	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
think	O
him	O
a	O
proper	O
Alliance	O
for	O
Miſs	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
if	O
therefore	O
it	O
shd	O
turn	O
out	O
that	O
an	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
is	O
going	O
on	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
too	O
confer	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
&	O
act	O
agreeable	O
to	O
your	O
Wishes	O
,	O
having	O
myself	O
a	O
great	O
desire	O
to	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
happineſs	O
&	O
comfort	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Ladies	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Madam	O
Your	O
very	O
Obt	O
Servt	O
John	B-pers
Kinderley	I-pers
Symonds	O
Inn	O
28	O
April	O
1798	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
