TOKEN	NE
Buxton	B-place
June	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
1773	O
It	O
is	O
My	O
dearest	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
greatest	O
ſign	O
imaginable	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
ſincere	O
regard	O
Love	O
&	O
friendship	O
for	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
now	O
sit	O
down	O
to	O
write	O
you	O
as	O
for	O
four	O
days	O
past	O
I	O
have	O
actually	O
been	O
so	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
Water	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
myself	O
and	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
absolutely	O
nothing	O
would	O
keep	O
me	O
here	O
but	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
in	O
short	O
the	O
Waters	O
do	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
year	O
&	O
I	O
am	O
reſolved	O
immediately	O
upon	O
getting	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
you	O
to	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
home	O
but	O
shall	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
hear	O
from	O
you	O
abt-	O
Your	O
motions	O
to	O
Kent	B-place
&	O
abt	O
,	O
both	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
&	O
your	O
health	O
as	O
believe	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
at	O
heart	O
than	O
that	O
both	O
should	O
be	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
You	O
.	O
Col	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
is	O
here	O
but	O
the	O
Kitten	O
and	O
her	O
Father	O
are	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
&	O
he	O
expects	O
to	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
returns	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
time	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
gone	O
to	O
Margate	B-place
so	O
wont	O
have	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
company	O
this	O
ſummer	O
.	O
You	O
dont	O
mention	O
in	O
yours	O
whither	O
the	O
News	O
papers	O
comes	O
regularly	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
you	O
mention	O
whither	O
you	O
have	O
read	O
Byrom	B-pers
's	O
poems	O
or	O
not	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
&	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
before	O
had	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
oppertunity	O
tho	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
them	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
to	O
get	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
ſending	O
unleſs	O
it	O
be	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Pastoral	O
which	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
8	O
th	O
Vol	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Spectator	O
,	O
but	O
such	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
are	O
at	O
my	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
's	O
service	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
better	O
she	O
wd	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
course	O
so	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
fault	O
of	O
mine	O
as	O
it	O
shall	O
always	O
be	O
my	O
study	O
to	O
do	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
oblige	O
so	O
very	O
amiable	O
a	O
Wa	O
rd	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
most	O
sincerely	O
every	O
Guardian	O
had	O
the	O
ſame	O
reaſon	O
to	O
be	O
contented	O
with	O
his	O
Ward	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
than	O
indeed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
pleaſure	O
&	O
not	O
a	O
Pain	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
proper	O
Guardian	O
but	O
My	O
dearest	O
Girl	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
at	O
the	O
ſame	O
time	O
was	O
every	O
Guardian	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
ſame	O
method	O
&	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
regard	O
,	O
Love	O
,	O
&	O
affection	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
Ward	O
without	O
any	O
self	O
interest	O
,	O
their	O
Wards	O
would	O
turn	O
out	O
better	O
than	O
they	O
com̄only	O
do	O
--	O
what	O
Pleaſure	O
would	O
it	O
give	O
me	O
to	O
oblige	O
you	O
with	O
ye	O
discription	O
of	O
our	O
Babilonians	O
was	O
I	O
either	O
in	O
spirits	O
or	O
able	O
at	O
preſent	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
spirits	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
Yours	O
to	O
anſwer	O
otherwiſe	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
ſome	O
thing	O
to	O
Mrs-	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
reſolved	O
only	O
to	O
wait	O
Your	O
anſwer	O
&	O
drink	O
no	O
more	O
water	O
this	O
year	O
I	O
hope	O
both	O
she	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
will	O
believe	O
me	O
most	O
Sincerely	O
theirs	O
&	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
my	O
dearest	O
dear	O
es	O
t	O
Mary	B-pers
will	O
excuse	O
the	O
shortneſs	O
of	O
this	O
especially	O
as	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
my	O
Honor	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
body	O
I	O
would	O
so	O
ſoon	O
write	O
too	O
&	O
who	O
is	O
likeways	O
upon	O
Honor	O
my	O
only	O
female	O
correspondant	O
except	O
Lady	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
and	O
My	O
Sister	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
love	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
my	O
Dear	O
est	O
Ward	O
Remember	O
me	O
mo	O
st	O
affctly-	O
to	O
yr-	O
Mama	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
ſay	O
My	O
Dear	O
e	O
st	O
Girl	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
ever	O
will	O
&	O
shall	O
be	O
yours	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
franks	O
from	O
Sir	B-pers
P.	I-pers
Warrender	I-pers
derected	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
one	O
I	O
now	O
send	O
