TOKEN	NE
71	O
,	O
Queen	O
Street	O
28	O
th	O
-	O
Decr	O
.	O
1808	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
Every	O
kind	O
wish	O
from	O
all	O
my	O
family	O
is	O
much	O
at	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
You	O
and	O
Yours	O
.	O
May	O
You	O
neither	O
be	O
frozen	O
,	O
nor	O
frost	O
bitten	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
happily	O
preserved	O
through	O
the	O
Winter	O
to	O
revive	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
to	O
busineſs	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
answer	O
me	O
accurately	O
&	O
speedily	O
--	O
A	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
is	O
preparing	O
a	O
Peerage	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Union	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
information	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
Marriages	O
&	O
Births	O
of	O
your	O
Grandfather	O
Lord	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
Descendants	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
undertaken	O
to	O
squeeze	O
out	O
of	O
You	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
lazy	O
,	O
but	O
gratify	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
,	O
that	O
Lord	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
was	O
twice	O
married	O
,	O
Who	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
?	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
Children	O
?	O
His	O
second	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Abercorn	I-pers
.	O
What	O
Children	O
had	O
he	O
by	O
her	O
?	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
born	O
,	O
&	O
when	O
did	O
they	O
die	O
?	O
of	O
what	O
profeſsion	O
were	O
the	O
Sons	O
?	O
Who	O
did	O
they	O
marry	O
?	O
What	O
iſsue	O
had	O
they	O
?	O
Who	O
did	O
his	O
Daughters	O
marry	O
?	O
What	O
Iſsue	O
had	O
they	O
?	O
After	O
answering	O
these	O
Queries	O
,	O
if	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
condescending	O
humour	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
add	O
whatever	O
more	O
You	O
chuse	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
You	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
grateful	O
for	O
your	O
goodness	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
deaf	O
&	O
dumb	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
very	O
quick	O
in	O
comprehending	O
what	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
instructed	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
utter	O
Sounds	O
,	O
like	O
speaking	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
understand	O
tolerably	O
well	O
.	O
Do	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Emily	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
is	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
next	O
month	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
rich	O
&	O
very	O
amiable	O
Mr-	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
He	O
made	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
China	B-place
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
universally	O
approved	O
of	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
Sister	O
.	O
Ever	O
Your	O
faithful	O
Friend	O
&	O
Affecte-	O
Brother	O
Napier	B-pers
