TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
propose	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
immediately	O
after	O
Church	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
June	O
8	O
th	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
about	O
one	O
o	O
clock	O
to	O
take	O
you	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
tuesday	O
She	O
will	O
return	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
habitation	O
safe	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
condition	O
,	O
the	O
dangers	O
of	O
the	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
excepted	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
line	O
with	O
your	O
answer	O
directed	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
and	O
pray	O
send	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
news	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
's	O
love	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
from	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
yet	O
?	O
Yours	O
dear	O
Madam	O
most	O
affectionately	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
24	O
May	O
1783	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
