TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
very	O
lately	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
--	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Decbr	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
if	O
the	B-pers
Veseys	I-pers
are	O
gone	O
to	O
Town	B-place
Yet	O
?	O
The	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
's	I-pers
are	O
still	O
at	O
Tunbridge	B-place
--	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
pleasant	O
Correspondent	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hundred	O
things	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
You	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
hundred	O
applications	O
for	O
the	O
Bas	O
bleu	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
been	O
Inflexible	O
.	O
If	O
Copies	O
are	O
multiplied	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
wi	O
ll	O
get	O
into	O
Prints	O
--	O
Therefore	O
prenez	O
Garde	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Theophrastu	O
's	O
Histry	O
of	O
St	O
ones	O
&	O
c	O
General	O
Natural	O
Histr	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
