TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
July	O
5	O
1785	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
sick	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
disturb	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
inauspicious	O
as	O
sickneſs	O
the	O
first	O
moment	O
of	O
your	O
happineſs	O
,	O
a	O
happineſs	O
which	O
I	O
sincerely	O
believe	O
and	O
heartily	O
hope	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
durable	O
as	O
your	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
warmest	O
congratulations	O
and	O
most	O
affectionate	O
good	O
wishes	O
attend	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
vastly	O
happy	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
from	O
the	O
secret	O
of	O
your	O
marriage	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
groaned	O
and	O
travailed	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
's	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
all	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
had	O
been	O
continually	O
inquiring	O
when	O
your	O
happy	O
day	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
natural	O
air	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
--	O
At	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
however	O
no	O
discoveries	O
were	O
made	O
,	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
had	O
been	O
very	O
faithful	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
His	O
lovely	O
daughter	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
preſsed	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hoped	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
soon	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
know	O
when	O
In	O
paſsing	O
thro	O
'	O
Town	B-place
,	O
I	O
received	O
your	O
kind	O
little	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
answered	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
behaved	O
very	O
ill	O
there	O
and	O
kept	O
my	O
bed	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
;	O
however	O
dont	O
waste	O
any	O
compaſsion	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
tolerably	O
well	O
again	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
return	O
You	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
precious	O
of	O
all	O
books	O
,	O
a	O
present	O
I	O
shall	O
value	O
thro	O
'	O
time	O
and	O
thro	O
'	O
Eternity	O
;	O
a	O
present	O
which	O
adds	O
the	O
highest	O
value	O
and	O
confers	O
the	O
truest	O
lustre	O
on	O
our	O
friendship	O
by	O
informing	O
us	O
that	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
immortal	O
.	O
A	O
pleasant	O
consideration	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
worth	O
cherishing	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
busineſs	O
and	O
bustle	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
allows	O
us	O
to	O
cherish	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
your	O
life	O
and	O
adventures	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
;	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
relates	O
to	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
interesting	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
remember	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
setting	O
off	O
for	O
your	O
little	O
retirement	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
?	O
how	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
town	B-place
?	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
need	O
I	O
say	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
one	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
you	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
terribly	O
afraid	O
You	O
wou	O
'd	O
make	O
an	O
excellent	O
Wife	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
treatment	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
had	O
met	O
with	O
from	O
her	O
abominable	O
husband	O
was	O
enough	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
whole	O
Sex	O
sour	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
quite	O
rich	O
and	O
proud	O
by	O
his	O
elegant	O
present	O
of	O
books	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
again	O
the	O
Mysterious	O
Mother	O
,	O
with	O
fresh	O
admiration	O
of	O
writing	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
indeed	O
admirable	O
,	O
and	O
wi	O
th	O
fresh	O
regret	O
at	O
his	O
choice	O
of	O
a	O
Story	O
,	O
objections	O
to	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
ever	O
be	O
got	O
over	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
I	O
am	O
surprised	O
and	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
turned	O
his	O
thoughts	O
to	O
dramatic	O
Writing	O
;	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
dialogue	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
much	O
superior	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
the	O
Modern	O
Stage	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
certainly	O
seized	O
the	O
true	O
Spirit	O
of	O
compositions	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
The	O
curiosity	O
is	O
excited	O
to	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
impatience	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
interest	O
never	O
slack	O
ens	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
contrived	O
to	O
throw	O
more	O
dignity	O
round	O
tha	O
t	O
excellent-execrable	O
Woman	O
than	O
other	O
Poets	O
h	O
ave	O
given	O
to	O
their	O
unstained	O
characters	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
disappointed	O
of	O
A	O
frank	O
,	O
but	O
wo	O
n't	O
wait	O
for	O
it	O
any	O
long	O
er	O
Horace	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
is	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
--	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
and	O
all	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
moment	O
a	O
visit	O
from	O
the	O
Russian	O
Prince	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
--	O
write	O
soon	O
.	O
Commend	O
me	O
kindly	O
to	O
Galitzin	B-pers
pray	O
give	O
my	O
Compts	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Yrs	O
.	O
most	O
truly	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
To	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	O
London	B-place
