TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
23	O
d	O
.	O
July	O
1782	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
notion	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
that	O
our	O
last	O
letters	O
paſsed	O
each	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
the	O
feelings	O
of	O
their	O
Writers	O
they	O
woud	O
have	O
felt	O
no	O
small	O
regret	O
at	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
intercourse	O
;	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
will	O
answer	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
unkind	O
to	O
entertain	O
suspicions	O
,	O
leſs	O
generous	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Philosophers	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
reasoning	O
by	O
Analogy	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
do	O
receive	O
so	O
many	O
agreeable	O
proofs	O
of	O
your	O
friendship	O
and	O
attachment	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
within	O
reach	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
never	O
suspect	O
you	O
of	O
indifference	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
has	O
been	O
here	O
lately	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
spirits	O
,	O
and	O
gay	O
quite	O
to	O
affectation	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
those	O
Subjects	O
that	O
were	O
most	O
present	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
our	O
thoughts	O
,	O
our	O
conversation	O
was	O
awkward	O
and	O
constrained	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
enquired	O
after	O
our	O
friend	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
lately	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ask	O
after	O
her	O
lover	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
spending	O
a	O
fortnight	O
at	O
Stourhead	B-place
,	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bristol	B-place
Wells	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
.	O
Her	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
O	I-pers
'	I-pers
K——	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
great	O
event	O
must	O
be	O
near	O
taking	O
place	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
O	I-pers
'	I-pers
K	I-pers
set	O
off	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
Ireland	B-place
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
write	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
friend	O
at	O
Deal	B-place
,	O
probably	O
these	O
things	O
may	O
be	O
new	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
writes	O
me	O
word	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
hearing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
matters	O
,	O
except	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
writing	O
to	O
her	O
frequently	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
your	O
domestic	O
history	O
,	O
or	O
daily	O
Memoirs	O
with	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
understanding	O
me	O
so	O
thoroughly	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Tis	O
well	O
that	O
you	O
Courtiers	O
have	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
dignity	O
and	O
reputation	O
to	O
atone	O
for	O
the	O
meritorious	O
sacrifices	O
you	O
must	O
make	O
of	O
liberty	O
and	O
leisure	O
.	O
“	O
Tis	O
meet	O
the	O
great	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
the	O
fame	O
of	O
Happineſs	O
,	O
“	O
The	O
consolation	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Envy	O
.	O
”	O
Edward	O
Young	O
,	O
Brothers	O
--	O
This	O
last	O
indeed	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
a	O
consolation	O
you	O
are	O
seldom	O
without	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
notion	O
do	O
not	O
derive	O
your	O
first	O
delights	O
from	O
this	O
consideration	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
dont	O
greatly	O
mistake	O
you	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
cast	O
of	O
mind	O
which	O
gives	O
you	O
most	O
pleasure	O
a	O
faire	O
des	O
heureux	O
,	O
than	O
des	O
Envieus	O
.	O
Finding	O
the	O
Aphorism	O
of	O
Solomon	O
,	O
that	O
th	O
ere	O
is	O
nothing	O
new	O
under	O
the	O
Sun	O
Ecclesiastes	O
1:9	O
.	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
in	O
literary	O
as	O
in	O
worldly	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
got	O
ba	O
ck	O
to	O
Terence	O
's	O
Comedies	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
's	O
Sermons	O
Rather	O
heterogeneous	O
matter	O
to	O
be	O
mixed	O
up	O
together	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
.	O
But	O
Terence	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
favorite	O
Author	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
thi	O
nk	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
rare	O
instance	O
of	O
a	O
Poet	O
without	O
a	O
redundant	O
word	O
;	O
and	O
whose	O
exact	O
delineation	O
of	O
character	O
and	O
manners	O
,	O
well	O
reward	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
fewneſs	O
of	O
his	O
incidents	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
his	O
plots	O
.	O
And	O
of	O
the	O
venerable	O
Arch	O
Bp	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
learned	O
Man	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Sermons	O
could	O
keep	O
him	O
good	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
some	O
till	O
tuesday	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
kept	O
him	O
good	O
the	O
whole	O
week	O
.	O
Your	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
our	O
excellent	O
Prince	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
Secker	B-pers
increased	O
and	O
revived	O
my	O
regret	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accept	O
the	O
kind	O
invitation	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
to	O
spend	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
summer	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
pleasure	O
could	O
I	O
listen	O
to	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
Wisdom	O
personified	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
Summers	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
begin	O
to	O
suspect	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
combination	O
among	O
the	O
booksellers	O
that	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
get	O
Secker	B-pers
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
provoking	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
waiting	O
with	O
anxiety	O
for	O
a	O
confirmation	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
agreeable	O
report	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
valuable	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
is	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Salisbury	B-place
.	O
If	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
never	O
was	O
preferment	O
better	O
bestowed	O
.	O
--	O
If	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Philosopher	O
and	O
a	O
Christian	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
course	O
can	O
not	O
never	O
want	O
the	O
best	O
consolations	O
under	O
any	O
disappointment	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
And	O
what	O
if	O
Madame	B-pers
Genlis	I-pers
wont	O
be	O
our	O
Minister	O
“	O
I	O
trust	O
we	O
have	O
within	O
the	O
realm	O
“	O
Five	O
hundred	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
.	O
”	O
If	O
by	O
good	O
the	O
Author	O
means	O
moral	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
w	O
e	O
need	O
not	O
doubt	O
it	O
.	O
