TOKEN	NE
We	O
will	O
with	O
pleasure	O
attend	O
at	O
ye	O
dejeuner	O
on	O
Saturday	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
will	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
.	O
HM	B-pers
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
