TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
The	O
shortneſs	O
of	O
the	O
moment	O
which	O
the	O
Post	O
allows	O
,	O
only	O
leaves	O
me	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
rejoyced	O
at	O
the	O
improved	O
state	O
of	O
your	O
health	O
!	O
--	O
How	O
glad	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
your	O
proposed	O
migration	O
hither	O
!	O
--	O
That	O
the	O
Castle	O
gates	O
shall	O
be	O
thrown	O
open	O
to	O
hail	O
the	O
approach	O
of	O
so	O
renown	O
'd	O
a	O
Knight	O
!	O
--	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
a	O
cordial	O
Welcome	O
on	O
Saturday	O
from	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
particularly	O
from	O
her	O
who	O
is	O
truly	O
Your	O
faithful	O
and	O
obliged	O
Han	B-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
22	O
July	O
--	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
18	O
Queen	O
Square	O
Bath	B-place
