TOKEN	NE
Teston	B-place
in	O
Kent	B-place
3	O
d	O
.	O
June	O
--	O
86	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
Many	O
thanks	O
to	O
You	O
for	O
Your	O
kind	O
condolence	O
on	O
my	O
late	O
very	O
affecting	O
loſs	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mitigated	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
alleviations	O
You	O
mention	O
.	O
The	O
age	O
indeed	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Mother	O
was	O
not	O
great	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
65	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
sufferings	O
were	O
extreme	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
resigned	O
but	O
thankful	O
for	O
her	O
release	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
that	O
the	O
f	O
irst	O
feelings	O
of	O
Nature	O
and	O
sorrow	O
have	O
given	O
w	O
ay	O
to	O
reason	O
and	O
reflection	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
suffered	O
very	O
sensibly	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
uneasineſs	O
produced	O
its	O
usual	O
consequence	O
,	O
a	O
d	O
isorder	O
in	O
My	O
Stomach	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
health	O
and	O
Spirits	O
are	O
now	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
much	O
mended	O
from	O
the	O
sweet	O
place	O
and	O
pleasant	O
society	O
,	O
I	O
now	O
enjoy	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
on	O
our	O
annual	O
visit	O
to	O
our	O
excellent	O
friends	O
Lady	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Bouverie	I-pers
at	O
this	O
charming	O
place	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ladies	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
me	O
speak	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
high	O
praise	O
My	O
Winter	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
a	O
pleasant	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
avoided	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
poſsible	O
those	O
great	O
aſsemblies	O
which	O
are	O
almost	O
always	O
positively	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
best	O
have	O
seldom	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
interest	O
or	O
delight	O
one	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
always	O
constantly	O
engaged	O
at	O
dinners	O
and	O
small	O
parties	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
our	O
friends	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
our	O
talking	O
and	O
thinking	O
friends	O
,	O
are	O
grown	O
wiser	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
meet	O
in	O
such	O
hords	O
as	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
me	O
meet	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
more	O
real	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
society	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
Our	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
has	O
not	O
those	O
set	O
Parties	O
at	O
which	O
You	O
have	O
so	O
often	O
aſsisted	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
at	O
home	O
she	O
is	O
seldom	O
without	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
had	O
little	O
regular	O
aſsignations	O
about	O
once	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
happy	O
as	O
to	O
escape	O
an	O
irruption	O
of	O
fine	O
ladies	O
,	O
have	O
enjoyed	O
ourselves	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
parting	O
dinner	O
there	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Town	B-place
,	O
but	O
our	O
dear	O
hosteſs	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
delightful	O
blunders	O
,	O
forgetting	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
invited	O
,	O
asked	O
so	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
became	O
too	O
large	O
and	O
spoilt	O
our	O
little	O
project	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
enjoying	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
dear	O
Soul	O
wasted	O
her	O
day	O
in	O
regret	O
for	O
what	O
She	O
fancied	O
She	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
deeply	O
grieved	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
declines	O
visibly	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
that	O
her	O
bodily	O
health	O
is	O
much	O
impaired	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
sweet	O
Mind	O
is	O
much	O
broken	O
and	O
her	O
memory	O
greatly	O
shatter	O
'd	O
.	O
Of	O
this	O
too	O
she	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
quick	O
perception	O
that	O
she	O
feels	O
her	O
own	O
decay	O
with	O
the	O
keenest	O
sensibility	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
interested	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
especially	O
now	O
that	O
her	O
friends	O
are	O
daily	O
dropping	O
away	O
;	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
her	O
great	O
dependence	O
already	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
going	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
some	O
idea	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Tunbridge	B-place
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
her	O
Nephew	O
's	O
kindneſs	O
will	O
enable	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
Young	O
Man	O
has	O
won	O
much	O
of	O
my	O
affection	O
by	O
his	O
generous	O
attention	O
to	O
our	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
indeed	O
conceive	O
how	O
great	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
your	O
joy	O
at	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
From	O
the	O
perverseneſs	O
of	O
croſs	O
engagements	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
profit	O
by	O
her	O
oblig'ing	O
d	O
ispositions	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
wished	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
a	O
few	O
nights	O
a	O
go	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
our	O
suffering	O
friend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
the	O
Accounts	O
I	O
got	O
of	O
him	O
were	O
not	O
comfortable	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
v	O
aluable	O
life	O
in	O
no	O
small	O
danger	O
;	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
s	O
ubdue	O
his	O
fever	O
and	O
cough	O
,	O
and	O
You	O
know	O
he	O
i	O
s	O
a	O
bad	O
Subject	O
for	O
these	O
violent	O
Attacks	O
.	O
His	O
life	O
is	O
not	O
only	O
a	O
bleſsing	O
to	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
but	O
q	O
uite	O
a	O
public	O
concern	O
to	O
all	O
who	O
wish	O
well	O
to	O
the	O
rising	O
race	O
.	O
Rev	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
dined	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
's	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
You	O
,	O
She	O
seemed	O
rejoiced	O
to	O
hear	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
Account	O
o	O
f	O
You	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
remember	O
her	O
to	O
You	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
(	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
Son	O
is	O
somewhat	O
better	O
)	O
The	O
Ball	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
birth	O
day	O
last	O
week	O
was	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
invited	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
excused	O
myself	O
on	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
spending	O
a	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
quiet	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
I	O
got	O
your	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
Your	O
Compliments	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
many	O
civilities	O
in	O
return	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
after	O
whom	O
You	O
enquire	O
,	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
miserable	O
time	O
of	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
A	O
violent	O
and	O
alarming	O
Sciatica	O
,	O
has	O
confined	O
him	O
a	O
close	O
prisoner	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
even	O
his	O
charming	O
Spirits	O
sunk	O
under	O
the	O
severity	O
of	O
this	O
Attack	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
comfort	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
much	O
better	O
and	O
to	O
wind	O
up	O
my	O
Town	B-place
adventures	O
by	O
spending	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
also	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
;	O
With	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
latter	O
the	B-pers
former	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
pleased	O
;	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
simplicity	O
in	O
his	O
person	O
dreſs	O
and	O
manners	O
,	O
indicative	O
of	O
that	O
excellent	O
good	O
Sense	O
he	O
poſseſses	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
extreme	O
,	O
very	O
shewy	O
in	O
her	O
person	O
and	O
appearance	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
sprightly	O
and	O
pleasant	O
manners	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
very	O
good	O
Accounts	O
of	O
dear	O
Husband	B-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
saw	O
her	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
expected	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
even	O
courage	O
enough	O
to	O
entertain	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Abbey	O
Music	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
glad	O
that	O
she	O
felt	O
bold	O
enough	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
more	O
glad	O
,	O
methinks	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
exectution	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
great	O
an	O
expence	O
of	O
health	O
and	O
Spirits	O
.	O
That	O
wretched	O
Woman	O
her	O
Niece	O
has	O
half	O
broken	O
her	O
heart	O
.	O
--	O
We	O
go	O
to	O
London	B-place
next	O
thursday	O
,	O
stay	O
only	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
days	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
carries	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Berkſhire	B-place
;	O
I	O
shall	O
remain	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
,	O
then	O
return	O
to	O
my	O
long	O
deserted	O
friends	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
establish	O
myself	O
at	O
my	O
beloved	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
for	O
the	O
Summer	O
;	O
having	O
excused	O
myself	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
,	O
Lady	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
and	O
my	O
other	O
good	O
friends	O
who	O
were	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
invite	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Cottage	O
for	O
their	O
Caſtles	O
.	O
Direct	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
usual	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
.	O
Say	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
kind	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
Edgcumbe	I-pers
and	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
respects	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
does	O
not	O
deserve	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
send	O
her	O
love	O
to	O
You	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
too	O
lazy	O
to	O
aſsure	O
You	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
!	O
Yrs	O
.	O
affectionately	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
