TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
24	O
June	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
The	O
reasons	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
friday	O
evening	O
from	O
Devizes	B-place
were	O
threefold	O
,	O
as	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Vellum	O
says	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
post	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
secondly	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
at	O
Devizes	B-place
as	O
I	O
had	O
proposed	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
on	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
a	O
nd	O
thirdly	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
Joseph	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
e	O
xtreme	O
badneſs	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
prevented	O
his	O
c	O
oming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
loſs	O
I	O
regretted	O
the	O
leſs	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
d	O
id	O
not	O
paſs	O
the	O
evening	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
t	O
he	O
bonne	O
fortune	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
first	O
Edition	O
of	O
t	O
hat	O
excellent	O
Epigram	O
on	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stonhouse	I-pers
directed	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
out	O
.	O
--	O
My	O
regret	O
at	O
leaving	O
London	B-place
was	O
rendered	O
much	O
more	O
lively	O
by	O
having	O
spent	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
my	O
sejour	O
there	O
so	O
delightfully	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
pleasant	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
revolve	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
the	O
kind	O
and	O
affectionate	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
leave	O
of	O
by	O
so	O
many	O
amiable	O
and	O
excellent	O
persons	O
whom	O
I	O
so	O
warmly	O
love	O
and	O
esteem	O
.	O
--	O
That	O
my	O
friends	O
often	O
flatter	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
perswaded	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
I	O
cordially	O
embrace	O
all	O
their	O
kindneſs	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
Hamlet	O
's	O
principle	O
--	O
“	O
Why	O
what	O
preferment	O
can	O
they	O
hope	O
from	O
me	O
”	O
?	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
Hamlet	O
3.2	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
Saturday	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
find	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
Shakespeare	B-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
devoted	O
all	O
my	O
time	O
to	O
shew	O
Miſs	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
whatever	O
was	O
worth	O
seeing	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
.	O
I	O
called	O
however	O
on	O
Miſs	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
good	O
luck	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Apropros	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Thrale	I-pers
pray	O
dont	O
forget	O
to	O
mention	O
how	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Thrale	I-pers
does	O
when	O
you	O
write	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
much	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
late	O
offence	O
,	O
so	O
disconnected	O
with	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
few	O
opportunities	O
of	O
hearing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Pray	O
say	O
something	O
handſome	O
and	O
affectionate	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
dear	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
tell	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
entertained	O
with	O
the	O
Poem	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
pretty	O
lines	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
especially	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Part	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
yourself	O
since	O
we	O
parted	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Wimpole	O
Street	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
?	O
I	O
expect	O
a	O
particular	O
detail	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
adventures	O
.	O
Remember	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
depend	O
entirely	O
on	O
the	O
charity	O
of	O
my	O
absent	O
friends	O
for	O
entertainment	O
and	O
information	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
think	O
of	O
you	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
charming	O
Party	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
!	O
And	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
all	O
so	O
agreeable	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
worthy	O
of	O
each	O
that	O
I	O
cant	O
in	O
reason	O
and	O
conscience	O
expect	O
that	O
a	O
stray	O
thought	O
shou	O
'd	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
wander	O
towards	O
Bristol	B-place
.	O
At	O
four	O
o'clock	O
I	O
shall	O
say	O
to	O
myself	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
sitting	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
--	O
at	O
seven	O
--	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
watching	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
the	O
declining	O
Sun	O
on	O
the	O
Silver	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
eight	O
--	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
separated	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
now	O
see	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
--	O
So	O
paſs	O
away	O
the	O
pleasures	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
Besure	O
say	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
the	O
Academy	O
Story	O
.	O
except	O
to	O
those	O
You	O
desired	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
&	O
Mr.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
feel	O
very	O
sensibly	O
the	O
honour	O
that	O
respectable	O
Aſsembly	O
has	O
done	O
,	O
me	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
so	O
ridiculous	O
in	O
the	O
idea	O
,	O
of	O
an	O
ignorant	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
female	O
Academician	O
that	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
stand	O
it	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
generally	O
known	O
.	O
Write	O
soon	O
to	O
your	O
ever	O
faithful	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
H.	B-pers
More	I-pers
Queens	O
Square	O
