TOKEN	NE
Hampton	B-place
12	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1783	O
My	O
dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Town	B-place
for	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
you	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
improper	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
return	O
hither	O
I	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
letter	O
as	O
made	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
answer	O
yours	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
dearest	O
and	O
best	O
of	O
Fathers	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
pity	O
me	O
and	O
forgive	O
my	O
not	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
saying	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
spirits	O
are	O
still	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
line	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
some	O
Weeks	O
.	O
I	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
joins	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
affectionate	O
,	O
with	O
,	O
dear	O
Madam	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
oblig	O
'd	O
&	O
faithful	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
——	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Esq	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
London	B-place
