TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
who	O
is	O
much	O
engaged	O
on	O
friday	O
wishes	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
breakfasting	O
Party	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
thursday	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
settle	O
it	O
so	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
will	O
be	O
agreeable	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
misfortune	O
will	O
attend	O
it	O
that	O
Thursday	O
can	O
produce	O
no	O
Hampton	B-place
cream	O
.	O
If	O
we	O
hear	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
we	O
shall	O
come	O
on	O
thursday	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
adjourned	O
to	O
another	O
day	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
will	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
.	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
's	O
eight	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
list	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
H.	B-pers
M——	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
13	O
th	O
-	O
March	O
1785	O
H.	B-pers
More	I-pers
