TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
!	O
A	O
multitude	O
of	O
Engagements	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
principal	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
reckon	O
the	O
concerns	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Poeteſs	O
,	O
have	O
so	O
filled	O
up	O
my	O
time	O
and	O
occupied	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
hardly	O
had	O
leisure	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
line	O
even	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
I	O
honour	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
warm	O
Sensibility	O
you	O
discover	O
in	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
this	O
delightful	O
Enthusiast	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
take	O
advantage	O
of	O
your	O
feelings	O
to	O
pick	O
your	O
Pocket	O
because	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
demands	O
your	O
bountiful	O
heart	O
has	O
upon	O
its	O
generosity	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
allow	O
your	O
own	O
Purse	O
Strings	O
to	O
open	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
thankful	O
to	O
You	O
to	O
aſsist	O
me	O
in	O
untying	O
those	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
friends	O
when	O
You	O
get	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
has	O
offered	O
her	O
aſsistance	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cause	O
And	O
did	O
the	O
charming	O
Duchess	O
and	O
her	O
charming	O
friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Delany	I-pers
really	O
shed	O
tears	O
over	O
the	O
wild	O
Wood	O
Notes	O
of	O
this	O
moaning	O
Nightingale	O
?	O
That	O
testimony	O
to	O
her	O
talents	O
and	O
her	O
distreſses	O
,	O
is	O
beyond	O
all	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
written	O
on	O
her	O
Subject	O
to	O
our	O
friends	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Pepys	B-pers
and	O
a	O
few	O
others	O
who	O
very	O
kindly	O
offer	O
me	O
their	O
Aſsistance	O
and	O
have	O
begun	O
a	O
little	O
Subscription	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
exceedingly	O
at	O
a	O
loſs	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
Six	O
pretty	O
little	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
husband	O
so	O
stupid	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
incapable	O
of	O
any	O
but	O
the	O
most	O
slavish	O
and	O
least	O
profitable	O
employments	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
eight	O
and	O
twenty	O
,	O
slender	O
and	O
not	O
ill	O
made	O
;	O
her	O
face	O
plain	O
but	O
not	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
her	O
countenance	O
rather	O
pensive	O
than	O
sad	O
,	O
her	O
pronunciation	O
vulgar	O
and	O
provincial	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
taste	O
uncommonly	O
accurate	O
and	O
her	O
Sentiments	O
very	O
noble	O
,	O
And	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
discovering	O
that	O
her	O
principles	O
are	O
haughtily	O
just	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
-	O
Thoughts	O
and	O
the	O
Paradise	O
Lost	O
are	O
the	O
Two	O
Poems	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
best	O
acquainted	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
has	O
formed	O
her	O
own	O
Style	O
and	O
the	O
Structure	O
of	O
her	O
Verse	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
holy	O
Scriptures	O
,	O
that	O
rich	O
and	O
inexhaustible	O
Treasury	O
of	O
divine	O
Wisdom	O
and	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
chief	O
Object	O
of	O
her	O
Study	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Source	O
of	O
her	O
Information	O
These	O
have	O
inriched	O
her	O
language	O
,	O
&	O
enlarged	O
her	O
Conceptions	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
charmed	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
much	O
an	O
illiterate	O
Christian	O
rises	O
superior	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Wit	O
and	O
learning	O
,	O
and	O
Wisdom	O
falsely	O
so	O
called	O
of	O
the	O
Pagan	O
World	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
knows	O
nothing	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
but	O
his	O
Eloisa	O
,	O
and	O
Pope	B-pers
was	O
quite	O
new	O
to	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
lately	O
put	O
his	O
Tales	O
into	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
charmed	O
beyond	O
Expreſsion	O
I	O
shall	O
inclose	O
as	O
large	O
Extracts	O
from	O
her	O
Poems	O
as	O
the	O
Frank	O
will	O
bear	O
,	O
en	O
attendant	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
and	O
pleasure	O
of	O
shewing	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
your	O
noble	O
Hosteſs	O
,	O
dear	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
or	O
Yourself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
thoughts	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
friends	O
do	O
not	O
disapprove	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
publishing	O
a	O
smal	O
l	O
Volume	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Poem	O
s	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
will	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
tolerable	O
Sum	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
determined	O
about	O
this	O
To	O
morrow	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
Dryden	B-pers
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
but	O
any	O
letter	O
directed	O
t	O
o	O
me	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
before	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
.	O
of	O
Decbr	O
.	O
will	O
find	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
.	O
My	O
best	O
respects	O
attend	O
Your	O
excellent	O
Party	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
and	O
affectionately	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Bristol	B-place
Nov	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
