TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
25	O
Feb	O
:	O
--	O
87	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
congratulate	O
You	O
on	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
recovery	O
of	O
health	O
and	O
strength	O
.	O
You	O
cant	O
imagine	O
how	O
delighted	O
both	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
welcome	O
intelligence	O
which	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
so	O
kindly	O
and	O
so	O
early	O
indulged	O
us	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
heartily	O
rejoyced	O
at	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
little	O
Miſsy	O
in	O
this	O
wicked	O
World	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
make	O
better	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
excellent	O
Education	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
will	O
receive	O
from	O
her	O
dear	O
Pappa	O
and	O
Mamma	O
;	O
pray	O
a'nt	O
You	O
both	O
vastly	O
delighted	O
with	O
those	O
two	O
Words	O
?	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
the	O
first	O
sound	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
the	O
sweetest	O
Music	O
You	O
ever	O
heard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	B-place
only	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
made	O
as	O
much	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
as	O
a	O
cruel	O
and	O
frequent	O
head	O
ach	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
.	O
My	O
first	O
sortie	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
two	O
Courtiers	O
of	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
joyful	O
meeting	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
first	O
evening	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
ever	O
been	O
out	O
;	O
for	O
her	O
friends	O
all	O
complain	O
sadly	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
entirely	O
lost	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
however	O
appears	O
well	O
and	O
happy	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
perfectly	O
well	O
dreſsed	O
You	O
cant	O
imagine	O
how	O
pretty	O
She	O
looked	O
She	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
complaint	O
of	O
her	O
situation	O
which	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
at	O
;	O
but	O
want	O
of	O
time	O
and	O
liberty	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
disorderly	O
spirit	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
no	O
small	O
hardships	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
so	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
,	O
our	O
old	O
flame	O
,	O
is	O
comfortably	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
pleasant	O
little	O
retreat	O
at	O
Kew	B-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
this	O
Winter	O
and	O
looked	O
as	O
handsome	O
as	O
an	O
Adonis	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Smelt	I-pers
has	O
her	O
old	O
Asthmas	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Cholmly	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Stratford	O
Place	O
we	O
drunk	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
and	O
the	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
's	O
;	O
Madame	O
goes	O
on	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
after	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
past	O
disappointments	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
succeſsful	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
has	O
great	O
pleasure	O
in	O
the	O
prospect	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Madam	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
aſsembly	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
come	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
talking	O
Party	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
we	O
contrived	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
decently	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
ever	O
elegant	O
and	O
ever	O
pleasant	O
Horace	B-pers
is	O
in	O
charming	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
ever	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
met	O
I	O
think	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
comfortable	O
way	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
talk	O
you	O
over	O
,	O
en	O
detail	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
shall	O
I	O
trust	O
to	O
morrow	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
Aſsignation	O
at	O
the	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
's	O
;	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
will	O
be	O
present	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
is	O
proper	O
and	O
prudent	O
and	O
to	O
save	O
our	O
reputation	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
has	O
interested	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Paston	O
Letters	O
just	O
published	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
Antiquary	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
delighted	O
greatly	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
letters	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
much	O
intrinsic	O
worth	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
give	O
some	O
little	O
insight	O
into	O
the	O
domestic	O
manners	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
information	O
of	O
public	O
events	O
in	O
that	O
bloody	O
period	O
of	O
the	O
Lancastrian	O
Wars	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
certainly	O
matter	O
of	O
great	O
curiosity	O
to	O
the	O
diligent	O
Investigator	O
of	O
old	O
Memoirs	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
curious	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
great	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
setter	O
up	O
and	O
puller	O
down	O
of	O
Kings	O
writing	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
exigence	O
to	O
desire	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
lend	O
him	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
letter	O
which	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
thought	O
admirable	O
in	O
any	O
collection	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
from	O
the	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Suffolk	I-pers
full	O
of	O
prudential	O
and	O
religious	O
advice	O
to	O
his	O
Son	O
.	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
has	O
been	O
very	O
seriously	O
ill	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
still	O
very	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
sees	O
nobody	O
but	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
,	O
who	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
tho	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
is	O
re-established	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
thinks	O
her	O
likely	O
to	O
d	O
o	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
lately	O
much	O
feared	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Q——	I-pers
sends	O
Miſs	B-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
her	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
presented	O
last	O
Week	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
finery	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
looked	O
vastly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dreſs	O
'd	O
with	O
g	O
reat	O
modesty	O
and	O
elegance	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
done	O
marvels	O
this	O
winter	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
progreſs	O
towards	O
decorating	O
the	O
new	O
House	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
Your	O
Meſsage	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
notification	O
of	O
the	O
birth	O
of	O
Your	O
daughter	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
kind	O
remembrances	O
;	O
She	O
never	O
names	O
You	O
but	O
with	O
great	O
esteem	O
and	O
high	O
commendations	O
Our	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
is	O
much	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
one	O
Vesey	O
evening	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Set	O
;	O
the	O
dear	O
Vesey	B-pers
herself	O
looks	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
tolerable	O
health	O
,	O
but	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
of	O
low	O
spirits	O
still	O
;	O
her	O
memory	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
grievously	O
shattered	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
still	O
the	O
same	O
benevolent	O
delight	O
in	O
collecting	O
her	O
little	O
band	O
of	O
favorites	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
really	O
enjoy	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
's	O
kind	O
and	O
good	O
natured	O
attention	O
to	O
her	O
shews	O
the	O
gentleneſs	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
amiable	O
point	O
of	O
view	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
he	O
often	O
sacrifices	O
his	O
own	O
convenience	O
to	O
amuse	O
and	O
delight	O
her	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
the	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
's	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
remember	O
your	O
message	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Lady	B-pers
Herries	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
talked	O
You	O
over	O
without	O
much	O
slander	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
Patty	B-pers
is	O
so	O
delighted	O
with	O
You	O
both	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
she	O
is	O
most	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
aſsures	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sweet	O
Baby	O
:	O
How	O
provoking	O
that	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
t	O
ime	O
of	O
Year	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
wished	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
!	O
Of	O
Your	O
Charrards	O
I	O
made	O
out	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
;	O
somebody	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	B-pers
Foxe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
French	O
one	O
I	O
am	O
still	O
to	O
learn	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
James	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
's	O
Oratorio	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
splendid	O
on	O
friday	O
;	O
Buckthorn	B-pers
is	O
gallant	O
and	O
sends	O
Tickets	O
to	O
the	O
Young	O
Ladies	O
,	O
The	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
but	O
honours	O
are	O
not	O
always	O
pleasures	O
for	O
they	O
dare	O
not	O
miſs	O
one	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
like	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
compliment	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Bear	O
who	O
sends	O
the	O
Tickets	O
.	O
G.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
dear	O
little	O
Girl	O
is	O
somewhat	O
better	O
.	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
sends	O
a	O
thousand	O
loves	O
to	O
You	O
and	O
the	O
Blackamoor	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
cordially	O
loves	O
.	O
Adieu	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
You	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
tho	O
it	O
will	O
only	O
increase	O
my	O
regret	O
at	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
Yours	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
most	O
faithfully	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cremorne	I-pers
London	B-place
february	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
1787	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
Abbey	O
Street	O
Bath	B-place
Free	O
H	B-pers
M	I-pers
