TOKEN	NE
Hampton	B-place
Whitsunday	O
Night	O
8	O
June	O
My	O
dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
We	O
are	O
exceſsively	O
disappointed	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
to	O
fix	O
for	O
your	O
Coming	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
again	O
to	O
you	O
three	O
days	O
ago	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
wou	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
fetch	O
you	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
She	O
accordingly	O
went	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
our	O
great	O
mortification	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
You	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
Servant	O
said	O
you	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
but	O
might	O
poſsibly	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
Night	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
has	O
therefore	O
sent	O
back	O
her	O
Chariot	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
in	O
case	O
You	O
are	O
returned	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
order	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
shall	O
come	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
find	O
you	O
to	O
night	O
he	O
has	O
orders	O
to	O
return	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
we	O
must	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
meeting	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
ourselves	O
leave	O
this	O
place	O
on	O
tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
proposed	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
you	O
home	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
unlucky	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
grieved	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
perhaps	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
e	O
v	O
er	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
