TOKEN	NE
Hampton	B-place
6	O
June	O
Ma	O
chere	O
Amie	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
expecting	O
a	O
line	O
from	O
you	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
my	O
note	O
written	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
to	O
negotiate	O
our	O
little	O
Treaty	O
for	O
Sunday	O
next	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
heard	O
from	O
you	O
we	O
construe	O
Silence	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
goes	O
to	O
Town	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
Night	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
away	O
after	O
Church	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
she	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
One	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
Madam	O
Yours	O
most	O
faithfully	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
London	B-place
