TOKEN	NE
Ma	O
chere	O
I	O
send	O
You	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Proposals	O
with	O
Rec	O
ei	O
pts	O
for	O
from	O
which	O
will	O
save	O
trouble	O
and	O
prevent	O
Mistakes	O
pray	O
charge	O
Yourself	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
for	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
When	O
You	O
want	O
more	O
sent	O
to	O
Hamp	B-place
--	O
If	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
will	O
condescend	O
to	O
trouble	O
herself	O
with	O
any	O
You	O
will	O
send	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
--	O
Yours	O
ever	O
H	B-pers
M	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
