TOKEN	NE
London	B-place
9	O
th	O
.	O
Feb	O
.	O
How	O
you	O
scold	O
a	O
body	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
a	O
body	O
is	O
very	O
sick	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
running	O
about	O
the	O
town	O
like	O
mad	O
e	O
as	O
you	O
suspect	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
's	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
!	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
serious	O
ly	O
ill	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
recover	O
'd	O
and	O
hope	O
to	O
take	O
wing	O
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
you	O
will	O
believe	O
so	O
harried	O
bringing	O
out	O
this	O
little	O
hasty	O
Poem	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
nearest	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Give	O
my	O
love	O
to	O
the	O
Sposo	O
,	O
and	O
kiſs	O
the	O
Brat	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
--	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
is	O
charmingly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
hours	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
sat	O
up	O
for	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
Christmas	O
at	O
Boyle	O
Farm	O
;	O
The	O
new	O
house	O
is	O
quite	O
complete	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
decorations	O
are	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
's	O
own	O
doing	O
.	O
Yours	O
ever	O
HM	B-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
Was	O
ever	O
any	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
and	O
thing	O
so	O
cruel	O
this	O
will	O
hold	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Frank	O
half	O
the	O
Poem	O
how	O
you	O
will	O
scold	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
vex	O
'd	O
London	B-place
Febry	O
.	O
ninth	O
1788	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Free	O
RPKnight	B-pers
Febry	O
1788	O
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
