TOKEN	NE
3	O
d	O
Janry	O
1785	O
Hampton	B-place
And	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
fell	O
in	O
love	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
did	O
we	O
?	O
For	O
the	O
paſsion	O
You	O
Say	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
conceived	O
for	O
us	O
is	O
returned	O
with	O
interest	O
.	O
In	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
most	O
formidable	O
Rival	O
,	O
She	O
therefore	O
desires	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
told	O
of	O
your	O
danger	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
instance	O
of	O
generosity	O
not	O
very	O
usual	O
on	O
these	O
occasions	O
.	O
Seriously	O
tho	O
'	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
delighted	O
with	O
his	O
unaffected	O
agreeable	O
manners	O
,	O
and	O
shou	O
'd	O
think	O
him	O
very	O
interesting	O
,	O
even	O
without	O
that	O
desire	O
of	O
thinking	O
him	O
so	O
which	O
his	O
connexion	O
with	O
You	O
wou	O
'd	O
naturally	O
inspire	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
may	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
condole	O
with	O
You	O
on	O
his	O
loſs	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
congratulate	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
Your	O
other	O
dear	O
friends	O
whose	O
society	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
console	O
You	O
I	O
hope	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
has	O
had	O
a	O
prosperous	O
Journey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
You	O
find	O
her	O
well	O
and	O
in	O
Spirits	O
;	O
pray	O
aſsure	O
her	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
love	O
.	O
--	O
/	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
thank	O
'd	O
the	B-pers
Duchſs	I-pers
..	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
again	O
and	O
again	O
for	O
her	O
noble	O
bounty	O
to	O
my	O
poor	O
Poeteſs	O
,	O
rich	O
Poeteſs	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
affairs	O
go	O
on	O
so	O
prosperously	O
.	O
When	O
You	O
see	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
pray	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
respectfully	O
offer	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
good	O
wishes	O
of	O
this	O
good	O
season	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
heartily	O
wish	O
every	O
new	O
Year	O
may	O
bring	O
with	O
it	O
an	O
augmentation	O
of	O
bleſsings	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
White	B-pers
's	O
(	O
Arabic	O
Profeſsor	O
)	O
Sermons	O
let	O
me	O
recommend	O
them	O
to	O
You	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
a	O
Parallel	O
between	O
the	O
History	O
and	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
Christ	O
and	O
of	O
Mahomet	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
written	O
in	O
a	O
noble	O
and	O
manly	O
strain	O
of	O
Piety	O
,	O
sense	O
,	O
and	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
;	O
they	O
unite	O
a	O
good	O
temper	O
with	O
a	O
warm	O
Spirit	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
eloquent	O
without	O
affectation	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
I	O
am	O
charmed	O
with	O
'em	O
When	O
you	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
charity	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
soon	O
,	O
pray	O
mention	O
how	O
Lady	B-pers
Dartrey	I-pers
does	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
concerned	O
to	O
h	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
.	O
And	O
besure	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
it	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
your	O
hands	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
unites	O
in	O
kind	O
love	O
with	O
Your	O
very	O
affectionate	O
&	O
faithful	O
H.	B-pers
More	I-pers
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
comfortable	O
Parties	O
yet	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
?	O
Hampton	B-place
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Year	O
--	O
Heaven	O
send	O
us	O
a	O
happy	O
new	O
one	O
!	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
