TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
An	O
opportunity	O
this	O
moment	O
presents	O
itself	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
some	O
more	O
proposals	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
hardly	O
allow	O
me	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Dont	O
be	O
alarmed	O
at	O
my	O
sending	O
two	O
Dozen	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
always	O
return	O
what	O
you	O
dont	O
use	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
enlisted	O
so	O
many	O
brave	O
Academical	O
Volunteers	O
into	O
our	O
service	O
.	O
--	O
What	O
a	O
charming	O
day	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
must	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
Portman	O
Square	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
one	O
that	O
has	O
more	O
true	O
genuine	O
wit	O
than	O
Mr.	B-pers
Jenyns	I-pers
something	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
sly	O
grave	O
humour	O
of	O
Addison	B-pers
.	O
--	O
You	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
yourself	O
,	O
I	O
therefore	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
better	O
and	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
goes	O
on	O
smoothly	O
.	O
--	O
Love	O
to	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
--	O
Yours	O
affectionately	O
H	B-pers
M	I-pers
Hampton	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
best	O
love	O
