TOKEN	NE
Hampton	B-place
25	O
Janry	O
:	O
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
The	O
sole	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
have	O
n	O
ot	O
sooner	O
thanked	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
letter	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
quite	O
isolée	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
or	O
its	O
ways	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
defer	O
writing	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
looked	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
a	O
musement	O
and	O
goſsip	O
for	O
you	O
among	O
our	O
friends	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
find	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
stir	O
this	O
fortnight	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
early	O
in	O
December	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
and	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
Christmas	O
fortnight	O
a	O
t	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
except	O
Lord	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
days	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
frequently	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
her	O
daughter	O
)	O
while	O
they	O
painted	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
any	O
comfort	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
often	O
affectionately	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
kindly	O
talked	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
spare	O
me	O
to	O
myself	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
finishing	O
a	O
little	O
Tale	O
which	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
light	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
glance	O
pretty	O
strongly	O
at	O
the	O
manners	O
of	O
our	O
fine	O
Men	O
;	O
the	O
gluttony	O
,	O
rudeneſs	O
,	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
indolence	O
of	O
modern	O
Ton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fully	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
without	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
over-ruled	O
by	O
the	O
only	O
two	O
friends	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
ever	O
named	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
adding	O
Bas	O
bleu	O
,	O
which	O
else	O
,	O
woud	O
probably	O
have	O
made	O
its	O
way	O
into	O
some	O
Magazine	O
from	O
the	O
numerous	O
copies	O
that	O
are	O
got	O
abroad	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
is	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
better	O
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
tolerable	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
neither	O
of	O
those	O
dear	O
friends	O
:	O
nor	O
indeed	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
,	O
Montagu	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Carter	B-pers
,	O
the	O
latter	O
only	O
for	O
5	O
Minutes	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
honour	O
my	O
fortitude	O
when	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
this	O
day	O
resisted	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
temptation	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
to	O
ask	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
annual	O
dinner	O
of	O
the	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
's	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
You	O
know	O
full	O
well	O
how	O
pleasant	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
delightful	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
but	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
dangerous	O
illneſs	O
of	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
left	O
not	O
my	O
Spirits	O
in	O
tune	O
for	O
this	O
sweet	O
Musick	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
amiable	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
has	O
somewhat	O
recovered	O
the	O
severe	O
shock	O
her	O
feelings	O
experienced	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
creature	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
administer	O
the	O
consolations	O
of	O
friendship	O
to	O
her	O
affliction	O
.	O
That	O
affords	O
the	O
best	O
human	O
help	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
suggest	O
any	O
thing	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
serviceable	O
to	O
your	O
worthy	O
Clergyman	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
rich	O
in	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
poor	O
in	O
power	O
.	O
You	O
cant	O
imagine	O
how	O
I	O
shall	O
miſs	O
You	O
when	O
I	O
paſs	O
by	O
the	O
dear	O
old	O
house	O
!	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
fortify	O
Your	O
virtue	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
weakning	O
it	O
by	O
such	O
rememberances	O
.	O
Yet	O
how	O
little	O
is	O
what	O
You	O
have	O
re	O
no	O
unced	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
solid	O
and	O
substantial	O
happineſs	O
you	O
have	O
secured	O
by	O
your	O
union	O
with	O
an	O
amiable	O
and	O
virtuous	O
Man	O
!	O
You	O
deserve	O
your	O
happineſs	O
because	O
You	O
are	O
sensible	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
his	O
affairs	O
will	O
go	O
on	O
prosperously	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
hands	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
asked	O
Sir	B-pers
William	I-pers
if	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
write	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
have	O
too	O
many	O
good	O
things	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
In	O
truth	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
both	O
afford	O
to	O
speak	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
--	O
She	O
sends	O
her	O
kind	O
love	O
to	O
both	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
no	O
frank	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
a	O
ridiculous	O
kind	O
of	O
poverty	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
folio	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
shoud	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
off	O
so	O
easily	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
that	O
that	O
sweet	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
so	O
agreeably	O
married	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
quite	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Ken	O
Wood	O
.	O
--	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Narrative	O
about	O
Miſs	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
stagger	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
as	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
were	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
foreigner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
head	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
very	O
scars	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
other	O
strong	O
circumstances	O
.	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
never	O
tell	O
You	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
Yr	O
.	O
faithful	O
Louisa	B-pers
To	O
H.	B-pers
More	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
Bart	O
Courteen	B-place
Hall	I-place
near	O
Northampton	B-place
