TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
after	O
having	O
made	O
engagements	O
for	O
every	O
day	O
this	O
week	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
and	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ill	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
You	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
indeed	O
an	O
age	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
next	O
tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
will	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
her	O
I	O
never	O
answer	O
as	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
knows	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
keep	O
myself	O
disengaged	O
for	O
Tuesday	O
till	O
I	O
hear	O
her	O
commands	O
;	O
&	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
any	O
engagement	O
;	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
engaged	O
I	O
will	O
wait	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	O
first	O
morning	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
so	O
far	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
You	O
soon	O
.	O
Glad	O
Baby	O
's	O
better	O
.	O
Your	O
affectionate	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
Wednesday	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
N	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
George	O
Stre	O
et	O
Han	O
:	O
Squ	O
are	O
