TOKEN	NE
Ma	O
chere	O
Amie	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
hopes	O
that	O
You	O
and	O
the	O
Blackamoor	O
will	O
come	O
here	O
on	O
friday	O
morning	O
to	O
breakfast	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
devote	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
blackguard	O
Holiday	O
.	O
Let	O
us	O
have	O
your	O
answer	O
to	O
Night	O
as	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
book	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
last	O
Night	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
You	O
.	O
Yrs	O
.	O
ever	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
20	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1788	O
