TOKEN	NE
Cheverel	B-place
Oct	O
:	O
18	O
th	O
-	O
M	O
y	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
You	O
had	O
le	O
ft	O
me	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
our	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
the	O
o	O
ther	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
comforted	O
myself	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
too	O
busy	O
a	O
nd	O
too	O
happy	O
to	O
find	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
regretted	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
your	O
le	O
tter	O
till	O
to	O
day	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
reason	O
by	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
our	O
ex	O
cellent	O
friends	O
the	B-pers
Stonhouse	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
most	O
co	O
nvenient	O
opportunity	O
of	O
delivering	O
Your	O
kind	O
Meſsage	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
indeed	O
envy	O
you	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
seem	O
so	O
well	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
delightful	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
one	O
a	O
more	O
lively	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
p	O
leasures	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
than	O
“	O
to	O
hear	O
wisdom	O
and	O
goodneſs	O
co	O
ntinually	O
dropping	O
from	O
the	O
lips	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
in	O
t	O
he	O
lives	O
of	O
your	O
noble	O
Hosteſs	O
and	O
her	O
honoured	O
friend	O
?	O
Pray	O
present	O
my	O
most	O
affectionate	O
respects	O
to	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
and	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
send	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
Dean	B-pers
's	I-pers
Swift	I-pers
's	O
charming	O
letter	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
get	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
;	O
the	O
letter	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
obey	O
'd	O
her	O
commands	O
directly	O
.	O
She	O
does	O
me	O
great	O
honour	O
in	O
asking	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
Les	O
Veillées	O
du	O
Chateau	O
.	O
Littl	O
e	O
as	O
that	O
opinion	O
is	O
worth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
en	O
etat	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
finished	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Vol	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
off	O
to	O
other	O
reading	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
therefore	O
speak	O
in	O
detail	O
of	O
a	O
Work	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
read	O
;	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
unexceptionable	O
as	O
to	O
morals	O
,	O
and	O
interesting	O
to	O
a	O
degree	O
that	O
surprises	O
one	O
,	O
considering	O
that	O
the	O
Narratives	O
and	O
Events	O
are	O
nothing	O
in	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
become	O
charming	O
by	O
the	O
Art	O
she	O
has	O
of	O
seizing	O
the	O
affections	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
giving	O
an	O
useful	O
turn	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
unpromising	O
circumstances	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
immediately	O
let	O
Stéphanie	B-pers
Félicité	I-pers
comtesse	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
have	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
Le	O
Bas	O
bl	O
eu	O
e.	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
flattered	O
by	O
her	O
desire	O
to	O
poſseſs	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
impertinent	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
enclos	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
Cover	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
burst	O
with	O
envy	O
at	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
Your	O
Hampton	B-place
Party	O
when	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
Lady	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
were	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
remembrance	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
Sir	B-pers
W.	I-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
did	O
not	O
convert	O
Envy	O
into	O
Pity	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
for	O
you	O
the	O
greatneſs	O
of	O
this	O
loſs	O
.	O
--	O
Sr.	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Treaty	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
return	O
this	O
Month	O
to	O
Sandleford	B-place
,	O
but	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
accommodate	O
our	O
time	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
have	O
agreed	O
that	O
my	O
Visit	O
shall	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
to	O
which	O
place	O
she	O
comes	O
with	O
the	O
Primate	O
of	O
Ireland	O
early	O
in	O
next	O
Month	O
;	O
towards	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
thinking	O
of	O
turning	O
my	O
face	O
towards	O
Hampton	B-place
I	O
spent	O
a	O
night	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
in	O
my	O
way	O
hither	O
,	O
I	O
divided	O
my	O
Time	O
between	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
and	O
Lady	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
who	O
are	O
both	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
day	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
.	O
--	O
Among	O
the	O
many	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
expect	O
You	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
promised	O
letter	O
,	O
the	O
principal	O
one	O
is	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
Town	B-place
:	O
this	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
interesting	O
piece	O
of	O
intelligence	O
;	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
sadly	O
mortified	O
to	O
lose	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
danger	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
forget	O
to	O
tell	O
You	O
of	O
a	O
Phenomenon	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
at	O
present	O
much	O
engages	O
my	O
Mind	O
.	O
The	O
excellent	O
Ducheſs	O
and	O
her	O
incomparable	O
friend	O
have	O
found	O
few	O
things	O
more	O
wonderful	O
in	O
all	O
their	O
deep	O
researches	O
into	O
Nature	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
made	O
a	O
friendship	O
with	O
a	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
born	O
and	O
bred	O
a	O
Milkwoman	O
whose	O
whole	O
life	O
has	O
been	O
devoted	O
to	O
the	O
lowest	O
offices	O
such	O
as	O
milking	O
Cows	O
,	O
selling	O
the	O
Milk	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
feeding	O
Hogs	O
to	O
support	O
a	O
miserable	O
existence	O
,	O
and	O
feed	O
Six	O
Small	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
who	O
writes	O
most	O
excellent	O
Verses	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
fine	O
Imagination	O
,	O
stored	O
with	O
abundance	O
of	O
Images	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
variety	O
of	O
Poetical	O
Expreſsion	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
ear	O
so	O
finely	O
tuned	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
five	O
hundred	O
lines	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
detect	O
an	O
unmusical	O
one	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
very	O
noble	O
sentiments	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
infinitely	O
better	O
,	O
very	O
good	O
principles	O
.	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
sent	O
You	O
some	O
Specimens	O
,	O
but	O
unluckily	O
,	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
ha	O
d	O
s	O
so	O
interlarded	O
all	O
her	O
Poems	O
with	O
undeserved	O
praises	O
of	O
your	O
unworthy	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
entirely	O
weed	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
can	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
choice	O
of	O
words	O
she	O
is	O
excellent	O
,	O
yet	O
has	O
never	O
seen	O
a	O
Dictionary	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
I	O
do	O
look	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
a	O
Prodigy	O
.	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
desire	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
them	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
kind	O
affectionate	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
good	O
D	O
r	O
.	O
bids	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
married	O
but	O
two	O
Couples	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
bring	O
The	B-pers
Stonhouses	I-pers
down	O
to	O
Cheverel	B-place
,	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
delighted	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
the	O
third	O
.	O
They	O
join	O
me	O
in	O
wishing	O
You	O
all	O
the	O
happineſs	O
You	O
desire	O
and	O
deserve	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
let	O
me	O
find	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Yo	O
u	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
.	O
Never	O
mind	O
Franks	O
Yours	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
most	O
affectionately	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
to	O
have	O
been	O
thrown	O
in	O
My	O
friend	O
s	O
way	O
&	O
what	O
a	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
her	O
benevolent	O
heart	O
to	O
be	O
ye	O
.	O
instrument	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
end	O
prove	O
so	O
,	O
of	O
raising	O
a	O
worthy	O
object	O
from	O
distreſs	O
&	O
of	O
transplanting	O
this	O
fair	O
field	O
flower	O
to	O
a	O
richer	O
soil	O
where	O
its	O
beauty	O
will	O
improve	O
by	O
cultivation	O
&	O
it	O
will	O
no	O
longer	O
“	O
waste	O
its	O
sweetneſs	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
!	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
in	O
the	O
post	O
send	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bulstrode	B-place
Gerrards	B-place
Croſs	I-place
Bucks	B-place
