TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
Monday	O
Night	O
Think	O
of	O
the	O
surprise	O
I	O
felt	O
at	O
reading	O
your	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
pleasure	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
felt	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
circumstance	O
the	O
most	O
vexatious	O
the	O
most	O
tormenting	O
--	O
To	O
morrow	O
morning	O
as	O
ever	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
hours	O
before	O
you	O
will	O
receive	O
this	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
,	O
Alas	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
London	B-place
;	O
--	O
Only	O
think	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
at	O
the	O
precise	O
moment	O
of	O
my	O
departure	O
!	O
was	O
ever	O
such	O
a	O
cruel	O
contretems	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
patience	O
at	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
London	B-place
early	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
repeat	O
all	O
your	O
fine	O
things	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
at	O
least	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
my	O
jealousy	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
my	O
sweet	O
Friend	O
I	O
really	O
thought	O
it	O
an	O
amazing	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
my	O
dreary	O
journey	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Hours	O
.	O
My	O
youngest	O
Sister	O
(	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
notion	O
you	O
will	O
like	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
fellow	O
Sufferer	O
with	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Annual	O
visitor	O
to	O
the	O
Bath	B-place
Waters	O
;	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
that	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
knowing	O
more	O
particulars	O
about	O
her	O
than	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
by	O
other	O
other	O
means	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
that	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
both	O
at	O
my	O
Cottage	O
!	O
but	O
who	O
knows	O
what	O
time	O
may	O
produce	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
hear	O
good	O
Accounts	O
of	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
Yours	O
dear	O
Sir	O
most	O
faithfull	O
y	O
Han	B-pers
:	I-pers
More	I-pers
Miſs	B-pers
H	I-pers
More	I-pers
Decbr	O
.	O
1786	O
recd	O
.	O
at	O
Bath	B-place
To	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
Bath	B-place
