TOKEN	NE
Dear	O
Sir	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
only	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
depart	O
without	O
seeing	O
her	O
Blackamoor	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
this	O
morning	O
about	O
Eleven	O
she	O
will	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
,	O
just	O
to	O
ask	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
return	O
directly	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
Yours	O
half	O
asleep	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
7	O
o	O
clock	O
Monday	O
Morn	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
s	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
