TOKEN	NE
Bristol	B-place
July	O
16	O
th	O
-	O
1784	O
Be	O
aſsured	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
most	O
lively	O
interest	O
in	O
all	O
your	O
concerns	O
.	O
Judge	O
then	O
how	O
very	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
your	O
last	O
letter	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
an	O
aſsurance	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
train	O
to	O
be	O
lastingly	O
happy	O
.	O
How	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
in	O
your	O
joy	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
impatient	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
cou	O
'd	O
almost	O
q	O
uarrel	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
cramming	O
so	O
interesting	O
so	O
important	O
an	O
information	O
into	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
compaſs	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
wonder	O
that	O
this	O
agreeable	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
favour	O
'd	O
Young	O
Lover	O
put	O
the	O
old	O
o	O
ne	O
as	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
head	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
curiosity	O
for	O
the	O
detail	O
you	O
had	O
promised	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
splendid	O
offers	O
and	O
pertinacious	O
attachment	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
rejected	O
Swain	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
now	O
so	O
engaged	O
in	O
happier	O
prospects	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
only	O
forgotten	O
his	O
pro	O
spect	O
posals	O
,	O
but	O
almost	O
his	O
existence	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
my	O
hearty	O
and	O
warm	O
wishes	O
that	O
your	O
present	O
agreeable	O
prospects	O
may	O
give	O
even	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
promise	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
enjoy	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
your	O
choice	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
prepared	O
to	O
love	O
and	O
esteem	O
)	O
all	O
the	O
happineſs	O
that	O
this	O
world	O
in	O
its	O
very	O
best	O
estate	O
can	O
bestow	O
,	O
in	O
waiting	O
for	O
that	O
perfection	O
of	O
goodneſs	O
and	O
of	O
happineſs	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
till	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
World	O
.	O
It	O
gives	O
me	O
pride	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
pleasure	O
to	O
be	O
remember	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
wicked	O
tho	O
'	O
about	O
Made	B-pers
.	I-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
whom	O
you	O
saucily	O
call	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
indeed	O
admire	O
her	O
Talents	O
;	O
I	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
heart	O
a	O
natural	O
propensity	O
to	O
love	O
ingenious	O
persons	O
with	O
an	O
Enthusiasm	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
sorrow	O
,	O
obliged	O
to	O
lower	O
considerably	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
know	O
their	O
private	O
history	O
.	O
But	O
can	O
this	O
Woman	O
be	O
such	O
an	O
Advocate	O
for	O
Virtue	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
really	O
no	O
principles	O
?	O
and	O
can	O
I	O
really	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
fool	O
to	O
ask	O
that	O
question	O
,	O
I	O
who	O
have	O
read	O
so	O
many	O
books	O
written	O
by	O
people	O
whose	O
whole	O
li	O
f	O
v	O
es	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
lie	O
to	O
their	O
writings	O
.	O
--	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
s	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
Cloke	O
wou	O
'd	O
really	O
be	O
an	O
excellent	O
one	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
any	O
hypocrite	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
written	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
writing	O
which	O
tho	O
very	O
innocent	O
,	O
yet	O
requires	O
a	O
Spirit	O
and	O
a	O
hardineſs	O
which	O
never	O
sit	O
well	O
on	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
notion	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
all	O
satire	O
and	O
all	O
Comedy	O
:	O
You	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
name	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
however	O
excellent	O
that	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
written	O
,	O
no	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
acquired	O
the	O
laurels	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
mean	O
of	O
Juvenal	O
or	O
Congreve	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
decent	O
comic	O
or	O
Satiric	O
poet	O
that	O
ever	O
lived	O
Pray	O
tell	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
that	O
neither	O
the	O
outside	O
nor	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
acquired	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
my	O
stay	O
at	O
Oxford	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
without	O
either	O
wig	O
or	O
Wisdom	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
otherwise	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
renounced	O
all	O
the	O
honours	O
they	O
have	O
to	O
bestow	O
ed	O
for	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
spending	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
describe	O
at	O
Strawberry	O
Hill	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
i	O
s	O
n	O
his	O
generous	O
wishes	O
towards	O
my	O
poor	O
Louisa	B-pers
and	O
pray	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
thankfully	O
accept	O
of	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
towards	O
her	O
support	O
.	O
--	O
The	O
unfortunate	O
Creature	O
is	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
rather	O
better	O
in	O
health	O
,	O
rather	O
worse	O
in	O
Mind	O
--	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
hear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
s	O
marriage	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
--	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
her	O
new	O
name	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
Town	B-place
and	O
how	O
she	O
does	O
,	O
and	O
write	O
soon	O
to	O
your	O
affectionate	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
I	O
had	O
looked	O
out	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
's	O
sweet	O
Verses	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
have	O
mislaid	O
them	O
--	O
Pray	O
send	O
the	O
inclosed	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ord	I-pers
