TOKEN	NE
My	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
seize	O
this	O
Scrap	O
of	O
paper	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
which	O
we	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
my	O
very	O
hearty	O
congratulation	O
on	O
Your	O
happy	O
prospects	O
.	O
May	O
they	O
be	O
realized	O
with	O
the	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
every	O
bleſsing	O
!	O
Amen	O
!	O
An	O
unforeseen	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
illneſs	O
of	O
a	O
dear	O
friend	O
detains	O
us	O
here	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
shou	O
'd	O
the	O
happy	O
Event	O
take	O
place	O
before	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
afraid	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
distreſt	O
for	O
neceſsary	O
Linnen	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
morrow	O
to	O
have	O
provided	O
for	O
Your	O
reception	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
case	O
You	O
must	O
provide	O
for	O
yourself	O
just	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
till	O
we	O
come	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
certainly	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
We	O
must	O
beg	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Adelphi	O
--	O
Wensday	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
's	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
--	O
God	O
bleſs	O
You	O
I	O
write	O
upon	O
the	O
Step	O
of	O
a	O
StairCase	O
.	O
--	O
H	B-pers
M	I-pers
--	O
The	O
Old	O
Woman	O
is	O
apprised	O
to	O
receive	O
any	O
orders	O
you	O
may	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
10	O
June	O
,	O
Kent	B-place
In	O
my	O
confusion	O
I	O
have	O
directed	O
Your	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
London	B-place
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Lovers	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
's	O
Adelphi	O
London	B-place
