TOKEN	NE
Barley	O
Wood	O
Feb	O
14	O
My	O
dear	O
Friends	O
!	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
written	O
a	O
line	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
very	O
interesting	O
and	O
important	O
event	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
papers	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
severe	O
preſsure	O
of	O
bodily	O
suffering	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
much	O
depreſsion	O
of	O
Spirits	O
from	O
the	O
recent	O
loſs	O
,	O
immediately	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
of	O
three	O
friends	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
brightest	O
and	O
best	O
Men	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
nearly	O
disqualified	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
grief	O
for	O
departed	O
friends	O
however	O
,	O
will	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
never	O
leſsen	O
the	O
affectionate	O
interest	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
those	O
which	O
remain	O
.	O
Accept	O
then	O
tho	O
late	O
,	O
my	O
very	O
cordial	O
congratulations	O
on	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
your	O
dear	O
and	O
very	O
amiable	O
daughter	O
.	O
May	O
it	O
please	O
God	O
to	O
bleſs	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
her	O
choice	O
(	O
who	O
I	O
trust	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
worthy	O
of	O
her	O
)	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
happineſs	O
as	O
this	O
world	O
can	O
give	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
;	O
and	O
which	O
indeed	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
promote	O
happineſs	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
new	O
Scene	O
they	O
are	O
entering	O
upon	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
enlarge	O
their	O
duties	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
usefulneſs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
trust	O
it	O
will	O
proportionally	O
increase	O
their	O
felicity	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
rejoyce	O
with	O
my	O
young	O
friends	O
on	O
their	O
marriage	O
I	O
am	O
generally	O
more	O
inclined	O
to	O
condole	O
with	O
the	O
parents	O
than	O
to	O
congratulate	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
desirable	O
union	O
the	O
personal	O
loſs	O
of	O
a	O
dear	O
daughter	O
,	O
whose	O
society	O
has	O
long	O
been	O
their	O
comfort	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
drawback	O
on	O
their	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
happineſs	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
mistaken	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
here	O
.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
notwithstanding	O
our	O
long	O
separation	O
,	O
my	O
attachment	O
to	O
so	O
old	O
and	O
kind	O
a	O
friend	O
still	O
continues	O
unabated	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
friends	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
alluded	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
were	O
called	O
away	O
within	O
3	O
weeks	O
were	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
Thornton	I-pers
the	O
great	O
Orientalist	O
and	O
Dr.	B-pers
Buchanan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
former	O
has	O
left	O
Nine	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
widow	O
whose	O
behaviour	O
is	O
most	O
angelic	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
the	O
most	O
accomplished	O
character	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
next	O
Month	O
to	O
a	O
sweet	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Bowdler	B-pers
whose	O
admir	O
works	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
read	O
.	O
His	O
piety	O
as	O
exemplary	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
talents	O
were	O
elevated	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gisborne	I-pers
sometimes	O
?	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
sometimes	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
troublesome	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
write	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
deserve	O
)	O
get	O
a	O
delightful	O
letter	O
from	O
our	O
agreeable	O
friend	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
saw	O
once	O
last	O
Year	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
mind	O
and	O
person	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
fo	O
u	O
rty	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
How	O
small	O
are	O
the	O
remnants	O
of	O
that	O
superior	O
Society	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
live	O
!	O
My	O
own	O
health	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
The	O
warnings	O
of	O
age	O
and	O
sickneſs	O
will	O
not	O
I	O
hope	O
be	O
thrown	O
away	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
best	O
love	O
to	O
the	O
bride	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
style	O
and	O
title	O
of	O
the	O
caro	O
Sposo	O
.	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dear	O
Sir	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Pepys	I-pers
believe	O
me	O
both	O
of	O
you	O
your	O
very	O
faithful	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
H.	B-pers
More	I-pers
Devonshire	O
Place	O
London	B-place
