TOKEN	NE
I	O
have	O
an	O
engagement	O
which	O
is	O
indispensable	O
to	O
my	O
Rose	O
trees	O
and	O
honeysuckles	O
at	O
Cowslip	B-place
Green	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
Planting	O
my	O
little	O
humble	O
Garden	O
,	O
And	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
trust	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
to	O
plant	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Pink	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
busy	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
much	O
this	O
occupation	O
interests	O
and	O
amuses	O
me	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
if	O
You	O
cou	O
'd	O
one	O
day	O
see	O
my	O
little	O
Cottage	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
cruelly	O
disappointed	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
finished	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
the	O
first	O
Week	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
quietly	O
with	O
our	O
friend	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
paſs	O
the	O
winter	O
in	O
a	O
sober	O
tete-a-tete	O
,	O
preparatory	O
to	O
the	O
bustle	O
and	O
hurry	O
of	O
the	O
Spring	O
in	O
London	B-place
.	O
I	O
shall	O
miſs	O
You	O
there	O
sadly	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
comf	O
ort	O
myself	O
with	O
thinking	O
that	O
You	O
are	O
well	O
and	O
happy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
chance	O
will	O
re	O
unite	O
us	O
.	O
Pray	O
say	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
kind	O
and	O
handsome	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
think	O
but	O
with	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Adieu	O
!	O
my	O
dear	O
friend	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
real	O
affection	O
Your	O
faithful	O
and	O
obliged	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
Bristol	B-place
Octbr	O
.	O
20	O
1785	O
Bristol	B-place
October	O
Twentieth	O
17	O
85	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
by	O
Chester	B-place
