TOKEN	NE
From	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
Library	O
Thames	B-place
Ditton	I-place
Sunday	O
19	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
this	O
moment	O
receives	O
Your	O
Note	O
--	O
She	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
on	O
Wensday	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
like	O
a	O
Chicken	O
to	O
bring	O
people	O
acquainted	O
She	O
hopes	O
You	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
will	O
eat	O
one	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Wensday	O
at	O
5	O
'.o	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Adelphi	O
.	O
--	O
As	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
Town	B-place
on	O
purpose	O
pray	O
dont	O
disappoint	O
us	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
come	O
Answer	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
by	O
return	O
of	O
Post	O
--	O
We	O
go	O
thither	O
to	O
Morrow	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
au	O
desespoir	O
--	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
to	O
Hampton	B-place
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
your	O
letter	O
--	O
Best	O
Compts	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
D	I-pers
Adieu	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
Yours	O
affectionately	O
H	B-pers
More	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
W	I-pers
's	O
very	O
kind	O
love	O
Mrs.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
no	O
Cook	O
in	O
Town	B-place
,	O
so	O
cant	O
give	O
You	O
a	O
fine	O
Dinner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
like	O
this	O
many-coloured	O
Epistle	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
Picadilly	O
London	B-place
