TOKEN	NE
Monday	O
Morng	O
.	O
8	O
oclock	O
11	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1779	O
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
Sister	O
Friend	O
,	O
my	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
myself	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
clear	O
myſelf	O
now	O
of	O
yt	O
.	O
imputation	O
which	O
you	O
accused	O
me	O
of	O
y——y	O
when	O
you	O
asked	O
me	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
last	O
dear	O
Billet	O
,	O
why	O
I	O
wld	O
..	O
force	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
R——	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
what	O
paſsed	O
before	O
yr	O
.	O
eyes	O
bore	O
very	O
much	O
yt	O
..	O
appearance	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
aſsure	O
you	O
by	O
what	O
really	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
clear	O
myself	O
totally	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
opinion	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
explain	O
this	O
I	O
must	O
resume	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
remember	O
my	O
dearest	O
friend	O
,	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
last	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
you	O
ſaid	O
to	O
me	O
you	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
yt	O
..	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
short	O
ſtay	O
at	O
W——or	B-place
for	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
low	O
Company	O
there	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
mean	O
t	O
by	O
yt	O
..	O
,	O
yt	O
..	O
I	O
made	O
myself	O
too	O
free	O
among	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
,	O
or	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
by	O
hunting	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
but	O
supposing	O
,	O
you	O
meant	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
,	O
or	O
both	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
answer	O
ym	O
..	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
most	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
of	O
yese	O
,	O
ever	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
confeſs	O
I	O
have	O
lowered	O
myſelf	O
much	O
by	O
familiarizing	O
myself	O
to	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
degree	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
,	O
&	O
especially	O
with	O
yt	O
..	O
little	O
Devil	O
W——	B-pers
R——	I-pers
however	O
since	O
what	O
you	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
more	O
within	O
bounds	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
before	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
course	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
ye	O
future	O
I	O
solemnly	O
promise	O
you	O
here	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
follow	O
yr	O
.	O
Preecepts	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
every	O
other	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
utmost	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
,	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
again	O
lower	O
demean	O
myſelf	O
either	O
to	O
ym	O
..	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
low	O
Company	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
ye	O
affair	O
of	O
hunting	O
,	O
I	O
ride	O
always	O
among	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
very	O
worthy	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
my	O
Father	O
I	O
believe	O
wishes	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
particularly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Nevil	B-pers
he	O
is	O
Son	O
to	O
a	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Nevil	I-pers
who	O
was	O
under	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
in	O
ye	O
late	B-pers
King	I-pers
s	O
Reign	O
&	O
who	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
Billingbear	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
is	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Berks	B-place
:	I-place
Militia	O
,	O
&	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
honest	O
civil	O
,	O
wellbehaved	O
,	O
polite	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
be	O
Heir	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
fortune	O
,	O
ye	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
receive	O
from	O
Sr.	B-pers
John	I-pers
&	O
La-y	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
young	O
Man	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
having	O
such	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
not	O
a	O
friend	O
Another	O
of	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
is	O
a	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
(	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
exactly	O
he	O
spells	O
his	O
name	O
)	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
also	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
Brother	O
in	O
law	O
to	O
Ld	B-pers
..	I-pers
Cholmondeley	I-pers
:	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
I	O
have	O
conversed	O
very	O
little	O
with	O
,	O
&	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
Character	O
which	O
every	O
body	O
yt	O
..	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
proceed	O
with	O
my	O
defense	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
my	O
forcing	O
W.	B-pers
R	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
praise	O
&	O
in	O
my	O
favor	O
.	O
W——	B-pers
R——	I-pers
is	O
much	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
genteel	O
way	O
imaginable	O
.	O
Well	O
then	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Sport	O
this	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
followed	O
me	O
very	O
closely	O
thro'out	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
of	O
ye	O
day	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
either	O
his	O
name	O
or	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
I	O
supposed	O
how	O
eager	O
I	O
was	O
after	O
ye	O
.	O
Sport	O
,	O
&	O
how	O
shocked	O
my	O
Nature	O
was	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
death	O
of	O
ye	O
poor	O
Animal	O
,	O
&	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
different	O
emotions	O
which	O
appeared	O
in	O
my	O
Countenance	O
upon	O
yt	O
..	O
occasion	O
.	O
A	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
sent	O
W——	B-pers
R——	I-pers
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
yt	O
..	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
yt	O
..	O
I	O
generally	O
go	O
&	O
lay	O
my	O
whip	O
&	O
Hat	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
riding	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Servants	O
Breakfast	O
Room	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
accordingly	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
Room	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
fetch	O
ym	O
..	O
away	O
--	O
W——	B-pers
R	I-pers
entreated	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
ped	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
his	O
manner	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
insinuate	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
)	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
Sentence	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
first	O
great	O
compliments	O
encomiums	O
on	O
my	O
Horsemanship	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
spirit	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
thro'out	O
ye	O
.	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
great	O
Compliments	O
on	O
ye	O
.	O
goodneſs	O
of	O
heart	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
this	O
sentence	O
he	O
snatched	O
ye	O
.	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
so	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
ye	O
.	O
signature	O
.	O
Upon	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
you	O
heard	O
me	O
preſs	O
W——	B-pers
R——	I-pers
but	O
it	O
was	O
merely	O
to	O
know	O
ye	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
very	O
Mr	B-pers
..	I-pers
Lisle	I-pers
I	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
,	O
yt	O
.	O
is	O
ye	O
whole	O
&	O
sole	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
case	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
fancy	O
you	O
will	O
think	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
blame	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
my	O
ſelf	O
flatter	O
'd	O
by	O
these	O
praises	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
when	O
I	O
receive	O
ym	O
.	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
think	O
myſelf	O
exalted	O
b	O
a	O
bove	O
any	O
earthly	O
Potentate	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
so	O
near	O
8	O
o	O
clock	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
bid	O
you	O
Adieu	O
.	O
Adieu	O
then	O
dearest	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Siſter	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
may	O
you	O
be	O
under	O
ye	O
especial	O
care	O
of	O
ye	O
Almighty	O
&	O
of	O
his	O
Angels	O
,	O
&	O
may	O
you	O
e	O
ver	O
find	O
from	O
yt	O
..	O
Allbenevolent	O
Being	O
ye	O
.	O
rewards	O
which	O
your	O
.	O
Virtues	O
so	O
much	O
deserve	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
&	O
ever	O
shall	O
be	O
yr	O
.	O
sincerely	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
Friend	O
Palemon	B-pers
,	O
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
P.S	O
.	O
Why	O
wld	O
..	O
my	O
friend	O
send	O
me	O
ye	O
.	O
Rose	O
Color	O
if	O
she	O
likes	O
ye	O
.	O
Brown	O
best	O
,	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
ym	O
.	O
back	O
again	O
looked	O
at	O
ym	O
.	O
again	O
,	O
&	O
chuse	O
that	O
wh	O
.	O
you	O
yrself	O
like	O
best	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
most	O
agreable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
be	O
plain	O
with	O
me	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
wear	O
ye	O
one	O
you	O
like	O
least	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
much	O
for	O
yr	O
Letters	O
,	O
I	O
like	O
ym	O
..	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
more	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
present	O
but	O
yt	O
..	O
you	O
are	O
dearer	O
to	O
me	O
now	O
than	O
ever	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
sister	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
P	B-pers
.	I-pers
