TOKEN	NE
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
,	O
Friend	O
;	O
I	O
understand	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
delight	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
comfort	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
company	O
at	O
W——	B-place
O	O
Heavens	O
how	O
shall	O
I	O
spend	O
these	O
long	O
Evenings	O
.	O
My	O
B——	O
is	O
contented	O
,	O
because	O
M-	B-pers
G-	I-pers
goes	O
,	O
but	O
poor	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
returning	O
f	O
t	O
o	O
ye	O
point	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
uppermost	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
Excuse	O
me	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
pardon	O
me	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
feel	O
even	O
by	O
these	O
trifling	O
little	O
separations	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
yes	O
my	O
ever	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
impoſsible	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
shock	O
much	O
too	O
ſtrong	O
for	O
either	O
my	O
ſpirits	O
or	O
constitution	O
to	O
support	O
;	O
do	O
not	O
comment	O
too	O
severely	O
upon	O
this	O
sentence	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
by	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
sacred	O
ever	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
which	O
does	O
not	O
proceed	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
M.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
sensible	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
she	O
takes	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
means	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
aſsuage	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
mightily	O
mistaken	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
she	O
really	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
pity	O
her	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
let	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
Ingratitude	O
is	O
ye	O
.	O
forrunner	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
ye	O
worst	O
of	O
all	O
vices	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
blackneſs	O
,	O
an	O
d	O
inveteracy	O
,	O
&	O
hardneſs	O
in	O
yt	O
..	O
vice	O
which	O
ſurely	O
one	O
wld	O
..	O
think	O
never	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
entered	O
into	O
ye	O
.	O
human	O
breast	O
.	O
However	O
now	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
beginning	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
last	O
Chapter	O
long	O
ſentence	O
or	O
rather	O
to	O
explain	O
ye	O
.	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
resuming	O
M——	B-pers
F——	I-pers
as	O
our	O
subject	O
again	O
well	O
then	O
on	O
W——	O
Evening	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
other	O
party	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
L.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
out	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
Room	O
after	O
our	O
party	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
,	O
L——	B-pers
C——	I-pers
had	O
been	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
Errand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
far	O
yr	O
.	O
party	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Pool	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
returning	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
ye	O
Door	O
way	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
Arm	O
&	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
yt	O
..	O
her	O
D——	O
H	B-pers
.	I-pers
had	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
a	O
ribband	O
watch	O
Chain	O
,	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
shd	O
..	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
if	O
ye	O
.	O
dear	O
P——	B-pers
of-	I-pers
W——	I-pers
wld	O
..	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
cld	O
..	O
I	O
answer	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
shd	O
..	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
of	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
accordingly	O
ſhe	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
Morning	O
,	O
now	O
may	O
I	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
,	O
flatter	O
myself	O
that	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
,	O
will	O
if	O
I	O
send	O
it	O
you	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
patron	O
if	O
you	O
she	O
do	O
es	O
not	O
exactly	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
yt.se	O
.	O
sort	O
of	O
thing	O
s	O
,	O
will	O
put	O
herself	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
trouble	O
of	O
working	O
me	O
one	O
by	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
beautiful	O
white	O
hands	O
,	O
take	O
not	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
compliment	O
but	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
real	O
truth	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
Plain	O
truth	O
Dear	O
Murray	B-pers
needs	O
no	O
flowers	O
of	O
Speech	O
Alexander	O
Pope	O
,	O
6th	O
Epistle	O
of	O
1st	O
Book	O
of	O
Horace	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
[	O
later	O
Lord	O
Mansfield	O
]	O
Pope	B-pers
I	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
My	O
M	O
.	O
remark	O
hundreds	O
&	O
hundreds	O
of	O
times	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
me	O
but	O
to	O
many	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
almost	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
beauties	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
,	O
adding	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
yt	O
..	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
so	O
frightful	O
as	O
thoſe	O
of	O
M——	B-pers
G——	I-pers
&	O
Mlle-	B-pers
M——	I-pers
You	O
once	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
in	O
London	B-place
my	O
Friend	O
that	O
I	O
wd	O
..	O
apply	O
to	O
you	O
whenever	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
therefore	O
just	O
say	O
yt	O
..	O
Miſs	B-pers
Fin-	I-pers
is	O
almost	O
worn	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
cld	O
..	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
wearing	O
her	O
work	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
therefore	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
trouble	O
yrself	O
upon	O
my	O
account	O
in	O
these	O
two	O
instances	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
ym	O
..	O
both	O
to	O
you	O
how	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
make	O
ym	O
..	O
I	O
only	O
send	O
you	O
ye	O
.	O
chain	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
sort	O
of	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
already	O
sent	O
my	O
answer	O
to	O
M——	B-pers
F——	I-pers
before	O
you	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mere	O
verbal	O
meſsage	O
of	O
thanks	O
,	O
it	O
wd	O
..	O
have	O
been	O
prostituting	O
yr	O
.	O
friendship	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
putting	O
her	O
upon	O
a	O
par	O
with	O
yrself	O
,	O
it	O
wd	O
..	O
have	O
been	O
making	O
her	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
flatter	O
my	O
ſelf	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
unfold	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
inward	O
receſses	O
of	O
my	O
Soul	O
.	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
esteem	O
yr	O
.	O
friendſhip	O
beyond	O
every	O
other	O
earthly	O
poſseſsion	O
,	O
a	O
happineſs	O
,	O
a	O
comfort	O
,	O
an	O
honor	O
wh	O
..	O
nothing	O
can	O
equal	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
Let	O
us	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
God	O
grant	O
,	O
long	O
continue	O
so	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
my	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Friend	O
may	O
you	O
enjoy	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
bleſsings	O
,	O
happineſses	O
&	O
comforts	O
of	O
this	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
hereafter	O
we	O
may	O
meet	O
neve	O
again	O
to	O
part	O
,	O
such	O
is	O
ye	O
first	O
&	O
last	O
Prayer	O
of	O
yr	O
ever	O
sincerely	O
affectionate	O
Palemon	B-pers
.	O
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
yr	O
.	O
employing	O
yrself	O
.	O
thus	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
some	O
little	O
amends	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
y	O
n	O
ot	O
having	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
having	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
recall	O
me	O
frequently	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
mind	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
doubted	O
I	O
shd	O
..	O
not	O
sometimes	O
occur	O
without	O
need	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
trifle	O
.	O
Encore	O
une	O
fois	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
que	O
je	O
vous	O
aimerez	O
toute	O
ma	O
vie	O
,	O
le	O
Ciel	O
en	O
est	O
temoin	O
,	O
et	O
que	O
vous	O
me	O
serez	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
Yr	O
Meſsenger	O
stays	O
here	O
he	O
will	O
carry	O
you	O
yr	O
.	O
N——	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
&	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
he	O
will	O
call	O
for	O
an	O
Answer	O
,	O
Pray	O
let	O
it	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
short	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
very	O
kind	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
consider	O
ye	O
.	O
Pennance	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
undergone	O
.	O
Encore	O
une	O
fois	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
