TOKEN	NE
P	O
P	O
George	B-pers
P	O
George	B-pers
P	O
George	B-pers
P	O
Prince	B-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
Windsor	B-place
Novbr	O
.	O
1802	O
1782	O
D	O
a	O
is	O
Dartrey	B-pers
