TOKEN	NE
recd	O
.	O
Satry-	O
Morng	O
27	O
th	O
-	O
Novbr-	O
1779	O
Friday	O
Night	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
.	O
Again	O
my	O
ever	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
indeed	O
every	O
time	O
I	O
write	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
you	O
longer	O
Letters	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
hope	O
neceſsity	O
will	O
plead	O
my	O
excuse	O
especially	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
inclination	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
how	O
wretched	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
hear	O
yt	O
.	O
my	O
Comforter	O
my	O
bosom	O
Friend	O
,	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
is	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
yrself	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
consider	O
me	O
,	O
consider	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
consider	O
what	O
it	O
wld	O
..	O
be	O
were	O
I	O
--	O
Heaven	O
curse	O
ye	O
.	O
thought	O
I	O
cld	O
:	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
,	O
thou	O
art	O
dearer	O
,	O
dearer	O
dearer	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
a	O
thousand	O
Worlds	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
next	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
Dr	B-pers
..	I-pers
T——	I-pers
according	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
promise	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
him	O
immediately	O
for	O
my	O
sake	O
,	O
unleſs	O
you	O
find	O
yrself	O
greatly	O
better	O
.	O
What	O
wld	O
..	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
had	O
you	O
known	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
who	O
am	O
but	O
this	O
very	O
day	O
perfectly	O
recovered	O
of	O
cold	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
ride	O
with	O
my	O
F——	O
to	O
Barnet	B-place
to	O
See	O
ye	O
.	O
East	B-place
Yorkshire	I-place
Melitia	O
&	O
was	O
out	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
wet	O
thro	O
'	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
skin	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
cold	O
Wind	O
wh	O
..	O
was	O
very	O
high	O
,	O
ye	O
snow	O
&	O
rain	O
till	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
1	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
tender	O
care	O
for	O
me	O
my	O
Sister	O
all	O
ye	O
.	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
however	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
ye	O
.	O
worse	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
ye	O
.	O
better	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
not	O
knowing	O
exactly	O
what	O
time	O
to	O
call	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
call	O
till	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
notwithstanding	O
my	O
impatience	O
to	O
be	O
informed	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
state	O
of	O
yr	O
health	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
.	O
God	O
bleſs	O
you	O
&	O
preserve	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
thy	O
tenderest	O
Brother	O
&	O
friend	O
Thy	O
Palemon	B-pers
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
found	O
what	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
good	O
&	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
it	O
soften	O
ye	O
.	O
pain	O
you	O
must	O
feel	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
breast	O
by	O
coughing	O
I	O
understand	O
L——d	B-pers
S——t	I-pers
cut	O
a	O
wonderful	O
great	O
figure	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Encore	O
une	O
fois	O
préservez	O
vôtre	O
chére	O
santé	O
pour	O
moi	O
a	O
.	O
a	O
.	O
a	O
.	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
Ton	O
P	B-pers
.	I-pers
.	O
