TOKEN	NE
Brighton	B-place
Sepbr	O
:	O
27	O
th	O
=	O
.	O
1801	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
desired	O
by	O
His	O
R	O
.	O
Hs	O
:	O
the	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
.	O
to	O
present	O
his	O
Compls	O
:	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
return	O
s	O
you	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
attention	O
,	O
--	O
am	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
;	O
to	O
know	O
by	O
return	O
of	O
post	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
applied	O
the	O
same	O
Receipt	O
the	O
very	O
instand	O
the	O
Accidtand	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
:	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
fortnight	O
since	O
His	B-pers
R	I-pers
:	I-pers
Hs	I-pers
:	I-pers
had	O
this	O
Accid	O
:	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
the	O
advice	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
Saurgeant	B-pers
Keat	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
ever	O
Since	O
,	O
His	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Hs	I-pers
:	I-pers
intend	O
's	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
trial	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
your	O
answer	O
returns	O
:	O
the	B-pers
Pr	I-pers
:	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
perfectly	O
recollected	O
Mrs	B-pers
:	I-pers
D	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
believe	O
my	O
good	O
scolar	O
also	O
I	O
am	O
also	O
greatly	O
Obliged	O
to	O
you	O
&	O
Dickenson	B-pers
for	O
your	O
goodneſs	O
concerning	O
myself	O
,	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
aquainting	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
aſsist	O
in	O
your	O
little	O
party	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
long	O
it	O
is	O
Louisa	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
pleasure	O
to	O
take	O
Leſsons	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
my	O
Duty	O
.	O
&	O
am	O
happy	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
afford	O
him	O
any	O
pleasure	O
;	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
probable	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
continue	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
yet	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dn	I-pers
.	I-pers
has	O
send	O
away	O
his	O
Military	O
Band	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
&	O
are	O
without	O
exeption	O
the	O
first	O
Band	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
the	O
only	O
consist	O
.	O
of	O
36.	O
able	O
Men	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Respects	O
to	O
His	B-pers
R.	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
His	B-pers
R.	I-pers
H	I-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
please	O
to	O
rember	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Brother	O
hope	O
he	O
conducts	O
himself	O
well	O
From	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
Your	O
very	O
Humble	O
Servt	O
:	O
Miſs	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
P.S	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
which	O
you	O
will	O
favour	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
produced	O
laid	O
before	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Msn	I-pers
:	I-pers
--	O
C.	B-pers
Schram	I-pers
Esq	O
:	O
Leighton	O
House	O
Leighton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
Beds	B-place
:	I-place
His	B-pers
R.	I-pers
Hs	I-pers
:	I-pers
1801	O
respg	O
the	O
J.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
