TOKEN	NE
16	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1779	O
Satry	O
.	O
afternoon	O
½	O
past	O
4	O
Dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
sincerely	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
additional	O
instance	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
confidence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
wanted	O
no	O
further	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
already	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
of	O
How	O
different	O
are	O
yr	O
.	O
views	O
from	O
those	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
family	O
's	O
friends	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
esteeming	O
yr	O
.	O
family	O
not	O
only	O
for	O
its	O
own	O
intrinsick	O
parts	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
it	O
has	O
ye	O
honor	O
of	O
claiming	O
my	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
family	O
can	O
boast	O
of	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
friend	O
M.	B-pers
G	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
love	O
and	O
esteem	O
for	O
her	O
vertues	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
friend	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
friend	O
is	O
there	O
of	O
my	O
Miss	B-pers
(	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
)	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
that	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
friendship	O
,	O
love	O
,	O
&	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
wld	O
..	O
not	O
also	O
be	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
You	O
tell	O
me	O
nothing	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
situation	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
health	O
,	O
&	O
spirits	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
yr	O
.	O
dreadful	O
pain	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
side	O
has	O
again	O
reminded	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
once	O
took	O
such	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
consider	O
how	O
anxious	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
these	O
several	O
heads	O
,	O
my	O
whole	O
happineſs	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
told	O
you	O
centers	O
entirely	O
yrs	O
.	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
does	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
pure	O
méchanceté	O
as	O
you	O
alone	O
you	O
pretend	O
not	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
alarm	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
cld	O
..	O
my	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
suppose	O
yt	O
.	O
what	O
she	O
writes	O
wld	O
..	O
either	O
be	O
tiresome	O
,	O
disagreable	O
,	O
or	O
trivial	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
conceived	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
opinion	O
of	O
me	O
from	O
that	O
which	O
you	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
suppose	O
my	O
ever	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
ye	O
.	O
Birds	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
,	O
proved	O
good	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
totally	O
meant	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
Miranda	B-pers
at	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
yrs	O
.	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Adieu	O
for	O
ye	O
.	O
present	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
I	O
will	O
write	O
you	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Tomorrow	O
Morning	O
.	O
To	O
tell	O
you	O
my	O
ever	O
dearest	O
Sr.	B-pers
George	I-pers
Mettam	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
,	O
honor	O
,	O
&	O
esteem	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
perfectly	O
aſsured	O
of	O
,	O
therefore	O
excuse	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
repeat	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
ever	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Miranda	B-pers
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
received	O
any	O
Paterns	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
forward	O
ym	O
..	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
receive	O
ym	O
..	O
for	O
yr	O
.	O
opinion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
we	O
are	O
besides	O
this	O
long	O
jaunt	O
to	O
W——r	B-place
to	O
paſs	O
ye	O
.	O
C——ſsChristmass	O
H——s	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
ye	O
happineſs	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
Palemon	B-pers
more	O
frequently	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
flattered	O
my	O
ſelf	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
you	O
hear	O
concerning	O
W——	B-place
You	O
have	O
not	O
of	O
late	O
signed	O
yrself	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Friend	O
,	O
&	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
ye	O
.	O
name	O
of	O
Brother	O
whh	O
..	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
do	O
again	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
dearest	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
.	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
wrote	O
ye	O
.	O
Postscript	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
Town	B-place
some	O
Paterns	O
of	O
some	O
cloaths	O
my	O
Taylor	O
says	O
they	O
are	O
ye	O
most	O
fashionable	O
wear	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
&	O
speaks	O
truth	O
,	O
pray	O
chuse	O
one	O
&	O
tell	O
me	O
truly	O
yr	O
..	O
ideas	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
Ad	O
.	O
ma	O
bien	O
aimée	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
