TOKEN	NE
17	O
Thursday	O
1	O
8	O
7	O
th	O
Aug	O
Sep	O
tr	O
Septr-	O
1779	O
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
Friend	O
,	O
Here	O
am	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
a	O
jaunt	O
which	O
wld	O
..	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
pleasant	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
may	O
add	O
very	O
chearful	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
had	O
ye	O
.	O
happineſs	O
of	O
enjoying	O
yr	O
.	O
Company	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
always	O
ye	O
.	O
greatest	O
comfort	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
can	O
enjoy	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
H——	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
M——	O
ye	O
.	O
owners	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
place	O
are	O
very	O
worthy	O
honest	O
,	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
mais	O
pas	O
des	O
plus	O
eclairés	O
,	O
ni	O
des	O
plus	O
agréables	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
L——y	B-pers
G——n	I-pers
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
ſhd	O
..	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
place	O
is	O
very	O
beautifully	O
situated	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
way	O
of	O
thinking	O
that	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
enjoyable	O
one	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
suitable	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
place	O
itself	O
.	O
On	O
M——	O
M——	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Ca——m	B-place
ye	O
.	O
place	O
is	O
beautiful	O
beyond	O
imagination	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
House	O
is	O
just	O
of	O
ye	O
same	O
sort	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
one	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
mentioned	O
,	O
L——y	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
looked	O
exceſsively	O
pretty	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
least	O
merit	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
all	O
yt	O
..	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
ought	O
be	O
,	O
perfectly	O
easy	O
,	O
civil	O
,	O
quiet	O
,	O
yet	O
very	O
lively	O
,	O
&	O
chearful	O
,	O
&	O
did	O
ye	O
.	O
honors	O
of	O
her	O
Houſe	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
properest	O
manner	O
poſsible	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
H——r	B-place
where	O
we	O
found	O
Ld	B-pers
...	I-pers
&	O
L——y	B-pers
B——n	I-pers
got	O
into	O
thr	O
.	O
new	O
Houſe	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
wch	O
..	O
was	O
decently	O
dull	O
--	O
So	O
far	O
for	O
my	O
Journal	O
,	O
now	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
most	O
agreable	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Letter	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
10	O
minutes	O
past	O
5	O
o	O
clock	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
resume	O
my	O
Pen	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
distreſsed	O
for	O
time	O
however	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
expreſsing	O
to	O
you	O
ye	O
.	O
sincerity	O
of	O
my	O
gratitude	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
proof	O
of	O
confidence	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
in	O
shewing	O
me	O
Ld	B-pers
..	I-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
s	O
.	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
H——r	I-pers
s	O
Letters	O
,	O
you	O
desir	O
e	O
my	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
&	O
Friend	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Napier	I-pers
,	I-pers
8th	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Napier	I-pers
character	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
open	O
honest	O
brave	O
,	O
&	O
rather	O
warm	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bit	O
too	O
much	O
upon	O
this	O
subject	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Man	O
as	O
I	O
shld	O
..	O
like	O
to	O
attach	O
to	O
my	O
ſelf	O
&	O
whom	O
I	O
hope	O
hereafter	O
to	O
have	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
late	O
my	O
Friend	O
this	O
Morning	O
&	O
I	O
must	O
dreſs	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
ye	O
.	O
next	O
Letter	O
ſhall	O
be	O
longer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
shame	O
upon	O
me	O
thanked	O
you	O
for	O
yr	O
.	O
pretty	O
Chain	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
admire	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
hurry	O
yrself	O
about	O
ye	O
.	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
still	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
carefully	O
treaſured	O
up	O
.	O
&	O
I	O
wld	O
..	O
not	O
begin	O
to	O
wear	O
ye	O
.	O
one	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
ready	O
to	O
supply	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
we	O
shall	O
meet	O
this	O
Evening	O
by	O
Lady	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Harpur	I-pers
going	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
every	O
thing	O
--	O
Adieu	O
eve	O
d	O
r	O
dearest	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
Sister	O
Friend	O
.	O
Yr	O
.	O
sincerely	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
L——	B-pers
N——	I-pers
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
.	O
