TOKEN	NE
6	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr-	O
1779	O
Satry	O
.	O
Afternoon	O
My	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
Excuse	O
my	O
not	O
sending	O
you	O
back	O
with	O
ye	O
note	O
a	O
long	O
Letter	O
wh	O
..	O
I	O
am	O
ſtill	O
writing	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
receive	O
it	O
T——w	O
M——g	O
with	O
ye	O
N——	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
line	O
on	O
ye	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
.	O
side	O
was	O
written	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
yr	O
.	O
amiable	O
&	O
dear	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
yt	O
Leter	O
between	O
M.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
M.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
before	O
I	O
quitted	O
W——	B-place
but	O
never	O
c.ld	O
.	O
find	O
out	O
into	O
whose	O
hands	O
it	O
had	O
fallen	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
was	O
ye	O
.	O
subject	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
inquired	O
about	O
it	O
from	O
many	O
persons	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
Pray	O
inform	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
power	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
me	O
too	O
i	O
m	O
pertinent	O
of	O
ye	O
Ladies	O
Names	O
mind	O
now	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
I	O
do	O
not	O
preſs	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
unleſs	O
you	O
can	O
with	O
ye	O
greatest	O
ease	O
to	O
yrself	O
.	O
Write	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
Answer	O
by	O
T——w	O
.	O
Excuse	O
ye	O
.	O
Shortneſs	O
&	O
hurry	O
of	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
Adieu	O
may	O
god	O
preserve	O
&	O
bleſs	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
Palemon	B-pers
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
P.S	O
.	O
6	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1779	O
recd-	O
