TOKEN	NE
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
by	O
recg	O
a	O
little	O
note	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
again	O
so	O
soon	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
better	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
feel	O
these	O
marks	O
of	O
attention	O
,	O
&	O
feel	O
more	O
real	O
gratitude	O
for	O
them	O
than	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
ostentatious	O
present	O
sent	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
indifferent	O
to	O
me	O
Wedy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
waiting	O
&	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
party	O
at	O
Cards	O
The	B-pers
K	I-pers
.	I-pers
Q	B-pers
:	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
Ly	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
at	O
one	O
Table	O
--	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Royal	I-pers
Pſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Augusta	I-pers
Lady	B-pers
C	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
&	O
myself	O
--	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
were	O
particularly	O
affectionate	O
&	O
attentive	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Thursday	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
Fk	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
old	O
days	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
I	O
saw	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
at	O
4	O
--	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
--	O
at	O
6	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Lord	B-pers
Stormont	I-pers
s	O
more	O
dead	O
than	O
alive	O
there	O
Lord	B-pers
S——	I-pers
not	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
only	O
my	O
Uncle	O
F	B-pers
:	I-pers
&	O
Cousin	O
Charlotte	B-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
:	I-pers
care	O
this	O
winter	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
S	I-pers
was	O
as	O
affte	O
&	O
friendly	O
as	O
poſsible	O
--	O
Friday	O
--	O
My	O
Uncle	O
again	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lyte	I-pers
came	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
mutually	O
glad	O
to	O
renew	O
their	O
former	O
acquaintance	O
--	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
½	O
past	O
12	O
I	O
was	O
something	O
better	O
&	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queens	O
House	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
whilst	O
my	O
hair	O
was	O
dreſsing	O
(	O
after	O
ye	O
Maids	O
of	O
Honor	O
s	O
dinner	O
)	O
Miſs	B-pers
Tryon	I-pers
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
--	O
or	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
called	O
by	O
her	O
friends	O
fatty	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
sat	O
with	O
me	O
--	O
The	O
former	O
has	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
good	O
&	O
amiable	O
qualities	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
rather	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
retailer	O
of	O
anecdotes	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
day	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
what	O
I	O
like	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
is	O
a	O
warm	O
generous	O
character	O
--	O
too	O
blunt	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
polite	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
ye	O
.	O
whole	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
waiting	O
this	O
Eveg	O
.	O
--	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
St.	B-place
J——	I-place
but	O
not	O
to	O
sleep	O
as	O
my	O
Cough	O
was	O
very	O
violent	O
--	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
recollection	O
that	O
that	O
night	O
last	O
year	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
watching	O
a	O
dying	O
Mother	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
fever	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
rejoiced	O
at	O
ye	O
.	O
return	O
of	O
Morng	O
&	O
gladly	O
quitted	O
my	O
bed	O
--	O
I	O
recd	O
.	O
your	O
welcome	O
affte	O
.	O
tender	O
note	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
careful	O
of	O
myself	O
I	O
know	O
ever	O
thing	O
I	O
write	O
will	O
be	O
sacred	O
--	O
only	O
be	O
careful	O
to	O
destroy	O
my	O
letters	O
