TOKEN	NE
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
additional	O
proof	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
kindneſs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
need	O
d	O
e	O
d	O
none	O
other	O
to	O
convince	O
me	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
affection	O
&	O
friendship	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
three	O
of	O
ye	O
Letters	O
from	O
yr	O
Friends	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
besides	O
ye	O
.	O
little	O
Note	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
G——g	I-pers
,	O
they	O
are	O
from	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
yr	O
.	O
Uncle	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
ye	O
.	O
latter	O
of	O
whom	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
excellent	O
heart	O
,	O
pray	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
next	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
ye	O
rich	O
Miss	B-pers
(	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
)	I-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
ye	O
.	O
young	O
Lady	O
you	O
was	O
once	O
speaking	O
of	O
in	O
London	B-place
yt	O
..	O
had	O
refused	O
more	O
than	O
twenty	O
offers	O
of	O
marriag	O
e	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
trifling	O
mark	O
of	O
attention	O
you	O
dwell	O
so	O
much	O
upon	O
of	O
my	O
making	O
Miſs	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
wait	O
upon	O
you	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
owe	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
My	O
P——	B-pers
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
wld	O
..	O
give	O
her	O
pleasure	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
well	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
entertained	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Morning	O
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
more	O
particularly	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
you	O
with	O
yr	O
.	O
Lettercase	O
ye	O
.	O
fore	O
going	O
ment	O
ioned	O
Letters	O
beside	O
ye	O
.	O
Little	O
Note	O
,	O
my	O
Lettercase	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
large	O
to	O
contain	O
ym	O
..	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
return	O
you	O
ye	O
.	O
others	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
ym	O
..	O
in	O
my	O
Lettercase	O
which	O
my	O
poor	O
Miranda	B-pers
gave	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
token	O
of	O
her	O
affection	O
before	O
she	O
married	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
keep	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
chuse	O
if	O
not	O
you	O
will	O
return	O
it	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
little	O
more	O
to	O
add	O
at	O
present	O
my	O
sweetest	O
Sister	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
hope	O
y	O
&	O
indeed	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
continue	O
yr	O
.	O
affection	O
to	O
me	O
thro'out	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
shall	O
be	O
unto	O
my	O
last	O
breath	O
,	O
My	O
dearest	O
Emily	B-pers
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
sincerely	O
affectionate	O
&	O
loving	O
Brother	O
Miranda	B-pers
toujours	O
de	O
meme	O
.	O
7	O
th	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
1779	O
Thursday	O
--	O
afternoon	O
