TOKEN	NE
21	O
st	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1779	O
The	O
affair	O
of	O
ye	O
Letter	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
fine	O
topic	O
for	O
the	O
rooms	O
&	O
teatables	O
at	O
——	B-place
&	O
no	O
little	O
addition	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
,	O
&	O
you	O
&	O
Miſs	B-pers
C——	I-pers
appear	O
together	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
in	O
verse	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
procure	O
you	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
this	O
production	O
--	O
“	O
Come	O
along	O
Sophia	B-pers
said	O
the	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
“	O
&	O
Sophia	B-pers
followed	O
willingly	O
'	O
&	O
a	O
Hunting	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
Adieu	O
for	O
ever	O
your	O
friend	O
&	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
really	O
mine	O
you	O
will	O
endulge	O
me	O
&	O
be	O
very	O
minutious	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
concerning	O
yourself	O
