TOKEN	NE
Thursday	O
Morng	O
.	O
Octbr	O
.	O
21	O
st	O
-	O
1779	O
My	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
,	O
Friend	O
You	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
last	O
as	O
to	O
expreſs	O
yt	O
.	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
ye	O
.	O
Weather	O
wld	O
..	O
be	O
favorable	O
for	O
us	O
on	O
S——y	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
&	O
ye	O
.	O
Sport	O
was	O
most	O
delightful	O
,	O
ye	O
.	O
Stag	O
after	O
having	O
gave	O
given	O
us	O
almost	O
ye	O
.	O
longest	O
Chace	O
ever	O
known	O
,	O
was	O
saved	O
At	O
a	O
moderate	O
computation	O
,	O
my	O
B——	O
&	O
myself	O
rode	O
,	O
(	O
what	O
with	O
riding	O
to	O
ye	O
spot	O
where	O
ye	O
Stag	O
was	O
first	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
spot	O
where	O
ye	O
.	O
Stag	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Billingbear	O
,	O
&	O
then	O
from	O
Billingbear	O
home	O
together	O
with	O
ye	O
Chace	O
itself	O
60	O
miles	O
.	O
If	O
my	O
Miranda	B-pers
had	O
rode	O
ye	O
.	O
chace	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
ſhd	O
..	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
mad	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
crazy	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
dearest	O
Sister	O
yr	O
.	O
health	O
continues	O
as	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
&	O
yt	O
.	O
you	O
feel	O
no	O
more	O
returns	O
of	O
yr	O
.	O
confounded	O
pain	O
in	O
yr	O
.	O
Side	O
.	O
Keep	O
up	O
yr	O
.	O
Spirits	O
also	O
dearest	O
Miranda	B-pers
according	O
to	O
yr	O
.	O
promise	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
let	O
me	O
as	O
we	O
shall	O
now	O
soon	O
meet	O
see	O
you	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
lively	O
,	O
giddy	O
,	O
wicked	O
,	O
severe	O
,	O
goodnatured	O
,	O
Satyrical	O
affectionate	O
Puſs	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
However	O
to	O
be	O
serious	O
let	O
me	O
oh	O
let	O
me	O
find	O
you	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
same	O
kind	O
sentiments	O
about	O
me	O
yt	O
.	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
never	O
let	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
be	O
supposed	O
poſsible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
forfeit	O
yr	O
.	O
esteem	O
friendship	O
,	O
&	O
affection	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
do	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
said	O
before	O
involuntarily	O
.	O
Adieu	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
dearest	O
,	O
Sister	O
,	O
Friend	O
Miranda	B-pers
,	O
&	O
pardon	O
not	O
only	O
ye	O
.	O
shortneſs	O
,	O
but	O
ye	O
bad	O
Style	O
of	O
this	O
Billet	O
,	O
consider	O
only	O
my	O
friend	O
yt	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
catch	O
here	O
&	O
there	O
a	O
moment	O
ever	O
since	O
my	O
arrival	O
&	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
hurry	O
myſelf	O
beyond	O
imagination	O
,	O
but	O
ye	O
.	O
first	O
opportunity	O
I	O
can	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
ſhall	O
have	O
a	O
longer	O
&	O
a	O
better	O
written	O
Letter	O
.	O
Adieu	O
,	O
Adieu	O
,	O
&	O
believe	O
Miranda	B-pers
&	O
believe	O
yt	O
.	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
one	O
upon	O
Earth	O
to	O
whom	O
you	O
are	O
dearer	O
than	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
Yr	O
.	O
ever	O
affectionate	O
Brother	O
--	O
Palemon	B-pers
toujours	O
de	O
même	O
P.S	O
.	O
Pray	O
inform	O
me	O
immediately	O
concerning	O
every	O
thing	O
you	O
hear	O
about	O
W——r	B-place
.	O
&	O
every	O
concerning	O
yr	O
dear	O
self	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
pray	O
inform	O
M——	B-pers
G——	I-pers
yt	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
So	O
Miss	B-pers
(	I-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
)	I-pers
Gunning	I-pers
&	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mrs	B-pers
..	I-pers
W——ingham	I-pers
--	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
she	O
is	O
acquainted	O
with	O
ye	O
latter	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
former	O
,	O
yt	O
.	O
made	O
me	O
name	O
ym	O
.	O
both	O
)	O
in	O
perfect	O
good	O
health	O
.	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
Adieu	O
toujours	O
chére	O
.	O
