TOKEN	NE
Norbury	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
July	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
bear	O
to	O
wait	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
till	O
next	O
Winter	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
entreat	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
pardon	O
for	O
my	O
apparent	O
neglect	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
kindneſs	O
during	O
the	O
laſt	O
month	O
of	O
my	O
stay	O
in	O
Town	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
She	O
knew	O
the	O
uneasineſs	O
which	O
dampt	O
all	O
my	O
pleaſure	O
even	O
in	O
the	O
charming	O
party	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
I	O
hope	O
when	O
she	O
hears	O
that	O
the	O
fatal	O
termination	O
of	O
that	O
suspence	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
wish	O
for	O
nothing	O
but	O
to	O
haſten	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
recruit	O
both	O
my	O
Health	O
&	O
Spirits	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
forgive	O
my	O
silence	O
,	O
omiſsions	O
,	O
&	O
various	O
misdemeanours	O
,	O
&	O
receive	O
next	O
Winter	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
wonted	O
good	O
humour	O
,	O
&	O
“	O
agreeable	O
smiles	O
,	O
”	O
her	O
obliged	O
humble	O
servant	O
F	B-pers
:	I-pers
Burney	I-pers
If	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
present	O
my	O
best	O
Respects	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
And	O
may	O
I	O
entreat	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
tell	O
both	O
Her	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
string	O
of	O
the	O
moſt	O
uncomfortable	O
circumstances	O
should	O
have	O
prevented	O
my	O
waiting	O
upon	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Town	O
?	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
July	O
1784	O
