TOKEN	NE
Berkley	O
Square	O
Dec	O
.	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
1789	O
.	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Some	O
time	O
ago	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
woodcocks	O
labelled	O
with	O
a	O
name	O
so	O
friendly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
you	O
for	O
so	O
kind	O
a	O
remembrance	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
look	O
very	O
gratefull	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
late	O
in	O
my	O
gratitude	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
&	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
till	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
&	O
neither	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
to	O
learn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
that	O
I	O
arrived	O
,	O
I	O
drove	O
to	O
Norfolk	O
street	O
--	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
removed	O
,	O
whither	O
was	O
not	O
known	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
beleived	O
at	O
Sunning	B-place
.	O
I	O
thence	O
went	O
to	O
melancholy	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
was	O
as	O
ignorant	O
;	O
but	O
yesterday	O
informed	O
me	O
I	O
shoud	O
find	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
in	O
Conduit	O
street	O
,	O
&	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
&	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
,	O
&	O
acquainted	O
me	O
that	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
but	O
is	O
quite	O
recovered	O
--	O
so	O
my	O
joy	O
is	O
pure	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
pleasure	O
,	O
the	O
hope	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
this	O
spring	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
with	O
your	O
sweet	O
little	O
girl	O
much	O
growing	O
&	O
improved	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
few	O
days	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
very	O
imperfect	O
accounts	O
of	O
our	O
Friends	O
,	O
The	O
poor	O
dear	O
Vesey	B-pers
is	O
quite	O
Childish	O
,	O
but	O
thence	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
unhappy	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
care	O
taken	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
we	O
coud	O
hope	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
comes	O
next	O
monday	O
;	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
is	O
at	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
but	O
not	O
coming	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
opposite	O
to	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
way	O
,	O
&	O
suffers	O
terribly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
beleive	O
disordered	O
,	O
as	O
reported	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bad	O
newsmonger	O
,	O
&	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
entertain	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
tire	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
sole	O
reason	O
for	O
writing	O
was	O
to	O
thank	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
to	O
seize	O
that	O
opportunity	O
of	O
aſsuring	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
yr	O
much	O
obliged	O
&	O
most	O
sincere	O
humble	O
Sert	O
HWalpole	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
.	O
