TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
21	O
Septr-	O
1786	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
must	O
appear	O
both	O
unkind	O
and	O
uncivil	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
long	O
without	O
acknowledging	O
your	O
very	O
kind	O
and	O
obliging	O
Letter	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
the	O
case	O
--	O
Coud	O
I	O
write	O
for	O
my	O
Self	O
I	O
shoud	O
more	O
frequently	O
send	O
you	O
testimonies	O
of	O
my	O
rememberance	O
and	O
affection	O
but	O
my	O
Secratary	O
having	O
many	O
occupations	O
to	O
call	O
Her	O
away	O
from	O
that	O
office	O
and	O
several	O
inquiring	O
Freinds	O
to	O
satisfy	O
makes	O
it	O
impoſsible	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
regular	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
in	O
my	O
answers	O
--	O
--	O
my	O
Niece	O
I	O
thank	O
god	O
has	O
now	O
quite	O
recoverd	O
the	O
Langour	O
that	O
she	O
Sufferd	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Measles	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
so	O
much	O
time	O
to	O
recover	O
with	O
Her	O
Masters	O
--	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
break	O
in	O
upon	O
--	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
writing	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
improves	O
very	O
much	O
and	O
begs	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
Her	O
particular	O
Compts	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
--	O
the	O
amiable	O
and	O
worthy	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
is	O
Establish	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
Her	O
satisfaction	O
much	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
Every	O
body	O
--	O
Especially	O
by	O
those	O
she	O
wishes	O
most	O
to	O
Please	O
--	O
I	O
certainly	O
am	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
Her	O
being	O
Placed	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
--	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seing	O
Her	O
often	O
tho	O
'	O
Her	O
Visits	O
are	O
generally	O
short	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
so	O
many	O
absent	O
Freinds	O
to	O
consider	O
that	O
all	O
Her	O
Spare	O
time	O
is	O
scarsly	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfy	O
their	O
different	O
demands	O
--	O
never	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
better	O
Calculated	O
for	O
the	O
Post	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
as	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
confinement	O
is	O
disagreeable	O
to	O
Her	O
This	O
moment	O
my	O
girl	O
is	O
steped	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Chaise	O
to	O
call	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
who	O
is	O
to	O
Chaperon	O
Her	O
to	O
Maidenhead	B-place
Races	O
which	O
began	O
yesterday	O
--	O
it	O
is	O
reported	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
without	O
foundation	O
that	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
(	O
Mr	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
s	O
Daughter	O
)	O
by	O
His	O
first	O
Wife	O
)	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
who	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
and	O
has	O
shown	O
a	O
steady	O
attachment	O
to	O
Her	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
fortune	O
is	O
sensible	O
and	O
agreeable	O
--	O
and	O
His	O
circumstances	O
I	O
suppose	O
are	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
Her	O
Friends	O
--	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
is	O
anxious	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
my	O
shatter	O
'd	O
frame	O
goes	O
on	O
I	O
feel	O
that	O
decline	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
Expected	O
many	O
years	O
ago	O
--	O
but	O
much	O
I	O
owe	O
to	O
Provedence	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
and	O
Comforts	O
I	O
dayly	O
Experience	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
recovering	O
from	O
a	O
Langour	O
that	O
often	O
Seizes	O
me	O
and	O
warns	O
me	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
--	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
I	O
ventured	O
to	O
Early	O
Prayers	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
my	O
chair	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
do	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
my	O
best	O
Health	O
--	O
after	O
Prayers	O
were	O
over	O
and	O
Collnl	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
had	O
with	O
their	O
usual	O
Condescen	O
sion	O
taken	O
notise	O
of	O
those	O
they	O
Paſsd	O
by	O
--	O
Queen	B-pers
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
is	O
my	O
Dear	O
Her	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
well	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
to	O
which	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
I	O
with	O
Pleasure	O
and	O
gratitude	O
Consented	O
to	O
--	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
Breakfasted	O
with	O
the	O
bright	O
Constellation	O
composd	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
and	O
5	O
Princeſses	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
depart	O
in	O
their	O
Coaches	O
for	O
Kew	O
the	O
Coronation	O
Day	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Kept	O
on	O
Friday	O
and	O
the	O
return	O
again	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
when	O
the	O
day	O
returns	O
--	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
flag	O
--	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
on	O
the	O
round	O
tower	O
Windsor	B-place
is	O
dismal	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
their	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
is	O
much	O
recoverd	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
being	O
quite	O
well	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
Cautious	O
and	O
dont	O
suffer	O
Her	O
to	O
use	O
any	O
great	O
Exersise	O
--	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
Amiable	O
and	O
I	O
some	O
times	O
spend	O
an	O
evening	O
with	O
Her	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
Lodge	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
shoked	O
by	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Eliz	I-pers
'	I-pers
which	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
unexpected	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
Ill	O
but	O
one	O
hour	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
--	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
loſs	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
she	O
was	O
Connected	O
with	O
Particularly	O
to	O
my	O
good	O
and	O
never	O
failing	O
Friend	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
--	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
had	O
accounts	O
from	O
my	O
nephews	O
of	O
their	O
agreeable	O
Freinds	O
Mr	B-pers
F	I-pers
Montagu	I-pers
&	O
Mr	B-pers
always	O
happy	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
enjoying	O
their	O
Conversation	O
s	O
no	O
wonder	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
is	O
universally	O
Lamented	O
--	O
the	B-pers
Marchioneſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
Graham	I-pers
was	O
one	O
day	O
last	O
week	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
Son	O
--	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
giving	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
dear	O
Lady	B-pers
St	I-pers
Asaph	I-pers
to	O
Congratulate	O
Her	O
--	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
last	O
Post	O
from	O
Badminton	B-place
from	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
were	O
she	O
is	O
happy	O
with	O
9	O
grandchildren	O
about	O
Her	O
besids	O
Sons	O
and	O
Daughters	O
when	O
I	O
write	O
I	O
will	O
obey	O
your	O
Commands	O
--	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
hear	O
Constantly	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
and	O
have	O
better	O
information	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
And	O
I	O
fear	O
my	O
much	O
respected	O
Friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Cremone	I-pers
is	O
in	O
a	O
declining	O
state	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
His	O
intelects	O
--	O
but	O
suffering	O
great	O
Ruins	O
from	O
Rheumatism	O
and	O
Sleepleſs	O
Nights	O
--	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
coud	O
fill	O
a	O
Page	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
I	O
as	O
able	O
as	O
willing	O
--	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
can	O
dictate	O
no	O
longer	O
--	O
but	O
what	O
Ever	O
Feelings	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
of	O
--	O
nothing	O
will	O
diminish	O
the	O
Esteem	O
and	O
affection	O
and	O
warm	O
wishes	O
of	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
and	O
Obligd	O
Lord	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
I	O
am	O
much	O
flatterd	O
with	O
MDelany	B-pers
s	O
Partiallity	O
Pray	O
make	O
my	O
very	O
Particular	O
Compts	O
to	O
Him	O
--	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
mutual	O
Happineſs	O
will	O
always	O
give	O
me	O
Pleasure	O
we	O
will	O
settle	O
about	O
the	O
Catalogue	O
when	O
we	O
Meet	O
Septr	O
.	O
1786	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
