TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
sincerely	O
boast	O
of	O
an	O
amendment	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
Dear	O
agreable	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
commands	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
sooner	O
obey	O
'd	O
--	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
flattering	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
neglect	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
poor	O
Languid	O
mortal	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
smelling	O
to	O
my	O
bottle	O
of	O
salts	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
charming	O
Locket	O
;	O
recollected	O
the	O
honours	O
my	O
heart	O
most	O
gratefully	O
feels	O
and	O
also	O
abounds	O
with	O
every	O
warm	O
wish	O
for	O
the	O
Health	O
&	O
true	O
felicity	O
of	O
yr	O
Royal	O
Mistreſs	O
so	O
amiable	O
!	O
that	O
tis	O
impoſsible	O
not	O
to	O
Love	O
her	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
Enviable	O
creature	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
worthy	O
of	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
it	O
)	O
envy	O
you	O
but	O
wish	O
you	O
many	O
years	O
enjoyment	O
of	O
that	O
&	O
every	O
Earthly	O
Felicity	O
Affectly	O
.	O
Yrs	O
MDelany	B-pers
The	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
cold	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
makes	O
me	O
better	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
5	O
th	O
Janry	O
.	O
1781	O
