TOKEN	NE
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
London	B-place
as	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
there	O
--	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
--	O
the	O
Weather	O
is	O
so	O
hot	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
send	O
my	O
usual	O
meſsenger	O
to	O
you	O
--	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
suppose	O
that	O
has	O
hinderd	O
your	O
tripping	O
over	O
here	O
--	O
Let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
&	O
believe	O
me	O
faithfully	O
yours	O
&	O
.	O
c	O
MDelany	B-pers
Was	O
you	O
flirting	O
at	O
the	B-pers
P——	I-pers
of	I-pers
W——	I-pers
s	O
Breakfast	O
--	O
?	O
Were	O
you	O
hopping	O
at	O
Mrs.	B-pers
C——	I-pers
s	O
Ball	O
--	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
says	O
you	O
will	O
Leave	O
me	O
no	O
room	O
to	O
say	O
anything	O
--	O
well	O
then	O
have	O
patience	O
&	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
done	O
--	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Comps-	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
is	O
gone	O
--	O
over	O
the	O
hills	O
&	O
far	O
away	O
P.S	O
.	O
will	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
evening	O
--	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
s	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
W——	I-pers
s	O
tomorrow	O
if	O
Able	O
my	O
Dr	O
.	O
Madam	O
tis	O
an	O
age	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
--	O
my	O
Aunt	O
pines	O
after	O
you	O
--	O
she	O
has	O
dictated	O
this	O
note	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
by	O
bits	O
&	O
scraps	O
this	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
riddle	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
read	O
Uncle	O
s	O
letter	O
pray	O
send	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
Dr	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
yours	O
GMAPort	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Stree	O
t	O
