TOKEN	NE
2	O
4	O
3	O
th	O
d	O
July	O
1782	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
London	B-place
It	O
is	O
an	O
age	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
or	O
even	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
——	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
gratify	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
pleasure	O
in	O
seeing	O
you	O
is	O
much	O
encreased	O
by	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
enquiring	O
after	O
those	O
whose	O
health	O
and	O
Happineſs	O
we	O
so	O
well	O
know	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
--	O
our	O
Dear	O
amiable	O
Dſs	B-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
is	O
now	O
deeply	O
engaged	O
with	O
Apollo	O
and	O
Neptune	O
at	O
margate	B-place
;	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
cool	O
breezes	O
of	O
one	O
will	O
soften	O
the	O
fiery	O
Beams	O
of	O
ye	O
other	O
;	O
How	O
hot	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
fervent	O
hope	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
long	O
sejour	O
at	O
margate	B-place
will	O
establish	O
the	O
Health	O
of	O
the	O
Dearest	O
and	O
most	O
Valuable	O
of	O
Friends	O
could	O
make	O
support	O
the	O
suffocations	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
busyneſs	O
detains	O
me	O
.	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
spent	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
at	O
her	O
rural	O
Villa	O
,	O
has	O
greatly	O
reviv	O
'd	O
me	O
tho	O
you	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
in	O
Town	B-place
to	O
Day	O
or	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
flatter	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
yr	O
flying	O
visit	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
woud	O
be	O
a	O
ray	O
of	O
Light	O
that	O
would	O
greatly	O
enliven	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
oblige	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
most	O
affecte	O
&	O
Faithful	O
MDelany	B-pers
I	O
hope	O
to	O
spend	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
next	O
week	O
with	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
I	O
had	O
Pleasant	O
Visitor	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
,	O
Doctr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warton	I-pers
of	O
Winchester	B-place
,	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
resided	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
instead	O
of	O
Winchester	B-place
that	O
I	O
might	O
enjoy	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
s	O
pri	O
ghtly	O
&	O
Edifying	O
conversation	O
.	O
