TOKEN	NE
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
June	O
1781	O
I	O
must	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
enquire	O
after	O
your	O
health	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
preccious	O
for	O
yr	O
Friends	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
interested	O
about	O
it	O
--	O
you	O
see	O
where	O
I	O
place	O
myself	O
and	O
expect	O
your	O
indulgence	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
fillip	O
to	O
the	O
Spirits	O
is	O
one	O
means	O
of	O
restoring	O
health	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
is	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Margate	B-place
entirely	O
to	O
my	O
Satisfaction	O
Then	O
judge	O
how	O
well	O
she	O
is	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
lonely	O
hours	O
in	O
her	O
absence	O
--	O
&	O
my	O
little	O
enlivener	O
gone	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
mortified	O
by	O
a	O
dissapointment	O
in	O
an	O
entertainment	O
I	O
was	O
given	O
encouragement	O
to	O
hope	O
for	O
;	O
no	O
leſs	O
than	O
the	O
Publication	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
s	O
tours	O
with	O
the	O
Drawings	O
;	O
both	O
so	O
excellent	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
:	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
Public	O
from	O
the	O
check	O
of	O
Prudence	O
wch	O
.	O
will	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
hazard	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
expence	O
I	O
think	O
diffidence	O
and	O
modesty	O
has	O
some	O
share	O
in	O
his	O
reluctance	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
steal	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
influence	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mischievous	O
banks	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Tables	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
bestow	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
work	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
do	O
Honour	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
worthy	O
and	O
ingenious	O
author	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
He	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
.	O
forgive	O
this	O
Lamentation	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
ar	O
e	O
too	O
favourable	O
to	O
Rational	O
entertainments	O
&	O
pleasu	O
res	O
that	O
enlarge	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
depreſsing	O
the	O
understand	O
ing	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
forgive	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
my	O
regret	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
to	O
quit	O
my	O
little	O
nitch	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
repairs	O
make	O
it	O
neceſsary	O
)	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
never	O
failin	O
g	O
aſsylum	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
her	O
Grace	O
proposes	O
maki	O
ng	O
her	O
visit	O
to	O
Weymouth	B-place
before	O
she	O
settles	O
at	O
Bulstrod	O
e	O
I	O
shall	O
then	O
bewail	O
my	O
Widdow	O
-hood	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
ho	O
use	O
or	O
at	O
Bill	O
Hill	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
comfortable	O
accounts	O
from	O
Lisbon	B-place
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
pleasure	O
to	O
communicate	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
know	O
without	O
my	O
repeating	O
them	O
how	O
constantly	O
and	O
ardently	O
my	O
wishes	O
hover	O
yo	O
u	O
and	O
your	O
illustrious	O
mansion	O
being	O
with	O
true	O
esteem	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
Your	O
most	O
Affectionate	O
and	O
most	O
Obliged	O
humble	O
Sert	O
MDelany	B-pers
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
D	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
desires	O
me	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
affectionate	O
compliments	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
dim	O
day	O
with	O
my	O
Eyes	O
