TOKEN	NE
My	O
veriest	O
dear	O
Madam	O
I	O
shall	O
like	O
Saturday	O
just	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
was	O
disengaged	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
but	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
posthumous	O
Engagement	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
.	O
Ly	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
pleaded	O
my	O
doubtfull	O
promise	O
for	O
wednesday	O
or	O
saturday	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
proved	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
I	O
woud	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
certainly	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
on	O
my	O
Way	O
to	O
Ham	B-place
,	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
head	O
as	O
sound	O
as	O
the	O
Inside	O
--	O
whether	O
his	O
heart	O
is	O
as	O
whole	O
,	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
best	O
knows	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
whole	O
Trio	O
's	O
most	O
devoted	O
HW	B-pers
.	O
Honble	B-pers
.	I-pers
Horace	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
July	O
1788	O
