TOKEN	NE
Windsor	B-place
May	O
29	O
th	O
1786	O
how	O
much	O
am	O
I	O
obligd	O
to	O
my	O
Dear	O
and	O
kind	O
Friends	O
for	O
their	O
mutual	O
Letter	O
and	O
most	O
flattering	O
Proposal	O
of	O
making	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
at	O
Windsor	B-place
any	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
16.	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
mortification	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
avail	O
my	O
self	O
of	O
it	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
obligd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
for	O
some	O
Days	O
the	O
time	O
not	O
yet	O
fix	O
'd	O
--	O
and	O
the	O
remaining	O
Part	O
of	O
June	O
is	O
already	O
ingaged	O
to	O
my	O
old	O
and	O
Worthy	O
Friends	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
in	O
succeſsion	O
if	O
my	O
Health	O
and	O
spirits	O
will	O
allow	O
of	O
my	O
enjoying	O
so	O
much	O
Comfort	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
spare	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
and	O
indeed	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
Present	O
in	O
to	O
low	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
spiri	O
ts	O
to	O
admit	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
will	O
contain	O
--	O
but	O
is	O
deferd	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
intirely	O
lost	O
--	O
but	O
that	O
some	O
lucky	O
opportunity	O
may	O
make	O
amen	O
for	O
this	O
unavoidable	O
delay	O
Mr	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
who	O
is	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Present	O
and	O
with	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
May	O
1785	O
Desires	O
His	O
best	O
Compts	O
.	O
He	O
leaves	O
me	O
to	O
morrow	O
and	O
looks	O
forward	O
with	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
June	O
after	O
which	O
Day	O
He	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Honour	O
and	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Wellsbourn	O
any	O
t	O
after	O
that	O
Day	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
Convenient	O
to	O
them	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Compts	O
&	O
best	O
wishes	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
for	O
her	O
kind	O
attentio	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
rememberance	O
of	O
so	O
worthy	O
a	O
Person	O
is	O
truly	O
Valuable	O
and	O
I	O
sincerly	O
Pitty	O
Her	O
for	O
the	O
Loſs	O
she	O
will	O
soon	O
hav	O
of	O
your	O
Company	O
--	O
Every	O
wish	O
for	O
yours	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
s	O
Health	O
and	O
Happineſs	O
Sincerly	O
attend	O
you	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
from	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
MDelany	B-pers
