TOKEN	NE
I	O
return	O
you	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
your	O
kind	O
and	O
comfortable	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
sufficiently	O
to	O
thank	O
my	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
to	O
admire	O
her	O
generous	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
feelings	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
one	O
could	O
only	O
expect	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
engroſs	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
she	O
does	O
me	O
but	O
Justice	O
in	O
believing	O
that	O
I	O
most	O
truly	O
Sympathised	O
in	O
her	O
affliction	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
apprehensive	O
for	O
her	O
health	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
written	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
Letter	O
addrest	O
to	O
herself	O
would	O
be	O
only	O
troublesome	O
and	O
afflicting	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
yours	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
comfort	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
who	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
admirably	O
our	O
excellent	O
friend	O
preserv	O
'd	O
her	O
sweet	O
and	O
patient	O
resignation	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
greatneſs	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
and	O
the	O
strength	O
of	O
her	O
principles	O
.	O
but	O
still	O
I	O
fear	O
for	O
her	O
Mortal	O
frame	O
.	O
a	O
selfish	O
fear	O
!	O
of	O
what	O
perhaps	O
constitutes	O
her	O
greatest	O
consolation	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
Town	B-place
who	O
must	O
be	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
support	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
much	O
fear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
wishes	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
gladly	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
have	O
tried	O
to	O
supply	O
her	O
place	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
flatter	O
'd	O
myself	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
acceptable	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
more	O
precious	O
Comforters	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
immediately	O
upon	O
your	O
Marriage	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
offer	O
'd	O
you	O
my	O
Sincere	O
congratulations	O
.	O
alas	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
now	O
add	O
condolence	O
to	O
them	O
!	O
your	O
loſs	O
is	O
indeed	O
a	O
general	O
Concern	O
--	O
but	O
heavy	O
indeed	O
must	O
it	O
be	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
enjoy	O
'd	O
so	O
high	O
a	O
place	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
friendship	O
of	O
the	O
excellent	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
!	O
--	O
how	O
unspeakably	O
great	O
to	O
her	O
first	O
Friend	O
!	O
May	O
God	O
Almighty	O
support	O
and	O
comfort	O
her	O
!	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
is	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
where	O
does	O
she	O
mean	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
the	O
honor	O
you	O
did	O
me	O
in	O
calling	O
at	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
always	O
happy	O
to	O
cultivate	O
your	O
acquaintance	O
and	O
kindneſs	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
and	O
Congratulations	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
expreſs	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
affectionate	O
wishes	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
to	O
my	O
dear	O
good	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
with	O
the	O
truest	O
Gratitude	O
for	O
her	O
kind	O
remembrance	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Burrowses	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
&	O
famy	O
all	O
desire	O
to	O
offer	O
their	O
kindest	O
Condolence	O
and	O
are	O
most	O
truly	O
touch	O
'd	O
and	O
interested	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Amy	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
was	O
withheld	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
from	O
writing	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
by	O
the	O
feat	O
of	O
disturbing	O
and	O
troubling	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
tender	O
heart	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
suffer	O
'd	O
like	O
deprivations	O
,	O
feels	O
sincerely	O
for	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
with	O
repeated	O
th	O
your	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
and	O
obedient	O
Servant	O
Hester	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
July	O
24	O
th	O
.	O
1785	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
thanks	O
and	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
poor	O
dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
(	O
the	O
late	O
accounts	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
V	I-pers
.	I-pers
's	O
will	O
fill	O
me	O
with	O
indignation	O
and	O
Concern	O
,	O
and	O
disappointed	O
me	O
the	O
more	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
account	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
2	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
Piccadilly	O
London	B-place
