TOKEN	NE
Bulstrode	O
Dem	O
23	O
.	O
1784	O
Happy	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
the	O
kind	O
rememberances	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
--	O
made	O
doubly	O
precious	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
being	O
united	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
and	O
inestimable	O
Friend	O
--	O
MD	B-pers
must	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
Her	O
Self	O
--	O
most	O
sensibly	O
have	O
I	O
miſsed	O
my	O
amiable	O
morning	O
Companion	O
.	O
my	O
works	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
slow	O
and	O
Sad	O
--	O
till	O
the	O
inlivening	O
Hour	O
of	O
a	O
Summons	O
to	O
the	O
Drawing	O
room	O
--	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
check	O
from	O
the	O
sympathising	O
Lamentations	O
at	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
Croſs	O
stitch	O
--	O
and	O
the	O
Table	O
of	O
dilligence	O
:	O
where	O
is	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
Her	O
Manuscripts	O
?	O
says	O
our	O
Dear	O
Dutcheſs	O
--	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
Exaltation	O
says	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
!	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
shift	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
regret	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
hope	O
and	O
Console	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
wednesday	O
the	O
29	O
or	O
rather	O
the	O
30	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
incapable	O
of	O
failing	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
ingagements	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
depend	O
upon	O
your	O
Eating	O
Beef	O
Stakes	O
according	O
to	O
promise	O
--	O
but	O
shoud	O
you	O
not	O
recolect	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
Freind	O
which	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
Him	O
will	O
not	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Danger	O
of	O
His	O
having	O
left	O
London	B-place
before	O
that	O
time	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
say	O
more	O
.	O
but	O
not	O
able	O
.	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
embarreſs	O
you	O
with	O
uneſsary	O
Compliments	O
and	O
wishes	O
to	O
those	O
Friends	O
--	O
who	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
remember	O
me	O
knowing	O
you	O
Lose	O
no	O
oppertunity	O
of	O
doing	O
Justice	O
to	O
your	O
Ever	O
obligd	O
and	O
affectionate	O
MDelany	B-pers
P.S	O
!	O
alas	O
I	O
am	O
reduced	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Cloak	O
my	O
self	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
bear	O
in	O
mind	O
that	O
kind	O
attention	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
at	O
XXX	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sorry	O
for	O
Mr	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
if	O
you	O
send	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
Him	O
--	O
be	O
so	O
generous	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Particular	O
inquiry	O
for	O
me	O
My	O
Dear	O
Freind	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
ask	O
if	O
your	O
Journals	O
are	O
worth	O
paying	O
for	O
to	O
me	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
infinite	O
Value	O
continue	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
beseech	O
you	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
Bustle	O
about	O
the	O
Tables	O
Mr	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
thought	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
exalt	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
case	O
his	O
best	O
respects	O
good	O
wishes	O
aſsure	O
Mr	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
my	O
b	O
est	O
Compts	O
that	O
Health	O
&	O
Happineſs	O
m	O
ay	O
attend	O
you	O
&	O
the	O
Hi	O
m	O
you	O
love	O
our	O
dear	O
Freind	O
very	O
well	O
MCPortland	B-pers
Written	O
by	O
the	O
Dear	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
Dowr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Dſs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dr.	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
Decbr-	O
84	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Clarges	O
Street	O
