TOKEN	NE
I	O
trust	O
I	O
shall	O
see	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
to	O
morrow	O
Evening	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
to	O
write	O
--	O
To	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
wth	O
a	O
Spinning	O
Wheel	O
go	O
Happy	O
Wheel	O
!	O
amuse	O
Her	O
leisure	O
Hour	O
Whose	O
Grace	O
&	O
Affability	O
refin	O
'd	O
Add	O
Lustre	O
to	O
Her	O
Dignity	O
&	O
Power	O
And	O
fill	O
with	O
Love	O
,	O
&	O
Awe	O
,	O
the	O
Grateful	O
Mind	O
.	O
26	O
th	O
.	O
Janry	O
.	O
1782	O
London	B-place
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
