TOKEN	NE
Welsbourn	O
Jany	O
18	O
1784	O
.	O
Without	O
meaning	O
any	O
Disrespect	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
has	O
followd	O
his	B-pers
Majesties	I-pers
Example	O
&	O
changed	O
her	O
Secretary	O
,	O
however	O
my	O
Vanity	O
may	O
suffer	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
purchase	O
ye	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
receiving	O
ye	O
new	O
Minister	O
s	O
Dispatches	O
,	O
at	O
ye	O
Expence	O
of	O
having	O
my	O
own	O
looked	O
into	O
wth	O
a	O
very	O
penetrating	O
Eye	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
disposed	O
to	O
defend	O
a	O
little	O
Inconsistency	O
(	O
wch	O
as	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
remains	O
of	O
Youth	O
I	O
am	O
half	O
unwilling	O
to	O
explain	O
away	O
)	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
difficult	O
Task	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
May	O
you	O
long	O
continue	O
to	O
consider	O
a	O
Cold	O
as	O
a	O
serious	O
Distemper	O
,	O
&	O
never	O
be	O
taught	O
by	O
a	O
woful	O
Experience	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
off	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
Nothing	O
worse	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
no	O
worse	O
for	O
your	O
second	O
Charge	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Taste	O
of	O
ye	O
Hurries	O
of	O
a	O
Warwickshire	B-place
Xmas	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
then	O
be	O
convinced	O
yt	O
ye	O
Life	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
lead	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
yt	O
wch	O
I	O
lead	O
in	O
London	B-place
is	O
Tranquility	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
As	O
to	O
your	O
last	O
Instance	O
of	O
Inconsistency	O
you	O
will	O
allow	O
when	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
ye	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
you	O
are	O
reading	O
ye	O
Letter	O
,	O
that	O
ye	O
Mind	O
does	O
not	O
always	O
grow	O
old	O
wth	O
ye	O
Body	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
old	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
insensible	O
to	O
ye	O
Beauties	O
of	O
ye	O
Country	O
&	O
ye	O
Approach	O
of	O
Spring	O
I	O
shall	O
care	O
very	O
little	O
what	O
becomes	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Inconsistencies	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
say	O
if	O
I	O
presume	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
entirely	O
free	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
meant	O
to	O
alarm	O
&	O
keep	O
me	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
criticise	O
in	O
a	O
leſs	O
agreeable	O
Manner	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
hardly	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
ye	O
Criticism	O
or	O
cease	O
to	O
wish	O
meet	O
ye	O
Critic	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
am	O
unwilling	O
to	O
frighten	O
you	O
at	O
your	O
first	O
Entrance	O
on	O
your	O
Office	O
wth	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Busineſs	O
,	O
&	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
ye	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
so	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
trouble	O
you	O
long	O
on	O
her	O
Account	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
only	O
say	O
how	O
happy	O
we	O
all	O
are	O
that	O
she	O
continues	O
so	O
well	O
thro	O
'	O
so	O
severe	O
a	O
Winter	O
&	O
how	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Aſsurance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
expect	O
my	O
Neice	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
shall	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
&	O
look	O
forward	O
wth	O
ye	O
greatest	O
Pleasure	O
in	O
ye	O
Hope	O
of	O
dining	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
on	O
Fryday	O
;	O
yt	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
ye	O
Trouble	O
of	O
taking	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
engaged	O
one	O
at	O
No	O
20	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
my	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
wch	O
will	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
.	O
All	O
our	O
Circle	O
are	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
ye	O
dreadful	O
Colds	O
are	O
almost	O
gone	O
,	O
all	O
join	O
in	O
best	O
Love	O
&	O
Duty	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Brother	O
Bernard	B-pers
begs	O
to	O
offer	O
his	O
Respects	O
to	O
yourself	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
go	O
on	O
much	O
farther	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
inconsistent	O
I	O
should	O
complain	O
of	O
Hurry	O
&	O
teize	O
you	O
with	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
In	O
fact	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
forget	O
myself	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
conversing	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
other	O
Calls	O
will	O
be	O
heard	O
&	O
allow	O
me	O
only	O
Time	O
to	O
add	O
yt	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
great	O
Truth	O
Madam	O
Your	O
much	O
obliged	O
&	O
obedient	O
humble	O
Servant	O
Court	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
.	O
Dewes	B-pers
Portland	B-pers
Delany	B-pers
--	O
Port	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
send	O
you	O
my	O
letter	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
night	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
hardly	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
.	O
--	O
