TOKEN	NE
I	O
was	O
Freeting	O
--	O
and	O
fuming	O
--	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
Put	O
off	O
our	O
Party	O
to	O
Harwood	B-place
this	O
fine	O
Cool	O
Morning	O
--	O
when	O
your	O
Meſsage	O
came	O
to	O
quiet	O
my	O
Spirits	O
and	O
reconsile	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
disappointment	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
Sir	B-pers
Willm	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
come	O
to	O
Town	B-place
--	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
perfect	O
&	O
Health	O
and	O
Spirits	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
Happy	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
both	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
bestow	O
that	O
Pleasure	O
on	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
and	O
obligd	O
MD	B-pers
P	O
s	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
flying	O
moment	O
of	O
you	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
St	O
James	O
Place	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
Delany	B-pers
17	O
Augst	O
--	O
84	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
