TOKEN	NE
St	O
Albans	O
St	O
Windsor	B-place
Jany	O
10	O
--	O
1786	O
Tho	O
I	O
addreſs	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
must	O
begin	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
best	O
acknowledgements	O
to	O
Her	O
amiable	O
Husband	O
and	O
return	O
you	O
dear	O
Sir	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
and	O
welcome	O
account	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
our	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
s	O
Health	O
of	O
the	O
Comfortable	O
araingment	O
of	O
your	O
affairs	O
which	O
now	O
do	O
not	O
oblige	O
you	O
to	O
separate	O
long	O
may	O
you	O
both	O
enjoy	O
a	O
union	O
that	O
Promises	O
so	O
much	O
Happineſs	O
My	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
woud	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
delayd	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
that	O
she	O
coud	O
have	O
written	O
Her	O
self	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
are	O
so	O
anxious	O
about	O
the	O
R——y	O
Family	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
Postpone	O
relieving	O
it	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
Princeſs	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
is	O
still	O
in	O
a	O
Mending	O
way	O
--	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
Please	O
god	O
to	O
Preserve	O
Her	O
from	O
a	O
relaps	O
Her	O
Dr	O
Sir	B-pers
george	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
makes	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
Her	O
recovery	O
tho	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
slow	O
Her	O
Dear	O
and	O
Excellent	O
Parents	O
have	O
sufferd	O
greatly	O
on	O
Her	O
account	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Lodge	O
last	O
night	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
good	O
spirits	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Princeſses	O
are	O
much	O
better	O
their	O
Hooping	O
cough	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
decline	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
very	O
favourable	O
and	O
Prince	B-pers
Agustus	I-pers
is	O
better	O
this	O
complaint	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
is	O
Bowels	O
--	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
sad	O
XmaſsChristmaſs	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
merry	O
one	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
new	O
year	O
will	O
make	O
amends	O
--	O
my	O
own	O
Health	O
is	O
very	O
tolerable	O
--	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
removing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
Royal	O
Neighbours	O
do	O
--	O
my	O
Poor	O
House	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
now	O
deprived	O
of	O
what	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
so	O
Happy	O
in	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
gloomy	O
Prospect	O
to	O
me	O
--	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
I	O
thank	O
god	O
is	O
much	O
better	O
Her	O
great	O
dejection	O
of	O
Spirits	O
has	O
ended	O
in	O
a	O
rash	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
establish	O
Her	O
Health	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
indulgent	O
as	O
to	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
Mary	B-pers
and	O
she	O
has	O
many	O
kind	O
Freinds	O
here	O
who	O
plead	O
for	O
her	O
returning	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
best	O
Compts	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
and	O
shall	O
rejoyce	O
to	O
receive	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Her	O
being	O
restored	O
to	O
that	O
Health	O
and	O
tranquillity	O
she	O
so	O
well	O
deserves	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
greatly	O
contribute	O
to	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
great	O
concern	O
of	O
this	O
time	O
for	O
Poor	O
Lady	B-pers
Brudenel	I-pers
whose	O
death	O
I	O
expect	O
every	O
Post	O
.	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
feeling	O
for	O
the	O
sufferings	O
of	O
Her	O
Friends	O
for	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Loss	O
I	O
Expect	O
Lady	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
in	O
Town	B-place
next	O
week	O
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Bute	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Boscawen	I-pers
have	O
been	O
settled	O
some	O
time	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
hear	O
Mr	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
has	O
been	O
confind	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
gout	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
uneasy	O
for	O
Mrs	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
and	O
her	O
Family	O
the	O
last	O
account	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Montagu	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
of	O
Mrs	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
s	O
being	O
Past	O
all	O
hopes	O
of	O
recovery	O
and	O
while	O
He	O
can	O
give	O
any	O
consolation	O
to	O
His	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
Expect	O
to	O
see	O
Him	O
in	O
Town	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
staid	O
with	O
me	O
3	O
week	O
s	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
last	O
Thursday	O
it	O
is	O
impoſsible	O
not	O
to	O
miſs	O
the	O
Loſs	O
of	O
so	O
sensible	O
and	O
amiable	O
a	O
Companion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
two	O
days	O
visit	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
John	I-pers
Sandford	I-pers
the	O
Sailor	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
were	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
our	O
Friends	O
in	O
Clarges	O
street	O
much	O
as	O
usual	O
those	O
of	O
Welsbourn	O
lament	O
your	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
fullfill	O
your	O
Promise	O
--	O
mr	B-pers
B	I-pers
Dews	I-pers
and	O
mr	B-pers
and	O
mrs	B-pers
granvill	I-pers
and	O
Their	O
Children	O
have	O
their	O
spent	O
their	O
XmaſsChristmaſs	O
there	O
--	O
I	O
am	O
ashamed	O
of	O
this	O
dul	O
Long	O
epistle	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
better	O
for	O
your	O
sake	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
some	O
merit	O
if	O
it	O
Conveys	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
to	O
do	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
and	O
obligd	O
--	O
MDelany	B-pers
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
s	O
best	O
Compts	O
and	O
Many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
your	O
Letter	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
sad	O
for	O
your	O
Friends	O
in	O
London	B-place
if	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
return	O
to	O
Taxel	B-place
The	O
oeconomy	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
here	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
when	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
fair	O
I	O
air	O
for	O
two	O
Hours	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
admit	O
old	O
Freind	O
and	O
aquaintance	O
--	O
the	O
new	O
ones	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
civil	O
meſsages	O
--	O
my	O
afternoons	O
are	O
entirely	O
devoted	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
benefactors	O
--	O
To	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Ser	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Bart	O
Courteenhall	B-place
Northampton	B-place
