TOKEN	NE
Novbr	O
.	O
29	O
th	O
.	O
1780	O
I	O
understood	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
that	O
you	O
intended	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
The	O
Locket	O
yesterday	O
but	O
as	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
happen	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
mistook	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
do	O
knowing	O
in	O
whose	O
hands	O
I	O
trust	O
the	O
precious	O
deposite	O
--	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
at	O
12	O
this	O
morning	O
suppose	O
it	O
can	O
hardly	O
be	O
return	O
'd	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
has	O
got	O
a	O
bad	O
cold	O
,	O
she	O
proposes	O
nursing	O
it	O
away	O
at	O
Bulstrode	O
which	O
I	O
wish	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
you	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
indulgence	O
to	O
excuse	O
my	O
not	O
sending	O
the	O
Paper	O
the	O
Dſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
fulneſs	O
of	O
Grateful	O
spirits	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
seen	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
Grace	O
--	O
(	O
so	O
sad	O
to	O
tell	O
!	O
)	O
she	O
betrayed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
struck	O
with	O
the	O
apprehension	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
appear	O
too	O
Presumptuous	O
and	O
impertinent	O
:	O
as	O
yu	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
Propriety	O
of	O
suppreſsing	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
flatter	O
my	O
self	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
your	O
most	O
obliged	O
&	O
Obedt	O
:	O
MDelany	B-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
