TOKEN	NE
how	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Anxiety	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
mine	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
yourself	O
had	O
cured	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
;	O
certainly	O
recovering	O
I	O
trust	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
rewarded	O
by	O
enjoying	O
her	O
again	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
will	O
dread	O
London	B-place
,	O
after	O
being	O
received	O
by	O
such	O
alarms	O
about	O
her	O
&	O
yr	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
remains	O
quite	O
well	O
,	O
&	O
that	O
she	O
&	O
you	O
may	O
live	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
's	O
age	O
&	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
beloved	O
.	O
yrs	O
most	O
&	O
c	O
HWalpole	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
