TOKEN	NE
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
Wednesday	O
18	O
th	O
.	O
April	O
1781	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
your	O
obliging	O
request	O
of	O
hearing	O
from	O
you	O
me	O
is	O
too	O
agreable	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
complied	O
with	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
double	O
pleasure	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dowr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
's	O
inveterate	O
Cough	O
is	O
much	O
abated	O
and	O
last	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
in	O
seeing	O
her	O
here	O
better	O
than	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
;	O
The	O
softneſs	O
and	O
cheerfulneſs	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
weather	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
contribute	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
quite	O
well	O
:	O
what	O
need	O
I	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
health	O
?	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
Barometer	O
--	O
&	O
yesterday	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
courage	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sr.	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
Lever	I-pers
s	O
and	O
Sr.	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
&	O
not	O
too	O
much	O
fatigued	O
.	O
how	O
,	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
pity	O
us	O
poor	O
Londoners	O
?	O
Well	O
you	O
may	O
,	O
who	O
enjoy	O
such	O
superiour	O
pleasures	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
truly	O
envy	O
you	O
were	O
I	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
you	O
&	O
so	O
sincerely	O
My	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamns	I-pers
.	I-pers
affectionate	O
&	O
most	O
Obliged	O
hum	O
ble	O
Sert	O
MDelany	B-pers
My	O
little	O
Girl	O
is	O
in	O
raptures	O
with	O
yr	O
.	O
kind	O
notice	O
&	O
I	O
no	O
leſs	O
flatter	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Chapone	I-pers
dines	O
wth	O
me	O
to	O
day	O
yr	O
cheeks	O
must	O
glow	O
.	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
