TOKEN	NE
circumstance	O
Alluding	O
to	O
an	O
anecdote	O
wch	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
used	O
to	O
relate	O
with	O
great	O
humor	O
--	O
or	O
when	O
Mrs.	B-pers
D	I-pers
she	O
was	O
very	O
young	O
&	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
parents	O
Mother	O
lived	O
in	O
Gloucesteshire	B-place
,	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
a	O
gentlemans	O
house	O
in	O
ye	O
.	O
Neighbourhood	O
wch	O
her	O
Mother	O
allowed	O
her	O
to	O
accept	O
--	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
company	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
smartly	O
dreſsed	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
the	O
road	O
was	O
too	O
bad	O
for	O
a	O
Carriage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
mounted	O
on	O
a	O
Pillion	O
behind	O
a	O
steady	O
old	O
Domestic	O
.	O
--	O
on	O
their	O
way	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Hounds	O
Miſs	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
was	O
enchanted	O
--	O
the	O
mettle	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
roused	O
&	O
old	O
John	B-pers
was	O
easily	O
prevaild	O
on	O
to	O
join	O
ye	O
chace	O
--	O
the	O
consequence	O
was	O
the	O
Lutestring	O
slip	O
was	O
rent	O
in	O
many	O
places	O
,	O
the	O
smart	O
shoes	O
lost	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
Hat	O
streamers	O
blown	O
over	O
the	O
Hills	O
&	O
far	O
away	O
.	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
after	O
joy	O
comes	O
sorrow	O
,	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
dinner	O
waiting	O
--	O
&	O
dreaded	O
returning	O
home	O
in	O
her	O
tattered	O
Garments	O
--	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
reproved	O
her	O
severely	O
&	O
This	O
unfortunate	O
Chace	O
cost	O
many	O
penitential	O
tears	O
