TOKEN	NE
I	O
fear	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
my	O
succeeding	O
in	O
the	O
request	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
to	O
you	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
as	O
yr	O
time	O
is	O
always	O
so	O
fully	O
&	O
so	O
happily	O
employ	O
'd	O
.	O
but	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lucky	O
moment	O
you	O
cou	O
'd	O
spare	O
me	O
any	O
time	O
tomorrow	O
Evening	O
and	O
cou	O
'd	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	B-place
again	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
it	O
woud	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
opportunity	O
I	O
so	O
much	O
wish	O
for	O
,	O
of	O
seeing	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamn	I-pers
:	I-pers
and	O
acknowleging	O
more	O
partic	O
l	O
u	O
larly	O
how	O
sensible	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
her	O
goodneſs	O
and	O
of	O
telling	O
her	O
how	O
Happy	O
I	O
was	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
--	O
I	O
wish	O
more	O
particularly	O
for	O
tomorrow	O
Evening	O
as	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
is	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
by	O
,	O
--	O
her	O
Affectte	O
&	O
most	O
obligd	O
MDelany	B-pers
just	O
going	O
to	O
Windsor	B-place
Sunday	O
Morning	O
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Palace	O
