TOKEN	NE
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
March	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
1787	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
does	O
me	O
great	O
injury	O
if	O
she	O
thinks	O
negligence	O
has	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Silence	O
she	O
Complains	O
of	O
.	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
thank	O
god	O
much	O
better	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
Expect	O
.	O
yet	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
exert	O
my	O
self	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
this	O
late	O
Illneſs	O
.	O
and	O
have	O
waited	O
till	O
I	O
coud	O
aſsure	O
you	O
with	O
truth	O
of	O
my	O
amendment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
dictate	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dewes	I-pers
since	O
He	O
left	O
London	B-place
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
--	O
you	O
make	O
me	O
very	O
happy	O
with	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
dear	O
and	O
agreeable	O
Freinds	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
--	O
to	O
all	O
whom	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
Justice	O
--	O
next	O
Monday	O
Mr	B-pers
B	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
carriys	O
away	O
My	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
Girl	I-pers
to	O
Welsbourn	O
to	O
meet	O
Her	O
Mamma	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
began	O
a	O
course	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
air	O
More	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
does	O
not	O
yet	O
do	O
with	O
Me	O
I	O
Languish	O
after	O
Windsor	B-place
and	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
better	O
there	O
--	O
in	O
all	O
Places	O
believe	O
me	O
trully	O
Grateful	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
for	O
your	O
kind	O
Solicitude	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Most	O
sincerly	O
wish	O
you	O
many	O
years	O
of	O
Happineſs	O
--	O
and	O
that	O
yo	O
Dear	O
Child	O
will	O
dayly	O
increase	O
that	O
Happineſs	O
--	O
being	O
most	O
sincerly	O
your	O
affectionate	O
Freind	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
Humb	O
MD	B-pers
My	O
Head	O
is	O
now	O
so	O
giddy	O
with	O
dictating	O
that	O
I	O
coud	O
not	O
sign	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
Mr	B-pers
B	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
beg	O
their	O
best	O
Comp	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
self	O
when	O
you	O
return	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
--	O
