TOKEN	NE
Bulstrode	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
10	O
th	O
.	O
Decbr	O
1780	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
last	O
in	O
St	O
J	O
Place	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
unlikely	O
that	O
Bulstrode	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
Honour	O
'd	O
by	O
Royal	O
Visit	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portd	I-pers
.	I-pers
is	O
very	O
much	O
indispos	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
cold	O
and	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
and	O
Chamber	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
tho	O
her	O
cold	O
oppreſses	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
her	O
submitting	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
care	O
,	O
Slops	O
,	O
and	O
warm	O
nursing	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
prove	O
as	O
Efficacious	O
as	O
our	O
good	O
Friend	O
Dr	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
's	O
advice	O
tho	O
that	O
I	O
esteem	O
excellent	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
believe	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
I	O
shall	O
be	O
an	O
attentive	O
deputy	O
,	O
feeling	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
of	I-pers
P	I-pers
:	I-pers
has	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
Ly	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weyth	I-pers
.	I-pers
or	O
Ly	B-pers
Stamfd	I-pers
her	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
hopes	O
her	O
cold	O
will	O
soon	O
grow	O
better	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
uneasyneſs	O
of	O
knowing	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
you	O
will	O
soon	O
perceive	O
why	O
I	O
write	O
all	O
this	O
--	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
wish	O
the	O
Honr	O
you	O
mention	O
'd	O
may	O
not	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
have	O
been	O
intended	O
as	O
that	O
wou	O
'd	O
leſsen	O
the	O
great	O
mortification	O
of	O
being	O
oblig	O
ed	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
Wise	O
wch	O
may	O
check	O
an	O
Honour	O
and	O
Happineſs	O
so	O
highly	O
Valued	O
by	O
The	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
Dr	I-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
;	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
name	O
my	O
own	O
sensibility	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
entre	O
nous	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
ye	B-pers
Dſs	I-pers
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
night	O
and	O
Lyes	O
quiet	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
if	O
her	O
cold	O
mends	O
enoh	O
for	O
her	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
Town	B-place
as	O
she	O
proposes	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
great	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
next	O
week	O
in	O
S	O
t	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Place	O
--	O
in	O
every	O
place	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
s	O
most	O
Obliged	O
&	O
most	O
Faithful	O
hum	O
ble	O
Sert	O
MDelany	B-pers
To	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
at	O
The	O
Queens	O
Lodge	O
Windsor	B-place
10	O
th	O
Decbr	O
:	O
1780	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
