TOKEN	NE
Tuesday	O
3	O
o'clock	O
If	O
Mr	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
does	O
not	O
apply	O
very	O
improperly	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
perhaps	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
&	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
sorry	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
will	O
she	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
,	O
&	O
when	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
leave	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
but	O
this	O
moment	O
come	O
to	O
town	B-place
,	O
&	O
therefore	O
hopes	O
to	O
be	O
pardoned	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
in	O
giving	O
this	O
trouble	O
.	O
Honble	B-pers
H	I-pers
Walpole	I-pers
June	O
7	O
th	O
1785	O
