TOKEN	NE
St	O
James	O
Place	O
Monday	O
Morn——	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
s	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamelton	I-pers
and	O
Desires	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
does	O
--	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Company	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
her	O
Company	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
--	O
she	O
will	O
call	O
Her	O
in	O
the	O
Duchess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
s	O
Coach	O
--	O
at	O
what	O
Hour	O
she	O
thinks	O
Proper	O
--	O
and	O
Desires	O
she	O
will	O
let	O
Her	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
Bearer	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamelton	I-pers
