TOKEN	NE
Strawberry	O
hill	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
1785	O
.	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
By	O
a	O
postscript	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
received	O
from	O
DMr	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
,	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
the	O
Ducheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
is	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
at	O
Ditton	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
thought	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
--	O
Still	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
comes	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
,	O
&	O
as	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
alarmed	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
indeed	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
so	O
much	O
altered	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
too	O
true	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
therefore	O
for	O
troubling	O
you	O
with	O
inquiring	O
about	O
poor	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
It	O
woud	O
be	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
town	B-place
on	O
thursday	O
,	O
but	O
Madame	B-pers
de	I-pers
Genlis	I-pers
has	O
invited	O
herself	O
hither	O
on	O
friday	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
miſsing	O
you	O
,	O
&	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
our	O
poor	O
Friend	O
over	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
French	O
account	O
of	O
poor	O
Louisa	B-pers
advertised	O
--	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
anything	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Pray	O
forgive	O
all	O
this	O
trouble	O
--	O
but	O
whom	O
does	O
one	O
tease	O
but	O
good	O
hearts	O
!	O
The	O
Bad	O
neither	O
encourage	O
nor	O
indulge	O
one	O
--	O
but	O
will	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
not	O
think	O
me	O
impertinent	O
?	O
yet	O
I	O
am	O
yr	O
most	O
devoted	O
HorWalpole	B-pers
Honble	O
H	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
July	O
19	O
:	O
1785	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
in	O
Clarges	O
street	O
ISLEWORTH	B-place
