TOKEN	NE
Bulstrode	O
July	O
11	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
Dearest	O
Sally	B-pers
will	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
a	O
Line	O
of	O
intelligence	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
her	O
Friends	O
do	O
at	O
Bulstrode	O
--	O
I	O
thank	O
god	O
there	O
is	O
as	O
Much	O
amendment	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
wish	O
'd	O
for	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
time	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
--	O
and	O
those	O
you	O
Love	O
and	O
Pray	O
tell	O
my	O
Godson	O
if	O
still	O
in	O
London	B-place
--	O
I	O
wish	O
He	O
woud	O
call	O
on	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
to	O
let	O
Her	O
know	O
the	O
Purport	O
of	O
this	O
Note	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
Her	O
My	O
spirits	O
have	O
not	O
recoverd	O
their	O
agetation	O
of	O
last	O
Friday	O
--	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
am	O
tolerably	O
well	O
and	O
Astley	B-pers
a	O
good	O
Deal	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
tranquillity	O
of	O
this	O
Place	O
will	O
make	O
us	O
all	O
well	O
--	O
believe	O
me	O
Ever	O
most	O
affectionately	O
yours	O
MD	B-pers
I	O
wish	O
I	O
coud	O
send	O
you	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
sweet	O
Air	O
ind	O
Comps	O
to	O
Lady	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
Argyle	O
Street	O
M	O
rs	O
S	O
S	O
M	O
rs	O
Da	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Bulstrode	O
july	O
11	O
