TOKEN	NE
T	O
M	O
onday	O
night	O
--	O
my	O
Dear	O
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
as	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
dont	O
go	O
to	O
White	B-place
Hall	I-place
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
--	O
can	O
you	O
bestow	O
an	O
Hour	O
upon	O
me	O
--	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
Come	O
by	O
a	O
Eleven	O
o	O
Clock	O
--	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
Bearer	O
--	O
and	O
the	O
Dutcheſs	B-pers
of	I-pers
Pld	I-pers
Coach	O
will	O
call	O
for	O
you	O
about	O
that	O
Hour	O
--	O
yours	O
affectionate	O
ly	O
