TOKEN	NE
Strawberry	O
hill	O
July	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
1785	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
begs	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
Thursday	O
or	O
Friday	O
next	O
will	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
to	O
dine	O
at	O
Strawberry	O
hill	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
hopes	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
too	O
&	O
the	B-pers
two	I-pers
Miſses	I-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
begs	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
to	O
ask	O
,	O
&	O
he	O
will	O
send	O
to	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
knows	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
fears	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
ask	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
yet	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
shoud	O
be	O
most	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
Her	O
&	O
Mrs	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
;	O
but	O
he	O
woud	O
not	O
propose	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
quite	O
right	O
.	O
P.S	O
He	O
directs	O
to	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
lest	O
the	O
Postman	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
wedding	O
,	O
shoud	O
mistake	O
M	O
r	O
.	O
Walpole	O
,	O
J	O
uly	O
1st	O
1785	O
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
at	O
Miſs	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Clarges	O
Street	O
[	B-place
IS	I-place
]	I-place
LEWORTH	I-place
