TOKEN	NE
St	O
Albans	O
Street	O
Windsor	B-place
October	O
16	O
--	O
1785	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
recieved	O
frequent	O
accounts	O
of	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
her	O
amiable	O
Husband	O
from	O
these	O
Friends	O
she	O
made	O
Happy	O
at	O
Calwich	B-place
and	O
Ilam	B-place
I	O
shoud	O
not	O
have	O
spared	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
without	O
a	O
more	O
Particular	O
inquiry	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
how	O
much	O
your	O
time	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
answering	O
the	O
numberleſs	O
inquiries	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
Friends	O
--	O
amongest	O
them	O
none	O
more	O
sincere	O
in	O
their	O
wishes	O
for	O
your	O
Happineſs	O
then	O
my	O
self	O
--	O
therefore	O
as	O
my	O
intelligence	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
as	O
frequent	O
now	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
--	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
goodneſs	O
to	O
indulge	O
me	O
when	O
at	O
Leisure	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
self	O
and	O
your	O
proceedings	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
so	O
pleasant	O
a	O
prospect	O
of	O
your	O
present	O
situation	O
that	O
the	O
resolution	O
of	O
it	O
often	O
proves	O
a	O
Cordial	O
my	O
Health	O
is	O
fluctuating	O
bitter	O
Prongs	O
of	O
grief	O
will	O
over	O
Cloud	O
the	O
many	O
Honours	O
and	O
comforts	O
that	O
are	O
Dayly	O
bestowed	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
trust	O
that	O
time	O
will	O
make	O
me	O
leſs	O
selfish	O
and	O
enable	O
me	O
to	O
rejoyce	O
rather	O
than	O
Moan	O
for	O
the	O
Exchange	O
my	O
unparalleld	O
Freind	O
has	O
made	O
--	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Honour	O
of	O
seeing	O
my	O
Royal	O
Neighbours	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
week	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Expectations	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
--	O
but	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
and	O
sometimes	O
the	B-pers
Egertons	I-pers
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
only	O
my	O
old	O
aquaintance	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
air	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
when	O
the	O
weather	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
delightfully	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Commodous	O
and	O
the	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
st	O
James	O
Place	O
sinks	O
my	O
spirits	O
and	O
I	O
shoud	O
not	O
have	O
Courage	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
sad	O
Home	O
--	O
were	O
it	O
not	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
very	O
choise	O
Freinds	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
attach	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
warmest	O
gratitude	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Port	I-pers
says	O
pray	O
my	O
love	O
and	O
respects	O
to	O
mr	B-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
she	O
is	O
I	O
thank	O
god	O
well	O
and	O
happy	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Honourd	O
with	O
very	O
kind	O
notice	O
her	O
head	O
is	O
not	O
turnd	O
--	O
Miſs	B-pers
Goldsworthy	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Planta	I-pers
have	O
often	O
inquird	O
after	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
no	O
one	O
beside	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
--	O
adieu	O
my	O
Dear	O
Friend	O
believe	O
me	O
unalterably	O
yours	O
affectionately	O
P	O
S	O
Pray	O
make	O
my	O
best	O
Compliments	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Mrs	B-pers
Waslingham	I-pers
and	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
have	O
calld	O
upon	O
me	O
presi	O
very	O
Preſsing	O
that	O
I	O
shoud	O
Make	O
Her	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
Thames	B-place
ditton	I-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
Promisd	O
if	O
able	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
Her	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
London	O
home	O
which	O
I	O
hope	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
till	O
after	O
xmaſsChristmaſs	O
--	O
I	O
expect	O
Mr	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
here	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
--	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
amiable	O
Miſs	B-pers
Burney	I-pers
--	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
has	O
mentiond	O
a	O
Desire	O
of	O
Her	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
thinks	O
it	O
woud	O
give	O
me	O
Pleasure	O
--	O
this	O
Letter	O
was	O
written	O
yesterday	O
This	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Early	O
Prayers	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
chapel	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
5	O
time	O
--	O
this	O
Evening	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
again	O
appointed	O
by	O
their	O
Majesties	O
this	O
Morning	O
so	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
dear	O
Friend	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
reject	O
the	O
Honours	O
and	O
Bleſsings	O
that	O
are	O
offerd	O
--	O
me	O
notwithstan	O
ding	O
the	O
sad	O
sorrow	O
fasend	O
at	O
my	O
Heart	O
--	O
and	O
now	O
adieu	O
--	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
little	O
garden	O
to	O
day	O
just	O
after	O
church	O
--	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
my	O
no	O
small	O
surprise	O
in	O
a	O
instant	O
surrounded	O
by	O
their	O
Majesties	O
&	O
Princeſses	O
and	O
3	O
attendants	O
--	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
fortified	O
by	O
their	O
dayly	O
I	O
may	O
almost	O
say	O
severly	O
benedictions	O
and	O
indulgences	O
I	O
shoud	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
overpowerd	O
by	O
the	O
Eclat	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Ilustrious	O
appearance	O
Mrs	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
Oct	O
:	O
16	O
th	O
1785	O
