TOKEN	NE
6	O
all	O
that	O
family	O
were	O
made	O
happy	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
With	O
an	O
account	O
from	O
Geneva	B-place
to	O
say	O
that	O
Madm-	B-pers
Sadalin	I-pers
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
cd	O
.	O
be	O
expected	O
&	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Little	O
Boy	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
must	O
say	O
Adieu	O
having	O
only	O
time	O
to	O
aſsure	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
most	O
Obliged	O
&	O
affet	O
Hle	O
Sert	O
GMA	B-pers
Port	I-pers
--	O
Lady	B-pers
Louisa	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
&	O
c	O
--	O
all	O
,	O
join	O
in	O
kind	O
Comt	O
&	O
good	O
wishes	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
let	O
my	O
neice	O
s	O
Letter	O
go	O
without	O
adding	O
my	O
particular	O
acknowledgements	O
for	O
your	O
most	O
kind	O
Letter	O
my	O
Dear	O
Madrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
&	O
am	O
truly	O
grateful	O
for	O
your	O
constant	O
remembrance	O
of	O
me	O
--	O
I	O
rejoice	O
for	O
your	O
happineſs	O
at	O
home	O
--	O
the	O
merit	O
of	O
all	O
party	O
's	O
I	O
trust	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
Lasting	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
interuption	O
it	O
has	O
met	O
with	O
by	O
your	O
good	O
&	O
excellen	O
t	O
friend	O
Lady	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
s	O
Late	O
Loſs	O
--	O
I	O
pi	O
ty	O
your	O
amiable	O
&	O
Dear	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
it	O
is	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
roguish	O
miners	O
to	O
Deal	O
with	O
--	O
without	O
being	O
mortified	O
by	O
your	O
absence	O
.	O
especialy	O
on	O
so	O
meloncholy	O
an	O
occasion	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
enjoy	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
a	O
comforter	O
to	O
so	O
worthy	O
a	O
Freind	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
good	O
my	O
Dear	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
in	O
explaining	O
that	O
strange	O
unaccountable	O
Letter	O
--	O
I	O
have	O
menti	O
oned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Dewes	I-pers
&	O
he	O
says	O
if	O
yo	O
u	O
remain	O
quiet	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
consequence	O
--	O
Adieu	O
ever	O
affect-	O
yours	O
--	O
MDelany	B-pers
