TOKEN	NE
Miſs	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
is	O
commanded	O
by	O
ye	B-pers
.	I-pers
King	I-pers
to	O
tell	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
that	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
sends	O
his	O
best	O
Compts	O
:	O
to	O
her	O
&	O
hopes	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
Gerrards	B-place
Croſs	I-place
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Stag	O
turnd	O
out	O
Queens	O
House	O
9	O
th	O
.	O
Novbr	O
.	O
1781	O
