TOKEN	NE
Strawberry	O
hill	O
aug	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
1790	O
.	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
's	O
present	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
thousand	O
thanks	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
especially	O
as	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
his	O
remembrance	O
&	O
friendship	O
.	O
The	O
Birds	O
arrived	O
perfectly	O
sweet	O
,	O
&	O
to	O
me	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
novelty	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
saw	O
growse-pouts	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
beautifull	O
new-invented	O
sort	O
of	O
Partridge	O
,	O
&	O
wished	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
life	O
again	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
eat	O
them	O
.	O
Your	O
letter	O
is	O
still	O
kinder	O
,	O
&	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
gratitude	O
&	O
return	O
of	O
attachment	O
can	O
poſsibly	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
unworthy	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
such	O
good	O
reasons	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
not	O
hope	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
soon	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
even	O
forced	O
to	O
approve	O
your	O
reasons	O
,	O
but	O
and	O
to	O
admire	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Indeed	O
when	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
act	O
with	O
sense	O
&	O
propriety	O
?	O
&	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
so	O
excellent	O
a	O
choice	O
,	O
can	O
a	O
true	O
friend	O
wish	O
you	O
to	O
deviate	O
from	O
the	O
line	O
of	O
conduct	O
that	O
so	O
much	O
becomes	O
you	O
?	O
&	O
which	O
may	O
interfere	O
with	O
some	O
kind	O
sentiments	O
but	O
does	O
justly	O
contribute	O
to	O
your	O
solid	O
happineſs	O
--	O
I	O
will	O
rest	O
on	O
that	O
thought	O
,	O
&	O
only	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
live	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
when	O
your	O
Duty	O
&	O
convenience	O
may	O
fall	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Were	O
I	O
of	O
a	O
travelling	O
age	O
how	O
gladly	O
shoud	O
I	O
accept	O
your	O
most	O
obliging	O
proposal	O
of	O
making	O
you	O
a	O
visit	O
!	O
&	O
kiſsing	O
your	O
pretty	O
Louisa	B-pers
!	O
--	O
but	O
my	O
clock	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
stroke	O
of	O
74	O
--	O
&	O
after	O
so	O
many	O
years	O
of	O
gout	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
I	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
content	O
&	O
thank	O
god	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
creep	O
about	O
my	O
own	O
small	O
garden	O
--	O
coud	O
I	O
call	O
on	O
you	O
&	O
Mr	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
it	O
woud	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Buxton	B-place
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
beleive	O
there	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
map	O
of	O
Medicine	O
a	O
fountain	O
so	O
salutory	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
temperance	O
&	O
regimen	O
,	O
and	O
cold	O
system	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
preserved	O
my	O
paper	O
frame	O
to	O
this	O
extended	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certainly	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
&	O
tho	O
I	O
have	O
frequent	O
parentheses	O
of	O
gout	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
only	O
short	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
without	O
pain	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
worst	O
hurt	O
they	O
do	O
me	O
is	O
to	O
confine	O
me	O
--	O
&	O
That	O
now	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
Evil	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
I	O
woud	O
not	O
be	O
cured	O
of	O
my	O
gout	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
coud	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
dance	O
like	O
Lord	B-pers
Barrymore	I-pers
with	O
Delpini	B-pers
--	O
nay	O
,	O
I	O
shoud	O
probably	O
have	O
some	O
other	O
Illneſs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shoud	O
not	O
Understand	O
so	O
well	O
how	O
to	O
manage	O
--	O
&	O
besides	O
old	O
people	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
complaint	O
,	O
are	O
mighty	O
apt	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
if	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
years	O
have	O
not	O
lamed	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
remained	O
at	O
a	O
stand	O
&	O
are	O
still	O
twenty	O
--	O
mercy	O
on	O
us	O
!	O
do	O
but	O
think	O
what	O
follies	O
are	O
committed	O
by	O
ancient	O
gentry	O
that	O
fancy	O
themselves	O
young	O
!	O
--	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
talked	O
too	O
many	O
lines	O
on	O
myself	O
,	O
&	O
will	O
now	O
answer	O
your	O
questions	O
.	O
Poor	O
dear	O
Mrs	B-pers
Vesey	I-pers
is	O
exactly	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
of	O
childhood	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
&	O
certainly	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
leſs	O
so	O
.	O
One	O
can	O
only	O
wish	O
now	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
restored	O
to	O
happineſs	O
thro	O
the	O
only	O
door	O
by	O
which	O
She	O
can	O
paſs	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
which	O
her	O
blameleſs	O
benevolent	O
life	O
makes	O
us	O
presume	O
She	O
will	O
enjoy	O
.	O
Mrs	B-pers
Garrick	I-pers
I	O
beleive	O
is	O
still	O
at	O
Bristol	B-place
,	O
whither	O
She	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
single	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
Miſs	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
friend	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
So	O
is	O
She	O
herself	O
,	O
&	O
tormenting	O
herself	O
,	O
more	O
to	O
mend	O
her	O
spotleſs	O
Soul	O
than	O
her	O
Constitution	O
--	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
nostrums	O
indeed	O
is	O
an	O
excellent	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
always	O
labouring	O
to	O
do	O
good	O
to	O
others	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
called	O
a	O
fortune	O
of	O
five	O
thousand	O
a	O
yr	O
.	O
is	O
really	O
Miſtreſs	O
of	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
half	O
is	O
contested	O
by	O
Lord	B-pers
Shannon	I-pers
by	O
some	O
informality	O
in	O
the	O
poor	O
Brother	O
's	O
Will	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
Mrs	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
's	O
presuming	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
title	O
to	O
it	O
without	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
both	O
causes	O
aſsigned	O
&	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
true	O
.	O
Miſs	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
is	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
her	O
Release	O
&	O
laughs	O
&	O
talks	O
&	O
gallops	O
&	O
drives	O
&	O
dances	O
from	O
night	O
to	O
morning	O
&	O
from	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
isle	O
tother	O
--	O
yet	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
moment	O
of	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
life	O
never	O
relaxed	O
one	O
moment	O
in	O
attention	O
;	O
&	O
since	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
torrent	O
of	O
spirits	O
has	O
done	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
blamed	O
,	O
&	O
behaves	O
with	O
great	O
regard	O
&	O
propriety	O
to	O
all	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
old	O
friends	O
.	O
Both	O
her	O
real	O
&	O
nominal	O
fortune	O
have	O
a	O
cohort	O
of	O
Suitors	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
no	O
preference	O
She	O
Shows	O
;	O
&	O
as	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
sense	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
advice	O
,	O
to	O
admit	O
no	O
female	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
who	O
woud	O
soon	O
recommend	O
a	O
Male	O
)	O
I	O
hope	O
She	O
will	O
not	O
fling	O
,	O
away	O
herself	O
&	O
her	O
liberty	O
&	O
felicity	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Sex	O
,	O
without	O
knowing	O
whether	O
he	O
deserves	O
her	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
rare	O
Clan	O
,	O
the	O
Dickensons	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
fortune-hunters	O
.	O
Our	O
early	O
post	O
allows	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
tho	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
happy	O
to	O
seize	O
this	O
moment	O
of	O
conversing	O
with	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
sincere	O
&	O
cordial	O
regard	O
and	O
esteem	O
my	O
dearst	O
.	O
Madam	O
yr	O
most	O
obliged	O
&	O
devoted	O
humble	O
Sert	O
HorWalpole	B-pers
To	O
Mrs	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
at	O
Taxal	B-place
Chapel	B-place
le	I-place
Frith	I-place
Derbyshire	B-place
