TOKEN	NE
2	O
Fishes	O
.	O
2a	O
-1484	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
sharks	O
jaw	O
from	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
Guinea	B-place
.	O
241	O
f	O
-1485	O
.	O
A	O
wholes	O
eye	O
from	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Craycoot	I-pers
.	I-pers
m.	O
7	O
-1486	O
.	O
Bones	O
from	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
fishes	O
small	O
.	O
P.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1487	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
larger	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1488	O
.	O
Dentes	O
raiæ	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1489	O
.	O
Lapides	O
e	O
capite	O
carpionum	O
.	O
L.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1490	O
.	O
Ova	O
piscium	O
petrefacta	O
.	O
mark	O
'd	O
382	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1491	O
.	O
The	O
sword	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
fish	O
,	O
rough	O
rounder	O
&	O
brown	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
-1492	O
.	O
22	O
w	O
A	O
small	O
dog	O
fish	O
,	O
from	O
D	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Massy	I-pers
.	I-pers
in	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
n.	O
7	O
-1493	O
.	O
1.	O
polypus	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
serpens	O
marinus	O
or	O
tenia	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Edgcomb	I-pers
from	O
near	O
Plymmouth	B-place
in	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
n	O
7	O
.	O
-1494	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
weaver	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Lumpus	O
?	O
w	O
t.	O
its	O
eggs	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
monstrous	O
Batata	O
resembling	O
a	O
human	O
body	O
.	O
in	O
Sp	O
V	O
n.	O
7	O
-1495.	O
cheple	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
round	O
bones	O
between	O
the	O
Vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
239	O
-1496.	O
chaple	O
Another	O
wt	O
.	O
the	O
cartilage	O
going	O
between	O
both	O
thrown	O
uppon	O
the	O
Island	O
of	O
Bermudas	B-place
by	O
a	O
Storm	O
239	O
.	O
-1497	O
.	O
Ossa	O
carpioaum	O
.	O
221	O
i	O
.	O
-1498	O
.	O
An	O
egg	O
w	O
t.	O
its	O
appendices	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
belly	O
of	O
a	O
dog	O
fish	O
.	O
at	O
Cows	O
.	O
Pet	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-1499	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
palat	O
of	O
an	O
orbis	O
.	O
P.	O
221.	O
l	O
-1500	O
.	O
Testapiscis	O
Catcher	O
dicta	O
Cun	O
.	O
P.	O
162.	O
g.	O
221.	O
i	O
-1501	O
.	O
The	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
1502	O
.	O
The	O
Sceleta	O
of	O
fishes	O
in	O
a	O
blackislate	O
from	O
er	O
Garnet	O
Pet	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
-	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
68	O
P.	O
17	O
3	O
Fishes	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Canis	O
Carchariæ	O
alt	O
.	O
Spec	O
.	O
u.	O
p.	O
+	O
n.	O
c.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
d.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
271	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Canis	O
Carchariæ	O
pinna	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Canis	O
Carchariæ	O
cauda	O
.	O
4	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Canis	O
Carchariæ	O
mandibulæ	O
.	O
f	O
5	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
slate	O
with	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Scales	O
appear	O
&	O
some	O
armatura	O
or	O
pyrites	O
.	O
An	O
Lapis	O
fissilis	O
Islebiams	O
.	O
222.	O
a	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
slate	O
with	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
fish	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
From	O
mount	B-place
Lebanon	I-place
.	O
222.	O
c	O
7	O
.	O
Faber	O
Salviani	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
S.	O
i6	O
.	O
+	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornutus	O
Clusÿ	O
:	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Rana	O
piscatrix	O
Salviani	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
E.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Charlton	O
p.	O
73	O
.	O
Worm	O
p.	O
27	O
.	O
Loppius	O
Arled	O
.	O
241	O
10	O
.	O
Ranæ	O
piscatricis	O
caput	O
.	O
Ib	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
8.	O
lesser	O
.	O
+	O
f	O
ÿ	O
241	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
An	O
Muræna	O
Salviani	O
.	O
Tab	O
.	O
G.	O
1	O
.	O
Will	O
?	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
An	O
Serpentis	O
Marini	O
caput	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
G.	O
4	O
?	O
f	O
241	O
14	O
.	O
Testudo	O
marina	O
.	O
Jonst	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
8.	O
ad	O
quadraped	O
241	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
Sun	O
fish	O
.	O
Mola	O
Salviani	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
taile	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Albacore	O
.	O
f	O
241.	O
&	O
17	O
.	O
Zygæna	O
Salviani	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
balance	O
fish	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
.	O
3a	O
-1503	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
remora	O
A	O
silver	O
fish	O
from	O
china	O
A	O
young	O
shark	O
A	O
scolopendra	O
from	O
China	B-place
.	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
.	I-pers
m	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
7.	O
m.	O
1504	O
.	O
225.	O
mm	O
22	O
W	O
Dog	O
fish	O
teeth	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
221.	O
w.	O
1505	O
.	O
The	O
vertebra	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
black	O
on	O
the	O
out	O
side	O
&	O
wi	O
thin	O
chalk	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
1506	O
.	O
Two	O
s	O
tickle	O
backs	O
from	O
Hampshire	B-place
w	O
t.	O
round	O
knobbs	O
like	O
pease	O
of	O
a	O
pearl	O
.	O
colour	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
kill	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
Niece	B-pers
sloane	I-pers
in	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
o-3	O
1507	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
22	O
W.	O
Ad	O
Glossopotra	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
Joh	O
.	O
Petrus	O
Tschudius	O
from	O
the	O
Canton	O
of	O
Glaris	O
in	O
Swisserland	B-place
1508	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
Piscis	O
diluviani	O
sceleton	O
fossili	O
in	O
Lapide	O
Glaronens	O
.	O
Idem	O
1509	O
37	O
.	O
Ichtyites	O
6	O
in	O
Lapide	O
fossili	O
nigro	O
Glaronens	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
1510	O
1500	O
The	O
bone	O
of	O
some	O
Fish	O
?	O
Vid	O
Antea	O
221	O
e	O
1511	O
Teeth	O
or	O
bones	O
?	O
vid	O
.	O
Antea	O
vid	O
.	O
433	O
.	O
221	O
e	O
4	O
18	O
.	O
Galeus	O
Glaucus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
+	O
4	O
The	O
blewshar	O
19	O
.	O
Pristis	O
sive	O
serra	O
Clusÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
B	O
.	O
9.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
288.	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Rostrum	O
delphini	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
1.	O
f	O
241	O
21	O
.	O
Squatino-raia	O
.	O
F.	O
cl	O
.	O
Column	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
D.	O
5	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
-22	O
.	O
EjuDem	O
.	O
Caput	O
?	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Maidstone	I-pers
.	I-pers
from	O
Virginia	B-place
?	O
Shagreen	O
.	O
Rays	O
head	O
.	O
f	O
23	O
.	O
Guacuima	O
Brasil	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
E.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
fig	O
.	O
3.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
24	O
.	O
Lampetra	O
major	O
Salv	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
G.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Lamprey	O
from	O
the	O
Severn	B-place
.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
Iperuquiba	O
Brasiliensibus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
G.	O
8	O
?	O
a.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Lupus	O
marinus	O
Schonfeldÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
H.	O
3	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Worm	O
p.	O
275	O
Ex	O
Piscis	O
hujus	O
dentiby	O
molaribus	O
fingere	O
solent	O
Gemmarÿ	O
frandulent	O
lapide	O
Bufonio	O
magno	O
diverdere	O
Pretio	O
241	O
f	O
27	O
.	O
Pristis	O
sive	O
Serræ	O
Serra	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
B	O
.	O
9.	O
fig	O
.	O
5.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
28	O
An	O
Orbis	O
Salvian	O
.	O
Primus	O
.	O
Rond	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
1	O
?	O
241	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Orbis	O
hirsutus	O
densis	O
&	O
exiquis	O
muric=	O
=ibus	O
donatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
Histrix	O
piscis	O
Clusÿ	O
Guamajacu	O
Guara	O
+	O
Brasiliensibus	O
an	O
orbis	O
muricatus	O
primus	O
&	O
alter	O
Clusÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
5.	O
vid	O
.	O
seg	O
.	O
f	O
✓	O
CLXXVII	O
4a	O
*	O
1484	O
.	O
*	O
1404	O
22	O
X	O
A	O
long	O
yellowish	O
bufornites	O
.	O
221	O
c	O
*	O
1485	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
blackish	O
221.	O
dd	O
221	O
c	O
*	O
14	O
The	O
tongue	O
of	O
a	O
nari	O
nari	O
blackish	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
one	O
joint	O
.	O
fossil	O
A	O
fishes	O
eye	O
.	O
221	O
c	O
*	O
1487	O
.	O
An	O
operculum	O
or	O
umbilicas	O
marinus	O
.	O
221	O
i	O
*	O
1488	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
fishes	O
head	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1489	O
.	O
Cataphractus	O
Brasilianus	O
?	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1490	O
.	O
The	O
severall	O
bones	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
ch	O
ap	O
aps	O
of	O
a	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1491	O
.	O
Sev	O
ll	O
.	O
chaps	O
of	O
the	O
lupus	O
pisai	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1492.	O
sev	O
ll	O
.	O
glossopetræ	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
&	O
malta	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1493	O
.	O
A	O
larger	O
&	O
smaller	O
.	O
of	O
sapies	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1494	O
.	O
A	O
strange	O
vertilne	O
of	O
as	O
fish	O
each	O
joint	O
being	O
a	O
hollow	O
cup	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1495	O
.	O
70	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
bone	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1496	O
.	O
A	O
white	O
meconits	O
w	O
t.	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
sharks	O
tooth	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1497	O
.	O
Meconites	O
cineres	O
coloris	O
e	O
birsa	O
fluvio	O
agri	O
-	O
Basileensis	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
scheuchrers	O
lithograph	O
.	O
Helvet	O
.	O
p.	O
40.	O
fig	O
.	O
55	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1498	O
.	O
Prichles	O
of	O
a	O
thorn	O
back	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
*	O
1499	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Siliquastra	O
from	O
Witney	B-place
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1500	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Bufonite	O
roundish	O
,	O
orange	O
coloured	O
black	O
&	O
brown	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1501	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
yellow	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
whiteish	O
eye	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1502	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Brown	B-pers
w	O
t.	O
a	O
yellow	O
eye	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1503.	O
many	O
small	O
grown	O
together	O
&	O
separate	O
22	O
X	O
*	O
1504.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
jaw	O
not	O
petrified	O
221	O
ff	O
*	O
1505	O
.	O
92	O
?	O
long	O
black	O
white	O
&	O
striated	O
.	O
1506	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
sharks	O
vertebre	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
1507	O
.	O
Very	O
small	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
.	O
-1508	O
.	O
Unicornn	O
fossile	O
Worm	O
.	O
M.	O
221	O
ff	O
7	O
-1509	O
.	O
The	O
sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
salmon	O
trout	O
7	O
6	O
foot	O
long	O
taken	O
near	O
Colchester	B-place
being	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
tide	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Panlet	I-pers
1510	O
.	O
Ossis	O
fragmen	O
forte	O
alicusus	O
ceti	O
ex	O
fodinis	O
Aren	O
=ariorum	O
fr	O
om	O
S	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Monti	I-pers
221	O
ff	O
5	O
-30	O
CLXXVIII	O
Histrix	O
piscis	O
longissimis	O
spinis	O
donatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I.	O
b.	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
Orbis	O
muricatus	O
&	O
reticulatus	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
e	O
M.	O
S.	O
R.	O
tab	O
.	O
I.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
33	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
.	O
34	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
35	O
.	O
Idem	O
with	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
31.	O
small	O
.	O
b	O
241	O
36	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
Orbis	O
muricatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
App	O
.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
241	O
38	O
.	O
Xiphias	O
piscis	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
270	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
sword	O
fish	O
.	O
Nez	O
d'Espadon	O
,	O
poisson	O
de	O
mer	O
.	O
B	O
iron	O
p.	O
276.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
39.	O
pisciculus	O
cornutus	O
.	O
Bont	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
40	O
.	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornibus	O
carens	O
.	O
+	O
Clus	O
.	O
p.	O
142	O
?	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
13.	O
capitis	O
cornibus	O
carens	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
16	O
?	O
ex	O
toto	O
cornibus	O
carens	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
J	O
.	O
18	O
?	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
41	O
.	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
ex	O
toto	O
maculosus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
b	O
241	O
42.	O
piscis	O
quadrangularis	O
rostratus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
11.	O
b	O
241	O
43	O
.	O
Guaperva	O
maxima	O
caudata	O
e	O
M.	O
S.	O
R.	O
Balisters	O
&	O
c	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
Arted	O
Sipion	O
p	O
8	O
f	O
241	O
44	O
.	O
Acus	O
Aristotelis	O
Species	O
altera	O
major	O
.	O
+	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
25.	O
f	O
241	O
5a	O
-1511	O
.	O
Drum	O
bones	O
.	O
Pet	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
-1512	O
.	O
Bones	O
of	O
some	O
cetacesus	O
fish	O
.	O
37	O
-1513	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Dog	O
fish	O
bones	O
.	O
teeth	O
.	O
37	O
-1514	O
.	O
Sev	O
ll	O
.	O
bones	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Witney	B-place
quarry	O
near	O
Oxford	B-place
.	O
37	O
-1515	O
.	O
Impressions	O
of	O
the	O
scales	O
of	O
fishes	O
on	O
stone	O
?	O
37	O
.	O
-1516	O
.	O
The	O
single	O
joint	O
of	O
a	O
whales	O
vertebræ	O
wherin	O
on	O
one	O
end	O
side	O
is	O
the	O
trencher	O
like	O
bone	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
gravele	O
pitt	O
8	O
foot	O
deep	O
8	O
miles	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
w	O
t.	O
shells	O
used	O
in	O
manuring	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
sceleton	O
was	O
40	O
foot	O
long	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	I-pers
222.	O
a	O
-1517	O
.	O
Pisum	O
lapideum	O
candidum	O
?	O
222.	O
c	O
-1518	O
.	O
Vesicaria	O
marina	O
ramosa	O
?	O
222.	O
c	O
-1519	O
.	O
A	O
Scaly	O
fish	O
wt	O
.	O
a	O
dentated	O
horn	O
on	O
its	O
back	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-1520	O
.	O
A	O
morses	O
jaw	O
&	O
head	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
-1521	O
.	O
A	O
morses	O
mustacho	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
1522	O
.	O
Rosmari	O
dens	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
1523	O
.	O
Raiæ	O
clavate	O
cauda	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
1524	O
.	O
A	O
plaise	O
both	O
sides	O
like	O
the	O
underside	O
of	O
an	O
ordinary	O
plaise	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
1525	O
.	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
a	O
raia	O
levis	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
1526	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
fish	O
w	O
t.	O
one	O
finn	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
1527	O
.	O
Young	O
carchariæ	O
?	O
n.	O
6	O
+	O
1528	O
The	O
round	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
whale	O
1529	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
trout	O
whose	O
upper	O
chap	O
was	O
mostly	O
wanting	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
1530.	O
a	O
small	O
black	O
fish	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
fins	O
under	O
the	O
gills	O
like	O
fore	O
.	O
feet	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
had	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
3541	O
.	O
Insect	O
?	O
)	O
n.	O
2	O
.	O
1531	O
.	O
A	O
scaly	O
fish	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
6	O
45	O
.	O
Lumpus	O
Anglorum	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
N.	O
+	O
n.	O
ÿ.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
46	O
.	O
Delphinus	O
Belgis	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
f	O
47	O
.	O
Monoceros	O
piscis	O
e	O
M.	O
S.	O
R.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
2	O
prickles	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
tasle	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
48	O
.	O
Hirundo	O
Salv	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
P.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
the	O
flying	O
fish	O
.	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
49	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
+	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
50	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
very	O
large	O
.	O
+	O
f	O
241	O
51	O
.	O
Acus	O
maxima	O
Squammosa	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
P.	O
8	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
52	O
.	O
Scorpius	O
Virginianus	O
.	O
Salviani	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
X	O
.	O
15	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
App	O
.	O
p.	O
25.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
53	O
.	O
An	O
Scorpius	O
ous	O
Salviani	O
major	O
Rond	O
.	O
Gesn	O
.	O
p.	O
1017	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
X	O
.	O
+	O
13	O
?	O
Barbulæ	O
?	O
f	O
54	O
.	O
An	O
Diaboli	O
marini	O
cutis	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
9	O
.	O
App	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
3	O
?	O
55	O
.	O
Piscis	O
Monocerotis	O
cornu	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
S	O
241	O
56	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
whale	O
bone	O
.	O
57	O
.	O
Torpedo	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
81	O
.	O
Torpille	O
on	O
Tremble	O
.	O
de	O
Reaumur	B-pers
+	O
memoires	O
de	O
ad	O
Roy	O
.	O
des	O
Sciences	O
Ameet	O
714	O
p.	O
344	O
.	O
4	O
to	O
.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
58	O
.	O
Squatina	O
.	O
Salv	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
D3	O
.	O
p.	O
79	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
monk	O
or	O
angel	O
fish	O
.	O
f	O
239	O
.	O
59	O
.	O
Idem	O
a	O
young	O
one	O
.	O
+	O
241	O
6a	O
1532	O
.	O
The	O
sail	O
of	O
the	O
Carvell	O
fish	O
.	O
Urtica	O
&	O
c	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
glossopetra	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
found	O
221.	O
dd	O
-1533	O
.	O
10	O
foot	O
under	O
ground	O
there	O
by	O
221	O
ff	O
1534	O
.	O
Shark	O
stone	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
ff	O
1535	O
.	O
Sharks	O
eggs	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Ames	I-pers
.	I-pers
m.	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
221	O
ff	O
227	O
-1536	O
.	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
221	O
ff	O
227	O
1537	O
.	O
Palat	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
Nari	O
nari	O
from	O
Brasile	B-place
221	O
ff	O
1538	O
.	O
158	O
A	O
deep	O
or	O
o	O
a	O
range	O
colourd	O
bufonites	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
221	O
ff	O
1539	O
.	O
A	O
acus	O
vulgaris	O
sive	O
oppiani	O
.	O
Acusprima	O
spec	O
i	O
es	O
condel	O
.	O
gesn	O
Bελo'rn	O
pαφis	O
Græcis	O
Pa	O
109	O
Rau	O
synops	O
piscium	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Horn	O
fish	O
or	O
Gar	O
fish	O
.	O
221	O
e	O
1540	O
1530	O
A	O
bufonites	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
colour	O
✓	O
172	O
1541	O
.	O
The	O
skin	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
one	O
of	O
.	O
68.	O
senter	O
'd	O
before	O
under	O
a	O
former	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
✓	O
221.	O
b	O
1542	O
Orbis	O
piscis	O
muricatus	O
without	O
his	O
two	O
Mandibles	O
&	O
pr	O
echaps	O
enter	O
'd	O
before	O
or	O
N	O
o	O
Lost	O
241	O
a	O
1543	O
.	O
Two	O
pieces	O
of	O
blue	O
slate	O
small	O
w	O
t.	O
the	O
impressions	O
of	O
Scalops	O
of	O
fishes	O
from	O
Whitehaven	B-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
vide	O
his	O
Description	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
12	O
37	O
1544	O
.	O
1543	O
Another	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
7	O
60	O
.	O
Catulus	O
minor	O
Salvian	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
+	O
B	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
61	O
.	O
A	O
whalebone	O
with	O
the	O
hair	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
56.	O
large	O
.	O
D	O
241	O
62	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
63	O
.	O
The	O
mandible	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Lupus	O
-	O
marinus	O
with	O
teeth	O
in	O
it	O
like	O
the	O
lapis	O
bufonis	O
.	O
241	O
f	O
64	O
.	O
Os	O
Sepiæ	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
65	O
.	O
An	O
the	O
intestines	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
or	O
skin	O
of	O
an	O
eel	O
?	O
66	O
.	O
An	O
Guaperva	O
histrix	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
+	O
21.	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
67	O
.	O
Acarauna	O
minor	O
quadrata	O
e	O
M.	O
S.	O
R.	O
+	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
O3	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
2.	O
a	O
241	O
68	O
.	O
Acus	O
maxima	O
squamosa	O
idem	O
N	O
o	O
?	O
51	O
+	O
f	O
✓	O
a	O
241	O
69	O
.	O
Lupus	O
Salviani	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
R.	O
1	O
?	O
+	O
241	O
.	O
70	O
.	O
Idem	O
?	O
+	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
71	O
.	O
Idem	O
?	O
+	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
72	O
.	O
Milvas	O
Salv	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
S.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
73	O
.	O
A	O
wing	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221	O
c	O
74	O
.	O
Scarus	O
Cretensis	O
Aldrovandi	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
X	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
75	O
.	O
7a	O
1545	O
.	O
A	O
Third	O
piece	O
mark	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
N	O
o	O
14	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
1546	O
.	O
The	O
fore	O
finn	O
of	O
the	O
Manati	O
.	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
sceleton	O
from	O
M	B-pers
rs	I-pers
.	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
218	O
288	O
1547	O
.	O
A	O
stone	O
with	O
Ova	O
piscium	O
.	O
Vid	O
A	O
tea	O
221	O
:	O
y	O
1548	O
A	O
yound	O
Dorado	O
?	O
vid	O
.	O
Antea	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
801	O
?	O
158	O
221	O
ff	O
1549	O
.	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
Whale	O
mark	O
'd	O
formerly	O
120	O
.	O
222.	O
c.	O
1550	O
.	O
Ichthyolithi	O
Eichstadensi	O
.	O
from	O
Ferdinandus	O
Jacobus	O
Barerus	O
at	O
Norimberge	B-place
222.	O
t.	O
1551	O
.	O
An	O
cupriscus	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
152.	O
tab	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
19.	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Rev	O
d.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
221.	O
aa	O
1552	O
.	O
An	O
Acarauna	O
Will	O
.	O
-	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
1553	O
.	O
An	O
Scarus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
306	O
Tab	O
.	O
v.	O
s.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
1554	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
jaws	O
of	O
the	O
Nari	O
Nari	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Rev	O
d.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
;	O
221.	O
c.	O
1555	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Teeth	O
of	O
some	O
Amphibious	O
creature	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
1556	O
.	O
A	O
Remora	O
and	O
a	O
centiqacs	O
sent	O
to	O
Dr.	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
from	O
Bengal	B-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stack	I-pers
m.	O
7	O
.	O
1557	O
.	O
The	O
Mango	O
Fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
vid	O
Edwards	B-pers
's	O
Ornitholog	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
4.	O
p.	O
208.	O
m.	O
7	O
.	O
1558	O
.	O
A	O
Remora	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
&	O
bought	O
by	O
D	O
r.	O
Stack	B-pers
at	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
his	O
museum	O
m.	O
7	O
.	O
8	O
76	O
.	O
Nari	O
Nari	O
Brasil	O
.	O
cauda	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
66.	O
tab	O
.	O
c.	O
1	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
?	O
The	O
whip	O
ray	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
Aquilæ	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
64.	O
tab	O
.	O
C.	O
2.	O
cauda	O
?	O
f	O
78	O
.	O
An	O
Aquilæ	O
caput	O
.	O
Ej	O
.	O
Ib	O
.	O
vel	O
Raiæ	O
f	O
241	O
79	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
80	O
.	O
Pastinacæ	O
Marine	O
D.	B-pers
F	I-pers
.	I-pers
C.	O
Cauda	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
D.	O
5	O
?	O
81	O
.	O
Idem	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
G	O
82	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
f	O
83	O
.	O
Pastinacæ	O
marinæ	O
vel	O
Raiæ	O
cauda	O
.	O
84	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Shagrin	O
.	O
smoother	O
.	O
an	O
tail	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
85	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
The	O
basilish	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
fins	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
An	O
The	O
finn	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
88	O
.	O
An	O
the	O
chops	O
or	O
mandibles	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
.	O
or	O
amphibious	O
animal	O
.	O
89	O
.	O
Mandibles	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
like	O
21	O
.	O
&	O
22	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
f	O
221	O
ff	O
8a	O
1559	O
.	O
The	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Fish	O
described	O
by	O
Catesby	B-pers
in	O
his	O
Nat	O
.	O
Hist	O
.	O
Flor	O
.	O
from	O
D	O
o	O
.	O
241.	O
a	O
1560	O
.	O
Sp	O
.	O
Roon	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
large	O
Fins	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
.	O
D	O
o	O
.	O
1561	O
.	O
Sp	O
.	O
Roon	O
A	O
young	O
Shark	O
stuff	O
'd	O
.	O
D	O
o	O
.	O
1562	O
A	O
small	O
orbis	O
.	O
D	O
o	O
.	O
221.	O
p.	O
1563	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
1490	O
.	O
D	O
o	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
End	O
.	O
Two	O
Teeth	O
of	O
the	O
Sperma	O
Ceti	O
Whale	O
Given	O
by	O
Gustavus	B-pers
Brander	I-pers
Esq	O
r.	O
A	O
Rana	O
piscatrix	O
in	O
Sp	O
.	O
given	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Theobabds	O
Esq	O
r.	O
9	O
90	O
.	O
Whales	O
pizzle	O
.	O
Penis	O
balence	O
grandis	O
.	O
91	O
.	O
A	O
roundish	O
bone	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
is	O
plac	O
'd	O
between	O
every	O
2	O
vertebres	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
The	O
ear	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
?	O
f	O
4	O
241	O
93	O
.	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
sperma	O
ceti	O
whale	O
.	O
b	O
241	O
94	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
92	O
.	O
✓	O
222	O
-95	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
&	O
mandibles	O
of	O
a	O
pike	O
.	O
✓	O
221.	O
i	O
-96	O
.	O
The	O
mandibles	O
of	O
aquila	O
piseis	O
or	O
Ray	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
78	O
?	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-97	O
.	O
Milvus	O
Salviani	O
.	O
From	O
Guinea	B-place
given	O
by	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Fortrey	I-pers
.	O
+	O
f	O
-98	O
.	O
Another	O
given	O
by	O
Coll	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wharton	I-pers
.	I-pers
+	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
99	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
radius	O
or	O
sting	O
of	O
the	O
pastinaca	O
marina	O
or	O
Aquila	O
.	O
221.	O
l	O
100	O
.	O
✓	O
Pikes	O
of	O
the	O
dog	O
fish	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
4	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Galeus	O
Acatithias	O
Clus	O
.	O
exotieus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
57.	O
tab	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
quadrup	O
.	O
1751	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
9.	O
fig	O
.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
Orkneyes	B-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
n	O
101	O
.	O
✓	O
Penis	O
&	O
testicles	O
of	O
an	O
alligator	O
or	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0.	O
crocodile	O
from	O
Surinam	B-place
.	O
vid	O
.	O
quadr	O
.	O
1751	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
22	O
102	O
.	O
✓	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
mandible	O
of	O
the	O
rana	O
pisca	O
=	O
=trix	O
?	O
Pike	O
?	O
221.	O
f.	O
103.	O
piscis	O
monocerotis	O
embryonis	O
alicusus	O
cornu	O
.	O
Willuglib	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
221	O
l	O
-104	O
.	O
✓	O
pars	O
cort	O
u	O
piscis	O
monocerotis	O
.	O
Ib	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Waldo	I-pers
at	O
suratte	B-place
.	O
221.	O
l.	O
105	O
.	O
✓	O
Galeus	O
glaucus	O
Rond	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
10	O
106	O
.	O
✓	O
pristis	O
sive	O
serra	O
.	O
+	O
221	O
l	O
107	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
D	O
+	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
108	O
.	O
Gelly	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
sharks	O
head	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
turns	O
to	O
a	O
white	O
powder	O
&	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
promote	O
travell	O
in	O
women	O
.	O
221.	O
l	O
221.	O
w	O
109	O
.	O
✓	O
Aquilæ	O
piscis	O
vel	O
pastinaæ	O
marinœ	O
radius	O
or	O
stiu	O
n	O
g.	O
f	O
110	O
.	O
Raiæ	O
cujusdam	O
mandibulæ	O
an	O
-	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Rockfish	O
Jaw	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221	O
dd	O
111.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
112	O
.	O
An	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Jaw	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
or	O
of	O
its	O
stomach	O
?	O
221.	O
dd	O
113	O
.	O
The	O
mandible	O
upper	O
?	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
an	O
of	O
the	O
Nari	O
nari	O
?	O
221.	O
cc	O
114	O
.	O
Teeth	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
an	O
of	O
the	O
aquila	O
?	O
221	O
ff	O
115	O
.	O
Round	O
bone	O
an	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
the	O
whale	O
,	O
porpesse	O
,	O
or	O
dolphin	O
?	O
221	O
c	O
116	O
.	O
✓	O
Galei	O
cujusdam	O
fætus	O
chorion	O
.	O
matricula	O
marina	O
vulgo	O
crapault	O
de	O
mer	O
.	O
Bell	B-pers
de	O
aq	O
.	O
p.	O
68	O
.	O
221	O
k	O
117	O
.	O
✓	O
Another	O
sort	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
Carolina	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
Squatina	O
Salv	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
D.	O
3.	O
a	O
+	O
young	O
one	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
119	O
.	O
The	O
ovarium	O
of	O
a	O
buccinum	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
5121.	O
de	O
Va	O
e.	O
221.	O
ff	O
11	O
120	O
.	O
The	O
ova	O
of	O
a	O
shell	O
?	O
fish	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
✓	O
Guacucuia	O
Brasiliensibus	O
.	O
Marcgr	O
.	O
Ray	O
.	O
p.	O
89.	O
tab	O
.	O
E.	O
2	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
n.	O
122	O
.	O
✓	O
Acara	O
mucu	O
Brasiliensibus	O
Marcgr	O
.	O
-	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
p.	O
91.	O
tab	O
.	O
E.	O
2	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
123	O
.	O
Passer	O
fluviatilis	O
,	O
a	O
Flounder	O
.	O
Raÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Tab	O
.	O
F.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
?	O
221.	O
ff	O
124	O
.	O
✓	O
Iperuquiba	O
Brasiliensibus	O
.	O
Marcgr	O
.	O
+	O
Ray	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
G.	O
8.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
An	O
Imper=	O
=ati	O
remora	O
.	O
App	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
9.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
?	O
ejusdem	O
?	O
221.	O
p.	O
-125	O
.	O
✓	O
Orbis	O
hirsutus	O
densis	O
&	O
exiguis	O
murici=	O
=bus	O
donatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
From	O
Virginia	B-place
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
126	O
.	O
✓	O
Histrix	O
piscis	O
Clusÿ	O
.	O
Guamaia	O
=cus	O
Guara	O
Brasiliensibus	O
.	O
an	O
orbis	O
muricatus	O
primus	O
&	O
alter	O
.	O
Clusÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
5	O
?	O
A	O
young	O
one	O
.	O
a	O
241	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
Psciculus	O
Cornutus	O
.	O
Bont	O
.	O
Will	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
13.	O
fig	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
D	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
g	O
128	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornibus	O
carens	O
Clus=	O
ÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
13.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
&	O
tab	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
129	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornutus	O
.	O
Clus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
12	O
130	O
.	O
✓	O
Guaperva	O
histrix	O
Will	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
0.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
131	O
.	O
✓	O
Acus	O
Aristotelis	O
species	O
altera	O
major	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
132	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
133	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
+	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
134	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
shorter	O
&	O
broader	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
e	O
135	O
.	O
✓	O
Hippocampus	O
non	O
aculeatus	O
incisuris	O
raris	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
25.	O
fig	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
136	O
.	O
Hippocampus	O
non	O
aculeatus	O
incisuris	O
crebris	O
Indiæ	O
Occidentalis	O
.	O
ib	O
.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
a	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
✓	O
Spina	O
scolopacis	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
p.	O
161.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
I	O
.	O
25.	O
fig	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
138	O
.	O
✓	O
Cataphractus	O
Schonfeldÿ	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
N.	O
6.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
&	O
3	O
.	O
221	O
a	O
139	O
.	O
Cutaphractus	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
✓	O
Lumpus	O
Anglorum	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
+	O
N.	O
11	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
141	O
.	O
✓	O
Guaperva	O
Brasiliens	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
1	O
?	O
vel	O
Aba	O
tab	O
.	O
S.	O
185	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
13	O
142	O
.	O
✓	O
Acus	O
Oppiani	O
Caput	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
P.	O
2	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
143	O
.	O
Accipenser	O
Salv	O
.	O
sturgeon	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
144	O
.	O
✓	O
Lyra	O
Salviaris	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
S.	O
3.	O
brought	O
by	O
me	O
from	O
Montpelier	B-place
.	O
+	O
221.	O
p.	O
145	O
.	O
✓	O
Faber	O
Salviaris	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
S.	O
16	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
.	O
146	O
.	O
✓	O
Scorpius	O
Salviaris	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
X	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
147	O
.	O
✓	O
Idem	O
redish	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
+	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
148	O
.	O
✓	O
Orbis	O
Muricatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
App	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
tab	O
.	O
5.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
149	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
with	O
128.	O
only	O
smaller	O
.	O
+	O
piscis	O
triangularis	O
parvulus	O
.	O
221.	O
l	O
150	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
Cataphractus	O
?	O
+	O
221.	O
n	O
151	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
mustelæ	O
fluviatilis	O
species	O
?	O
+	O
221	O
l.	O
152	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
Turdus	O
?	O
+	O
221.	O
n.	O
14	O
153	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
corax	O
vel	O
cuculi	O
species	O
?	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
154	O
.	O
Ruffe	O
percæ	O
species	O
?	O
+	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
O	O
.	O
2	O
155	O
.	O
An	O
rana	O
piscatrix	O
?	O
221.	O
n	O
156	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
157	O
.	O
221	O
r	O
158	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
159	O
.	O
The	O
mandibles	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
an	O
orbis	O
vel	O
raiæ	O
species	O
?	O
221	O
y	O
160	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
of	O
a	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
an	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
.	O
161.	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
mandible	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-162	O
.	O
The	O
entire	O
mandibles	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
/	O
Toadstones	O
or	O
the	O
grinding	O
teeth	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
lupus	O
marinus	O
vid	O
.	O
Johnston	O
tab	O
.	O
47	O
.	O
/	O
Maxilla	O
cum	O
truplus	O
serve	O
dentium	O
manati	O
.	O
P./A	O
fragment	O
of	O
the	O
mandible	O
of	O
the	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
w	O
t.	O
the	O
dentes	O
moles	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-163	O
.	O
Halfe	O
of	O
the	O
mandible	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-164	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
or	O
mandible	O
of	O
another	O
of	O
these	O
fishes	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
c	O
165	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
fishes	O
head	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
14a	O
X	O
Langue	O
de	O
Serpent	O
,	O
Glossopetra	O
.	O
Biron	O
.	O
265	O
.	O
15	O
166	O
.	O
An	O
lumpus	O
Anglorum	O
?	O
+	O
167	O
.	O
Lumpus	O
?	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
-168	O
.	O
Cataphractus	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-169	O
?	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
154	O
:	O
+	O
221.	O
a	O
-170	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
clay	O
from	O
the	O
tile	B-place
pitts	I-place
at	I-place
Richmond	I-place
y	O
e.	O
two	O
vertebres	O
are	O
dislocated	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
-171	O
.	O
22	O
w	O
The	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
filled	O
with	O
stony	O
matter	O
&	O
fossil	O
?	O
221.	O
c	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
large	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
imbedded	O
in	O
a	O
whitish	O
friable	O
stone	O
from	O
.	O
Malta	B-place
.	O
Gray	O
&	O
serrated	O
.	O
X	O
221.	O
cc	O
221.	O
dd	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
teeth	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
bed	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
221.	O
y	O
174	O
.	O
A	O
lesser	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
imbedded	O
in	O
its	O
stone	O
or	O
earth	O
.	O
From	O
malta	B-place
yellow	O
&	O
not	O
serrated	O
.	O
221.	O
c.c	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
bed	O
gray	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
176	O
.	O
A	O
sharks	O
tooth	O
short	O
&	O
gray	O
w	O
t.	O
2	O
lesser	O
ones	O
at	O
its	O
base	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
177	O
.	O
One	O
longer	O
&	O
narrower	O
w	O
t.	O
2	O
appendices	O
221.	O
cc	O
178	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
one	O
w	O
t.	O
appendices	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
179	O
.	O
W	O
A	O
long	O
one	O
w	O
t	O
out	O
appendices	O
.	O
3	O
Boxes	O
221.	O
ff	O
16	O
180	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
or	O
mandible	O
of	O
an	O
orbis	O
muricatus	O
?	O
dugg	O
up	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
This	O
fish	O
eats	O
shell	O
fish	O
&	O
grinds	O
them	O
with	O
between	O
the	O
upper	O
&	O
under	O
mandibles	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
are	O
like	O
millstones	O
.	O
✓	O
183	O
.	O
181	O
.	O
The	O
spine	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
?	O
182	O
.	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
or	O
back	O
bone	O
with	O
the	O
Spines	O
&	O
vertebres	O
black	O
&	O
a	O
whitish	O
stone	O
?	O
221.	O
g	O
183	O
.	O
A	O
bone	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
for	O
facilitating	O
the	O
motion	O
.	O
From	O
Dr.	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
in	O
-	O
Lancashire	B-place
.	O
221.	O
c	O
184	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
Glossopetra	O
,	O
serrated	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
black	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
185	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
smaller	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
186	O
.	O
22	O
W.	O
One	O
of	O
those	O
Small	O
ones	O
called	O
birds	O
tongues	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
187	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
Transverse	O
Section	O
of	O
a	O
whales	O
pizzle	O
.	O
220	O
f.	O
188	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
133.	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Massy	I-pers
who	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
Norfolk	B-place
near	O
Wisbich	B-place
.	O
this	O
is	O
variegated	O
.	O
+	O
221.	O
ff	O
189	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
cuticula	O
or	O
Scarfe	O
skin	O
of	O
y	O
e.	O
Fin	O
or	O
whalebone	O
whale	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	B-place
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
17	O
-190	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
finn	O
of	O
whale	O
bone	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-191	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
matricula	O
marina	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
-192	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
teeth	O
of	O
the	O
mandible	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
.	O
Bufonites	O
.	O
221	O
i	O
.	O
-193	O
.	O
✓	O
Bones	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
stone	O
.	O
221	O
y	O
-194	O
.	O
Pinnæ	O
byssus	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-195	O
.	O
Lingua	O
piscis	O
,	O
N.C.	O
Lingua	O
Nari	O
nari	O
Brasil	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
species	O
raiæ	O
Anglice	O
Skate	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
hath	O
no	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
teeth	O
but	O
his	O
tongue	O
&	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
supply	O
that	O
defect	O
being	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
a	O
hard	O
bony	O
substance	O
his	O
tail	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
is	O
ab	O
t.	O
2	O
yards	O
long	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
some	O
use	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
as	O
horse	O
whips	O
,	O
his	O
skin	O
is	O
curiously	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
enameld	O
w	O
t.	O
white	O
&	O
black	O
spootts	O
.	O
1	O
st.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Walraven	I-pers
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-196	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
triquetrous	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
echinated	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
221.	O
y	O
-197	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
sett	O
w	O
t.	O
sharp	O
small	O
teeth	O
in	O
great	O
numbers	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
198	O
.	O
Dentes	O
Raiæ	O
.	O
199	O
.	O
Hippocampus	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
colour	O
bought	O
of	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Beverland	I-pers
.	I-pers
2	O
sh	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
-200	O
.	O
120	O
.	O
The	O
small	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
sperma	O
ceti	O
whale	O
?	O
stranded	O
in	O
Essex	B-place
the	O
had	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
g	O
den	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-201	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
20	O
An	O
dens	O
physeteris	O
?	O
rosmari	O
?	O
221.	O
ff	O
-202	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
20	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
18	O
203	O
.	O
123	O
.	O
Dens	O
lamiæ	O
.	O
-	O
L.	O
221.	O
ff	O
204	O
.	O
124	O
.	O
A	O
serrated	O
stone	O
or	O
bone	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
whiting	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
205	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
fish	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
126	O
.	O
The	O
matricula	O
marina	O
or	O
chorion	O
ovary	O
of	O
a	O
Galeas	O
or	O
dogg	O
fish	O
221.	O
f.	O
207	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
The	O
tarpum	O
fish	O
's	O
scale	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
Stones	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
fishes	O
head	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Wight	I-place
.	O
given	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Bonivert	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
a	O
carp	O
?	O
209	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetra	O
3	O
sorts	O
,	O
&	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
vertebre	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
from	O
Sheppey	B-place
Island	I-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
210	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
nari	O
nari	O
found	O
fossil	O
in	O
Mary	B-place
Land	I-place
w	O
t.	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
&	O
its	O
tongue	O
it	O
grinds	O
its	O
food	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
211	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
The	O
tongue	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
Halfe	O
of	O
a	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
tongue	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
213	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
214	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
Halfe	O
of	O
a	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
fossil	O
,	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
?	O
or	O
England	B-place
?	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
215	O
135.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
palate	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
216	O
.	O
136	O
.	O
A	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
217	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
18a	O
+	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
225.	O
p.	O
405.	O
where	O
tis	O
named	O
,	O
Scolo	O
pendra	O
marina	O
a	O
capile	O
Cationi	O
vesus	O
candam	O
sensim	O
gracilescens	O
,	O
limbo	O
pulcherrime	O
hirsuto	O
,	O
spinulszq	O
crebris	O
inters	O
tincto	O
e	O
mari	O
Hibernico	O
of	O
S	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Molyneux	I-pers
.	I-pers
19	O
218	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
Severall	O
vertebres	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
219	O
.	O
139	O
.	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
shark	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
220	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
A	O
tooth	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
precedent	O
?	O
bating	O
two	O
small	O
appendices	O
,	O
w	O
t.	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
stone	O
sticking	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
221	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
Dens	O
lamiæ	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
222	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
fossil	O
.	O
In	O
Sp	O
.	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
223	O
.	O
Lolligo	O
.	O
Bellon	O
.	O
de	O
aq	O
.	O
p.	O
337	O
.	O
TEVӨIS	O
Græins	O
,	O
Lolligo	O
Latinis	O
,	O
Totena	O
Massiliensibus	O
,	O
Cala=	O
=maro	O
Venetis	O
,	O
Casseron	O
Gallis	O
,	O
Corneths	O
vel	O
Cornichets	O
Baionensibus	O
.	O
&	O
.	O
p.	O
339.	O
a	O
good	O
figure	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Een	O
Surinaamse	O
Zee	O
Duyvel	O
.	O
of	O
Clark	B-pers
of	O
whom	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Holland	B-place
.	O
p.	O
7	O
224	O
.	O
Eruca	O
marina	O
Bellon	O
.	O
de	O
aq	O
.	O
p.	O
436.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cods	O
stomach	O
in	O
the	O
Irish	B-place
sea	I-place
vid	O
.	O
Transact	O
.	O
They	O
feed	O
on	O
submarine	O
alga	O
&	O
are	O
the	O
food	O
of	O
tortoises	O
Bell	B-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
their	O
villi	O
for	O
creeping	O
&	O
swimming	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
r.	O
8	O
225	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
r.	O
8	O
226	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
r.	O
8	O
.	O
227.	O
o.	O
l	O
The	O
flying	O
fish	O
/	O
another	O
in	O
Sp	O
.	O
V.	O
241.	O
b	O
20	O
228	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
+	O
o	O
.	O
7	O
229	O
.	O
Mugil	O
alatus	O
.	O
+	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
230	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
flying	O
fish	O
or	O
Harengus	O
+	O
alatus	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
231	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
remora	O
.	O
The	O
Sucking	O
fish	O
Dampier	B-pers
Voyage	O
.	O
Lon	O
d.	O
169	O
97	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
1.	O
p.	O
64.	O
who	O
says	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
is	O
fair	O
Weather	O
a	O
but	O
little	O
wind	O
they	O
will	O
play	O
about	O
the	O
Ship	O
:	O
but	O
in	O
blustering	O
weather	O
or	O
when	O
the	O
ship	O
sails	O
quick	O
they	O
commonly	O
fasten	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Ships	O
bottom	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
neither	O
the	O
ship	O
motion	O
,	O
the	O
never	O
so	O
swift	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
most	O
tempestuo=	O
=ous	O
sea	O
can	O
remove	O
them	O
They	O
will	O
like	O
wise	O
fasten	O
Themselves	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
bigger	O
fish	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
Sticking	O
to	O
a	O
Shark	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
usual	O
also	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
Sticking	O
to	O
Turtle	O
,	O
to	O
any	O
old	O
trees	O
,	O
planks	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
that	O
lye	O
driving	O
in	O
the	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
of	O
these	O
sucking	O
fishes	O
in	O
great	O
plenty	O
in	O
the	O
Bay	O
of	O
Campeetry	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
sea	O
between	O
that	O
&	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
Cartacus	O
as	O
ab	O
t.	O
there	O
Islands	O
Rocas	O
,	O
Blanco	O
,	O
Tertugas	O
&	O
c	O
They	O
have	O
no	O
scales	O
and	O
are	O
very	O
good	O
meat	O
.	O
f	O
n.	O
5	O
.	O
24	O
1	O
232	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
lesser	O
.	O
p.	O
3	O
233	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
p.	O
5	O
234	O
.	O
A	O
bottle	O
where	O
in	O
are	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
remora	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
lantern	O
fly	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
branch	O
of	O
white	O
corall	O
.	O
r.	O
5	O
.	O
235	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
hippo	O
campus	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
large	O
belly	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
n.	O
5	O
236	O
.	O
A	O
brown	O
hippo	O
campus	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
3	O
o	O
.	O
6	O
237	O
.	O
A	O
brown	O
hippocampus	O
spotted	O
w	O
t.	O
white	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
238	O
.	O
A	O
fish	O
from	O
China	B-place
w	O
t.	O
3	O
finns	O
in	O
the	O
tail	O
.	O
4	O
21	O
239	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
240	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
a	O
litle	O
blacker	O
.	O
These	O
sorts	O
of	O
fishes	O
were	O
brought	O
from	O
China	B-place
to	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
mary	O
alive	O
&	O
kept	O
in	O
fair	O
water	O
shifting	O
it	O
often	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
241	O
.	O
Urtica	O
marina	O
?	O
n.	O
2	O
242	O
.	O
Muræna	O
omnium	O
autorum	O
.	O
Willughb	O
.	O
+	O
p.	O
103	O
.	O
Tab	O
.	O
G.	O
1	O
.	O
Murena	O
.	O
Bellon	O
.	O
p.	O
158.	O
figu	O
red	O
well	O
.	O
p.	O
160.	O
p.	O
7	O
243	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Orbis	O
hirsutus	O
densis	O
&	O
exiguis	O
muri=	O
=cibus	O
donatus	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
3	O
?	O
2	O
.	O
Eruca	O
a	O
Suriname	O
in	O
y	O
e.	O
same	O
bottle-	O
p.	O
7	O
244	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
in	O
litle	O
?	O
Scorpion	O
fish	O
.	O
-1	O
Ind	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
sh	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0.	O
n.	O
2	O
245	O
.	O
Acus	O
2	O
a	O
.	O
Species	O
Rond	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
25.	O
fig	O
.	O
+	O
6	O
.	O
Will	O
?	O
2	O
dark	O
brown	O
small	O
fishes	O
.	O
n.	O
5	O
246	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
small	O
fishes	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
247	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
248	O
.	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
white	O
fasciæ	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
22	O
249	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Guaperva	O
Brasiliensis	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
+	O
O	O
.	O
1.	O
fig	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
phalangium	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
White	O
corall	O
.	O
n.	O
3	O
250	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Guaperva	O
.	O
w	O
t.	O
249	O
.	O
+	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
251	O
.	O
Acarauna	O
nigra	O
zonis	O
luteis	O
distincta	O
+	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
3.	O
fig	O
.	O
4.	O
from	O
Maurit=	B-place
=ius	I-place
,	O
as	O
bigg	O
as	O
a	O
flounder	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
252	O
.	O
Klip	O
fish	O
seu	O
soldaten	O
fish	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
5	O
.	O
App	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
4.	O
p.	O
2	O
253	O
.	O
Solea	O
fascÿs	O
albis	O
&	O
brunis	O
transver=	O
=sis	O
variegata	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
221.	O
ff	O
254	O
.	O
Serpens	O
marinus	O
fuscus	O
&	O
c	O
?	O
an	O
Barra	O
cuda	O
?	O
n.	O
5	O
255	O
.	O
Serpens	O
marinus	O
argenteus	O
?	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
256	O
.	O
Small	O
fishes	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
w	O
t.	O
young	O
ones	O
like	O
pease	O
?	O
Galei	O
pisces	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
23	O
257	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
7	O
258	O
.	O
Piscis	O
.	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
259	O
.	O
Pisces	O
3	O
.	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
n.	O
7	O
260	O
.	O
Pisces	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
?	O
Aves	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
?	O
Serpens	O
?	O
Lacer=	O
ta	O
?	O
p.	O
7	O
261	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
262	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
p.	O
1	O
263	O
.	O
Piscis	O
.	O
D.	B-pers
N	I-pers
?	O
n.	O
5	O
264	O
.	O
Piscis	O
.	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
n.	O
6	O
265	O
.	O
Piscis	O
.	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
n.	O
4	O
6	O
266	O
.	O
Piscis	O
.	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
an	O
Scorpius	O
?	O
A	O
small	O
tortoise	O
?	O
267	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
p.	O
3	O
m.	O
1	O
23a	O
283	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Square	O
Box	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
24	O
268	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
n.	O
3	O
269	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
p.	O
2	O
270	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
o	O
.	O
6	O
271	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
o	O
.	O
6	O
272	O
.	O
Piscis	O
N.	O
D	O
?	O
p.	O
2	O
-273	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
lolligo	O
w	O
t.	O
223.	O
only	O
blacker	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
barnacles	O
sticking	O
together	O
.	O
Acus	O
.	O
m.	O
1	O
-274	O
.	O
30	O
A	O
saucer	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
-275	O
.	O
30	O
Another	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
234	O
-276	O
.	O
30	O
Another	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
-277	O
.	O
30	O
A	O
cup	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
-278	O
.	O
30	O
A	O
cover	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
-279	O
.	O
30	O
Another	O
cup	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
221	O
-280	O
.	O
30	O
A	O
ball	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
221	O
.	O
-281	O
.	O
30	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
221	O
-282	O
.	O
30	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
0	O
221	O
25	O
283	O
.	O
Three	O
small	O
loligo	O
s.	O
&	O
another	O
small	O
fish	O
.	O
m.	O
5	O
-284	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
tri	O
angular	O
fossil	O
siliquastrum	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
?	O
/	O
Ichthyodontium	O
metamorphoses	O
seu	O
glosso	O
petrarum	O
in	O
vulgares	O
calculos	O
abeuntum	O
Specimina	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
lith	O
.	O
p.	O
65	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1294	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-285	O
.	O
Dog	O
fish	O
or	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
?	O
286	O
.	O
One	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
tongue	O
of	O
the	O
Nari	O
Nari	O
vid	O
.	O
antea	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
288	O
.	O
Siliquastrum	O
subnigrum	O
pectinatum	O
maximum	O
of	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Floyd	I-pers
dugg	O
up	O
in	O
England	B-place
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
289	O
.	O
22	O
W.	O
The	O
same	O
dugg	O
up	O
in	O
Maryland	B-place
&	O
Vid	O
458.	O
sent	O
from	O
thence	O
given	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
ff	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
290	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
458	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-i	O
291	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
palat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-i	O
.	O
292	O
.	O
A	O
gray	O
lapis	O
bufonius	O
or	O
toadstone	O
?	O
an	O
Bonduch	O
?	O
199.	O
b	O
+	O
293	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
of	O
an	O
orbis	O
piscis	O
fossil	O
small	O
199	O
b	O
26	O
294.	O
a	O
siliquastrum	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Floid	I-pers
.	I-pers
295	O
.	O
Radix	O
of	O
the	O
trochites	O
?	O
siliquastrum	O
?	O
echinites	O
?	O
199.	O
b	O
296	O
.	O
Another	O
sort	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
199	O
b	O
297	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
hollow	O
long	O
toadstone	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Floid	I-pers
.	I-pers
298	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
ish	O
yellowish	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
162.	O
a	O
p.	O
6	O
299	O
.	O
A	O
long	O
yellowish	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
300	O
.	O
Ichthyodontites	O
teretiformis	O
.	O
D.	B-pers
Floid	I-pers
.	I-pers
301	O
.	O
Siliquastrum	O
minimum	O
subviride	O
.	O
Ejusd	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
162.	O
a	O
302	O
.	O
The	O
vertelbra	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
303	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Lapis	O
bufonius	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
5.	O
gray	O
788	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
304	O
.	O
22	O
w	O
Glossopetra	O
fossilis	O
striata	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
199.	O
b	O
305	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Siliquastrum	O
maximum	O
subviride	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
199	O
b	O
306	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Phallus	O
saxatilis	O
.	O
199	O
b	O
307	O
.	O
Glossopetra	O
an	O
siliquastrum	O
.	O
-308	O
.	O
The	O
Vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
241	O
.	O
27	O
-309	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
porpesse	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-310	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
whip	O
ray	O
or	O
Sting	O
ray	O
.	O
partinaca	O
marina	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
given	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Petiver	I-pers
.	I-pers
/	O
w	O
t.	O
severall	O
stings	O
.	O
221	O
r	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
1	O
&	O
c	O
-312	O
.	O
A	O
Barracuda	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
-313	O
.	O
A	O
quadr	O
angular	O
fish	O
.	O
b	O
241	O
314.	O
piscis	O
triangulatis	O
ex	O
toto	O
maculosus	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
315	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
small	O
saw	O
of	O
the	O
pristis	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
316	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
something	O
larger	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
317	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
318	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
pisas	O
triangularis	O
.	O
319	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
ovarium	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
221.	O
e.	O
221.	O
g.	O
221.	O
n.	O
320	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
g.	O
321	O
.	O
The	O
bone	O
of	O
an	O
asellus	O
221	O
y	O
.	O
-322	O
.	O
The	O
pitcher	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
Isles	O
of	O
Orkney	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
D	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	I-pers
an	O
Lumpus	O
?	O
241	O
f	O
-323	O
.	O
A	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
whales	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
222.	O
c	O
-324	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
222.	O
c	O
28	O
325	O
.	O
✓	O
piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornutus	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-326	O
.	O
The	O
cranium	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
lEast	B-place
Indies	I-place
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
k.	O
i	O
-327	O
.	O
Another	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
328	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
bone	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
329	O
.	O
A	O
shark	O
or	O
galeus	O
's	O
tooth	O
from	O
malta	B-place
lying	O
in	O
its	O
bed	O
of	O
gray	O
earth	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
330	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
teeth	O
sett	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
221	O
dd	O
cc	O
.	O
331	O
.	O
A	O
buforites	O
or	O
toads	O
tone	O
fastened	O
in	O
plaister	O
of	O
Paris	O
or	O
chalk	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
-	O
Buforites	O
medius	O
or	O
biculatus	O
sen.	O
bufonites	O
vulgatior	O
Anglicus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Eth	O
.	O
p.	O
70	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1363	O
.	O
183	O
.	O
332	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
brown	O
/	O
bufonites	O
majusculus	O
atrorubens	O
instar	O
capsulæ	O
glandis	O
quercinæ	O
:	O
lapidis	O
bufiru	O
varietas	O
1	O
a.	O
apud	O
Auselmum	O
Boetuim	O
delineata	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
p.	O
750	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
fig	O
.	O
6.	O
lith	O
.	O
1362.	O
pietra	O
di	O
rospo	O
di	O
figura	O
.	O
circolare	O
.	O
Imp	O
.	O
p.	O
661	O
?	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
333	O
.	O
A	O
smaller	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
-334	O
.	O
Sperma	O
ceti	O
from	O
the	O
whate	O
cast	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
.	O
221.	O
e	O
-335	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
dogg	O
fish	O
fossil	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
29	O
-336	O
92	O
A	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
round	O
tooth	O
or	O
fishes	O
bone	O
fossil	O
.	O
/	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
deal	O
board	O
turnd	O
into	O
flint	O
Stone	O
found	O
at	O
Richmond	B-place
in	I-place
surry	I-place
,	O
an	O
lobsters	O
tail	O
?	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Edwin	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
222	O
c	O
-337	O
.	O
92	O
A	O
fossil	O
brown	O
siliquastru	O
a	O
m	O
lupini	O
siliquam	O
nonnihil	O
referens	O
seu	O
siliquastrum	O
lupinatum	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
747.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
L.	O
Siliquastrum	O
latiuscubum	O
seu	O
lypini	O
valvulo	O
emulun	O
.	O
es	O
usd	O
.	O
lishophyl	O
.	O
p.	O
73	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1448	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
245	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
c	O
-338.	O
small	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
a	O
sellus	O
?	O
221	O
ff	O
-339	O
.	O
Ichthyites	O
seu	O
Ichthyomorphus	O
subflavi	O
coloris	O
,	O
qui	O
attritus	O
-	O
cornn	O
ustum	O
redolet	O
.	O
Ex	O
lapicidina	O
Oeningensi	O
prope	O
lithopolin	O
ad	O
Rhenum	O
.	O
from	O
D	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Lavater	I-pers
.	I-pers
222.	O
c	O
340	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
skin	O
of	O
an	O
orbis	O
.	O
221.	O
p.	O
-341	O
.	O
✓	O
Ising	O
glasse	O
or	O
fish	O
glew	O
the	O
swoon	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fish	O
from	O
Astracan	O
.	O
221.	O
f	O
-342	O
.	O
Acus	O
221.	O
e	O
-343	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
-344	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
finn	O
of	O
the	O
sperma	O
ceti	O
whale	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	B-place
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-345.	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
cutcula	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
g	O
-346	O
.	O
Sperma	O
ceti	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
purified	O
after	O
ettmullers	O
way	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
30	O
-347	O
.	O
The	O
scale	O
of	O
a	O
sturgeon	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-348	O
.	O
The	O
ovarium	O
of	O
a	O
dogg	O
fish	O
?	O
/	O
ovum	O
Raiæ	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
P.	O
221.	O
g	O
-349	O
.	O
The	O
back	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
fossil	O
?	O
From	O
Richmond	B-place
tile	I-place
pitts	I-place
.	O
350	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
?	O
or	O
frog	O
?	O
221.	O
y	O
351	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
cuculus	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
w	O
ch	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
sterard	I-pers
gave	O
M	O
r.	O
Courten	B-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
p	O
352	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
kind	O
of	O
dorado	O
?	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
353.	O
prickles	O
of	O
the	O
thorn	O
back	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-354	O
.	O
A	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
.	O
fossil	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
i	O
-355	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Two	O
Siliquastrum	O
minus	O
triangulum	O
seu	O
minus	O
conchæ	O
adinstar	O
rest	O
ellatum	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
N	O
o	O
,	O
200.	O
p.	O
748.	O
fig	O
.	O
3.	O
lithophyl	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1488	O
.	O
1489.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
246	O
.	O
/	O
tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
29.	O
m.	O
221	O
cc	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
sha	O
green	O
or	O
fish	O
skin	O
?	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Viller	I-pers
mont	O
.	O
Lizards	O
skin	O
?	O
221.	O
e	O
357	O
.	O
A	O
sharks	O
tooth	O
.	O
221	O
cc	O
-358	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
skin	O
of	O
a	O
litle	O
whale	O
or	O
Pike	O
fish	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
Cramond	B-place
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
Oct.	O
1699	O
.	O
31	O
-359	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
substance	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
of	O
the	O
pike	O
fish	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
Cramond	B-place
.	O
An	O
the	O
teeth	O
of	O
a	O
soft	O
fish	O
or	O
beetle	O
.	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
Polypas	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
221.	O
f.	O
221.	O
e.	O
-360	O
.	O
The	O
prickle	O
stands	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
called	O
an	O
old	O
wife	O
?	O
221.	O
g	O
-361	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
Loligo	O
?	O
221.	O
p.	O
-362	O
.	O
✓	O
Os	O
sæpiæ	O
.	O
Cuttle	O
bone	O
.	O
221.	O
t.	O
-363	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
artificiall	O
dragon	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
rays	O
skin	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-364	O
.	O
✓	O
Acus	O
?	O
221.	O
a	O
-365	O
.	O
✓	O
Acus	O
piscis	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
?	O
221.	O
r	O
-366	O
.	O
Fucus	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
ray	O
or	O
dogfish	O
ovary	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
-	O
367	O
.	O
Round	O
small	O
bone	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
368	O
The	O
ovary	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
or	O
dog	O
fish	O
.	O
Galei	O
g	O
Cauci	O
.	O
1	O
sh	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
32	O
369	O
.	O
✓	O
Bones	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
a	O
large	O
asellus	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
370	O
.	O
A	O
fish	O
bone	O
sharpen	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
bodkin	O
from	O
Magellan	B-place
Streights	I-place
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
371	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
fish	O
bone	O
petrified	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-372	O
.	O
Tri	O
angular	O
white	O
bones	O
from	O
the	O
maw	O
or	O
Stomach	O
of	O
a	O
cod	O
?	O
373	O
.	O
Teeth	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
are	O
the	O
toad	O
stones	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
374	O
.	O
Stone	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
-	O
shark	O
.	O
221.	O
g	O
-375	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Shark	O
&	O
dogg	O
fish	O
teeth	O
of	O
severall	O
sorts	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
a	O
222.	O
a	O
-376	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
fishes	O
scale	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
1386	O
.	O
✓	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
377	O
.	O
A	O
whales	O
vertebre	O
?	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
given	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	I-pers
fossil	O
.	O
1697	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
378	O
.	O
A	O
smaller	O
.	O
222.	O
c	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
33	O
379	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
bone	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
cetaceous	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
-380	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
round	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
yellowish	O
colour	O
.	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
fossil	O
.	O
222.	O
c	O
381	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
bone	O
of	O
the	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
-	O
whale	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
black	O
&	O
fossil	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-382	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
scapula	O
of	O
a	O
cetaceous	O
fish	O
fossil	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
383	O
.	O
22	O
w	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
rib	O
of	O
a	O
cetaceous	O
fish	O
petrified	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
?	O
221.	O
e	O
-384	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
glossopetra	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-385	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
white	O
Dogg	O
fish	O
tooth	O
or	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
w	O
t.	O
2	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
root	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-386	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
same	O
black	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
34	O
-387	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Smaller	O
dogg	O
fish	O
or	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
or	O
serpents	O
tongues	O
,	O
black	O
&	O
white	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
-388	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Larger	O
&	O
smaller	O
broad	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
serrated	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-389	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
same	O
not	O
serrated	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
390	O
.	O
✓	O
Whale	O
bone	O
.	O
220.	O
d	O
391	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
The	O
ear	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
cetaceous	O
fish	O
auditory	O
bones	O
of	O
a	O
cods	O
head	O
.	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
's	O
one	O
mine	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
392	O
.	O
92	O
Sharkes	O
vertebres	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
393	O
.	O
22	O
y	O
The	O
same	O
,	O
petrified	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
394	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
Sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Wight	I-place
.	O
f.	O
221.	O
a	O
395	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
396	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
chops	O
of	O
a	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
35	O
-397	O
.	O
Two	O
bufonites	O
one	O
large	O
oblong	O
the	O
other	O
round	O
&	O
small	O
.	O
medius	O
rotularis	O
alveolo	O
utrinqz	O
donatus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
7.	O
lith	O
.	O
p.	O
70	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1365	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-398	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
tongue	O
of	O
the	O
nari	O
nari	O
-	O
fossil	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
399	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
shoulder	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
,	O
black	O
&	O
fossil	O
?	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
from	O
Mary	B-place
land	I-place
.	O
221.	O
n	O
400	O
.	O
A	O
vertebre	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
401	O
.	O
A	O
round	O
bone	O
w	O
ch	O
.	O
lyes	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
402	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
colour	O
:	O
221.	O
c	O
403	O
.	O
The	O
Bones	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
palate	O
&	O
tongue	O
of	O
the	O
Nari	O
-	O
nari	O
.	O
M	O
r.	O
-	O
Vernon	B-pers
's	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
404	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
some	O
teeth	O
or	O
palate	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
like	O
Siliquastra	O
dugg	O
up	O
at	O
making	O
the	O
fortifications	O
of	O
Livonia	B-place
&	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Krieg	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
cc	O
36	O
-405	O
.	O
Lapis	O
tiburonum	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
406	O
.	O
✓	O
Teeth	O
of	O
the	O
cod	O
fish	O
?	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernons	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
y	O
407	O
.	O
✓	O
26	O
Whitings	O
teeth	O
.	O
/	O
Os	O
ex	O
capitea	O
ss	O
elli	O
majoris	O
cum	O
fluore	O
adnato	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
748.	O
fig	O
.	O
3a	O
.	O
The	O
fluor	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
bone	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
.	O
408	O
.	O
✓	O
6	O
whitings	O
teeth	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
mother	O
of	O
pearle	O
or	O
shining	O
.	O
409	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
.	O
Vernons	O
.	O
/	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
4	O
sorts	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
410	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Dogfish	O
teeth	O
or	O
Serpents	O
tongues	O
glossopetræ	O
.	O
English	O
?	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
411	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Small	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
?	O
English	O
.	O
/	O
The	O
largest	O
from	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
in	O
Kent	B-place
near	O
Woolwich	O
.	O
/	O
Glossopetra	O
exigua	O
cum	O
mandibulæ	O
fragmento	O
lapideo	O
adnato	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p	O
754.	O
fig	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
221	O
cc	O
412	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
sea	O
morse	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
crooked	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
Streight	O
sent	O
into	O
Turky	B-place
to	O
make	O
scimiters	O
handles	O
sold	O
at	O
5	O
sh	O
.	O
&	O
lib	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
-413	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
whale	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
/	O
From	O
Jamaica	B-place
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
221.	O
t.	O
-414	O
.	O
The	O
teeth	O
of	O
some	O
cetaceous	O
fish	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
.	O
Vernon	B-pers
's	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
37	O
415	O
.	O
A	O
mandible	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
416	O
.	O
The	O
scale	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
?	O
an	O
of	O
a	O
scaly	O
Lizard	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2.	O
lacerta	O
squamosa	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
417	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetra	O
tooth	O
or	O
dog	O
fish	O
from	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
sheppey	B-place
Isle	I-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Snakes	O
tongue	O
petrified	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
418	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
small	O
w	O
t.	O
severall	O
a	O
pices	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
root	O
.	O
221	O
dd	O
419	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetæ	O
&	O
dogfish	O
teeth	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
.	O
fossil	O
.	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
y	O
420	O
.	O
22	O
Y	O
Two	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
sharks	O
back	O
bone	O
one	O
fossil	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
.	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
.	O
/	O
Larger	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Plott	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
dd	O
222.	O
c	O
421	O
.	O
92	O
A	O
siliquastrum	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
422	O
.	O
A	O
tooth	O
from	O
the	O
Jaw	O
of	O
the	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
-423	O
.	O
✓	O
Lapides	O
Carpionum	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
38	O
-424	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
J.	O
Ammonites	O
seu	O
Hammites	O
s	O
f	O
ubfla=	O
=vus	O
ovis	O
cinereis	O
refertus	O
reperi	O
tur	O
in	O
Argovia	O
in	O
Schenkenberg	O
retro	O
Arce	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
scheuchzer	O
lithog	O
.	O
Helvet	O
.	O
curios	O
.	O
p.	O
40.	O
fig	O
.	O
55.	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lavater	I-pers
.	I-pers
37	O
-425	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetræ	O
minores	O
e	O
lapicidina	O
ad	O
villam	O
saw	O
prope	O
Bulacum	O
Drtionis	O
Tigurinæ	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
426	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
ribb	O
of	O
a	O
porpus	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
-427	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
A	O
small	O
acus	O
or	O
needle	O
fish	O
.	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
4	O
-428	O
.	O
The	O
heart	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
lamprey	O
eel	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
-429	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
variegated	O
Histrix	O
piscis	O
from	O
the	O
Leeward	B-place
Islands	I-place
given	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	I-pers
-430.	O
some	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
polypus	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221	O
c	O
38a	O
#	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
245.	O
tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
39	O
-431	O
.	O
An	O
Hippocampus	O
from	O
the	O
E.	B-place
Indies	I-place
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
.	I-pers
Vid	O
.	O
Du	O
Hald	O
tom	O
.	O
3.	O
page	O
.	O
484	O
Du	O
Hai	O
ma	O
ov	O
Chevalde	O
mar	O
concerning	O
the	O
Virtues	O
&	O
uses	O
of	O
this	O
in	O
China	B-place
221.	O
n	O
-432	O
.	O
The	O
horn	O
of	O
a	O
rhinoceros	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
421	O
-433	O
.	O
✓	O
Bones	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
Mauritius	B-place
Island	I-place
.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
221.	O
k	O
-434	O
.	O
Shark	O
stone	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
-435	O
.	O
Ichthyospondylus	O
latruncularis	O
-	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
medius	O
.	O
from	O
Purton	O
-	O
passage	O
.	O
from	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
the	O
same	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221	O
i	O
.	O
-436	O
.	O
Glossopetra	O
rostrum	O
corvinum	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
referens	O
auriculata	O
from	O
the	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Sheppey	I-place
in	O
Kent	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-437	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Plectronites	O
lævis	O
mucrone	O
paulo	O
acutiore	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
751.	O
fig	O
.	O
B.	O
lith	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1338.	O
vulgaris	O
from	O
Marcham	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Lluid	I-pers
.	I-pers
an	O
dog	O
fish	O
tooth	O
?	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-438.	O
siliquastrum	O
phases	O
latum	O
sea	O
ad	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
#	O
phaseoli	O
valonlum	O
quo	O
dammodo	O
accedens	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
200.	O
p.	O
747.	O
fig	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
&	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
L.	O
litho	O
phis	O
L.	O
1440	O
.	O
1441	O
.	O
&	O
2	O
from	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Stansfield	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
221.	O
c.	O
c	O
40	O
-439	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
siliquastrum	O
marmoreum	O
punctu	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
=laria	O
tortilis	O
dictum	O
Act	O
.	O
S.	O
R.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Num	O
.	O
200.	O
fig	O
.	O
4.	O
p.	O
748.	O
from	O
Stansfield	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-440	O
.	O
92	O
Bufonites	O
medius	O
planovalis	O
from	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
Marcham	B-place
in	I-place
Berkshire	I-place
from	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
the	O
same	O
/	O
several	O
sized	O
,	O
/	O
Partick	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
a	O
jaw	O
with	O
one	O
small	O
tooth	O
&	O
a	O
broken	O
one	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-441	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
small	O
orbis	O
echinatus	O
or	O
histrix	O
piscis	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-442	O
.	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
cornutus	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-443	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-444	O
.	O
The	O
toad	O
fish	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-445	O
.	O
A	O
jaw	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
,	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
41	O
-446	O
.	O
Two	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-447	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
acus	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
Acus	O
.	O
Salvian	O
.	O
p.	O
68	O
.	O
Gesn	O
.	O
p.	O
13	O
.	O
Acus	O
Vulgaris	O
oppiani	O
Aldrov	O
.	O
lib	O
.	O
cap	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
Gar	O
Fish	O
.	O
Nat	O
.	O
Hist	O
of	O
Jamaica	O
tom	O
.	O
2.	O
p.	O
283.	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
by	O
the	O
Rev	O
d.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
l.	O
241.	O
b	O
.	O
-448	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Turdus	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
l.	O
-449	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Barracuda	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
l.	O
-450	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
Snook	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
l.	O
-451	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
turdus	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
l.	O
-452	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
silver	O
fish	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
perishd	O
221.	O
l.	O
-453	O
.	O
Another	O
sort	O
of	O
silver	O
fish	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
42	O
-454	O
.	O
An	O
Hippocampus	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-455	O
.	O
An	O
Hippocampus	O
echinated	O
or	O
w	O
t.	O
prickles	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-456	O
.	O
Prickly	O
knobbs	O
of	O
the	O
thornback	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-457	O
.	O
Sting	O
of	O
the	O
sting	O
ray	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-458	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Tongue	O
of	O
the	O
nari	O
nari	O
from	O
the	O
289	O
.	O
290	O
same	O
.	O
One	O
joint	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Markd	O
131	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
-459	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
,	O
fossil	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-460	O
.	O
The	O
beak	O
of	O
the	O
parrot	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-461	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
mouth	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
fish	O
?	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221	O
43	O
-462	O
.	O
The	O
chops	O
of	O
the	O
orbis	O
piscis	O
fossil	O
in	O
England	B-place
.	O
/	O
From	O
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
.	O
/	O
Flatter	O
&	O
larger	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-463	O
.	O
A	O
fossil	O
large	O
Sharks	O
tooth	O
serrated	O
from	O
Malta	B-place
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Arundel	I-pers
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-464	O
.	O
A	O
whales	O
cornea	O
or	O
eye	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-465	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
-466	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
w	O
t.	O
auriculæ	O
or	O
appendices	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
from	O
Lancashire	B-place
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-467	O
.	O
Small	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
called	O
serpents	O
tongues	O
mark	O
'd	O
H.H	O
.	O
/	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
-	O
Richmond	B-place
.	I-place
tile	I-place
pitts	I-place
/	O
L.	O
/	O
Boccone	O
Recherches	O
et	O
Obs	O
.	O
Natural	O
.	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
42.	O
et	O
Edit	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
fig	O
.	O
p.	O
314	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-468	O
.	O
Lapis	O
Tuberonum	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-469	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
prickly	O
fish	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	B-place
of	I-place
Wight	I-place
?	O
Sco	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
44	O
-470	O
.	O
Ichthyocolla	O
.	O
off	O
.	O
181.	O
i	O
.	O
-471	O
.	O
Mandibula	O
lucÿ	O
piscis	O
.	O
off	O
.	O
181	O
i	O
-472	O
.	O
Os	O
sepiæ	O
,	O
testa	O
sepiæ	O
off	O
.	O
181.	O
i	O
.	O
-473	O
.	O
Sperma	O
ceti	O
off	O
.	O
181.	O
x	O
.	O
-474	O
.	O
Testæ	O
aquatilium	O
entalium	O
off	O
?	O
stone	O
of	O
the	O
codfish	O
?	O
181.	O
x	O
-475	O
.	O
The	O
Spikes	O
or	O
aculei	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-476	O
✓	O
Lapis	O
carpionum	O
or	O
stone	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
carps	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-477	O
.	O
The	O
Scale	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
called	O
Tarpum	O
silverd	O
in	O
part	O
over	O
.	O
221	O
g	O
-478	O
.	O
A	O
Spike	O
which	O
sticks	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
called	O
an	O
old	O
wife	O
?	O
221	O
g	O
-479	O
.	O
Ossa	O
ex	O
cazne	O
rhombi	O
majoris	O
.	O
221.	O
l.	O
-480	O
.	O
Acus	O
?	O
221.	O
e	O
45	O
-481	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
nerves	O
or	O
tendons	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
-482	O
.	O
A	O
sharks	O
jaw	O
.	O
f	O
-483	O
.	O
A	O
sculpin	O
fish	O
,	O
toad	O
fish	O
or	O
orbis	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
-484	O
.	O
The	O
under	O
jaw	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
dolphin	O
?	O
221.	O
y	O
-485	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
needle	O
fish	O
.	O
P.	O
221.	O
e	O
-486	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
stone	O
of	O
the	O
codfish	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
embodied	O
in	O
chalk	O
&	O
lying	O
in	O
its	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
bed	O
.	O
from	O
Kent	B-place
the	O
chalk	O
pitts	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
An	O
counterfeit	O
?	O
221.	O
y	O
-487	O
.	O
The	O
lesser	O
stones	O
of	O
the	O
codfish	O
-	O
kind	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-488	O
.	O
The	O
hard	O
row	O
>	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
.	O
Or	O
whither	O
it	O
be	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
some	O
insect	O
of	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
a	O
honey	O
comb	O
.	O
P.	O
221	O
y	O
-489	O
.	O
A	O
toadstone	O
in	O
its	O
chalky	O
bed	O
.	O
221	O
y	O
-490	O
.	O
Sperma	O
ceti	O
.	O
246.	O
o	O
-491	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
The	O
ear	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
fossil	O
from	O
Maryland	B-place
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
dd	O
46	O
-492	O
.	O
The	O
hippocampus	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
g	O
-493	O
.	O
The	O
ovarium	O
of	O
a	O
ray	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Hicks	I-pers
from	O
Devonshire	B-place
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-494	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
Hippocampus	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
-495	O
.	O
An	O
hippocampus	O
very	O
prickly	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
given	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
g	O
-496.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
scale	O
of	O
a	O
sturgeon	O
?	O
called	O
Cachimar	O
in	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
where	O
't	O
is	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
drugg	O
&	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
thence	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Adair	I-pers
.	I-pers
-497	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
remora	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
-498	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
prickly	O
cartilaginous	O
fish	O
.	O
f	O
-499	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Large	O
black	O
sharks	O
tooth	O
.	O
P.	O
22	O
47	O
-500	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
scorpion	O
?	O
fish	O
from	O
,	O
Portsmouth	B-place
.	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
221	O
ff	O
-501	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
spotted	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
-502	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
long	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
-503	O
.	O
✓	O
Acus	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Portsmouth	B-place
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-504	O
.	O
The	O
scorpion	O
fish	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-5	O
The	O
ovary	O
of	O
the	O
polypus	O
?	O
-505	O
.	O
508	O
A	O
sepia	O
or	O
loligo	O
from	O
the	O
cape	O
of	O
good	O
hope	O
by	O
Dr.	B-pers
Dolnas	I-pers
.	I-pers
o	O
.	O
7	O
506	O
.	O
509	O
piscis	O
cornutus	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-507	O
.	O
✓	O
Orbis	O
piscis	O
muricatus	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
48	O
-508	O
.	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
,	O
bufonites	O
,	O
siliquastras	O
&	O
c.	O
stuck	O
upon	O
Malta	B-place
earth	O
?	O
As	O
a	O
Talisman	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-509	O
.	O
Sperma	O
ceti	O
whale	O
's	O
tooth	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-510	O
.	O
✓	O
Another	O
.	O
221.	O
t.	O
-511	O
.	O
The	O
sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
flatt	O
fish	O
?	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
-512	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
orbis	O
muricatus	O
from	O
Virginia	B-place
.-	O
221.	O
r	O
-513	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
whales	O
tooth	O
crooked	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
t.	O
-514	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
vesica	O
natatoria	O
or	O
Swimm	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fish	O
?	O
221.	O
p	O
-515	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
cornea	O
of	O
the	O
eye	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
fish	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
-516	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
49	O
-517	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
shark	O
?	O
fossil	O
?	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
.	O
W.	O
-518	O
.	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
shark	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-519.	O
part	O
of	O
large	O
fishes	O
bone	O
petrified	O
&	O
brought	O
from	O
Harwich	B-place
cliffe	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
-520	O
.	O
✓	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fishes	O
tooth	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
-521	O
.	O
✓	O
One	O
joint	O
of	O
a	O
sharks	O
back	O
bone	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-522	O
.	O
✓	O
22	O
W	O
Two	O
joints	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
petrified	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
t	O
-523	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
whales	O
tooth	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
-524	O
.	O
-523	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
unicorns	O
horn	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
.	O
-525	O
.	O
-524	O
✓	O
A	O
large	O
fishes	O
tooth	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
50	O
-526	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
quadrangularis	O
cornutus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221	O
a	O
-527	O
.	O
Piscis	O
quadrangularis	O
non	O
cornutus	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
given	O
me	O
by	O
D	B-pers
r	I-pers
.	O
221.	O
g	O
-528	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
bones	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
cods	O
head	O
or	O
the	O
auditory	O
bones	O
observe	O
how	O
they	O
by	O
&	O
how	O
they	O
may	O
conferre	O
to	O
hearing	O
&	O
read	O
Casseruis	O
about	O
that	O
organ	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
hath	O
only	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
a	O
pikes	O
head	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
now	O
examine	O
two	O
cods	O
heads	O
they	O
being	O
common	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
bones	O
are	O
also	O
in	O
whitings	O
&	O
haddocks	O
.	O
S	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Tho	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
ff	O
221.	O
n	O
-529	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
cods	O
head	O
?	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
p	O
-530	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
Sturgeons	O
bone	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
p	O
-531	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
mouth	O
of	O
the	O
aquila	O
Piscis	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
51	O
-532	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
fish	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-533	O
.	O
Two	O
chrystallin	O
humours	O
of	O
a	O
dogg	O
fish	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
tunica	O
&	O
processus	O
ciliaris	O
,	O
The	O
other	O
without	O
.	O
S	B-pers
t.	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
g	O
-534	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
chrystallin	O
humour	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fish	O
.	O
221.	O
p	O
-535	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
chrystallin	O
humour	O
of	O
the	O
eye	O
of	O
a	O
gladius	O
piscis	O
,	O
Xiphias	O
or	O
-	O
swordfish	O
.	O
S	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Tho	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
p.	O
-536	O
.	O
The	O
chrystallin	O
humour	O
of	O
a	O
salmon	O
Id	O
.	O
221	O
e	O
-537	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
cornea	O
of	O
a	O
gladius	O
piscis	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-538	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
221.	O
p	O
52	O
-539	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
long	O
tapering	O
fish	O
w	O
t.	O
2	O
finns	O
prickly	O
all	O
a	O
long	O
the	O
back	O
&	O
belly	O
?	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
vid	O
.	O
Willuglib	O
.	O
221.	O
p.	O
-540	O
.	O
✓	O
Another	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
make	O
w	O
t.	O
soft	O
finns	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-541	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
small	O
fish	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
rough	O
skin	O
,	O
prickle	O
hamated	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
&	O
long	O
snout	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-542	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
scorpion	O
fish	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-543.	O
pars	O
ossis	O
cæti	O
capti	O
in	O
Thamesi	O
fluvio	O
prope	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
Jun	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
1658	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
-544	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
some	O
Siliquastra	O
sticking	O
in	O
gravell	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
e	O
-545	O
.	O
87	O
Os	O
piscis	O
vulgo	O
vocat	O
.	O
ex	O
dono	O
fratris	O
Tatton	O
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Br	I-pers
.	I-pers
states	O
221.	O
ff	O
53	O
-546	O
.	O
Urtica	O
marina	O
soluta	O
purpurea	O
oblonga	O
cirrhis	O
longissimis	O
.	O
A	O
Carvell	O
.	O
Hist	O
.	O
Jam	O
.	O
p.	O
7.	O
tab	O
.	O
4.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Holo=	O
=thurius	O
Indicus	O
velivolans	O
.	O
Zoophytum	O
venenatissimum	O
&	O
causticum	O
per	O
summa	O
maris	O
Indici	O
velificars	O
,	O
coloreiridem	O
forma	O
expansam	O
sed	O
vacuam	O
vesicam	O
referens	O
,	O
parte	O
superna	O
velo	O
,	O
inferna	O
multis	O
longissimis	O
filamentis	O
quasi-	O
remis	O
instractum	O
.	O
Een	O
Bezaantie	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
14	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
L	O
'	O
Ortie	O
marine	O
.	O
Seba	O
tom	O
.	O
1.	O
p.	O
45	O
.	O
Tab	O
.	O
29.	O
fig	O
.	O
2.	O
u	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
-547	O
.	O
Sepiola	O
Americana	O
Nigra	O
.	O
Een	O
klein	O
.	O
swart	O
Americaanse	O
Zeekatie	O
.	O
p.	O
61.	O
mus	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
249	O
.	O
-548	O
.	O
Aselli	O
piscis	O
uterus	O
cum	O
annexis	O
testiculis	O
.	O
Hom	O
en	O
Kint	O
van	O
een	O
Cabeljauw	O
aan	O
een	O
ander	O
gewassen	O
.	O
Mus	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
p.	O
7	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
83.	O
n.	O
7	O
-549	O
.	O
Tiburonis	O
minoris	O
,	O
galeo	O
similis	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Haaring	O
-	O
Haay	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
5	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
49.	O
n.	O
7	O
54	O
-550	O
.	O
Anguilla	O
Zeylanica	O
saxatilis	O
Venenz	O
=ata	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Zeylonse	O
.	O
Vergiftige	O
Aal	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
1	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
-551	O
.	O
Carpio	O
Indicus	O
piscis	O
minor	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
Karper	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
2	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
10.	O
n.	O
1	O
-552	O
.	O
Piscis	O
Indicus	O
seserino	O
affinis	O
nigri=	O
=cantibus	O
Lati	O
strÿs	O
ex	O
transverso	O
insignitus	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
plat=	O
=vis	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
8	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
103.	O
m.	O
5	O
-553	O
.	O
Piscis	O
marinus	O
Indicus	O
seserino	O
affinis	O
pallide	O
flavescens	O
,	O
fuscis	O
per	O
transversum	O
lineis	O
notatus	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
Zee	O
Vis	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
4	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
37.	O
o	O
.	O
5	O
-554	O
.	O
Piscis	O
Indicus	O
marinus	O
,	O
truttæ	O
facie	O
minor	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
-	O
Voorens	O
-	O
geewÿs	O
Zee	O
vispe	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
8	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
105.	O
p.	O
1	O
55	O
-555	O
.	O
Anguilla	O
Americana	O
marina	O
.	O
Een	O
Americaanse	O
Zee-Aal	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
13	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
192.	O
o	O
.	O
1	O
-556	O
.	O
Aper	O
marinus	O
Indicus	O
piscis	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaans	O
Zee	O
varken	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
14	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
202.	O
b	O
241	O
-557	O
.	O
Pisciculus	O
Indicus	O
quadragularis	O
,	O
frontern	O
daobus	O
cornubus	O
armatus	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaans	O
vier	O
kantig	O
visje	O
,	O
met	O
twee	O
horens	O
op	O
het	O
voor	O
hoofd	O
en	O
twee	O
by	O
de	O
stoart	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
19	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
305.	O
p.	O
4	O
-558	O
.	O
Piscis	O
saxatilis	O
Indicus	O
,	O
maculis	O
gryseis	O
distinctus	O
insignitus	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
steenactige	O
vis	O
n.	O
1	O
56	O
-559	O
.	O
Orbis	O
marinus	O
colore	O
subcæruleo	O
&	O
viridi	O
permixtus	O
Gesn	O
.	O
mixinus	O
seu	O
Maco	O
vulgo	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
een	O
Blaaw-vis	O
,	O
snotol	O
=fie	O
genaant	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
4	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
-560	O
.	O
Anguilla	O
Americana	O
venenata	O
,	O
varÿs	O
quasi	O
characteribus	O
Arabicis	O
perpulchre	O
inscripta	O
.	O
Een	O
Americaans	O
vegiftig	O
Aaltie	O
seer	O
fra	O
a	O
y	O
met	O
Arabise	O
characters	O
gevlakt	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
12	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
179.	O
n.	O
7	O
-561	O
.	O
Acus	O
marinus	O
Indicus	O
major	O
.	O
Een	O
groote	O
Indiaanse	O
Zee	O
-	O
naklde	O
.	O
Herm	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
15	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
232.	O
n.	O
5	O
-562	O
.	O
Pisciculus	O
Danubÿ	O
fluvÿ	O
,	O
tempestates	O
indicans	O
,	O
cœlo	O
nubilo	O
profundum	O
,	O
sereno	O
superficiem	O
petens	O
.	O
Een	O
Visse	O
uit	O
de	O
Donnaw	O
,	O
Onweer	O
te	O
kennen	O
gevende	O
.	O
Hema	O
.	O
Mus	O
.	O
p.	O
17	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
265.	O
n.	O
5	O
57	O
-563	O
.	O
Pisciculus	O
Chinensis	O
argenteus	O
.	O
Vivus	O
argenteo	O
colore	O
Splenders	O
.	O
Een	O
Chineses	O
silver	O
visje	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
18	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
276.	O
p.	O
2	O
-564	O
.	O
Serra	O
piscis	O
.	O
Yonge	O
swaard	O
of	O
Laag	O
visies	O
?	O
Herm	O
.	O
mus	O
.	O
p.	O
22	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
19	O
?	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-565	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
-566	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
marinus	O
Indicus	O
seserino	O
affinis	O
pallide	O
flavescens	O
,	O
fuscis	O
per	O
transversum	O
lineis	O
notatus	O
.	O
Belg	O
.	O
Een	O
Indiaanse	O
Zee	O
vis	O
.	O
Mus	O
.	O
Herm	O
.	O
p.	O
10	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
221.	O
n.	O
-567	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
A	O
stone	O
consisting	O
of	O
eggs	O
or	O
Spawn	O
of	O
fishes	O
,	O
near	O
Kerby	O
in	O
Northampton	B-place
shire	I-place
.	O
170	O
-568	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
stone	O
yellowish	O
from	O
Althrop	B-place
.	O
58	O
-569	O
.	O
Whitings	O
or	O
codfish	O
bones	O
.	O
-570	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
The	O
ear	O
of	O
a	O
porpesse	O
?	O
221.	O
g	O
-571	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
hippocampus	O
.	O
spinosus	O
221	O
a	O
-572	O
.	O
✓	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
long	O
toothe	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
or	O
siliquastrum	O
lying	O
in	O
stone	O
?	O
221.	O
p.	O
-573	O
.	O
Branchiale	O
of	O
a	O
gray	O
colour	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
-574	O
.	O
22	O
y	O
Salmarium	O
trinare	O
anthracinum	O
majus	O
:	O
sive	O
ichthyo	O
spondylus	O
salinum	O
referens	O
,	O
tribus	O
utrinqz	O
naribus	O
ferestratus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
84	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1627	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-575	O
.	O
22	O
y	O
The	O
large	O
vertebre	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
fossil	O
.	O
221	O
ff	O
.	O
221.	O
g	O
-576	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glosso	O
petra	O
picæ	O
linguam	O
referens	O
,	O
sioe	O
ornithoglossum	O
sessile	O
vulgane	O
.	O
Ophio=	O
glossum	O
petræum	O
glossopetra	O
minor	O
Wagneri	O
.	O
p.	O
310	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
59	O
-577	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Siliquastrum	O
tortile	O
gibbosum	O
,	O
minutis	O
punctulis	O
subinde	O
conspersum	O
seu	O
siliquastrum	O
mazmoreum	O
punctularia	O
fortilis	O
dictum	O
phil	O
.	O
Trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
fig	O
.	O
4.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
74	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1283	O
?	O
221.	O
ff	O
-578	O
.	O
92	O
Siliquastrum	O
pisi	O
siliquam	O
referens	O
anthracini	O
coloris	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
73	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1446	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-579	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Plectronites	O
breviusculus	O
radice	O
admodum	O
sessili	O
;	O
seu	O
compactilior	O
eleganter	O
striatus	O
,	O
patellam	O
quandam	O
aduncam	O
nonnihil	O
referens	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
66	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1321	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
-580	O
.	O
A	O
gray	O
redish	O
soft	O
slat	O
in	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
impressions	O
of	O
fish	O
stalks	O
&	O
c	O
?	O
-581	O
.	O
A	O
blew	O
slat	O
where	O
in	O
are	O
the	O
impressions	O
of	O
something	O
like	O
the	O
Scales	O
of	O
fishes	O
.	O
Coal	O
till	O
with	O
land	O
shells	O
on	O
it	O
from	O
Partick	O
wi	O
thin	O
2	O
miles	O
of	O
Glasgow	B-place
in	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-582	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
Hippocampus	O
from	O
Holland	B-place
.	O
221.	O
p	O
60	O
-583	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
scorpius	O
marinus	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Worm	O
.	O
p.	O
267	O
.	O
221	O
a	O
.	O
-584	O
.	O
Monoceros	O
piscis	O
e	O
M.	O
S.	O
R.	O
Will	O
.	O
tab	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Island	O
Maurituis	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0.	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
47	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0.	O
b	O
241	O
.	O
-585	O
.	O
A	O
Turdus	O
marinus	O
?	O
spotted	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-586	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
Whales	O
tooth	O
?	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
p.	O
-587	O
.	O
A	O
canthiodos	O
sive	O
galei	O
spinacis	O
vel	O
acanthiæ	O
Rondeletÿ	O
dens	O
fossilis	O
majusculus	O
atrorubens	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
72	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1417	O
.	O
-588	O
.	O
Pila	O
marina	O
e	O
pïsciculorum	O
ossibus	O
constans	O
.	O
-589	O
.	O
The	O
saw	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
saw	O
fish	O
.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Ayrie	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
c	O
61	O
-590	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
milvus	O
flying	O
fish	O
0	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
0.	O
ef	O
-591	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
smooth	O
hippocampus	O
.	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Ayrie	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
a	O
-592	O
.	O
✓	O
An	O
echinated	O
hippocampus	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-593	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
milvus	O
flying	O
fish	O
from	O
Barbadoes	B-place
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	I-pers
-594	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
back	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
loligo	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
/	O
Gladiolus	O
loliginis	O
.	O
-595	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
mouth	O
&	O
gills	O
of	O
a	O
Turbutt	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-596	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
a	O
turbutt	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
-597	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
side	O
finn	O
of	O
a	O
turbutt	O
.	O
221.	O
a	O
-598	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
221.	O
w	O
62	O
-599	O
.	O
The	O
zygæna	O
or	O
balance	O
fish	O
.	O
From	O
Dr.	B-pers
Colas	I-pers
of	I-pers
Prussia	I-pers
.	I-pers
X	O
p.	O
1	O
-600	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
sawfish	O
or	O
Pristis	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
X	O
p.	O
4	O
-601	O
.	O
A	O
Faber	O
w	O
t	O
out	O
spotts	O
&	O
a	O
large	O
prickle	O
on	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
finn	O
:	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
X	O
p.	O
4	O
o	O
.	O
7	O
-602	O
.	O
The	O
angel	O
fish	O
?	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
X	O
p.	O
4	O
-603	O
.	O
The	O
toadfish	O
?	O
or	O
orbis	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
X	O
n.	O
4	O
6	O
-604	O
.	O
A	O
bacutaya	O
Brasil	O
?	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
X	O
o	O
.	O
3	O
-605	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
without	O
the	O
long	O
finns	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
X	O
63	O
-606	O
.	O
The	O
acus	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
n.	O
4	O
-607	O
.	O
The	O
loligo	O
?	O
From	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
p.	O
3	O
-608	O
.	O
The	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
loligo	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
m.	O
2	O
-609	O
.	O
A	O
gray	O
smooth	O
orbis	O
w	O
t.	O
black	O
spotts	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
n.	O
6	O
-610	O
.	O
A	O
faber	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
spott	O
towards	O
the	O
tail	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
ring-	O
round	O
it	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
-611	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
flatt	O
gray	O
orbis	O
?	O
Id	O
.	O
o	O
.	O
2	O
-612	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
eels	O
?	O
skin	O
from	O
y	O
e.	O
Sea	O
64	O
-613	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
ball	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
cast	O
up	O
in	O
Cornwall	B-place
after	O
whales	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
pursuing	O
spratts	O
whose	O
bones	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
They	O
were	O
thrown	O
up	O
one	O
tide	O
&	O
left	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Lady	B-pers
Coply	I-pers
.	O
221	O
.	O
-614	O
.	O
The	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
Thorn	O
back	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
gravell	O
walk	O
in	O
Wisbech	B-place
given	O
me	O
by	O
D	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Massy	I-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
c	O
-615	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
small	O
fish	O
an	O
lupi	O
species	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Colas	I-pers
from	O
C	B-place
P	I-place
onigsberg	I-place
.	O
p.	O
5	O
616	O
.	O
The	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
;	O
?	O
crooked	O
.	O
or	O
of	O
a	O
morse	O
?	O
b	O
223	O
-617	O
.	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
a	O
thornback	O
w	O
t.	O
the	O
prickles	O
on	O
it	O
&	O
one	O
w	O
t.	O
double	O
spikes	O
.	O
f	O
241	O
-618	O
.	O
16	O
J.	O
Ammonites	O
seu	O
Hammites	O
subflavis	O
ovis	O
minor	O
bus	O
refertus	O
.	O
A	O
stone	O
in	O
England	B-place
supposd	O
to	O
be	O
rows	O
>	O
of	O
the	O
fish	O
petri	O
=fied	O
.	O
Br	O
.	O
170	O
65	O
-619	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
thin	O
scale	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
where	O
outward	O
silver	O
'd	O
over	O
.	O
Br./	O
Tarpum	O
fish	O
scale	O
vid	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
221.	O
g	O
-620	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
grinder	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fish	O
?	O
w	O
t.	O
4	O
fangs	O
.	O
From	O
Jamaica	B-place
?	O
221.	O
t	O
621	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Three	O
tri	O
angular	O
white	O
sharks	O
teeth	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
221	O
:	O
g	O
-622	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
Siliquastrum	O
pisi	O
Siliquam	O
referens	O
vibrato	O
margine	O
insignitum	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
748.	O
lithoph	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1445	O
.	O
221	O
dd	O
.	O
-623	O
.	O
✓	O
Os	O
ex	O
capite	O
aselli	O
minoris	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
748.	O
fig	O
.	O
3	O
+	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
-624	O
.	O
Siliquastrum	O
os	O
e	O
capite	O
aselli	O
minoris	O
referens	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
748.	O
fig	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
221.	O
u	O
.	O
-625	O
.	O
22	O
✓	O
Siliquastro	O
accedens	O
ricinus	O
seu	O
siliquastrum	O
minimum	O
instar	O
seminis	O
phaseoli	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
749.	O
fig	O
.	O
5.	O
lishoph	O
.	O
1493	O
.	O
1494	O
.	O
221.	O
n	O
66	O
-626	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Mandibule	O
fossilis	O
fragmentum	O
bufontis	O
minimis	O
colore	O
ad	O
granatum	O
accedenti	O
interstinctum	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
lith	O
.	O
p.	O
71	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1409	O
.	O
L.	O
221.	O
u	O
-627	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
X	O
Bufonites	O
mininus	O
a	O
convex	O
core	O
parte	O
rugosus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
L.	O
Lithophyl	O
.	O
1368	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
.	O
-628	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Bufonites	O
minor	O
trocluli	O
adinstar	O
fastig=	O
=iatus	O
Seu	O
bufonites	O
trochilus	O
dictus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
10.	O
lith	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1383	O
.	O
221	O
dd	O
-629	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Bufonites	O
minimus	O
trochylo	O
affinis-	O
calyculo	O
striato	O
longuisculo	O
donatuc	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
t	O
r	O
ans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
700.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
11	O
?	O
lith	O
.	O
1380	O
?	O
221.	O
cc	O
.	O
-630	O
.	O
Bufonites	O
Scaphoides	O
extremo	O
altero	O
latiore	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
ph	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
p.	O
750.	O
fig	O
.	O
12.	O
lith	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1384	O
.	O
Pietra	O
di	O
Rospo	O
di	O
figura	O
ovale	O
.	O
Imperat	O
.	O
p.	O
bbi	O
?	O
of	O
Sev	O
ll	O
magnitudes	O
/	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
244.	O
tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
67	O
-631	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Gracyrrinchus	O
falactus	O
vulgaris	O
Sinistrorsum	O
falcatus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
lith	O
.	O
p.	O
64	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1265	O
.	O
L.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-632	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
Plectronites	O
maximus	O
corticeus	O
seu	O
rostrago	O
maxima	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
-	O
lithoph	O
.	O
.	O
p.	O
66	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1318	O
.	O
L.	O
221.	O
dd	O
-633	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
Sinuated	O
bone	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
some	O
fish	O
?	O
L.	O
221.	O
e	O
l.	O
-634	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
A	O
grain	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Ammonites	O
.	O
L.	O
The	O
egg	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
?	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
-635	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
fish	O
bones	O
found	O
fossil	O
?	O
L.	O
221	O
w	O
-636	O
.	O
✓	O
16	O
.	O
J	O
Egg	O
stone	O
under	O
the	O
Yorke	O
Wooltes	O
.	O
L	O
221.	O
n	O
68	O
-637	O
.	O
16	O
J	O
Ammonites	O
Seu	O
Hammites	O
subrufus	O
laxior	O
ovulis	O
minoribus	O
refertus	O
.	O
Ketten	O
or	O
Kettering	O
Stone	O
in	O
North=	B-place
=amptonshire	I-place
,	O
a	O
freestone	O
.	O
L.	O
37	O
.	O
-638	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
J.	O
Ammonites	O
Seu	O
Hammites	O
cinereus	O
durior	O
ovulis	O
minoribus	O
refertus	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
d.	O
Layer	O
or	O
bedd	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
freestone	O
of	O
Wansford	O
code	O
quarrie	O
beyond	O
Stamford	B-place
.	O
L.	O
37	O
.	O
-639	O
.	O
16	O
J	O
Ammonites	O
Seu	O
Hammites	O
Subrufus	O
laxior	O
ovulis	O
minimis	O
refert	O
s	O
Keel	O
a	O
freestone	O
so	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
free	O
masons	O
at	O
Stamford	B-place
,	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
dug	O
&	O
wrought	O
for	O
London	B-place
&	O
other	O
parts	O
:	O
It	O
being	O
the	O
uppermost	O
bed	O
or	O
grit	O
of	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
quarrie	O
.	O
L.	O
170	O
-640	O
.	O
16	O
J.	O
Ammonites	O
seu	O
Hammites	O
subrufus	O
durior	O
ovulis	O
minimis	O
albis	O
&	O
fluoribus	O
refertus	O
.	O
Anunder	O
bed	O
of	O
Freestone	O
at	O
Stamford	B-place
.	O
L.	O
170	O
69	O
-641	O
.	O
Ammonites	O
seu	O
Hammites	O
durus	O
subflavas	O
ovulis	O
majoribus	O
refertus	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
-642	O
.	O
Ammonites	O
seu	O
Hammites	O
darus	O
subcœruleus	O
ovulis	O
minoribus	O
cinereis	O
refertus	O
.	O
The	O
freestone	O
of	O
the	O
Quarries	O
at	O
Crown	O
beck	O
Hinderscleffe	O
.	O
L.	O
white	O
one	O
larger	O
&	O
lesser	O
.	O
37	O
-643	O
.	O
A	O
fishes	O
chaps	O
?	O
L.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-644	O
.	O
A	O
bone	O
congenerous	O
with	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Lluids	I-pers
rhombus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
L.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-645	O
.	O
The	O
chaps	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
w	O
t.	O
crooked	O
triangular	O
Serrated	O
teeth	O
.	O
O.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-646	O
.	O
The	O
chaps	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
w	O
t.	O
Streight	O
tri	O
angular	O
serrated	O
&	O
pointed	O
teeth	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
70	O
-647	O
.	O
The	O
vertebroe	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
-648	O
.	O
The	O
finns	O
by	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
Squatina	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
-649	O
.	O
The	O
small	O
Cha	O
green	O
dog	O
fish	O
.	O
O	O
-650	O
.	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
a	O
porpesse	O
.	O
O.	O
f	O
241	O
.	O
-651	O
.	O
The	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
skin	O
of	O
the	O
piscis	O
trian=	O
=gularis	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
-652	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
70	O
foot	O
long	O
Seen	O
at	O
black	B-place
wall	I-place
March	O
169	O
8/9	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
213.	O
l	O
-653	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
very	O
odd	O
semi	O
circular	O
fish	O
bone	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
t	O
-654	O
.	O
A	O
fishes	O
large	O
Scale	O
finely	O
wrought	O
w	O
t.	O
lines	O
&	O
protuberances	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
71	O
655	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
A	O
small	O
black	O
round	O
bufonites	O
,	O
yellow	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
clay	O
or	O
marle	O
stone	O
.	O
From	O
Malta	B-place
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
656	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
A	O
yellowish	O
bufonites	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
.	O
657	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
A	O
yellowish	O
bufonites	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
brown	O
mark	O
in	O
its	O
center	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-658	O
.	O
The	O
sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
sepia	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
-659	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
turdus	O
piscis	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
p.	O
-660	O
.	O
The	O
fossil	O
chap	O
of	O
the	O
lupus	O
piscis	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-661	O
.	O
92	O
A	O
fossil	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
?	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c	O
72	O
-662	O
.	O
Sharks	O
teeth	O
in	O
a	O
slat	O
stone	O
?	O
L	O
221.	O
ff	O
-663	O
.	O
The	O
sceleton	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
221.	O
e	O
l	O
664	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
An	O
ash	O
coloured	O
siliquastrum	O
?	O
irreg=	O
ularly	O
figured	O
.	O
221	O
dd	O
665	O
.	O
22	O
x	O
A	O
black	O
irregularly	O
figured	O
sili=	O
quastrum	O
?	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-666	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Crooked	O
black	O
serrated	O
teeth	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-667	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Large	O
striated	O
gray	O
streight	O
tooth	O
of	O
a	O
dog	O
fish	O
.	O
fossil	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-668	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Large	O
Smooth	O
Streight	O
teeth	O
of	O
a	O
dog	O
fish	O
fossil	O
.	O
O	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
73	O
-669	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
whales	O
tooth	O
?	O
P.	O
Quadr	O
?	O
222.	O
b	O
-670	O
.	O
A	O
perfect	O
eruca	O
marina	O
.	O
vid	O
.	O
Bellon	O
.	O
phil	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
-671	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
fish	O
skin	O
?	O
an	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
shagreen	O
?	O
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
O	I-pers
.	I-pers
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
r.	O
8	O
.	O
-672	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
fish	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
sand	O
stone	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
quarre	O
near	O
Belvoir	B-place
castle	O
&	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Rutland	I-pers
.	I-pers
222.	O
c	O
-673	O
.	O
A	O
fish	O
bone	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
spike	O
or	O
small	O
sharp	O
bone	O
jointed	O
on	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
river	O
Ganges	O
in	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
The	O
fish	O
is	O
as	O
bigg	O
as	O
a	O
salmon	O
.	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Maidstone	I-pers
vid	O
.	O
Pet	O
.	O
Garoph	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
-674	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
entire	O
chaps	O
of	O
the	O
parrot	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6.	O
fish	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
w.	O
-675	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
chaps	O
of	O
the	O
nari	O
nari	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
petrified	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
c	O
-676	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
rana	O
piscatrix	O
?	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
r	O
74	O
-677	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
sort	O
of	O
apua	O
or	O
stickle	O
back	O
from	O
Carolina	B-place
from	O
M	B-pers
r.	I-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	I-pers
o	O
.	O
2	O
-678	O
.	O
Gracyrhynchus	O
atronitens	O
cerncues	O
:	O
sive	O
acuminatus	O
corneus	O
mucrone	O
acuto	O
,	O
dcorsum	O
vergeute	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
64	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1263.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
243	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
w	O
-679	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Plectronites	O
vulgaris	O
seu	O
striatus	O
medius	O
mucrone	O
paulo	O
acutiore	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
67	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1331.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
243	O
.	O
Tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
dd	O
221.	O
dd	O
-680	O
.	O
22	O
X.	O
Bufonites	O
medius	O
orbiculatus	O
seu	O
vulgatior	O
Anglicus	O
coloris	O
exalbidi	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
70	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1363.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p	O
244	O
.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c	O
-681	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
X	O
The	O
same	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
pale	O
furrow	O
>	O
eaten	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
ib	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
-682	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
Bufonites	O
orbiculatus	O
rugosus	O
seu	O
a	O
parte	O
nveniore	O
areola	O
quadam	O
cusej	O
-	O
=nitus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
70	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1382	O
.	O
M.	O
tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
221.	O
cc	O
75	O
-683	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
A	O
bufonites	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
shape	O
&	O
size	O
with	O
the	O
orbiculatus	O
scarce	O
at	O
all	O
excavated	O
at	O
the	O
root	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
244	O
.	O
Bufonites	O
medius	O
castanei	O
coloris	O
in	O
elitensium	O
:	O
seu	O
castaneus	O
minimum	O
aut	O
non	O
omnino	O
excavatus	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
70	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1359	O
?	O
M.	O
221	O
c.	O
c.	O
-684	O
.	O
✓	O
22	O
X	O
A	O
small	O
sort	O
of	O
bufonites	O
of	O
a	O
more	O
raised	O
shape	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
245	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-685	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetra	O
Zygenæ	O
piscis	O
dentem	O
referens	O
:	O
seu	O
acanthina	O
vulgaris	O
Marchamensaim	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
65	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1286.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
243	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1286	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-686	O
.	O
92	O
Siliquastrum	O
minimum	O
vibratum	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
74	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1466.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
245	O
.	O
M.	O
221	O
c.	O
c.	O
-687	O
.	O
92	O
Siliquastro	O
congener	O
Ricinus	O
;	O
seu	O
siliquastrum	O
minus	O
instar	O
seminis	O
phaseoli	O
.	O
phil	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
fig	O
.	O
5	O
?	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
246	O
?	O
221	O
cc	O
76	O
-688	O
.	O
92	O
Siliquastram	O
minus	O
gibbosum	O
subtenue	O
,	O
seu	O
vulgari	O
similes	O
arcuatum	O
angustius	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
74	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1467.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
Nat	O
.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
246	O
.	O
221	O
cc	O
.	O
-689	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
siliquastrum	O
tortile	O
gibbosum	O
,	O
minutis	O
punctulis	O
subinde	O
conspersum	O
,	O
seu	O
Siliquastrum	O
marmoreum	O
punctularia	O
tortilis	O
dictum	O
.	O
phil	O
.	O
trans	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
200.	O
fig	O
.	O
4.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
74	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1482.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
246	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-690	O
92	O
Siliquastrum	O
silo	O
condictum	O
:	O
seu	O
recurvirostrum	O
gibbosum	O
,	O
striga	O
quadam	O
a	O
dorso	O
.	O
ad	O
mucronem	O
procurrente	O
.	O
livids	O
coloris	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
74	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1478.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
246.	O
tab	O
.	O
10.	O
fig	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
M.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-691	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
A	O
canthiodonti	O
congener	O
rhombiseus	O
major	O
sive	O
uncialis	O
.	O
Lluid	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
72	O
.	O
N	O
o	O
.	O
1421	O
?	O
M.	O
221.	O
c.	O
c.	O
-692	O
.	O
A	O
vertebra	O
or	O
single	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
backbone	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
fish	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
247.	O
tab	O
.	O
11.	O
fig	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
M.	O
222.	O
c	O
77	O
-693	O
.	O
22	O
Y	O
A	O
vertebra	O
of	O
smaller	O
size	O
found	O
at	O
Oxendon	B-place
in	O
Northam=	O
=ptonshire	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
p.	O
247	O
.	O
Sp	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
M.	O
222.	O
c.	O
-694	O
.	O
A	O
vertebra	O
broader	O
but	O
not	O
near	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
247.	O
tab	O
.	O
11.	O
fig	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
M.	O
222.	O
cc	O
-695	O
.	O
22	O
Y	O
A	O
vertebra	O
in	O
shape	O
agreeing	O
w	O
t.	O
the	O
last	O
but	O
of	O
a	O
much	O
lesse	O
size	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
247	O
.	O
M.	O
222.	O
b	O
-696	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
white	O
vertebra	O
from	O
Dr.	B-pers
Plott	I-pers
.	I-pers
222.	O
c	O
-697.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
spine	O
bone	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
fish	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
248.	O
tab	O
.	O
11.	O
fig	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
M.	O
222.	O
a	O
.	O
-698	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
J.	O
Ova	O
of	O
fishes	O
in	O
flint	O
.	O
Mort	B-pers
.	I-pers
N.	O
h.	O
N.	O
p.	O
248	O
.	O
221.	O
e.	O
-699	O
.	O
The	O
palat	O
or	O
tongue	O
of	O
some	O
large	O
ray	O
from	O
the	O
East	B-place
Indies	I-place
.	O
Dr.	B-pers
Waldo	I-pers
.	I-pers
221.	O
ff	O
78	O
-700	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
flatt	O
bones	O
between	O
the	O
vertebres	O
of	O
a	O
whale	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
-701	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
-702	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
solid	O
whales	O
tooth	O
almost	O
streight	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
Spermaceti	O
whale	O
221.	O
t.	O
-703	O
.	O
✓	O
Another	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
i	O
.	O
221.	O
t	O
-704	O
.	O
✓	O
Another	O
very	O
crooked	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
t	O
-705	O
.	O
✓	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
codfish	O
bone	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
e	O
221.	O
b	O
&	O
c	O
-706	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
eye	O
of	O
a	O
shark	O
.	O
Id	O
.	O
221.	O
y	O
707	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
alt	O
.	O
cornutus	O
parvus	O
.	O
C.	O
221.	O
w	O
-708	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
from	O
suratte	B-place
.	O
Waldo	B-pers
.	I-pers
221	O
w.	O
-709	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Oculi	O
balenæ	O
exdono	O
Dom	O
.	O
Peterson	O
.	O
221	O
221.	O
ff	O
79	O
710	O
.	O
22	O
W	O
Glossopetræ	O
from	O
sheppey	B-place
Island	I-place
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
one	O
w	O
t.	O
a	O
stone	O
growing	O
to	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6.	O
the	O
roots	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
711	O
.	O
✓	O
The	O
same	O
smaller	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
221.	O
ff	O
712	O
.	O
✓	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
whiting	O
221.	O
y	O
713	O
.	O
Prickles	O
of	O
a	O
fish	O
from	O
Scotland	B-place
.	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6.	O
dog	O
fish	O
pike	O
.	O
E.	O
E	O
0	O
.	O
0	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
714	O
.	O
✓	O
Piscis	O
triangularis	O
from	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
221.	O
l.	O
715	O
.	O
Serpents	O
horn	O
or	O
glossopetra	O
from	O
.	O
Malta	B-place
?	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-716	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
gray	O
clouded	O
round	O
bufonites	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
button	O
221.	O
dd	O
-717	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
large	O
dark	O
brown	O
round	O
bufonites	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-718	O
.	O
22	O
X	O
A	O
smaller	O
one	O
round	O
&	O
dark	O
coloured	O
.	O
221.	O
dd	O
.	O
-719	O
.	O
One	O
shaped	O
like	O
a	O
deus	O
caninus	O
.	O
