TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1702	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
Jan	O
1702	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Holdish	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Turberville	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lichburne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clift	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Trinity	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hilow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hood	O
in	O
her	O
Table-Drawer	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Saying	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
lent	O
them	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilshire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Basishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget-stuff	O
,	O
from	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Drugget	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Ware	O
house	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Drugget	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
she	O
was	O
perceived	O
,	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
there	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Drugget	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
discoursing	O
with	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
had	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pickt	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Furber	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Slieve	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
sender	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Combridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Peate	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
shagreen	O
Hood	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lockt	O
his	O
Doors	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
him	O
,	O
leapt	O
over	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Susan	B-pers
Satterwaite	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
:	O
The	O
Marriage	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Niccolls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lettice	B-pers
Strudwick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
16	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland-sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lettice	O
Strudwick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Awker	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
from	O
Bellinda	B-pers
Hawton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
arose	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pantry-door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
but	O
12	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
a	O
Spoon	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Strudwick	O
's	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
some	O
Kenting	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Furbellow-Scarf	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
callico	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
espied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
thought	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
dropt	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
revenge	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
divers	O
blows	O
with	O
an	O
Oaken-stick	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
of	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
an	O
earthen	O
Mug	O
,	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Birket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
Jones	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
was	O
never	O
seen	O
after	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
lived	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
now	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Rugs	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Phenix	B-pers
Wannerton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
lost	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
43	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tose	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Towse	B-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blood-stone	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Tenderness	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Corey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
NightGown	O
,	O
2	O
Drugget	O
Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Scotch	B-pers
Nell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland-sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
;	O
2	O
callico	O
Smocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dorrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Holland-Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
whilst	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
100	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Bacon	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buttle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
4	O
Flitches	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Bee-hive	O
by	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
Ware	O
,	O
by	O
Waltham-Cross	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bacon	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fudge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Fosters	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
narrow	O
Lawn	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belt	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
Price	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Fudge	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owning	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
silver	O
Braded	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
under	O
the	O
Arch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
He	O
heard	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
Fraud	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Gauger	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
for	O
Bow	O
and	O
Bromley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
did	O
between	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1698	O
,	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Drink	O
that	O
was	O
Brewed	O
at	O
one	O
Prisca	O
Coburnes	O
Brew-houses	O
,	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Stepny	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
false	O
returnof	O
his	O
Account	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
cheated	O
the	O
late	O
King	B-pers
William	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
brewed	O
922	O
Barrels	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
238	O
Barrels	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Small	O
,	O
the	O
Excise	O
of	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
208	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
returned	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
Collector	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
than	O
640	O
Barrels	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Strong	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
Barrels	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Small	O
;	O
which	O
Account	O
amounted	O
to	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
than	O
147	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
so	O
that	O
within	O
5	O
Weeks	O
he	O
had	O
cheated	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
above	O
60	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
shared	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
30	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
one	O
Bradley	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Clerks	O
,	O
had	O
15	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
half	O
penny	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Clerk	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
common	O
Practice	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
when	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Recorder	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Chambers	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Arthur	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Chambers	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
Dr.	O
in	O
Divinity	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
leaning	O
his	O
Body	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
distance	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
jumpt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
Indictments	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sherston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
divers	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chesworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Edmunds	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Laron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
29th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Newington	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Gracedieu	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Wife	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Taking	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cornelian-stone	O
from	O
Griffith	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Algate	O
with	O
some	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
snatcht	O
it	O
,	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Lumbard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
the	O
hinder-part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
only	O
by	O
misfortune	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Stephen	I-place
Walbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Mier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mathew	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Subbornation	O
,	O
for	O
subborning	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Limble	I-pers
,	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Oath	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
George	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Susanna	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
in	O
Berwick-street	B-place
,	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Metal	O
melting	O
in	O
a	O
Fire-shovel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flasks	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
so	O
hot	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
further	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Pocket	O
,	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Tools	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Hat	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
matters	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
accquitted	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Motley	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
,	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Play-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
People	O
josled	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
Perriwing	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heav	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Periwig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
They	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
King	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Young	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cane	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Tobias	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Derby	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
10	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pots	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
Soldier	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Back-seller	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pewter	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Back-Kitchen	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Pole	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Piece	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
he	O
cockt	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fired	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
afterwards	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Pots	O
in	O
a	O
Waggon	O
,	O
that	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
fired	O
,	O
he	O
wounded	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Arthur	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
buying	O
twenty	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
for	O
a	O
less	O
value	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
within	O
the	O
time	O
limited	O
in	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
4	O
Spoons	O
,	O
3	O
Sales	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Van-mossen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepny	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
7th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
10	O
Holland-shirts	O
,	O
12	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread-Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Hair	O
Portmanto-Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
a	O
Hair-Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Parchment	O
Deed	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Trunks	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bristol-Coach	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Cups	O
in	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
going	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
stopt	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
2	O
Passengers	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
more	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Trunks	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Ratclif	O
High-way	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stopt	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
mistrusting	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
his	O
Beadle	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
the	O
Beadle	O
come	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
drive	O
down	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
at	O
another	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Headborough	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
met	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Ship	O
's	O
Crew	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
intoxicated	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Wapping	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
Excuse	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
Indictments	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Cheyney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
Taking	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Cornelins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledging	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Trinity	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
9	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Holland-Aprons	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
fall	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Aprons	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
a	O
Dunghil	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Indian-Sattin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cliping	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Arm	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Report	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
Taking	O
from	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
Beard	I-pers
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Cast	O
home	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
secretly	O
Taking	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonards	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland-sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
fetcht	O
the	O
foul	O
Linnen	O
from	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
wash	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
took	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
TRIALS	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
William	O
Brookes	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Lee	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Price	O
,	O
Robert	O
Spencer	O
,	O
and	O
Susanna	O
Hughes	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
John	O
Roberts	O
,	O
alias	O
Arthur	O
Chambers	O
,	O
is	O
respited	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheek	O
7	O
.	O
Martha	O
Bromley	O
,	O
Ann	O
Combridge	O
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
Jane	O
Jones	O
,	O
Mary	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Ellinor	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Wilson	O
.	O
For	O
her	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
8	O
.	O
Susanna	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
Edward	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Ann	O
Mason	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Marjoram	O
,	O
Rachel	O
Smith	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Turner	O
,	O
Ann	O
Wilshire	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	O
Young	O
.	O
For	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Peter	O
Brookes	O
,	O
Richard	O
Furber	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Simons	O
.	O
Robert	O
King	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Towse	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Clayton	O
's	O
Work-house	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Warren	O
,	O
Fined	O
300	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Mathew	O
Stone	O
,	O
Fined	O
4	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Swist	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
at	O
hard	O
Labour	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
Susanna	O
Hughes	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
WHeras	O
some	O
Persons	O
have	O
lately	O
assumed	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
putting	O
out	O
several	O
Sham-papers	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Dying	O
Criminals	O
;	O
wherein	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
far	O
defective	O
and	O
unjust	O
,	O
as	O
sometimes	O
to	O
mistake	O
even	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Crimes	O
of	O
those	O
Persons	O
.	O
Therefore	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
World	O
's	O
being	O
any	O
longer	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
:	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
That	O
only	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Dying	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
comes	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
their	O
Execution	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o	O
Clock	O
,	O
attested	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
printed	O
for	O
Elizabeth	O
Maller	O
;	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Title	O
of	O
which	O
Account	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
false	O
ones	O
)	O
constantly	O
begins	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
ORDINARY	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
by	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BOOKS	O
sold	O
by	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Mallet	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Living	O
Men	O
,	O
or	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
,	O
the	O
Ministers	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
principal	O
Natives	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Kingdoms	O
;	O
being	O
an	O
Essay	O
on	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Persons	O
that	O
are	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Poem	O
upon	O
each	O
Life	O
:	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
Prince	O
George	O
of	O
Denmark	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Petticoat-Government	O
;	O
In	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Court-Ladies	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Post-Angel	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
New	O
Quevedo	O
.	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Vision	O
of	O
Charon	O
's	O
Passengers	O
:	O
From	O
the	O
Creation	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1702	O
.	O
With	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
Qualities	O
,	O
and	O
particular	O
Crimes	O
;	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
Part	O
.	O
Price	O
of	O
each	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Commitment	O
,	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
Condemnation	O
of	O
Nicholas	O
Bajard	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
subvert	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Province	O
of	O
New	O
York	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
signing	O
and	O
procuring	O
others	O
to	O
sign	O
scandalous	O
Libels	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Petitions	O
or	O
Addresses	O
to	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
the	O
Parliament	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Cornbury	O
,	O
now	O
Governour	O
of	O
that	O
Province	O
.	O
Before	O
William	O
Atwood	O
Esq	O
;	O
Abraham	O
de	O
Peystyer	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	O
Walters	O
Esq	O
;	O
Appointed	O
by	O
a	O
special	O
Commission	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
New-York	O
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
1701	O
.	O
Collected	O
from	O
several	O
Memorials	O
taken	O
by	O
divers	O
Persons	O
privately	O
,	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
having	O
strictly	O
prohibited	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Tryals	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Libels	O
,	O
Addresses	O
themselves	O
.	O
Printed	O
at	O
New-York	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
his	O
Excellency	O
the	O
Lord	O
Cornbury	O
,	O
and	O
reprinted	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
1703	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
R.	O
Smith	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
of	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
B.	O
Lmtot	O
at	O
the	O
Temple-gate	O
,	O
and	O
E.	O
Maltes	O
at	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Interest	O
of	O
England	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
Protestand	O
dissenting	O
from	O
the	O
establish	O
'd	O
Church	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
Thoughts	O
about	O
Occasional	O
Conformity	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
short	O
Historical	O
Essay	O
,	O
touching	O
general	O
Councils	O
,	O
Synod	O
Convocations	O
,	O
Creeds	O
,	O
and	O
Imposition	O
in	O
Religion	O
;	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Marvel	O
Esq	O
;	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Fight	O
Fables	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
Posture	O
of	O
Affairs	O
in	O
Europe	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Devil	O
and	O
the	O
Priest	O
,	O
or	O
Porto	O
Carero	O
's	O
Will	O
:	O
The	O
Courtier	O
:	O
The	O
Pilgrims	O
:	O
The	O
Usurers	O
and	O
Merchants	O
:	O
The	O
Ingrates	O
:	O
The	O
Partizan	O
:	O
The	O
Confederacy	O
:	O
The	O
Interview	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
Aelop	O
's	O
Advice	O
,	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Princes	O
and	O
People	O
of	O
Europe	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
||+||	O
A	O
Vindication	O
of	O
Magna	O
Charta	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Summary	O
of	O
English	O
Rights	O
and	O
Liberties	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
its	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confirmations	O
procured	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
several	O
Reigns	O
,	O
are	O
fully	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
The	O
glorious	O
Actions	O
of	O
the	O
Peers	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
maintain	O
the	O
Privileges	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
are	O
related	O
and	O
defended	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
excellency	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
English	O
Constitution	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
noblest	O
Constitution	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
+++	O
An	O
Argument	O
proving	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Imposition	O
of	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Qualification	O
for	O
a	O
secular	O
Office	O
,	O
is	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
express	O
Laws	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
.	O
and	O
(	O
4	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
National	O
and	O
Natural	O
Rights	O
of	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Reasonableness	O
and	O
Necessity	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
at	O
this	O
Juncture	O
,	O
is	O
particularly	O
consider	O
'd	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Remark	O
on	O
the	O
Condition	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
of	O
the	O
Victualing	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Notion	O
of	O
Fortifying	O
of	O
Garrisons	O
is	O
exploded	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
only	O
Security	O
of	O
England	O
consists	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Fleet	O
,	O
1700	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
-	O
The	O
second	O
Part	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
Reply	O
to	O
the	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Part	O
:	O
With	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
the	O
Discipline	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
,	O
shewing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Abuses	O
of	O
the	O
Seamen	O
are	O
the	O
highest	O
Violation	O
of	O
Magna	O
Charta	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Rights	O
and	O
Liberties	O
of	O
English	O
men	O
.	O
1700	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
present	O
Condition	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Navy	O
,	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
a	O
Dialogue	O
betwixt	O
young	O
Fudge	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Steermel	O
an	O
Oliverian	O
Commander	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
+++	O
Plantation	O
Justice	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
Constitution	O
of	O
their	O
Courts	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Judges	O
they	O
have	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
By	O
which	O
Merchants	O
may	O
see	O
the	O
occasions	O
of	O
their	O
great	O
Losses	O
and	O
Sufferings	O
in	O
the	O
Plantation	O
Trade	O
;	O
Lawyers	O
may	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
Model	O
of	O
Justice	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
see	O
how	O
those	O
Parts	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
are	O
Governed	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
HARMAN	O
STRODTMAN	O
's	O
last	O
Legacy	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
:	O
Containing	O
most	O
excellent	O
Meditations	O
and	O
Prayers	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Exercise	O
both	O
of	O
Devout	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Sinners	O
;	O
are	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
design	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
perusal	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Persons	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Mallet	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet	O
bridge	O
.	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
within	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
large	O
and	O
small	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Urul	O
'd	O
,	O
Bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
,	O
extraordinary	O
on	O
plain	O
,	O
or	O
unbounds	O
Also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
Large	O
and	O
Articles	O
and	O
Canons	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
Tate	O
,	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
new	O
Version	O
of	O
the	O
singing	O
Psalms	O
,	O
bound	O
with	O
the	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
newly	O
printed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
all	O
Books	O
neatly	O
Bound	O
,	O
at	O
Reasonable	O
Rates	O
.	O
The	O
Bible	O
in	O
large	O
Folio	O
for	O
Churches	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Tho	O
.	O
and	O
References	O
more	O
than	O
Dr.	O
Scatergood	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Years	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
Christ	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Primate	O
Usher	O
's	O
Annals	O
,	O
Revised	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Worcester	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chronological	O
Table	O
:	O
Also	O
a	O
Table	O
and	O
Index	O
of	O
Scripture	O
Measures	O
,	O
Weights	O
and	O
Coins	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Appendix	O
containing	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
Calculating	O
its	O
Measures	O
of	O
Surface	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Peterborough	O
.	O
Published	O
at	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing-Office	O
in	O
Black-friars	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
read	O
,	O
Bound	O
of	O
Rob	O
.	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate-street	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
now	O
Lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
,	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
selleth	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
20	O
Years	O
)	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
,	O
Pimple	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vive	O
.	O
Tinctura	O
Vita	O
.	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Powders	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
all	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Female	O
Sex	O
,	O
likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Anti-scorbutick	O
Pills	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
Titters	O
,	O
Itch	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
where	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Aches	O
,	O
and	O
Strains	O
,	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
who	O
now	O
doth	O
understand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effect-answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s	O
.	O
