TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1707	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
,	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedingfeld	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Ward	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Maddock	I-pers
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Austin	B-pers
Oldsworth	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Daywood	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harriotts	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Beatnife	I-pers
John	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Saunders	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Greyset	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gaydon	I-pers
,	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Evidence	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Five	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
upon	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Broker	O
in	O
Ragg-Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Pawn	O
Broker	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Hooks	I-pers
;	O
Anne	O
Hooks	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
producing	O
any	O
such	O
Woman	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Weigh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Coach	O
Cushions	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
white	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
Day	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
.	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Feloniously	O
Steal	O
16l	O
.	O
of	O
Beeswax	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Alphage	I-place
,	O
near	O
Cripplegate	B-place
within	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Shoemakers	O
Gum	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
her	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
reach	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Beeswax	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
understanding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
foung	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spoforth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
78	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
M	B-pers
--	I-pers
M	I-pers
--	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
78	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Knit	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
then	O
confess	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Mony	O
(	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Fathers	O
Landlady	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
.	O
Justice	O
Tully	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
that	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
used	O
Threatening	O
Words	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
which	O
drew	O
that	O
Confession	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
reality	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
:	O
And	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Collinswood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Nightrail	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
3s	O
.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cambull	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
Septem	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Box	O
and	O
Case	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
3	O
Pendulum	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Clocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mansel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Pendulum	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
7	O
Years	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
time	O
being	O
expired	O
,	O
he	O
Covenanted	O
for	O
him	O
30s	O
.	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
return	O
from	O
Wales	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
agoing	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
trust	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
lockt	O
up	O
the	O
Clocks	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
being	O
rob	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
search	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Watches	O
upon	O
two	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
.	O
The	O
Brokers	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watches	O
were	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
one	O
Sly	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appearing	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
stealing	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Queens	O
High	O
Way	O
(	O
near	O
Ealing	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
14s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Day	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
riding	O
along	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
London	B-place
Road	I-place
near	O
Ealing	B-place
Common	I-place
;	O
two	O
Men	O
Mask	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Pistols	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
met	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Mony	O
and	O
Rings	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
her	O
Mony	O
and	O
one	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
Ring	O
from	O
her	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
Deposed	O
,	O
they	O
immediately	O
purs	O
'd	O
and	O
chas	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
escap	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
still	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
to	O
Kensington	O
Road	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Country	O
being	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Brompton	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
divers	O
tokens	O
,	O
were	O
described	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
offer	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
fully	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Barham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
200	O
ll	O
.	O
Of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
and	O
120	O
ll	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Brazeletto	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Guilling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
2	O
Tun	O
of	O
Logwood	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
when	O
he	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
about	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Divers	O
Porters	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
Logwood	O
to	O
one	O
Walker	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Dyer	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall	O
Street	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
receive	O
4s	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wood	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Landlady	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
burn	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clemtree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
Septem	O
.	O
Last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
37	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Day	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
one	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Mugg	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Design	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Martin	O
Mugg	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
five	O
more	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
61th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
mounted	O
the	O
Pallisadoes	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Sash	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Men	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
demanded	O
their	O
Businesses	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
replied	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
an	O
Appearance	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
to	O
serve	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
joining	O
to	O
that	O
wherein	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
broken	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
hasten	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
entring	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
time	O
this	O
was	O
,	O
replied	O
just	O
at	O
Candle	O
lighting	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
Candle	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Writ	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Mugg	O
.	O
and	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
any	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
firing	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
10	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Day	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Fire	O
in	O
Lion	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Desk	O
with	O
Papers	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
almost	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Boards	O
;	O
that	O
looking	O
further	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
a	O
flat	O
Candlestick	O
burning	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
singed	O
the	O
Bedcloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Rooms	O
where	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
,	O
were	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
had	O
Keys	O
to	O
the	O
Doors	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
therefore	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
step	O
by	O
step	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mahew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
17l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
last	O
Sept.	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
her	O
rising	O
that	O
Morning	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
an	O
Hour	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
rise	O
at	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
order	O
when	O
he	O
arose	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
appearance	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
Thieves	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
alleg	O
'd	O
divers	O
things	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blunden	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hilliard	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Matter	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Matter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1706.	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
William	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
undertook	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
3	O
Husbands	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
now	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
other	O
proof	O
than	O
his	O
saying	O
so	O
appearing	O
,	O
Evidence	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
certificate	O
from	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
No	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
could	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Henry	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
and	O
Industrious	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Theodorus	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
23	O
tann	O
'd	O
Bassel	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Travis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
saw	O
Day	O
and	O
Bourne	O
carry	O
the	O
skins	O
to	O
Revel	O
.	O
The	O
Skins	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Day	O
and	O
Bourne	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Skins	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Revel	O
;	O
but	O
Revel	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Day	O
and	O
Bourne	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Revel	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ellis	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Arms	O
,	O
Short	O
Ribs	O
and	O
Loins	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Pump	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
himself	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Provocation	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Wooden	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Pump	O
from	O
a	O
Turner	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Deceased	O
therewith	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Wounds	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
continued	O
upon	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Friends	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
Justice	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
brought	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
,	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
beat	O
Teeth	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Doctor	O
and	O
Apothecary	O
that	O
open	O
'd	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Death	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
caused	O
from	O
any	O
Wound	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
sign	O
of	O
any	O
Bruise	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
divers	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
spit	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
Blood	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
before	O
this	O
matter	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nutkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Brigham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
20s	O
and	O
25l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
Brigham	O
,	O
and	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
Setting	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
proposed	O
a	O
way	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
taking	O
down	O
a	O
side	O
of	O
Glass	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
assisted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
alleged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
nature	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Substantial	O
persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
49s	O
6d	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
W-	B-pers
M-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
stoln	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
in	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
stoln	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Green	I-pers
in	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
,	O
a	O
person	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
Plate	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Paul	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
who	O
were	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Plate	O
was	O
likewise	O
sold	O
to	O
Paul	O
Whittle	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
'em	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
a	O
false	O
Information	O
upon	O
Oath	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
against	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
said	O
Palmer	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Newmarket	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
,	O
in	O
Epping	O
Forest	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
2	O
persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
David	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Drapdeberry	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
another	O
Affidavit	O
made	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
David	O
Davis	O
did	O
not	O
commit	O
that	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
inform	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
living	O
nigh	O
Hide	O
Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
who	O
promised	O
him	O
10s	O
reward	O
for	O
his	O
service	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
else	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
second	O
Information	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Tottenham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
that	O
agreed	O
to	O
his	O
Description	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
elaps	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stoln	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
as	O
a	O
stray	O
in	O
Enfield	O
Chace	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
convinced	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Mistake	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
simple	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
James	O
Coats	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Cheeck	O
,	O
4	O
Elizabeth	O
Clemtree	O
,	O
Jane	O
Barham	O
,	O
Ann	O
Collins	O
and	O
Mary	O
Ball	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
William	O
Read	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gray	O
,	O
Nathaniel	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
Theodorus	O
Bourne	O
.	O
To	O
go	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
George	O
Weigh	O
and	O
John	O
Page	O
.	O
William	O
Palmer	O
fined	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
and	O
Temple-bar	O
.	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Bedingfeld	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Charles	O
Brome	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
West-end	O
of	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
.	O
Lestranges	O
Alliance	O
of	O
Divine	O
offices	O
,	O
Folio	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Comber	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
.	O
Folio	O
-on	O
the	O
Church	O
Catechism	O
.	O
8vo	O
-Christians	O
best	O
Exercise	O
.	O
4vo	O
-Daily	O
frequenting	O
the	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
.	O
8vo	O
Heylin	O
on	O
the	O
Creed	O
.	O
Folio	O
Bp	O
.	O
Taylors	O
Life	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
Folio	O
-	O
Holy	O
,	O
Living	O
and	O
Dying	O
.	O
8vo	O
-Golden	O
Grove	O
.	O
120	O
Bp	O
Rens	O
Exposition	O
on	O
the	O
Church	O
Catechism	O
.	O
8vo	O
-Directions	O
for	O
Prayer	O
.	O
8vo	O
Stitcht	O
pr	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
-3	O
Hymns	O
.	O
Sticht	O
2d	O
.	O
-Manual	O
of	O
Prayers	O
for	O
Winebester	O
Scholars	O
.	O
120	O
Blomes	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
.	O
410	O
Bp	O
Wilkins	O
Real	O
Character	O
.	O
Folio	O
-Natural	O
Religion	O
.	O
8vo	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
Whereas	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
book	O
,	O
page	O
2.	O
first	O
Column	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
put	O
M.	O
B.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
five	O
Dollars	O
from	O
Robert	O
Russel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
said	O
M.	O
B.	O
must	O
be	O
Mary	O
Bowers	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
is	O
desired	O
may	O
be	O
corrected	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Is	O
sold	O
a	O
Never-failing	O
Ointment	O
,	O
that	O
cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
tho	O
the	O
Party	O
be	O
reduced	O
to	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth	O
Ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
