TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
5th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedingfeld	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Ld	O
.	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Selathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
her	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ask	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Maylin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pardos	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Backhurst	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bankford	I-pers
George	B-pers
Hammon	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
James	B-pers
Kintish	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ramage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Marnam	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Carolina	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridgets	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discovered	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
But	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brestead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Silver	B-pers
Junier	I-pers
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Indian	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
1	O
silk	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
1	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
2	O
Ghenting	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
3	O
ll	O
.	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Silver	O
Junier	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
left	O
fasten	O
'd	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
was	O
found	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
divers	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
near	O
Bethnal-Green	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
produc	O
'd	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
not	O
proving	O
that	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gailing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brestow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
shewn	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Ring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
cheapned	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Brass	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
11	O
1/4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Pursival	B-pers
Chandlor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
TheEvidence	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
Buy	O
Muslen	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
she	O
Dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Assisting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Escue	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Escue	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
Drinking	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
together	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
they	O
met	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
singled	O
the	O
Deceased	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
among	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
Men	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Struck	O
this	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
Stun	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
who	O
Committed	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
his	O
Round	O
then	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
stepping	O
up	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
Struck	O
at	O
his	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
Fled	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Man	O
had	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Token	O
of	O
his	O
Innocency	O
Surrendred	O
himself	O
voluntarily	O
while	O
his	O
Companions	O
Fled	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
divers	O
Substantial	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Small	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Drowning	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
Thames	B-place
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Wherry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
then	O
Riding	O
at	O
the	O
Custom	O
House	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
the	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
Ride	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remove	O
his	O
Vessel	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Cut	O
the	O
Rope	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
a	O
Drift	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
Beat	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Hand-Spike	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
Strike	O
him	O
)	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
Accidently	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
left	O
Legg	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
perished	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
Produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
his	O
endeavour	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
design	O
of	O
Drowning	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Divers	O
Books	O
to	O
a	O
Considerable	O
Value	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Buckworth	I-pers
Bart	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
Friday-night	O
last	O
his	O
Study	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
and	O
Fastned	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
found	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Others	O
deposed	O
that	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Water	O
at	O
Mortlock	O
for	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Bundle	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Record	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
before	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
broken	O
Prison	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
denyed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Luke	B-pers
Levesee	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
38	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
one	O
20	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
5	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Pistole	O
,	O
36	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Mansion	B-place
House	I-place
of	O
William	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Cupido	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Peruke	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Peruke	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Strangeway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Strangeway	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Perukes	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Peruke	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Conversant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Strangeway	O
's	O
Family	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
private	O
Stealing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine-Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bed-Ticks	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Beddal	I-pers
;	O
on	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Saracen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
and	I-place
Bell	I-place
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	B-place
)	O
to	O
lodge	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
she	O
ript	O
up	O
3	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
let	O
out	O
the	O
Feathers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Ticks	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Elby	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dunn	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
2	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nicholas	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Barry	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
's	O
House	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
arose	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Window	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
2	O
Men	O
without	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
the	O
Prosecutorwilling	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
up-stairs	O
for	O
Arms	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
stept	O
back	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
for	O
a	O
Spit	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
drove	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Pantry	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Stabb	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
twelve	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
divers	O
concurring	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
as	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
scuffling	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Thief	O
shot	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
disingage	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Shot	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Leg	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Another	O
Circumstance	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
Button	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Pantry	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
a	O
Bloody	O
Sword	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
an	O
Hay	O
Cock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Receipt	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
Money	O
paid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
99	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Lace	O
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
1	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Camlet	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kemster	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
1705	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cutbert	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d	O
,	O
of	O
Habbakkuk	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pinchens	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
1702	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pound	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Mitten	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Furbelo	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath-rash	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
multitude	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Persons	O
of	O
a	O
Good	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bault	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bowlin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewellin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dennis	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Freeman	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
1706	O
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
whom	O
she	O
Married	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
April	O
1706	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
plainly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Dennis	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Freeman	O
,	O
while	O
Dennis	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
likewise	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Dennis	O
had	O
a	O
former	O
Wife	O
living	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Married	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Marriage	O
with	O
Dennis	O
being	O
Null	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Corbett	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
with	O
the	O
sharp	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Broken	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Cary	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Gibbons	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Mermaid	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Cornhil	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
plaid	O
at	O
Cards	O
together	O
till	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Cards	O
were	O
chang	O
'd	O
into	O
Dice	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
won	O
Money	O
of	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
occasion	O
to	O
demand	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
never	O
paid	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
I	O
be	O
paid	O
?	O
Whereupon	O
some	O
high	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Blow	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
struck	O
him	O
backwards	O
)	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Sword	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
likewise	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
Parry	O
'd	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
small	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
continu	O
'd	O
Fighting	O
till	O
the	O
Wounds	O
were	O
given	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen-endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
farther	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Fighting	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Hilt	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
broken	O
Sword	O
,	O
disarm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Swords	O
thrown	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
point	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
broken	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
present	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
interval	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
Fray	O
being	O
ended	O
in	O
less	O
then	O
two	O
Minutes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
produced	O
divers	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Worth	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
The	O
Queen	O
's	O
Warrant	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
to	O
respite	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
Judgment	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Warminger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hornsey	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Farthings	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Swell	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10Years	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
been	O
abus	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
bore	O
hard	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Consummate	O
Rape	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
5	O
Books	O
of	O
Moses	O
,	O
Written	O
in	O
Hebrew	O
,	O
2	O
Cases	O
Embroider	O
'd	O
and	O
Trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
.	O
2	O
Sticks	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Silver	O
Bells	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sold	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Cases	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Roll	O
wherein	O
the	O
5	O
Books	O
of	O
Moses	O
were	O
written	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Taylor	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Measures	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defeece	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
price	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wadmouth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
to	O
be	O
Chang	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
proving	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
10	O
more	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
wrap't	O
up	O
in	O
single	O
Papers	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
he	O
Confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
East	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
into	O
small	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Muslin	O
,	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Girdle	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Stafford	B-pers
Fairbone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Agnes	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edith	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
William	O
Elby	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
More	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Peter	O
Small	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Corbet	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
had	O
Judgment	O
respited	O
by	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Warrant	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
Order	O
'd	O
by	O
Court	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
an	O
Antient	O
Statute	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
Prison	O
Eleven	O
Months	O
,	O
without	O
Bail	O
or	O
Mainprize	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Gailing	O
,	O
Philip	O
Levy	O
,	O
Luke	O
Levesee	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Osbourn	O
,	O
Agnes	O
Waters	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Cupido	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Carr	O
,	O
Mary	O
Paul	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Stephens	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Wadmouth	O
Fin	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
Bound	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
SHORT-HAND	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
approved	O
Method	O
extant	O
,	O
is	O
taught	O
to	O
Perfection	O
,	O
by	O
William	O
Robinson	O
,	O
at	O
Persons	O
Habitations	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
taketh	O
Tryals	O
and	O
Sermons	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
Oration	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
Exactness	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
spoken	O
with	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow-Coffee-House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
on	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
and	O
Fridays	O
,	O
from	O
9	O
till	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
at	O
Jones	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Finch-lane	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
daily	O
,	O
from	O
two	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minorie	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
IS	O
sold	O
,	O
a	O
never	O
failing	O
Ointment	O
,	O
that	O
Curs	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduced	O
a	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
time	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
.	O
It	O
all	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
make	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
