TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1707-8	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powel	O
,	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wind	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
John	B-pers
Comyn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Boulter	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Faudry	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Conningham	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
William	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
John	B-pers
East	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Predy	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Beatnife	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
office	O
,	O
where	O
't	O
was	O
suffocated	O
with	O
Filth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
dry	O
Gripes	O
,	O
her	O
illness	O
continu	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
till	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bosom	O
of	O
her	O
Shift	O
was	O
stain	O
'd	O
with	O
Milk	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
those	O
about	O
her	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
the	O
Dry	O
Gripes	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Distemper	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
then	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
young	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
Miscarried	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
foul	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
upon	O
search	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
growth	O
of	O
it	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
gone	O
her	O
full	O
time	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
she	O
heard	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
us	O
'd	O
any	O
endeavour	O
to	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
I	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
requires	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Welder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stol'n	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clear	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Swate	I-pers
alias	O
Sweet	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Inglesby	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Stab	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Inglesby	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Inglesby	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Shoomaker	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
Ratcliff	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
Pig	O
the	O
Shoomaker	O
had	O
just	O
bought	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
without	O
speaking	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Provocation	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
from	O
divers	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Distracted	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
white	O
Dimity	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Vanderbrook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cales	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Chain	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
70	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lady	O
the	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
upon	O
Tower	B-place
Wharf	I-place
carrying	O
off	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
towards	O
the	O
Water-side	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
take	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
from	O
Tower-Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
A	O
Smith	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
Hoops	O
several	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
Heaters	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
A	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Walner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
staid	O
4	O
Nights	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
11	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trahern	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Dowlace	O
Smock	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
ready	O
open	O
to	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Box	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
enquiry	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
of	O
hers	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
13	O
Ells	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
value	O
56s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Stuff	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
back	O
being	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Peticoats	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
P-	B-pers
J-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dansy	I-pers
alias	O
Vigo	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Chain	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
70	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lady	O
the	O
Queen	B-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Dansy	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
that	O
Dansy	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
piece	O
of	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Dansy	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
Abbot	O
,	O
but	O
divers	O
substantial	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Trusty	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
Parish	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
thrust	O
against	O
the	O
People	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crafts	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Table	O
Books	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
2	O
Leather	O
Cases	O
,	O
2	O
Needle	O
Books	O
with	O
Silver	O
Cases	O
,	O
2	O
Glasses	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
8	O
Turkey	O
Garters	O
,	O
1	O
Tortois	O
Shell	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Glass	O
Case	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
her	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
Imprest	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
than	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
L-	B-pers
P-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
an	O
Inquisition	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Fenwick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Fenwick	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Harrison	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
going	O
with	O
one	O
Bennet	O
,	O
by	O
Billiter	B-place
Lane	I-place
end	I-place
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
2	O
Women	O
;	O
that	O
Harrison	O
taking	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
with	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
by	O
that	O
Instant	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
?	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Provocation	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
divers	O
blows	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
there	O
arose	O
a	O
small	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
down	O
and	O
Died	O
immediately	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
2	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Leaden-Hall	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
such	O
Violence	O
,	O
as	O
struck	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Channel	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
went	O
likewise	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
first	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Croud	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
these	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
confronted	O
by	O
the	O
Queens	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
Dirty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hamson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
Instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Hamson	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
Murder	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
there	O
was	O
information	O
given	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Watch	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
making	O
enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Chisel	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
Case	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Movement	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
from	O
Aldersgate	O
with	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
cross	O
the	O
Farthing	O
Pyhouse	O
Fields	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
A	O
Porter	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hoxton	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
near	O
which	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
Men	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Painters	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Farthing	O
Pyhouse	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
after	O
an	O
unusual	O
manner	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
this	O
way	O
or	O
that	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
very	O
Stern	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
this	O
Evidence	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
Case	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
pieces	O
near	O
the	O
Steps	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
divers	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
In	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Enormities	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
receiving	O
several	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
wrong	O
laid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Orders	O
for	O
preferring	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
5l	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Eeves	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
1	O
blew	O
Apron	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Swallow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lunt	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Lunt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
family	O
being	O
all	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
broken	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Widow	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
a	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
bruising	O
the	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
buying	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
by	O
Christianus	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Elexander	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
2	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Beans	O
and	O
5	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
in	O
corresponding	O
with	O
her	O
Majesties	O
Enemies	O
:	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
Printed	O
by	O
itself	O
,	O
and	O
Published	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Whereas	O
last	O
Sessions	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Alice	O
Jones	O
it	O
is	O
Printed	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
40	O
Pound	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
15	O
Pound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
William	O
Gregg	O
,	O
Alexander	O
Carrol	O
,	O
Ann	O
Gardner	O
,	O
William	O
Swallow	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Read	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
Francis	O
Read	O
,	O
Ann	O
Williams	O
,	O
Henry	O
Cales	O
and	O
John	O
Davis	O
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Twelves	O
,	O
Robert	O
Dansy	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hare	O
,	O
Mary	O
Newman	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Chapman	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bly	O
,	O
John	O
Crases	O
,	O
Henry	O
Arnold	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Underhill	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
she	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
Printed	O
at	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Printing	O
Office	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
In	O
400.	O
upon	O
very	O
good	O
Paper	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
Parish-Clarks	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
Families	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
also	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
All	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
un-Rul	O
'd	O
,	O
also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
Large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Volumes	O
.	O
Newly	O
Published	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
and	O
Enlarged	O
to	O
more	O
than	O
Double	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
Sheets	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Impression	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
on	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Easiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
;	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
,	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruined	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practises	O
are	O
clearly	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Venereal	O
and	O
other	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Introductory	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
their	O
Life	O
and	O
Abuse	O
,	O
are	O
briefly	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
potent	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publish	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Precise	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
)	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
W.	O
Hawes	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
street	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Ilsted	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
4s	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-Birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
IS	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
a	O
never-failing	O
Oyntment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
it	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
,	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
Dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
Sudden	O
Surprises	O
,	O
and	O
sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
and	O
inveterate	O
Giddinesses	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Falterings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
forcefully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experience	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
)	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
;	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
Incomparable	O
Cordial	O
Stomach	O
Pills	O
,	O
Which	O
without	O
Purging	O
,	O
Confinement	O
,	O
or	O
Trouble	O
,	O
absolutely	O
Cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
,	O
Indigestion	O
,	O
Stoppage	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
safe	O
and	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ache	O
,	O
Whither	O
it	O
proceeds	O
from	O
Rheume	O
,	O
Rottenness	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Sold	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
at	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
Stationer	O
,	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Milner	O
at	O
the	O
red	O
Meg	O
in	O
Popes	O
Mead	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Milk	O
Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
a	O
Cane	O
Shop	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Horn	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Flood	O
Street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Forsey	O
Perfumer	O
next	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Howel	O
Perfumer	O
,	O
next	O
Leicester	O
House	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Da	O
.	O
Perfonce	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
Arms	O
in	O
Dyot	O
Street	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Just	O
Published	O
.	O
Biography	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Touch	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Tails	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Lampoon	O
privately	O
dispers	O
'd	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
Wells	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
1707	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Water-Drinker	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Water-Drinkers	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
merry	O
Elegy	O
upon	O
Mother	O
Jefferies	O
,	O
the	O
ancient	O
Water-Dirper	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Pulpit	O
Fool	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
distinct	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Clergy-Men	O
in	O
the	O
Queens	O
Dominions	O
,	O
both	O
Church-Men	O
and	O
Dissenters	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
THE	O
Prophetical	O
Warnings	O
of	O
John	O
Lacy	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
pronounc	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Operation	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
,	O
and	O
faithfully	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
spoken	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
,	O
Price	O
6d	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
Parts	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Author	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
Book	O
Entitled	O
,	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Impostors	O
,	O
no	O
Prophets	O
.	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Villanous	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Robber	O
,	O
Pen	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
exact	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
General	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
lively	O
Representation	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
Inhabitaries	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Manners	O
and	O
Customs	O
observed	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Nature	O
and	O
Means	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
several	O
Thefts	O
and	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Distinctliness	O
observed	O
in	O
their	O
respective	O
Functions	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Cant	O
generally	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
those	O
Sort	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
conceal	O
their	O
Villanies	O
;	O
and	O
Rules	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
Robb	O
'd	O
or	O
Cheated	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Usefully	O
set	O
forth	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Instance	O
of	O
many	O
honest	O
People	O
.	O
THE	O
Sot-weed	O
Factor	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Maryland	O
,	O
a	O
Satyr	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
is	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Laws	O
,	O
Governments	O
,	O
Courts	O
and	O
Constitutions	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Buildings	O
,	O
Feasts	O
,	O
Frolicks	O
,	O
Entertainments	O
and	O
Drunken	O
Humours	O
of	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
America	O
:	O
In	O
Burlesque	O
Verse	O
,	O
By	O
Eben	O
.	O
Cook	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
Quakerisin	O
Dissected	O
and	O
laid	O
open	O
.	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Preacise	O
containing	O
a	O
faithful	O
Discovery	O
of	O
near	O
upon	O
six	O
Hundred	O
of	O
their	O
Errors	O
and	O
horrible	O
Blasphemies	O
;	O
tending	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
Destruction	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Christian	O
Faith	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
total	O
subversion	O
of	O
the	O
Established	O
Government	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Sincerely	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
choicest	O
and	O
most	O
celebrated	O
Writers	O
:	O
and	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
publick	O
view	O
of	O
all	O
Men	O
.	O
Occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
late	O
Discourse	O
,	O
publish	O
'd	O
by	O
Rich	O
.	O
Clarridge	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Melius	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Just	O
and	O
Honest	O
return	O
for	O
his	O
unjust	O
and	O
dishonest	O
charge	O
of	O
Blasphemes	O
(	O
In	O
that	O
contain	O
'd	O
)	O
against	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Fathers	O
and	O
Writers	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Will	O
.	O
Carter	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
THe	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Siege	O
of	O
Toulon	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Political	O
Reasons	O
that	O
mov	O
'd	O
the	O
Confederates	O
to	O
undertake	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
all	O
that	O
happened	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Savoy	O
's	O
entering	O
Provence	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
march	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Port	O
of	O
Toulon	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
particular	O
during	O
the	O
Siege	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
further	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
kill	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
Harbour	O
,	O
Fortifications	O
,	O
French	O
and	O
Confederate	O
Camps	O
,	O
Batteries	O
and	O
Mountains	O
.	O
Done	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
Copy	O
,	O
Printed	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2s	O
.	O
THe	O
3d	O
Volume	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Poems	O
on	O
divers	O
subjects	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Charitable	O
Citizen	O
.	O
Fortunes	O
bounty	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
against	O
the	O
corrupt	O
use	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
A	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Musical	O
Entertainment	O
.	O
The	O
Libertine	O
's	O
Choice	O
.	O
All	O
Men	O
mad	O
.	O
Helter	O
Skelter	O
.	O
Honesty	O
in	O
Distress	O
.	O
The	O
1st	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Journey	O
to	O
H-	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
against	O
Wine	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
in	O
praise	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
.	O
A	O
Poem	O
on	O
the	O
Success	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Poems	O
never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
;	O
where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Friendly	O
Correspondences	O
,	O
or	O
Epistolory	O
Satyrs	O
upon	O
Virtue	O
and	O
Vice	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
Letters	O
under	O
the	O
following	O
Heads	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1st	O
Tom	O
Brewer	O
's	O
last	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
witty	O
Friends	O
and	O
Companions	O
.	O
2d	O
,	O
A	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
concerning	O
the	O
Publick	O
Affairs	O
of	O
his	O
Town	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
pleasant	O
,	O
comical	O
,	O
and	O
delightful	O
Predictions	O
and	O
Observations	O
upon	O
every	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
throughout	O
the	O
Year	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Writings	O
hitherto	O
excl	O
:	O
