TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hassel	I-pers
,	O
Major	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	O
Fitz-hugh	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Beswick	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kidgell	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Whiteband	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huce	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rofford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellenor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olives	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Filth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
:	O
That	O
thinking	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
things	O
suitable	O
to	O
the	O
Distemper	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Illness	O
continued	O
upon	O
her	O
till	O
Morning	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
when	O
by	O
divers	O
Circumstances	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
newly	O
thrown	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
,	O
but	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
her	O
full	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Service	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Muslin	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walley	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
suspecting	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Shop-lifter	O
,	O
had	O
their	O
Eyes	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
treating	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
draw	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
under	O
some	O
Callico	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
immediately	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
them	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stonnell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Brewer	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
Ells	O
of	O
black	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mosell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
3	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Companions	O
were	O
amusing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
cheapning	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
abovementioned	O
Goods	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sollors	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Johnson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
Baskets	O
of	O
Goods	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
Arm	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
,	O
examined	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
that	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offering	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithins	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
10	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
6	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Cecil	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
44	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Lutestring	O
Silk	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tissue	O
Silk	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lidgett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
his	O
Kitchin	O
Fire	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
to	O
come	O
softly	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
Confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shewell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Coral	O
and	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Shewell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Sash	O
espy	O
'd	O
a	O
strange	O
Man	O
opening	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
leap	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
closely	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
Ring	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
buying	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Brass	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Ax	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chaffin	O
Dish	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
Nunes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Jews	O
Synagogue	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
returned	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
their	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
giving	O
no	O
Reason	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
the	O
manner	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
producing	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sophia	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Damask	O
Side-board	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
15	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
7	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lucin	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
landed	O
at	O
Hungerford	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Potter	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aldley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
12	O
l.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
an	O
Inn	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
suspecting	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
Feathers	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
laid	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
him	O
at	O
Work	O
about	O
Midnight	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
producing	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-pag	O
,	O
10	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Brocade	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Books	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Chambers	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Books	O
at	O
a	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Teader	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ormorod	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Drugger	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chitts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spinks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Crocket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Jaccobus	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Melsom	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Edgsbrook	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Vineyard	O
a	O
Lodger	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
drinking	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Body	O
hear	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
hall	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Bed	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground-Floor	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
his	O
Landlady	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
snoaring	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
all	O
Bloody	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
throwing	O
down	O
the	O
Bedcloaths	O
his	O
Throat	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Cut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wound	O
not	O
dangerous	O
,	O
his	O
Shirt-Sleeves	O
were	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
his	O
Arm	O
Wounded	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
that	O
cover	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
cut	O
;	O
a	O
bloody	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
them	O
a	O
Pole-Ax	O
:	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
suspecting	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
murdered	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Shed	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Throat	O
cut	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
;	O
her	O
Stomach	O
cut	O
down	O
throughout	O
like	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Bowels	O
and	O
Heart	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Tub	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
holewas	O
discover	O
'd	O
which	O
exactly	O
filled	O
the	O
blunt	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Pole-Ax	O
;	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
fast	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Murder	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
committed	O
by	O
any	O
without	O
Doors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
his	O
Throat	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
a	O
black	O
Man	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
well	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
not	O
Bloody	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
Shirt	O
Sleeves	O
being	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hands	O
all	O
Bloody	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
bloody	O
Knife	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pole-Ax	O
which	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
found	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
of	O
no	O
Body	O
but	O
himself	O
(	O
except	O
Vineyard	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
)	O
being	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
left	O
a-jar	O
when	O
Vineyard	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
bolted	O
when	O
she	O
arose	O
:	O
All	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
concurring	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aggitha	B-pers
Ashbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
strangling	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
List	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
been	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Female	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
strangled	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lift	O
braided	O
about	O
its	O
Neck	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Corin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Marshal	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Eling	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Turkies	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Turkies	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
Watkins	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Chain	O
from	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brownrigg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mallicoat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nightingal	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
be	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
very	O
friendly	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
accidentally	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
discover	O
'd	O
nothing	O
of	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
lived	O
like	O
two	O
Brothers	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dyed	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Strut	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishop	I-place
's	I-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Trunk	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
between	O
Islington	O
and	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
David	I-pers
Castelian	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilt	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Bed	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tables	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
Diamonds	O
10	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Massier	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Briggs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slaorgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Weaver	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
concealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Furnace	I-pers
for	O
150	O
l.	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Harwich	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
imbark	O
with	O
his	O
Effects	O
for	O
Holland	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
their	O
Warrant	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Exibition	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
design	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
Holland	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
Dutch	O
Checks	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
quick	O
return	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beacher	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
principal	O
Creditors	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Beacher	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Messenger	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Creditors	O
were	O
severe	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Words	O
frighted	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Beacher	O
,	O
to	O
satisfie	O
him	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
up	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
favourably	O
received	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
was	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
surrendred	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
kindly	O
dealt	O
with	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
gave	O
himself	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
almost	O
all	O
satisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Conduct	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Callon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Callow	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
1707	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
One	O
Catherine	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
that	O
Morning	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
him	O
2	O
bloody	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Tooth-pick	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Steel	O
Tobacco-Stopper	O
,	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
run	O
with	O
Cotton-thread	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
Things	O
and	O
Mony	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
on	O
.	O
Millar	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
Things	O
at	O
Gaming	O
;	O
But	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
moreover	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Johnson	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
prov	O
'd	O
Millar	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
lewd	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
had	O
kept	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
gratifie	O
her	O
with	O
Mony	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
constant	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
worth	O
250.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
under	O
no	O
Temptation	O
to	O
commit	O
such	O
a	O
villanous	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bossingham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Susanna	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ear-Ring	O
,	O
2	O
Guinea	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evividence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shammy	O
Gloves	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
Exciseman	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
carrying	O
on	O
a	O
corrupt	O
Confederacy	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Queen	B-pers
of	O
her	O
Customs	O
of	O
Excise	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Brewer	O
gave	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
among	O
4	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
to	O
connive	O
at	O
his	O
mixing	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
with	O
Strong	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
found	O
his	O
Dealings	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
such	O
mixture	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Matter	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
heard	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
them	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Sollors	O
,	O
Mary	O
Booth	O
,	O
Mary	O
Ellener	O
,	O
Aggitha	O
Ashbrook	O
,	O
John	O
Barnes	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Hard	O
Labour	O
12	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bell	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Aldley	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Brewer	O
,	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
,	O
Sophia	O
Ballard	O
,	O
Mary	O
Phillips	O
,	O
William	O
White	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Lidget	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Price	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Newman	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Marsh	O
,	O
Mary	O
Saunders	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
1	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Corin	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
THis	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Ministers	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Cassocks	O
,	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Sashes	O
,	O
Lawyers	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Livery	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Gowns	O
for	O
Mayors	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
any	O
Corporation	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Anthony	O
Ingram	O
,	O
Robe-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Livery	O
Hood	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
North	O
Gate	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
ready	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Prices	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
Black	O
Cloath	O
and	O
Prunella	O
sold	O
for	O
Ministers	O
Wear	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
Cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescribed	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
on	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easy	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
,	O
Edmond	O
Curle	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
fam	O
'd	O
Canker-Water	O
,	O
WHich	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
immediately	O
cures	O
all	O
Cankers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heats	O
and	O
Inflammations	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
gone	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
Tongue	O
,	O
Checks	O
,	O
or	O
Lips	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
saved	O
be	O
Lives	O
of	O
several	O
both	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
Robine	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Exchange-alley	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
its	O
Vertue	O
decays	O
no	O
in	O
keeping	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
and	O
much	O
esteemed	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
Just	O
Published	O
the	O
sixth	O
Edition	O
with	O
great	O
Additions	O
,	O
of	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
,	O
Business	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skillful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
.	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Venereal	O
and	O
other	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Introductory	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
,	O
are	O
briefly	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Preface	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
)	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Isted	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
Dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressious	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Faintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
)	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
RObert	O
Whitlege	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Bull	O
in	O
Ave-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
,	O
also	O
other	O
fine	O
cuts	O
fitted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
,	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
.	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
vnd	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
Supplement	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
Washington	O
and	O
Wingate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Clarendon	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folio	O
and	O
Octavo	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Translation	O
of	O
Esop	O
's	O
Fables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
Y.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercer	O
Chappel	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
MEmoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Villianous	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
and	O
Notorious	O
Robber	O
.	O
Pen	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
soule	O
time	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
exact	O
Life	O
and	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
General	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
lively	O
Representations	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Manners	O
and	O
Customs	O
observed	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Nature	O
and	O
Means	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
commit	O
their	O
several	O
Theifts	O
and	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Distinctions	O
observed	O
in	O
their	O
respective	O
Functions	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
cant	O
generally	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
conceal	O
their	O
Villanies	O
;	O
and	O
Rules	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
Robbd	O
or	O
Cheated	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Usefully	O
,	O
set	O
forth	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Instance	O
of	O
many	O
honest	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
the	O
Complete	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Prisons	O
for	O
Debt	O
.	O
THE	O
Power	O
and	O
Prerogatives	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Faction	O
exemplified	O
in	O
variety	O
of	O
modern	O
Instances	O
in	O
Private	O
Transactions	O
and	O
publick	O
Affairs	O
.	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
seditious	O
Insects	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Levellers	O
assembl	O
'd	O
in	O
Convocation	O
,	O
a	O
Poem	O
.	O
p	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Tale	O
,	O
a	O
Poem	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
28th	O
Book	O
of	O
Orlando	O
Furinso	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Cante	O
's	O
p.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Don	O
Politico	O
Piscatori	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Political	O
Fisherman	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
translated	O
from	O
the	O
original	O
Manuscript	O
in	O
the	O
Vatican	O
Library	O
,	O
and	O
humbly	O
inscrib	O
'd	O
to	O
C	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
st	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
,	O
against	O
whimsical	O
Innovators	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Court	O
Favourite	O
,	O
representing	O
the	O
Mischiefs	O
that	O
flow	O
from	O
Ministers	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
more	O
great	O
than	O
good	O
;	O
the	O
Arts	O
they	O
use	O
to	O
secure	O
their	O
Masters	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
unhappiness	O
of	O
Princes	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
curs	O
'd	O
with	O
such	O
destructive	O
Servants	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
,	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Sot	O
weed	O
Factor	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
a	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Maryland	O
,	O
a	O
Satyr	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
is	O
described	O
,	O
the	O
Laws	O
,	O
Governments	O
,	O
Courts	O
,	O
and	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Buildings	O
.	O
Feasts	O
,	O
Frolicks	O
,	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
and	O
drunken	O
Humours	O
of	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
America	O
.	O
In	O
burlesque	O
Verse	O
.	O
By	O
Eben	O
.	O
Cook	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
p.	O
6	O
d.	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
Tracts	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
True-Born-Englishman	O
,	O
sing	O
All	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Bragge	O
in	O
Pater	O
Noster-Row	O
.	O
MUrder	O
within	O
Doors	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
a	O
War	O
among	O
our	O
selves	O
.	O
Proving	O
there	O
are	O
more	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Vintners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
than	O
saved	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Baochanalian	O
Dialogue	O
,	O
representing	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
modern	O
celebrated	O
Liquors	O
.	O
Which	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
prevented	O
while	O
the	O
Vimners	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
Syder-men	O
,	O
our	O
Punch-makers	O
with	O
the	O
Apothecaries	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Derby	O
and	O
Nottingham-Ale	O
Brewers	O
with	O
the	O
Lime-Kilns	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Dishonour	O
of	O
the	O
Grape	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
irreparable	O
Disgrace	O
of	O
immortal	O
Barley	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
-	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
