TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
1701	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DUNCOMBE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Ld	O
.	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
William	B-pers
Humerton	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Honick	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Longbothom	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
William	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Mundy	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lovelock	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
next	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
learn	O
'd	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
be	O
within	O
presently	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kickson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Boot	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pantry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Northcoat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Little	I-pers
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
Little	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pots	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Boucher	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
Cistern	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
drop't	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
and	O
1/2	O
of	O
Broadcloth	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Critchlow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busy	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Zacheus	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
then	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bolster	O
,	O
3	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
returning	O
from	O
the	O
Country	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Lodging	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
entered	O
his	O
Lodging	O
twice	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
rusty	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offering	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
'em	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chaffen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
50s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Chaffen	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
B-	B-pers
J-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Piggels	I-pers
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
alias	O
Rawlinson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
gilt	O
Coral	O
value	O
38s	O
.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grevil	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Holland	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
way	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
already	O
attainted	O
)	O
did	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
Steal	O
a	O
Show	O
Glass	O
with	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
100l	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Lombards	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Rabbit	O
Skins	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Northern	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
imploy	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
to	O
hang	O
up	O
Rabbit	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Organ	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Atwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
apprehended	O
her	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Prisilla	B-pers
Cleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Bason	O
,	O
3	O
China	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shot	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Boskon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
shewing	O
several	O
Drawers	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
perceiving	O
she	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
:	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stern	I-pers
alias	O
Carr	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
Linen	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
Golden	O
Square	O
,	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Lady	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
wait	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Landlord	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
showing	O
him	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Shetton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Poysoning	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
Rats	O
Bane	O
in	O
Broth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Parish	O
Nurses	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Ladle	O
half	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Broth	O
,	O
stirring	O
it	O
about	O
with	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Porridge-Pot	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Family	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
eat	O
of	O
the	O
Broth	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
15	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
Vomiting	O
;	O
it	O
wrought	O
to	O
that	O
degree	O
upon	O
the	O
2	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
died	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
severalApothecaries	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
to	O
buy	O
Rats	O
Bane	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
succeeded	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
discover	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
her	O
intent	O
of	O
getting	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Poyson	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
thought	O
see	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Ladle	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Design	O
upon	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
whole	O
Series	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
Distracted	O
,	O
and	O
fancied	O
she	O
was	O
Damn	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Spirit	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
Outragious	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
chain	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
likewise	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
great	O
disorder	O
of	O
Mind	O
when	O
she	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Lunatick	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
aged	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
of	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
River	B-place
of	I-place
Thames	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Daughter	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
Child	O
under	O
the	O
Ice	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Heaven	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
plainly	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
hath	O
not	O
been	O
seen	O
since	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
was	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
been	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
trouble	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
disponding	O
Condition	O
(	O
for	O
Misfortunes	O
relating	O
to	O
her	O
Family	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
commit	O
many	O
extravagant	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
In	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
would	O
rise	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
and	O
Dance	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
which	O
Disorders	O
of	O
Mind	O
continu	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
under	O
those	O
unhappy	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Lunatick	O
at	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
affectionate	O
Mother	O
to	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
its	O
being	O
miserable	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
good	O
Credit	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Senses	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
discreet	O
Person	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
Vice	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kidder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Yard	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bonfield	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Pin	O
upon	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
offering	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
stop	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Person	O
so	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
knotty	O
Stick	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Arms	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
divers	O
Reasons	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Conly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Morrice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
engag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hug	O
'd	O
and	O
Kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Doe	O
Skin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
apprehended	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Halson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Boylers	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Bell	O
Mettle	O
Skillets	O
20	O
s.	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
30	O
s.	O
30	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
Hartshorn	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Moss	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
a	O
Breach	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Brick	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
large	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
enter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
after	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
And	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
giving	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Henry	O
Halson	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
and	O
White	O
Stuff	O
;	O
and	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Anterine	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Chamber	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Anterine	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Discovery	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc'din	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
and	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chapman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Halson	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
11	O
.	O
W	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
,	O
Richard	O
Northcoat	O
,	O
Christian	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Catherine	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Barbara	O
Smith	O
,	O
Ann	O
Paxton	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Stern	O
,	O
Susa	O
.	O
Blackwell	O
,	O
Charles	O
Conly	O
.	O
Petit	O
Larcenies	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Timms	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Clark	O
,	O
Alice	O
Boskon	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cooper	O
,	O
John	O
Greenway	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THis	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Ministers	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Cassocks	O
,	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Sashes	O
,	O
Lawyers	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Livery	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Gowns	O
for	O
Mayors	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
any	O
Corporation	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Anthony	O
Ingram	O
,	O
Robe-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Livery	O
Hood	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
North-Gate	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
who	O
back	O
of	O
them	O
ready	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Prices	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Prunella	O
sold	O
for	O
Ministers	O
wear	O
.	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Bull	O
in	O
Ave-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
is	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plan	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
also	O
other	O
fine	O
Cuts	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
of	O
Common-Prayer	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
.	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common	O
.	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
Supplement	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
Washington	O
and	O
Wingate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Clarendon	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folio	O
and	O
Octave	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Translation	O
of	O
Esops	O
Fables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
Y.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercer	O
Chapplin	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Also	O
By	O
.	O
Beweridges	O
Works	O
in	O
5	O
Vol	O
.	O
Dean	O
Stanhoye	O
on	O
the	O
Epistles	O
and	O
Gospels	O
,	O
in	O
4	O
Vol	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Rememedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinemen	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
or	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazarious	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
received	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
of	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
cases	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Churle	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
RElief	O
and	O
a	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
stubborn	O
and	O
inveterate	O
Poxes	O
,	O
of	O
so	O
long	O
standing	O
that	O
the	O
very	O
Bones	O
are	O
Infected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Patient	O
so	O
deplorable	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
violent	O
Pains	O
,	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
to	O
despair	O
of	O
ever	O
being	O
cured	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Method	O
and	O
Medicine	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
near	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
successful	O
,	O
Practice	O
,	O
to	O
perform	O
in	O
such	O
cases	O
a	O
specify	O
,	O
sale	O
effectual	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Gonorrbau	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
at	O
Clap	O
,	O
the	O
Infection	O
is	O
perfectly	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
hindrance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
Days	O
time	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
Passage	O
(	O
the	O
most	O
private	O
place	O
in	O
London	O
)	O
three	O
doors	O
beyond	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Hony	O
Lane	O
Market	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
The	O
fam	O
'd	O
Canker	O
Water	O
.	O
WHich	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
immediately	O
cures	O
all	O
Cankers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
eating	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heats	O
and	O
inflammations	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
ho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
gone	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Tongue	O
,	O
Cheaks	O
or	O
Lips	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
saved	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
several	O
both	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
Robina	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Exchange-alley	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Its	O
Vertue	O
decays	O
no	O
in	O
keeping	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
and	O
much	O
esteemed	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Treatise	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Easiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
,	O
Reasons	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Even	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
is	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
Sec	O
.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
or	O
Seminal	O
,	O
briefly	O
describing	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
their	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
at	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publishd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
Modern	O
,	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
A.	O
Collins	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
beyond	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
John	O
Marten	O
Surgeon	O
writ	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Appendix	O
to	O
sixth	O
Edition	O
of	O
his	O
Booh	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
w	O
System	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
secret	O
Infirmities	O
and	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Natural	O
,	O
Accidental	O
and	O
Venereal	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
defile	O
and	O
ruin	O
the	O
Healths	O
of	O
themselves	O
and	O
their	O
Posterity	O
,	O
obstruct	O
Conjugal	O
Delectancy	O
and	O
Pregnancy	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
various	O
Methods	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Somethings	O
particular	O
concerning	O
Generation	O
and	O
Conception	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
Miscarriages	O
in	O
Women	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Causes	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
Useful	O
for	O
Physicians	O
,	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
Apothecaries	O
and	O
Midwives	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
Have	O
,	O
or	O
Are	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
falling	O
under	O
any	O
such	O
Impure	O
or	O
Defective	O
:	O
Indispositions	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
further	O
warning	O
against	O
Quacks	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
some	O
torious	O
Abuses	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
People	O
may	O
avoid	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Letter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Paper	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
his	O
Book	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
please	O
may	O
bind	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Sold	O
in	O
Octavo	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Places	O
above	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
THE	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Murders	O
,	O
Robberies	O
and	O
Burnings	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Bradforton	O
and	O
Upton-Snodsbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Worcester	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
Examination	O
.	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
,	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	O
Hobbins	O
and	O
John	O
Allen	O
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
Crimes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Bp	O
.	O
of	O
Oxford	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
their	O
Condemnation	O
.	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners-And	O
remarks	O
on	O
their	O
dying	O
Speeches	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
on	O
Occasion	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
imperfect	O
,	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entituled	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
were	O
executed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
R.	O
W.	O
-	O
Printed	O
or	O
Jonah	O
Bowyer	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
THE	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Robert	O
Feilding	O
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
her	O
Grace	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Cleeaveland	O
;	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mary	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
With	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Letters	O
between	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
and	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mrs.	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Anne	O
Countess	O
of	O
Fielding	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
all	O
the	O
Learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
Persued	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Spiritual	O
Court	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sentence	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Morphew	O
near	O
Stationers-Hall	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Wind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressions	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Fainting	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
JOHN	O
BARBER	O
on	O
Lambeth-hill	O
in	O
Old	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
1709	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
