TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1709	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
GARRARD	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Powys	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
King	I-pers
William	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hedgeabout	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Kelling	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Rohdes	I-pers
George	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Serjenson	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
&	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pennyfeather	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Moss	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
one	O
Lamas	O
,	O
going	O
together	O
near	O
Marribone	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
Men	O
with	O
Sacks	O
upon	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
Lamas	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
Jones	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
Murder	O
was	O
then	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
Lamas	O
's	O
Relief	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
;	O
when	O
1	O
of	O
the	O
Sacks	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kettle	O
was	O
found	O
therein	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Accomplices	O
)	O
Depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Bacon	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Shear	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wells	O
and	O
Jones	O
came	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Heat	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
they	O
staid	O
so	O
late	O
?	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
they	O
came	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Fray	O
;	O
Jones	O
,	O
saying	O
moreover	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
like	O
an	O
Ox	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Kettle	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Pennyfeather	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Royly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
amus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
asking	O
to	O
hear	O
her	O
Read	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
were	O
again	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Jones	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lamas	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
following	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
Wells	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
Jones	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murder	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
by	O
Jones	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
Wells	O
assisting	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pennyfeather	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
12	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
12	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Haydon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Owen	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Jones	O
and	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Pennyfeather	O
was	O
any	O
further	O
concern	O
'd	O
than	O
being	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dalkieth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
,	O
who	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jewman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
pitch	O
Forks	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gidden	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gidden	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Linen	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Washer	O
Womans	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Gidden	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Disposing	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Brigget	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
18s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
Fixing	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
alias	O
Bearbanks	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bellingam	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Pain	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Shootwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Wearing	O
Cloths	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Billingam	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
outward	O
Door	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
returning	O
about	O
8	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
Information	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
Pain	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Billingam	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Billingam	O
's	O
Lap	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
newly	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Pain	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dark	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Eysene	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
18s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Culthorp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Pastry	O
Cook	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
eat	O
Pyes	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Cup-board	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
off	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offering	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
alias	O
Hider	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Shoomaker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
bespeak	O
Shooes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
were	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
bundled	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wisden	I-pers
alias	O
More	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Blackfriars	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lauton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lauton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Elephants	O
Teeth	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bissouth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
clearly	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
value	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sharpley	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
20s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tho	O
.	O
Sharpley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
R-	B-pers
J-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
6	O
Elephants	O
Teeth	O
,	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Louton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Louton	I-pers
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Bissouth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
R-	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
John	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Louton	O
,	O
(	O
Apprentice	O
Boys	O
)	O
were	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
weigh	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
value	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Hempen	O
Smock	O
,	O
4	O
Aprons	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
7s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
between	O
Wild-street	B-place
and	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
out	O
?	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
his	O
Mony	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Witton	I-pers
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Lead	O
and	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Scale	O
Beam	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Witton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
being	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
who	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cushion	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
velvet	O
Cushion	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Evers	B-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
Smith	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6l	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
and	O
Hopley	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
stolen	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
G.	B-pers
Pom-	I-pers
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
30	O
Gal-	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultrey	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
alias	O
Marven	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnus	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Shadwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
back	O
being	O
turned	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
immediately	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Varnom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carkass	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Antholins	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Binks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bridget	O
Jones	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Cow	O
from	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Broomer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
giving	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lassel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dunstall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harmsworth	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Bloth	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
a	O
Packhorse	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
proving	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Danban	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
2	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
and	O
40	O
pound	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brockburn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Rout	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Cure	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
an	O
Agat	O
handle	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Cure	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
36	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nichols	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
more	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Tyburn	B-place
;	O
Rout	O
rob	O
'd	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
Long	O
rob	O
'd	O
Nichols	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
both	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Long	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cure	O
's	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
swapt	O
by	O
Rout	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Henry	O
Rout	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Raisor	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
Medals	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cook	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Riding	O
to	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
between	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
and	O
Pindar	B-place
of	I-place
Wakefield	I-place
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Rout	O
and	O
Evans	O
assaulted	O
him	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
These	O
2	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
view	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
seen	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Rout	O
and	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
nothing	O
more	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
S	O
-	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Heatly	I-pers
alias	O
Butler	B-pers
alias	O
Irish	B-pers
Moll	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Munford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
his	O
Right-Arm	O
with	O
a	O
Musket	O
laden	O
with	O
Small-Shot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thanksgiving-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
were	O
merry-making	O
together	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
about	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
from	O
words	O
to	O
blows	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Murder	O
was	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Beadle	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Queens-Peace	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
Trap-Door	O
into	O
the	O
Gutter	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
the	O
Aggressors	O
,	O
they	O
commanded	O
them	O
to	O
surrender	O
themselves	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
Outrageous	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Tiles	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
his	O
Assistant	O
,	O
and	O
dangerously	O
Wounded	O
a	O
Watchman	O
upon	O
the	O
Eye	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Gun	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
from	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
Intreaties	O
were	O
used	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
surrender	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
obstinacy	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
either	O
kill	O
or	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Gun	O
to	O
the	O
Hole	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Shot	O
all	O
alighting	O
on	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
shatter	O
'd	O
the	O
Bone	O
to	O
that	O
degree	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
advice	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
have	O
sav	O
'd	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
following	O
that	O
advice	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
all	O
along	O
blam	O
'd	O
himself	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
imputed	O
all	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Obstinacy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
producing	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Westmorland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Repeating-Clock	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
154	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crimson-Damask	O
,	O
70	O
l.	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
an	O
Indian	O
Quilt	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Parliament	O
Robe	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
otherthings	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Earl	O
of	O
Westmorland	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Nath	B-pers
,	O
Waters	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
or	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
taller	O
Man	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
Sash-Window	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
divers	O
Locks	O
of	O
Chests	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
abundance	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
loaded	O
themselves	O
5	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
whom	O
they	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
were	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Napkins	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
touching	O
Mason	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Whykes	I-pers
and	O
Ester	B-pers
Wiles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Ream	O
of	O
Writing-Paper	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brownsword	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
Easter	O
Wiles	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
Sermon-time	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Marvel	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Dunban	O
,	O
Aaron	O
Jones	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Walls	O
,	O
Henry	O
Rout	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Evans	O
,	O
John	O
Long	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
13	O
.	O
Mary	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Pain	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Billingam	O
,	O
William	O
Ward	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Gidden	O
,	O
Mary	O
Gidden	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hopley	O
,	O
Edward	O
Drake	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
John	O
Louton	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Louton	O
,	O
R	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
.	O
Petty	O
Larcenies	O
15	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lee	O
,	O
Ann	O
Varnom	O
,	O
William	O
Hall	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hayes	O
,	O
S	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
,	O
Ann	O
Wisdell	O
,	O
Francis	O
Smith	O
,	O
Jane	O
Isaacson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Royly	O
,	O
John	O
Price	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cross	O
,	O
Ann	O
Williams	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wykes	O
,	O
Esther	O
Wiles	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
THE	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Taylors	O
Friendly	O
Society	O
,	O
for	O
Insurance	O
upon	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
is	O
kept	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Witch-street	O
,	O
3	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Tuesdays	O
and	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
from	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
10	O
l	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
to	O
7	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
,	O
every	O
second	O
and	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
every	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
Trustees	O
constantly	O
meet	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
the	O
crooked	O
Billet	O
in	O
Billeter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Spotted-Dog	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryars	O
,	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Hours	O
.	O
Here	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
assuring	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
and	O
his	O
Wifes	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
when	O
1500	O
have	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
,	O
200	O
l.	O
at	O
their	O
Deaths	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
which	O
Subscribes	O
upon	O
their	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
shall	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
be	O
reduced	O
to	O
Poverty	O
and	O
want	O
Relief	O
,	O
all	O
such	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
and	O
assisted	O
with	O
all	O
things	O
necessary	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
,	O
till	O
their	O
Claims	O
come	O
due	O
.	O
The	O
charge	O
which	O
each	O
Subscriber	O
pays	O
,	O
for	O
Policies	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Entrance	O
and	O
first	O
Claim	O
being	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
Insurance	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
,	O
kept	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Places	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Amicable	O
Society	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
Subscriber	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
whether	O
Male	O
or	O
Female	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
may	O
if	O
they	O
pleas	O
become	O
Subscribers	O
here	O
also	O
,	O
by	O
paying	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Policy	O
,	O
Stamps	O
Entrance	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
Quarter	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
will	O
120	O
l.	O
be	O
divided	O
Quarterly	O
among	O
the	O
Executors	O
,	O
Administrators	O
or	O
Nominees	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
overtaken	O
with	O
Poverty	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
relieved	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Society	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
other	O
Benefits	O
which	O
are	O
too	O
large	O
here	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
shall	O
therefore	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Abstract	O
of	O
the	O
Settlement	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Print	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Gratis	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
the	O
Office	O
is	O
kept	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
directed	O
.	O
SToughton	O
's	O
great	O
Cordial	O
Elixir	O
:	O
Now	O
famous	O
throughout	O
Europe	O
for	O
the	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Blood	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
describ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Balls	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
only	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Unicorn	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
set	O
forth	O
19	O
Years	O
:	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
best	O
Purl	O
in	O
Beer	O
or	O
Ale	O
,	O
Purl	O
Royal	O
in	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bitter	O
Draught	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
pleasant	O
Bitter	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
now	O
drank	O
by	O
most	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
their	O
Wine	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
,	O
much	O
exceeding	O
any	O
Bitter	O
made	O
with	O
Wormwood	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
so	O
excessive	O
hot	O
and	O
drying	O
,	O
thickens	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
dulls	O
the	O
B	O
and	O
spoils	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
besides	O
it	O
hinders	O
Vigour	O
and	O
Sprightliness	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
excites	O
.	O
Sold	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
many	O
Book	O
sellers	O
and	O
Coffee-houses	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
also	O
at	O
some	O
one	O
such	O
place	O
in	O
most	O
Cities	O
and	O
great	O
Towns	O
in	O
Europe	O
at	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Where	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
sold	O
,	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
send	O
first	O
,	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
with	O
good	O
Allowance	O
,	O
many	O
now	O
selling	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
Dozen	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Seal	O
on	O
each	O
Bottle	O
has	O
Richard	O
Stoughton	O
cut	O
round	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Rememedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
trut	O
way	O
of	O
Curing	O
(	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relation	O
,	O
cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Methods	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
or	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
received	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Gleets	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
Seminal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
pertiment	O
Obsen	O
vaticon	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easie	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
polluted	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Curl	O
at	O
the	O
Dial	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1	O
s.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Treatise	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
the	O
Future	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
;	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Basiness	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
,	O
Reasons	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
cots	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
.	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taiot	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
or	O
Seminal	O
,	O
briefly	O
describing	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
their	O
Genital	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
,	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
Women	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cases	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
,	O
never	O
Publishd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Marten	O
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Copious	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
A.	O
Collins	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Seneca	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
beyond	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
John	O
Marten	O
Surgeon	O
write	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4	O
s.	O
RObert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ave-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
Booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
Bibles	O
and	O
common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plain	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
,	O
also	O
other	O
same	O
Cuts	O
,	O
and	O
fisted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
of	O
Common-Prayer	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
.	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
Supplement	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vots	O
.	O
Washington	O
and	O
Wingate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Clarendown	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folto	O
and	O
Octavo	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Translation	O
of	O
Esops	O
Fables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercers	O
Chappel	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Also	O
Bp	O
.	O
Beveridges	O
Works	O
in	O
5	O
Vol	O
.	O
Dean	O
Stanhope	O
on	O
the	O
Epistles	O
and	O
Gospels	O
,	O
in	O
4	O
Vol	O
The	O
Watch	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressions	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
Spirits	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
unless	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Paintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
.	O
THat	O
Susanna	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
she	O
having	O
had	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
Experience	O
in	O
the	O
Dr.	O
Life	O
time	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
making	O
of	O
Medicines	O
,	O
but	O
knowing	O
the	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
administring	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Pills	O
and	O
Drink	O
hindring	O
no	O
Business	O
,	O
Cures	O
all	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurf	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
which	O
Medicines	O
she	O
makes	O
as	O
her	O
Father	O
did	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
dangerous	O
use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
that	O
is	O
generally	O
used	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
cured	O
many	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
after	O
fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
raiseth	O
the	O
Malignity	O
and	O
other	O
Evils	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
fixes	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
Take	O
heed	O
whom	O
you	O
trust	O
in	O
these	O
Cures	O
,	O
for	O
many	O
pretends	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
few	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
deals	O
with	O
all	O
Persons	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
Abilities	O
.	O
The	O
Pills	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Drink	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
she	O
gives	O
her	O
Advice	O
Gratis	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
write	O
or	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
still	O
lives	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
Lanthorn	O
in	O
Plow-yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
