TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
8th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1710	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
GILBERT	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Trevor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powes	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kimble	I-pers
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cookson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pansford	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hulton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
Laurence	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Christian	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Saddle-Bags	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Neckclothes	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
again	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
Bags	O
,	O
with	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
riding	O
together	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
dog	O
them	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
Miles	O
missing	O
of	O
his	O
Bags	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
riding	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
Butcher	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Miles	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lamas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
23	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
English	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
(	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
being	O
backward	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arose	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessing	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anne	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing-Clothes	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Broady	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Anne	B-pers
Broady	I-pers
's	O
Servant	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Broady	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Michael	B-pers
Franso	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Paul	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Killet	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Tacker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Franso	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
hung	O
a	O
drying	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Franso	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Johnson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Sesill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
,	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
Shop	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
full	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Allen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonions	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Bulk	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
was	O
himself	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batersby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fabion	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
one	O
Oldrid	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Oldrid	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
ofhis	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Leverston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	O
without	B-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat-Case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Beaver-Hat	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
alighting	O
from	O
an	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
some	O
Resistance	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queen	I-place
Higth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Malt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
Sacks	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
29	O
Ells	O
of	O
Hamborough	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Whitsters	B-place
Grounds	I-place
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
upon	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Lodging	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mocket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillow	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Pictures	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
afore-said	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
his	O
Landlady	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cortup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
were	O
shewed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
disagreeing	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
without	O
buying	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
missing	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denying	O
it	O
;	O
Threats	O
were	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
F	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
46	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
twenty	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
granted	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Lomax	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Brentford	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
17	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Meechim	I-pers
alias	O
Murfey	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Murfey	I-pers
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pullets	O
,	O
one	O
Hen	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Cocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
among	O
his	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Window	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
alias	O
Seymour	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Peticoat	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
Dowlace	O
Smocks	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
Idiot	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellows	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
:	O
And	O
Indicted	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Pewter	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callico	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
privately	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
160	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Maribone	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Suits	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Muslen	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
furbelow	O
Aprons	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Williams	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
Impress	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
House	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
stick	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Johnson	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Johnson	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
likewise	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridget	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tuckey	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbond	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
the	O
detestible	O
Sin	O
of	O
Buggary	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	O
Stiles	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stand	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
gilt	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	O
la	O
Peiper	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Gross	O
of	O
Silk	O
Laces	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Lace	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sayers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Back-Shop	O
,	O
espy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Counter	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
totake	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
his	O
Goods	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fishpond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
Allamode	O
Scarf	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gallier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Tin	O
Plates	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
send	O
the	O
Prentice	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in-order	O
to	O
discover	O
him	O
,	O
plac	O
'd	O
his	O
Journey-man	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
afore-said	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blinker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
from	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterward	O
taken	O
upon	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Person	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curdley	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hamstead	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbert	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Bell-mettle	O
Porrage-Pot	O
,	O
some	O
Ducks	O
,	O
a	O
Goose	O
and	O
Gander	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbert	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Houses	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Man	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
immediate	O
Pursuit	O
after	O
the	O
Thieves	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
their	O
Pursuit	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
under	O
an	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Westmorland	I-pers
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Kettleby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
by	O
discharging	O
a	O
Gun	O
with	O
small	O
Shot	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
a	O
Prison	O
for	O
Debt	O
on	O
Tower-hill	B-place
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Prison	O
for	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
broke	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Cock	O
loft	O
(	O
a	O
Place	O
contiguous	O
with	O
the	O
Cock-loft	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prison	O
)	O
It	O
likewise	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
formerly	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
those	O
French	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Defence	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Gun	O
laden	O
with	O
small	O
Shot	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Garret	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Sceiling	O
over	O
the	O
Garret	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
bend	O
by	O
the	O
trampling	O
of	O
Feet	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
further	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Loft	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
designing	O
to	O
fright	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Mussle	O
of	O
his	O
Gun	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
of	O
the	O
Sceiling	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
discharge	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Tiles	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
tripp	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Guyces	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Hole	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
discharg	O
'd	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Chance	O
Medley	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Peticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Serge	O
Peticoat	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellows	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Peticoats	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
ample	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Albert	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
7	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Buttons	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
5	O
l.	O
140	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
14	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jonas	B-pers
Albert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Byworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
Date	O
afore-said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Straps	O
of	O
his	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
and	O
150	O
Pound-weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
3	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fownes	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
gone	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
self	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Ann	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
T	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sheets	O
hung	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Line	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
off	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Satchell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Day	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
giving	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
alias	O
Newman	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Harris	O
and	O
Blackwell	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Feather	O
Muffs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gause	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brecknot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
Hannah	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Harris	O
and	O
Blackwell	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Muffs	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
Harris	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Blackwell	O
escap	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Britton	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
as	O
appear	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
by	O
both	O
their	O
Confessions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Giles	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bengall	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
lac	O
'd	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
privately	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
her	O
self	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Tubman	I-pers
alias	O
Green	B-pers
alias	O
Lightfoot	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Apron	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
alias	O
More	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
alias	O
Allison	B-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Chisel	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
his	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Buckle	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
drop't	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blew	O
and	O
White	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Morchen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Grate	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	O
King	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
granted	O
to	O
some	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
others	O
upon	O
certain	O
Conditions	O
,	O
as	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Samson	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Goldring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hodskins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tedbury	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Boult	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Baines	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dammery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
Florence	B-pers
Donaghue	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debuke	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Battersby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Curdley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
22.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Miles	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Sefril	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Seton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fishpond	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maunders	I-pers
.	O
Petty	O
Larcenies	O
,	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mocket	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Franso	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Blackwell	O
,	O
Han	O
.	O
Britton	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
1	O
Mark	O
.	O
P	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
,	O
fined	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
granted	O
to	O
some	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
others	O
upon	O
certain	O
Conditions	O
,	O
as	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Samson	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Goldring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hodskins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tedbury	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Boult	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Baines	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dammery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
Florence	B-pers
Donaghue	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debuke	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
John	B-pers
Bragnell	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
King	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wopping	O
,	O
Stepney	O
,	O
being	O
affected	O
with	O
a	O
Cancer	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
eat	O
away	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
my	O
Life	O
was	O
dispair	O
'd	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Cures	O
daily	O
perform	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
deplorable	O
Diseases	O
,	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Vanderplase	O
,	O
in	O
Upper	O
Shadwel	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
I	O
address	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
has	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Perfect	O
and	O
Sound	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
this	O
Certificate	O
may	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
others	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bragnell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Dr.	O
may	O
be	O
advis	O
'd	O
with	O
every	O
Day	O
at	O
Yates	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Pav'd-Ally	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall	O
Market	O
,	O
at	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Heaven	O
upon	O
Earth	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
best	O
Friend	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
worst	O
Times	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Legacy	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
James	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Marrow	O
of	O
the	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
made	O
Plain	O
and	O
Easie	O
to	O
the	O
Understanding	O
of	O
any	O
ordinary	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
Geometry	O
,	O
Astronomy	O
,	O
Gauging	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Sector	O
,	O
Surveying	O
,	O
Dyaling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Navigation	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
several	O
Cuts	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
Explanation	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
New	O
,	O
Compendious	O
,	O
Easy	O
Method	O
By	O
W.	O
Pickering	O
,	O
Merchant-Adventurer	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Measuring	O
Surfaces	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Plank	O
,	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Joiners	O
,	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
Glasiers	O
,	O
Painters	O
and	O
Paviers	O
Work	O
:	O
Each	O
Proposition	O
being	O
wrought	O
Vulgarly	O
,	O
Decimally	O
,	O
Practically	O
and	O
Instrumentally	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
small	O
Tract	O
of	O
Gauging	O
Wine	O
,	O
Ale	O
,	O
or	O
Malt	O
,	O
without	O
Inches	O
,	O
or	O
Division	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
Gauge	O
ten	O
Backs	O
or	O
Floors	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
another	O
shall	O
Guage	O
one	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
now	O
used	O
.	O
Altogether	O
New	O
,	O
and	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
Censure	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Excise	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
L.	O
P.	O
M.	O
Both	O
Printed	O
for	O
Eben	O
.	O
Tracy	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Bibles	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
1710	O
.	O
+++	O
A	O
Letter	O
from	O
South	O
Carolina	O
;	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Soil	O
,	O
Air	O
,	O
Product	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Government	O
,	O
Laws	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
People	O
,	O
Military	O
Strength	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
that	O
Province	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
necessary	O
Charges	O
of	O
Settling	O
a	O
Plantation	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Annual	O
Profit	O
it	O
will	O
produce	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
a	O
Swiss	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
at	O
Bern	O
.	O
+++	O
The	O
Managers	O
Pro	O
and	O
Con	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
said	O
at	O
Child	O
's	O
and	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee-Houses	O
,	O
for	O
and	O
against	O
Dr.	O
Sacheverell	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Both	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
1710	O
.	O
POlitics	O
in	O
Select	O
Discourses	O
of	O
Monsieur	O
Balzae	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Aristippus	O
or	O
Wise	O
Scholar	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
by	O
Basil	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
Fellow	O
of	O
C.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
Translation	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Writings	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
SAcramental	O
Exercises	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Christians	O
Employment	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Hearing	O
:	O
Being	O
a	O
Farewel	O
Sermon	O
;	O
preach	O
'd	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
September	O
29	O
,	O
1706	O
.	O
By	O
Jabez	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
DR.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
also	O
his	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Family	O
Prayer	O
,	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
relating	O
to	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
Printed	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Printing-House	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vol	O
.	O
Wingate	O
's	O
and	O
Washington	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
rul	O
'd	O
and	O
unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
and	O
without	O
;	O
also	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Books	O
and	O
Cuts	O
are	O
sold	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitledge	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Avey-Mary-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
,	O
Printor	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
