TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1711/12	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEACHCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Lovell	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
William	B-pers
Langmore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Woodrof	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
George	B-pers
Trim	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Noden	I-pers
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wyburn	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Penkman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Eddy	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Catmore	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Calwich	I-pers
Nevil	B-pers
Meal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Jane	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holloway	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pope	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
cheapen	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
shew	O
'd	O
several	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
bought	O
one	O
Pair	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
Sawyer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
some	O
Offers	O
at	O
a	O
Defence	O
and	O
Sawyer	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
Ribbon-weaving	O
;	O
Boreman	O
also	O
produc	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
Sawyer	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Boreman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Dowgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Davis	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
in	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Bunting	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Dyer	O
,	O
he	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Cole	O
sold	O
several	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Lodger	O
of	O
Clay	O
's	O
sold	O
two	O
Pieces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
burnt	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Dyer	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Piece	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Dyer	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
22	O
s.	O
Davis	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
late	O
from	O
t'other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
so	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
)	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
met	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
between	O
'em	O
both	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
jostled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Anne	B-pers
Noel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
4	O
Ells	O
and	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Little	B-place
Britain	I-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
ty	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
wounded	O
one	O
Person	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ivery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goodswere	O
stoln	O
by	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
Instant	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
another	O
Woman	O
dropt	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
'em	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencoe	O
,	O
concerning	O
an	O
Escape-Warrant	O
,	O
against	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
set	O
aside	O
the	O
said	O
Warrant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
,	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
and	O
bought	O
divers	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Sheep	O
of	O
one	O
Welsh	O
of	O
Wormlayton	O
,	O
at	O
Daintry	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
(	O
particularly	O
September	O
14	O
.	O
1709	O
.	O
)	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
countenance	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Welsh	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
entitle	O
Welsh	O
that	O
was	O
last	O
try	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Executor	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
Daintry	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
villanous	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Word	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
O	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
a	O
Sweetner	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
cheating	O
James	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
of	O
20	O
Guineas	O
at	O
a	O
Game	O
on	O
the	O
Cards	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Preaching	O
the	O
Parson	O
.	O
Hathaway	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Country-man	O
's	O
Habit	O
,	O
who	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
left	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
O	O
-	O
perswading	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
felt	O
to	O
the	O
Game	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
drew	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
won	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
borrow	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
cheated	O
him	O
likewise	O
.	O
One	O
Welsh	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
of	O
O	O
-	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
since	O
become	O
a	O
Discoverer	O
of	O
such	O
Practices	O
,	O
swore	O
the	O
Matter	O
also	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
several	O
Counties	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
76	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Crape	O
,	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Saunders	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pool	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
5	O
Cups	O
20	O
l.	O
6	O
Casters	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Value	O
;	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gawen	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Denton	O
being	O
at	O
Islington	O
for	O
his	O
Health	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
shut	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
inner	O
Doors	O
,	O
with	O
Chests	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
Trunks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
afterwards	O
,	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Difficulty	O
found	O
out	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Lodging	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Denton	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
Fulham	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
melted	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
a	O
Trunk	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch-Case	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
afterwards	O
coming	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
dropt	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
exceeding	O
full	O
and	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Gawen	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
Instant	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Tenters	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
amongst	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Butterwick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-Lane	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Chamber	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
round	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
into	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
at	O
Dorchester	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Country	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stoke	O
'em	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
but	O
a	O
Lad	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
aLodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Britain	O
in	O
Cole-yard	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
so	O
suddenly	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Debt	O
:	O
but	O
had	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Keech	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coats	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Cloth-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
deceased	O
Husband	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Living	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
sell	O
'em	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
find	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
her	O
an	O
honest	O
poor	O
Woman	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Farendon	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
42	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Farendon	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
first	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
who	O
was	O
engag	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Law-Suit	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
Several	O
times	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
honest	O
as	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
Farendon	O
convey	O
'd	O
into	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
again	O
.	O
Farendon	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
Johnson	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
Money	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Farendon	O
gave	O
'em	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
found	O
'em	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
8	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
Information	O
that	O
two	O
Boys	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
a	O
Bundle	O
into	O
Soams	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Evidence	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
Soams	O
's	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
Soams	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
two	O
Boys	O
brought	O
'em	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
would	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
away	O
with	O
'em	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
without	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
after	O
seiz	O
'd	O
as	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Brown	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
part	O
hid	O
in	O
two	O
Beds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
One	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Coney	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Brown	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
said	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
without	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
:	O
some	O
Persons	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Coney	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Prestridge	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Lambs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Gander	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gibb	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
their	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon'em	O
in	O
a	O
Wallet	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
dead	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
'em	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
Beladine	O
Silk	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
2	O
Brass	O
Mortars	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pestle	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Boys	O
bring	O
them	O
into	O
Salmon	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boys	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Hoods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
8	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
swears	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
latch	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
Blake	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shifts	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
'em	O
of	O
an	O
Earthen-ware	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Cecil	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
foregoing	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linen	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Blake	O
had	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
hang	O
some	O
Clothes	O
drying	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Girl	O
gave	O
leave	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
serv	O
'd	O
a	O
Warrant	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediatelyconfess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
restor	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Tayler	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
drank	O
pretty	O
plentifully	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
enter	O
some	O
South-Sea	O
Bills	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
(	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Defence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Scrimshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yarwood	I-pers
and	O
Rodry	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
(	O
two	O
Boys	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
5	O
Casters	O
,	O
6	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mahon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Parlor-door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
which	O
way	O
.	O
But	O
afterwards	O
by	O
accident	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
Boys	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
Hockly	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
where	O
by	O
some	O
Passages	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
Yarwood	O
said	O
that	O
Awdry	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Aunt	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Awdry	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Perkins	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
Leave	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
to	O
strengthen	O
such	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Eland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Febuary	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
blown	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
Scales	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mills	O
and	O
Jones	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
Fisher	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Salmon	O
bought	O
'em	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fisher	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jones	O
,	O
Mills	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
Sen.	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
Jun	O
:	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Money	O
and	O
Gold	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
Zacheus	B-pers
Wisdom	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Wisdom	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stoln	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Mat	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Pendergrass	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
Gill	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
was	O
young	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
1.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
23.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Windam	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Farendon	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Yarwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Rodry	O
Awdry	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holloway	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prestridge	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Nobles	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Field-Lane	O
End	O
,	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapside	O
Conduit	O
.	O
O	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
removed	O
to	O
Exeter	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
be	O
kept	O
at	O
hard	O
Labour	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMEMENTS	O
.	O
Multitudes	O
of	O
Children	O
reduced	O
to	O
extream	O
Sufferings	O
and	O
Danger	O
by	O
the	O
violent	O
Breeding	O
and	O
Cutting	O
of	O
their	O
Teeth	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
happily	O
restored	O
to	O
perfect	O
Ease	O
and	O
Safety	O
,	O
by	O
only	O
using	O
to	O
their	O
Gums	O
a	O
Medicine	O
prepared	O
for	O
those	O
Cases	O
.	O
The	O
constant	O
and	O
admirable	O
Success	O
thereof	O
evidently	O
appears	O
by	O
Certificates	O
from	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
Worth	O
and	O
Credit	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Print	O
gratis	O
where	O
this	O
Remedy	O
is	O
sold	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Vial	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Perronet	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Allcraft	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-coat-boy	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	B-pers
Perfumer	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Beanford	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Tobacconist	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Any	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
willing	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
most	O
useful	O
Medicine	O
,	O
may	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
Paintings	O
,	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlesness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick-fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
,	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
)	O
for	O
JOHN	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Boldwin	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
