TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencow	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Yateman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hillyard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Grosvenour	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pomroy	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Malling	I-pers
Matthias	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ingram	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kinch	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dionys	I-place
Back-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradbourn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Stockings	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
a	O
Woman	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Stockings	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
which	O
Stockings	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
on	O
the	O
River	B-place
of	I-place
Thames	I-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Possession	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Bottomly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
bundl	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thrust	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Newgate	B-place
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Crowd	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Bell-man	O
's	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
the	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
small	O
Stand	O
,	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cast	O
his	O
Eye	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grinley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
Broadstreet	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
being	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Cree	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Lawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Muslin	O
being	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
it	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Glass	O
take	O
the	O
Muslin	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
whereupon	O
be	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
excus	O
'd	O
her	O
Comrade	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
but	O
Glass	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
:	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assualting	O
Andrew	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
North	O
Britain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
these	O
Parts	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
Talk	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
there	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Note	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
which	O
pretended	O
Note	O
having	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Brandy	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
found	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
play	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
expressing	O
an	O
Aversion	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
lose	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
one	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Gold	O
,	O
while	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
drawing	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
shortning	O
it	O
,	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
Noise	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Under	O
this	O
Terror	O
they	O
kept	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
Stories	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
conducted	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
known	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
did	O
know	O
the	O
Prissoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
after	O
much	O
search	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Name	O
to	O
be	O
Whittle	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pretended	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Whittle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
at	O
play	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
crediting	O
that	O
Story	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
under	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Huddlestone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
with	O
a	O
quick	O
motion	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Edenburgh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Distiller	B-place
's	I-place
Shop	I-place
in	O
Forestreet	B-place
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Liqours	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
)	O
snatch	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
swore	O
Da	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
't	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
but	O
an	O
impudent	O
Denial	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bracey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
match	O
a	O
Pattern	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
about	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Drugget	O
from	O
a	O
heap	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Things	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wareman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Books	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compting-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seabroke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hepburn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rye	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oven	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
above	O
100	O
Persons	O
more	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
appear	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
riotous	O
and	O
tumultuous	O
manner	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Terror	O
and	O
Afright	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
assault	O
and	O
evil	O
intreat	O
Joshua	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gansborne	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Attorney-General	O
first	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
general	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Riot	O
:	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Words	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Rioters	O
,	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
his	O
Assistance	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Constables	O
between	O
Bow-Church	O
and	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Mob	O
,	O
their	O
common	O
Cry	O
was	O
,	O
no	O
Hanoverian	O
,	O
no	O
Presbyterian	O
;	O
High-Church	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
;	O
High-Church	O
and	O
Sacheveral	O
;	O
a	O
Second	O
Restoration	O
;	O
no	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
but	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Race	O
of	O
the	O
Stenarts	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Words	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Riot	O
in	O
general	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
against	O
each	O
particular	O
Criminal	O
;	O
and	O
first	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rye	I-pers
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
within	O
2	O
Doors	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stop	O
several	O
People	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
Hat	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Quaker	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Jardin	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Against	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
down	O
Foster-lane	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
bits	O
at	O
the	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
:	O
A	O
Watchman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Watchmen	O
being	O
down	O
,	O
Harvey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
held	O
him	O
so	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rise	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
die	O
before	O
he	O
'd	O
yield	O
.	O
Another	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
hollowing	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
words	O
.	O
Against	O
Stringer	O
it	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
Compter	I-place
brandishing	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
,	O
no	O
Hanoverian	O
,	O
no	O
Presbyterian	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
amongst	O
the	O
Rioters	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
utter	O
any	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fought	O
very	O
resolutely	O
against	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Watch	O
.	O
Against	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oven	I-pers
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sought	O
the	O
Constables	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
rescue	O
Harvey	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
was	O
accus	O
'd	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Game	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
amongst	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
opposing	O
the	O
Constables	O
.	O
Against	O
Richard	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
Assistance	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
he	O
accus	O
'd	O
Cannon	O
as	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
attempted	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
required	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
resisted	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
by	O
their	O
Counsel	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Defence	O
.	O
For	O
Mr.	O
Rye	O
it	O
was	O
pleaded	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
about	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
till	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
Drink	O
:	O
That	O
from	O
thence	O
coming	O
towards	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Aldersgatestreet	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
along	O
the	O
pav	O
'd	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
mix	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Crowd	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
t'other	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
turn	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
Hat	O
half	O
round	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
steps	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
's	O
Man	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
For	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
Apprentices	O
had	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
in	O
Carew-lane	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
near	O
Three	O
Quarters	O
past	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Candles	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
were	O
returning	O
down	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
Harvey	O
saying	O
something	O
they	O
immediately	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
soundly	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
Person	O
given	O
to	O
Mobbing	O
,	O
or	O
Rioting	O
upon	O
any	O
Account	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Oven	O
's	O
Uncle	O
depos	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
till	O
Harvey	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
by	O
as	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
(	O
Harvey	O
's	O
Master	O
)	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
made	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
too	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Attorney-General	O
having	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
she	O
pursus'dand	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Valentine	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Marsh	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
rub	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Charles	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
125	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corwall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Bennet	I-place
Paul's-Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Constantine	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Sea	O
she	O
run	O
him	O
extravagantly	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Law	O
commenc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
swore	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
contracted	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
consent	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Verdict	O
was	O
obtain	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
annul	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
Process	O
was	O
now	O
depending	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
perjur	O
'd	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
as	O
such	O
whenever	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Steps	O
at	O
Doctor	B-place
Commons	I-place
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
some	O
Words	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drew	O
;	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
drew	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
retired	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dropt	O
his	O
Point	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
spare	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushing	O
on	O
,	O
stuck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
in	O
substance	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
taken	O
the	O
greatest	O
care	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
the	O
Expression	O
of	O
treating	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
perjur	O
'd	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
reference	O
but	O
to	O
prosecuting	O
him	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
by	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
Perjury	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
hard	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
sin	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
than	O
to	O
kill	O
a	O
Dog	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
to	O
try	O
out	O
the	O
Law-Suit	O
by	O
the	O
Sword	O
.	O
A	O
Barber	O
also	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Villain	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
where-ever	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
stab	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
a	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Sword	O
was	O
down	O
but	O
an	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
before	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
laugh	O
in	O
derision	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
with	O
Contempt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
struck	O
first	O
.	O
A	O
Third	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
how	O
by	O
the	O
position	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
the	O
Wound	O
might	O
be	O
receiv	O
'd	O
in	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
and	O
Honour	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
suming	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Marston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
moving	O
Wardrobe	O
at	O
Whitehall	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Ball-Room	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Crimson	O
Velvet	O
Carpet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
4	O
Velvet	O
Cases	O
for	O
Stools	O
,	O
and	O
44	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sometimes	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Wardrobe	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Chair	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
25th	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Public	B-place
House	I-place
near	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Degree	O
,	O
that	O
Blows	O
past	O
between	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
at	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
slipping	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
unfortunately	O
got	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
violent	O
Tongue	O
had	O
provok	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Stockins	O
,	O
sound	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
thrust	O
under	O
her	O
Stays	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Waldron	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
permitted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
'em	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fitz	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barnet	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Conyers	B-pers
Darcey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Riccard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
believing	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Thief	O
in	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Alley	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
3	O
several	O
Indictments	O
for	O
buying	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Heywood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Noel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Mr.	B-pers
Heywood	I-pers
;	O
and	O
was	O
also	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deran	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kipling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Morter	O
,	O
5	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tandy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
bearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
below	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
carry	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Scamwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hanwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Damport	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Shop	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
a	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
up	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Stockins	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
remov	O
'd	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Blount	O
creep	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Witness	O
;	O
but	O
against	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
running	O
within	O
some	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Blount	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bonnely	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Elsey	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
deflowring	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
against	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
filling	O
his	O
Quillis	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
finding	O
something	O
unusual	O
in	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
took	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
search	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
wrong	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
understanding	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
as	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
German	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Chiswick	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
Abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gillison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
No	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Chippendale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Bell-metal	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
a	O
Nurse-keeping	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
absence	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
deny	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Hatton	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
something	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
accordingly	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Hatton	O
,	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
trifling	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Ja	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tho	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.Hall	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
but	O
that	O
Night	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bundl	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
dropping	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
5d	O
.	O
in	O
Farthings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
two	O
Men	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Church-Lane	B-place
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
three	B-place
Travellers	I-place
,	O
where	O
Turner	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
strip	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Resistance	O
.	O
Turner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
being	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
them	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
complaining	O
of	O
any	O
lots	O
.	O
Nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Wells	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
,	O
same	O
Murder	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Gaming-Table	O
at	O
the	B-place
Phoenix	I-place
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Davies	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
whereupon	O
some	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
particular	O
saying	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
but	O
just	O
that	O
every	O
Gentleman	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
resenting	O
his	O
meddling	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
first	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
or	O
Stick	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
making	O
a	O
Push	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Eye	O
;	O
immediately	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
dismal	O
Convulsions	O
till	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
sled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
till	O
lately	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
rough	O
,	O
and	O
pressing	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
Cane	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
push	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Lorg	I-pers
,	O
Bar	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
9	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
9	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
83	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
Hooker	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
walking	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
urg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
promise	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
should	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
did	O
promise	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Wosdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Stice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
leaden	O
Weights	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Chaloner	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fore	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
whereupon	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Hodgson	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Hollington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delfoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scuff	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Hollington	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Canister	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
looking	O
a	O
little	O
odly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Worth	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Saffamour	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Stample	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Paddington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
to	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Cyprian	B-pers
Dutier	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Dubois	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
had	O
sought	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
who	O
seem'dto	O
be	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
understood	O
to	O
be	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Rynalsden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Albert	B-pers
Coleton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
,	O
bruising	O
,	O
and	O
kicking	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
'	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
very	O
imperfect	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
prov	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Anger	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
jestingly	O
pushing	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
his	O
Elbow	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
his	O
Death	O
came	O
by	O
any	O
Bruise	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Forbs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Habading	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Fowls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Persons	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
an	O
ill	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
had	O
been	O
pick	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
got	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
rifl	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Smith	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
through	O
Hide-Park	B-place
with	O
the	O
Whig	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Review	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
were	O
hovering	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
Box	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Whig	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
accus	O
'd	O
another	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Whig	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Girl	O
is	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
That	O
upon	O
her	O
complaining	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Gleet	O
;	O
one	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Gonorrhea	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
starching	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
press	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
modest	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
declare	O
what	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
had	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
said	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
enter	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Penetration	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gleet	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
a	O
Strain	O
,	O
or	O
Weakness	O
,	O
or	O
ill	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wharry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
Was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ems	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drown	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Boat	O
being	O
adrift	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
fasten	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Ship-side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
Liter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
preparing	O
to	O
row	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
,	O
struck	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Stretcher	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
hereupon	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
stepping	O
towards	O
the	O
Liter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
instant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shov	O
'd	O
away	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
in	O
and	O
was	O
drown	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
some	O
Persons	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
altogether	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
shov	O
'd	O
his	O
Boat	O
away	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Face	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
Design	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
21	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
base	O
and	O
vexatious	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Savoy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drown	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
witness	O
was	O
one	O
Dyer	O
,	O
a	O
Waterman	O
'	O
,	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Landing-place	O
at	O
Somerset-house	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
Cushions	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
ashore	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Boy	O
cry	O
,	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
J	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
throw	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swim	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
flounce	O
in	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Dog	O
swims	O
bravely	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murfet	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
drown	O
her	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
held	O
fast	O
by	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
A	O
Coachman	O
and	O
Groom	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marquis	O
de	O
Merimont	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
idle	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Dunghil	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
the	O
Girl	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
talk	O
'd	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Boy	O
drown	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
drown	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
swore	O
they	O
heard	O
some-body	O
say	O
.	O
Push	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
flounce	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
is	O
Porter	O
of	O
Somerset-house	O
Water-gate	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
such	O
't	O
is	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
strolling	O
,	O
idle	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
frequently	O
come	O
there	O
a-Nights	O
,	O
and	O
hide	O
themselves	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
went	O
upon	O
search	O
for	O
such	O
People	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
strike	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
24	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Gregory	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulcher	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Jun	O
e	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Brush	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
said	O
Baker	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
committed	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Brush	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Order	O
)	O
he	O
lay	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
Ague	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
as	O
usual	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
ill	O
;	O
which	O
his	O
Master	O
hearing	O
of	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Doctor	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
blooded	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
laying	O
his	O
Death	O
to	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
brought	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Pleuresie	O
;	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
finding	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Symptom	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
was	O
much	O
emaciated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Remains	O
contracted	O
to	O
the	O
Pleura	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
against	O
him	O
had	O
been	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
and	O
Malice	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
had	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
an	O
indictment	O
was	O
preferr	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
who	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
Ignoramus	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
this	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
proceeded	O
to	O
call	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maliciousness	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
judg	O
'd	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
produc	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
sufficiently	O
clear	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Marston	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
16.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Bottomly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grinley	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Edenburgh	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pooly	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bares	I-pers
,	O
A	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Thrust	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
German	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Chippendale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Wosdale	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
James	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
not	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Sentence	O
against	O
the	O
Rioters	O
is	O
respited	O
till	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
instant	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Day	O
the	O
Session	O
is	O
adjourn	O
'd	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
(	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
)	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
;	O
dwelling	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Tin-shop	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
Abroad	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
THE	O
same	O
Gentlewoman	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
Wash	O
to	O
beautify	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
far	O
excels	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
quality	O
have	O
found	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-burn	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
and	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Young	O
it	O
keeps	O
always	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
:	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
from	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
five	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
Pomatums	O
,	O
White-Pots	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Snow	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
where-ever	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
;	O
she	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
Light	O
or	O
Dark	O
Brown	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
shapes	O
the	O
Eye	O
brows	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
Beautiful	O
;	O
she	O
hath	O
a	O
delicate	O
Paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red	O
Pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	O
CROUCH	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head	O
Ally	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
)	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchange	O
.	O
