TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
William	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Overall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Nithol	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Boddell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Adlamb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pannett	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
David	B-pers
Fisield	I-pers
William	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
John	B-pers
Charlwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Alice	B-pers
Cabarel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
went	O
under	O
presence	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
several	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
like	O
any	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
,	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop	O
lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grimsted	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Shoes	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
till	O
lately	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
some	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sold	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
discover	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
(	O
being	O
also	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
Shoes	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
reputable	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jenkinson	O
having	O
bought	O
the	O
Tea	O
to	O
send	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
some	O
Goods	O
in	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
Tea	O
upon	O
an	O
empty	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Lads	O
more	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
pursuit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Musquets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Sanders	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
seduc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Guns	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bad	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
induc	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Chrisolite	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
House	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
House	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
like	O
a	O
Country	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Diamond	O
cut	O
Ring	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Rings	O
being	O
set	O
before	O
him	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
several	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
conceal	O
two	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
doing	O
accordingly	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Rings	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Duke	I-place
's	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
which	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
conceal	O
'd	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beldam	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
40	O
Pound-weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
Swore	O
his	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Street-door	O
open	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
afterwards	O
to	O
search	O
a	O
suspected	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
,	O
94	O
Guineas	O
,	O
11	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
9	O
French	O
Guineas	O
,	O
9	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dog-Tavern	B-place
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lister	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
intimate	O
Friend	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
next	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
;	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
Minutes	O
time	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
,	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
a	O
Constable	O
might	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
and	O
Parker	O
;	O
Parker	O
offer	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
threw	O
the	O
Pocket-Book	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Pocket	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
)	O
saying	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Parker	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lister	O
drank	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Rummer	O
of	O
a	O
Quart	O
and	O
Half	O
pint	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
Health	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
writ	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
handed	O
round	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
help	O
'd	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Condition	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Company	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
believing	O
him	O
a	O
Person	O
uncapable	O
of	O
carrying	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
after	O
the	O
Health	O
was	O
writ	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
off	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
upon	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
for	O
rasing	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
altering	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
upon	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
was	O
drawn	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Odam	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
90	O
l.	O
was	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
endors	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
in	O
such	O
manner	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Bill	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Indorsement	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
85l	O
.	O
paid	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
endors	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
finding	O
some	O
Bills	O
overpay	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Loss	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
Collins	O
made	O
the	O
following	O
Discovery	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
swore	O
to	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
)	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
too	O
scrupulous	O
a	O
Conscience	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
vast	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
seeming	O
to	O
hearken	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
by	O
applying	O
a	O
certain	O
Liquor	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Ink	O
,	O
the	O
Letters	O
disappear	O
'd	O
.	O
Collins	O
having	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
got	O
sufficiently	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Governour	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
very	O
Bill	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
an	O
Account	O
in	O
Writing	O
of	O
several	O
Bills	O
,	O
their	O
Numbers	O
,	O
and	O
Sums	O
receiv	O
'd	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
Mors	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
10000	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
engage	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
make	O
the	O
Experiment	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
third	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Profit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
allow	O
'd	O
Council	O
,	O
they	O
argu	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Odam	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Servant	O
qualify	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
such	O
Bills	O
,	O
unless	O
authoriz	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Corporation-Seal	O
;	O
That	O
writing	O
with	O
Red	O
Ink	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
;	O
Nor	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
were	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
,	O
can	O
the	O
Fact	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
rasing	O
or	O
altering	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
reply	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Odam	O
is	O
a	O
Servant	O
qualify	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
such	O
Bills	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Articles	O
are	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Dennings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
Sale	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Metal	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Pewter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
the	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
accus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
sending	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
Stuart	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Clawson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Dukes-place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Girdles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Beacham	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Box	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Girdles	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bournois	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prejudice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Title	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Katherine	O
Creed-church	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	B-place
,	O
go	O
hollowing	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
shaking	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
is	O
right	O
and	O
lawful	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
is	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Protector	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
George	O
is	O
an	O
Usurper	O
.	O
Another	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
is	O
rightful	O
and	O
Lawful	O
Heir	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
fourth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
is	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
huzzaing	O
along	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
utter	O
'd	O
the	O
Words	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
He	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
gets	O
his	O
Bread	O
by	O
teaching	O
a	O
little	O
School	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
personating	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Huchinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
cheating	O
Mary	B-pers
Carnedy	I-pers
of	O
several	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Lyddel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Richard	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Passingham	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
6	O
Gross	O
of	O
Ferret	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Passingham	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
,	O
your	O
Master	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
on	O
;	O
come	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
him	O
about	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
,	O
but	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
amus	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
from	O
Chamber	O
to	O
Chamber	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Slip	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Baker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Assault	O
or	O
Robbery	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Dalton	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Mistres	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
bring	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Satinet	O
Hand-Kerchiefs	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
putting	O
them	O
up	O
accordingly	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Nurse	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
now	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shag-Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fryer	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
and	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Debarah	B-pers
Godman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
giving	O
any	O
Notice	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
gutted	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
after	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Askey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kellaway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sagathy	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Skains	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
4.s	O
.	O
6.d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
Goods	O
having	O
been	O
lost	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
hanging	O
out	O
to	O
whiten	O
,	O
the	O
Ground	O
was	O
narrowly	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
)	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Yarn	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
ty	O
'd	O
round	O
her	O
Middle	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
wrought	O
several	O
Years	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
him	O
any	O
harm	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Accusers	O
are	O
worse	O
than	O
she	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Argent	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
Marriages	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
buys	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
these	O
in	O
Barbican	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tyrwhit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Cloth-Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Stable	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
hanging	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
-	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
11	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
also	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Causeway	B-place
to	O
Holloway	B-place
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
t'other	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
coming	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
flash	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
swore	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
bold	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
assaulted	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
is	O
dead	O
of	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mich.	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Spearman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Winnifred	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Puzey	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
stoln	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Cornwall	O
(	O
executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
commited	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Gibbons	O
swore	O
falsly	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
times	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Lambs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Lambs	O
were	O
stoln	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Gibson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Winnifred	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fishpond	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vivier	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
7	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Giles	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
32	O
Hats	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
2	O
Child	O
's	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Wagon	O
going	O
into	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	B-place
Mile	I-place
beyond	I-place
St.	I-place
Alban	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Driver	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
rifl	O
'd	O
the	O
Wagon	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Wagon	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Letter	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
)	O
acquainting	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
one	O
Dibdin	O
's	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
;	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
seiz	O
'd	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
when	O
after	O
much	O
Struggling	O
he	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Woman	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
through	O
Spight	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rowlands	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Okes	B-pers
Pickford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sometimes	O
drank	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
being	O
then	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
.	O
Being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Sunbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
18	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Dishes	O
,	O
4	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Household	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Buttery-Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
found	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
flat	O
Denial	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
Sunbury	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Walker	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Chance	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hillingdon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barradale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
a	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Line	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
carried	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
within	O
a	O
Field	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
packing	O
up	O
Linnen	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Line	O
into	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
him	O
ride	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Linnen	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Barradale	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Line	O
was	O
also	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Calboune	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Calvin	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Calson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
Proof	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Brightman	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Marriot	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Three	O
as	O
Aiders	O
and	O
Abetters	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
betwixt	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
4	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
London	B-place
Spaw	I-place
,	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
refusing	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
those	O
without	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
they	O
were	O
breaking	O
in	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Servants	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
getting	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
and	O
Servants	O
going	O
after	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
)	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Gentlemen	O
making	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
retreated	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
Williams	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
3	O
Wounds	O
is	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
through	O
his	O
Small	O
Gut	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
he	O
saw	O
four	O
Gentlemen	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Saw	O
,	O
and	O
chopp	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
upon	O
the	O
Pales	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
50	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
out	O
came	O
3	O
Men	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
who	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
keep	O
off	O
at	O
their	O
Peril	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Wound	O
given	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
be	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
no	O
more	O
could	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Reason	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
accus	O
'd	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Buckland	O
happening	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Saintloe	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Islingtons	O
they	O
had	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
not	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saintloe	O
hearing	O
afterwards	O
of	O
this	O
Accident	O
at	O
the	O
Spaw	O
,	O
related	O
what	O
Buckland	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
found	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hatton	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Humfreys	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
the	O
Fellow	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
do	O
well	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
consider	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
Smart-Money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
became	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Distinction	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Callicoe	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
removed	O
the	O
Shutters	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchin-Window	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
this	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
Off-wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Coal-Cart	O
over	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
going	O
very	O
soberly	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
fell	O
down	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
stop	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Wine	O
Flasks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Morden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bodt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Spicer	B-pers
Minshul	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
try	O
'd	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
presently	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockale	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cockale	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
17	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cellar-Plank	O
was	O
broke	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
Collins	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
becoming	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
four	O
Men-Prisoners	O
broke	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
Stole	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Collin	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Men	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Collins	O
Accessary	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
8	O
Stone	O
of	O
Beef	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
Cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Beef	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Powdring-Tub	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
swore	O
the	O
Men-Prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Beef	O
to	O
Collin	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Cockale	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stabler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
7	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Henry	O
Cockale	O
,	O
Richard	O
Clare	O
,	O
Robert	O
Andrews	O
,	O
John	O
Wilkinson	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Margaret	O
Collins	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Featherbeds	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Lane-Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
taken	O
and	O
furnish	O
'd	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
she	O
gutted	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
alledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
have	O
his	O
Note	O
with	O
Vaughan	O
for	O
payment	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Station	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Banister	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
proving	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
Books	O
as	O
the	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rice	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Edwards	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
Aiders	O
and	O
Abetters	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	O
G	O
scow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lodging	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Words	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
Edwards	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
but	O
Newland	O
prevented	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
join	O
'd	O
Company	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fresh	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
Edwards	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Tothill	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
where	O
soon	O
after	O
a	O
Witness	O
heard	O
clothing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Edwards	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
or	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
hop	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
be	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
I	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
run	O
him	O
twice	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Words	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drew	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
weighing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
against	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Harmans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
trifling	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Warden	B-pers
Elford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruk	O
,	O
value	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cresset	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
which	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
kept	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
fraudulently	O
concealing	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Estate	O
from	O
the	O
Assignees	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Commission	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
issu	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1709	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
Bankrupcy	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
such	O
Concealment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrow-hog	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
driving	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
a	O
String	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
was	O
challeng	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Husbands	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linsey-Wolsey	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Witness	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Midnight	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
9	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charity	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hockaday	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Prime	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bulman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
him	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
knocking	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
at	O
Bowstreet	B-place
End	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lose	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
lewd	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Credit	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12.	O
Alice	B-pers
Cabarel	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
alias	O
Worral	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
alias	O
Fishpond	O
alias	O
Vivier	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockale	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
U	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Fra	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
alias	O
Fryer	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Askey	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kalloway	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Spearman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowlands	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
alias	O
Walker	O
alias	O
Chance	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Calbourne	I-pers
alias	O
Calvin	O
alias	O
Colein	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bodt	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barrister	I-pers
,	O
Warden	B-pers
Elford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Woodford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Prime	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
alias	O
Clawson	O
,	O
Rice	O
Edwards	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Sureties	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bournois	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Sentence	O
is	O
respited	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Meeting	O
of	O
this	O
Session	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
Adjournment	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Cabarel	I-pers
,	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
empannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewoman	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
(	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
)	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
cures	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
sure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gent	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
;	O
BY	O
Recourse	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
applying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Parts	O
aggrieved	O
,	O
the	O
Cause	O
is	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
immediate	O
Ease	O
given	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
ecquisite	O
Pains	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
Crutches	O
,	O
as	O
will	O
be	O
attested	O
by	O
both	O
Sexes	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
safe	O
and	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
that	O
gives	O
Ease	O
the	O
Moment	O
it	O
is	O
applied	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
It	O
likewise	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Teeth	O
from	O
Rotting	O
or	O
Decaying	O
:	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Bow-Lane	O
,	O
turning	O
down	O
by	O
Bow	O
Church	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Tin-Shop	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
Abroad	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
THE	O
same	O
Gentlewoman	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
Wash	O
to	O
beautify	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
far	O
excels	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
found	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
our	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-burn	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
and	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Young	O
it	O
keeps	O
always	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
:	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
from	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
five	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
Pomatums	O
,	O
White-Pots	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Snow	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
where-ever	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
;	O
she	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
Light	O
or	O
Dark	O
Brown	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
shapes	O
the	O
Eye-brows	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
Beautiful	O
;	O
she	O
hath	O
a	O
delicate	O
Paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red	O
Pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
8	O
Volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainment	O
Consisting	O
of	O
One	O
Thousand	O
and	O
One	O
Stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indias	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
Marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
even	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
avenge	O
himself	O
for	O
the	O
Disloyalty	O
of	O
his	O
first	O
Sultaness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Pr	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
The	O
diverting	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	O
D'Anois	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Fairys	O
,	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
A	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
instructing	O
Youth	O
in	O
reading	O
.	O
With	O
Forty	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
Lines	O
British	O
and	O
Foreign	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Great	O
Men	O
that	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Years	O
1711	O
and	O
12.	O
pr	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	O
CROUCH	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head	O
Ally	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Pater-master-row	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
)	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholworn-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchanges	O
.	O
