TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
17	O
14/15	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
20	O
January	O
.	O
171	O
4/5	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Prat	O
,	O
and	O
Duncan	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Howton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Howet	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilmott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hoffman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sherburn	I-pers
John	B-pers
Standish	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Mundy	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgore	I-pers
Rowland	B-pers
Beatknife	I-pers
John	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsman	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Livsey-Wolsey	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Kath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Acon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Goods	O
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
thereupon	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Houseman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Shaloon	O
,	O
and	O
Houseman	O
did	O
buy	O
some	O
and	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Willoughby	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Druggets	O
,	O
was	O
shew	O
'd	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
pleasing	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Colour	O
,	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Slade	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Back-Shop	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
something	O
bulky	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
Houseman	O
to	O
be	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Panner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
End	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
Shew-glass	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
any	O
one	O
be	O
positive	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eaglesfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
and	O
Half-pint	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
mixed	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Spoon	O
to	O
scum	O
the	O
Froth	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
tasted	O
his	O
and	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
small	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
another	O
Half-pint	O
of	O
strong	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
slipt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
before	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fairbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Cole-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Shop-door	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
7	O
Handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Beaver-skins	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Caswell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
imperfect	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth	B-pers
.	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
by	O
Evan	B-pers
Grono	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hockhead	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Moor	O
and	O
Vernon	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
Bundles	O
of	O
Hemp	O
upon	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Wiggins	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
under	O
a	O
Crane	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
Hockhead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
Prayers	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
next	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
devout	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
missing	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Choir	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
Creechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lb	O
Weight	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journey-man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
stoln	O
and	O
sold	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
to	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
Boddice-maker	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
bone	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
2	O
lb	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
near	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
Guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Cambricks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
instant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Writer	O
in	O
his	O
Compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
had	O
Access	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
lost	O
from	O
thence	O
Cambricks	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
90	O
l.	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
Favour	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
evaded	O
that	O
Confession	O
,	O
by	O
alledging	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
Evan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Streek	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
600	O
lb	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wardly	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Hogs-heads	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
Sugar	O
being	O
found	O
scatter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
they	O
found	O
one	O
Hogshead	O
almost	O
empty	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
Thorp	O
and	O
Streek	O
both	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
One	O
Spikeman	O
also	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
enter	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
off	O
the	O
Sugar	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Thorp	O
and	O
Streek	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
by	O
buying	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Sugar	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
but	O
Spikeman	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Dust-hole	O
,	O
who	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
several	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Matches	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	O
Mayly	O
alias	O
,	O
Mayberry	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
:	O
But	O
Thomas	O
resisting	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
accus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
)	O
Mayly	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
by	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
instant	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Quartren	O
Loaf	O
,	O
2	O
lb	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
over-night	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Hole	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
which	O
Hole	O
being	O
mended	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
Nights	O
after	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
starve	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
Want	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
carried	O
two	O
Carcasses	O
to	O
Leaden-hall	B-place
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
stoln	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Presgrove	O
's	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
alias	O
Hales	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Furnace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
until	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Furnace	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Furnace	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
20	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Mills	O
,	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
Mills	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Verdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
5	O
Guinea	O
Piece	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lost	O
his	O
Piece	O
;	O
which	O
making	O
some	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Changing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
frequently	O
there	O
,	O
several	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
pawning	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
supply	O
a	O
present	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
her	O
Circumstances	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wetberrell	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Wigg	O
comb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
off	O
a	O
Block	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
upon-pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Boyard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spence	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Catlinz	I-pers
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
an	O
Acquaitance	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
lying	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
such	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sprag	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
13	O
oz	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
;	O
Matthews	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
being	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
going	O
through	O
Half-Moon-Alley	B-place
by	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happen	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Matthews	O
knockt	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
King	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
threw	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
till	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
8	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fracture	O
in	O
his	O
Skull	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
had	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Matthews	O
's	O
Wife	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Long-ally	O
,	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
which	O
caus	O
'd	O
Matthews	O
to	O
run	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
towards	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Blows	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
:	O
whereupon	O
Matthews	O
;	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
(	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
pacify	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
all	O
that	O
while	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Ally	O
)	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
without	O
fighting	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
King	O
did	O
take	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Dunghil	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
his	O
Death	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
Security	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Officers	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	B-place
,	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
conceive	O
some	O
Way	O
for	O
his	O
Release	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
for	O
his	O
Debt	O
:	O
but	O
receiving	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
flying	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Violence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Staple	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
flew	O
off	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
the	O
Design	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Outrage	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
duly	O
weigh	O
'd	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
64	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Bear	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Hughs	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Money	O
thither	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
thicher	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Note	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
and	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
entrust	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
dogged	O
by	O
some	O
Confederate	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Success	O
.	O
That	O
carrying	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Bear	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hughs	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
by	O
Hughs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
and	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
Hughs	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
waiting	O
the	O
Success	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
his	O
Comerade	O
's	O
Mishap	O
,	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
one	O
Bill	O
of	O
52	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sent	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
they	O
who	O
sent	O
it	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Barebone	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Secretary	O
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
by	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
both	O
so	O
exactly	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
nicest	O
Eye	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
them	O
from	O
true	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Forgery	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
O-Brian	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Crony	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fowls	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
some	O
People	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her-Money-box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
blew	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
somebody	O
put	O
the	O
Box	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
tell	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
his	O
Defence	O
and	O
Youth	O
,	O
were	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
struggling	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lamas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
marrying	O
Ann	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
last	O
Marriage	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kembal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Linen	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
'em	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitehappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Hood	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
Friend	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Huckaback	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Selly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
permitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fawcet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Oatmeal	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Brooms	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Bartrup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Oatmeal	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
so	O
trifling	O
a	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
some	O
Lead	O
from	O
a	O
Freehold	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sidney	B-pers
Mountagne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susan	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barns	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
appointment	O
at	O
the	O
Hare	B-place
and	I-place
Hound	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
taking	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
some	O
Mischief	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
meet	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Barns	O
's	O
Husband	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
very	O
insufficient	O
to	O
ground	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
but	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
cause	O
for	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
leave	O
to	O
bring	O
one	O
accordingly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Charles	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hays	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Maypowder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
a	O
hole	O
was	O
broke	O
from	O
a	O
Stable	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Lome	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Good	O
's	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Tayler	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Kettlewel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
confident	O
denial	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Breeches	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Plunket	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Bed	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
R	O
-	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Bed	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
rise	O
till	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edgware	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Geese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Geese	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Dog	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Dog	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
of	O
Edgware	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Owners	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
found	O
2	O
Geese	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
verily	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plush	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stud	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
stript	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cap	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
deals	O
in	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
five	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
but	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
40	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
more	O
Words	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
all	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
E	O
-	O
's	O
to	O
melt	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
's	O
Arms	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
what	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
's	O
Plate	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
like	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
borrow	O
's	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
at	O
the	O
Coronation	O
Feast	O
in	O
Westminster	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Property	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Bottomly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Wagstaff	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
Lady	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
Coll	O
.	O
.	O
Butler	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Collonel	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
as	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Godolphin	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
at	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
next	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Supper	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
get	O
the	O
Side-board	O
in	O
Order	O
;	O
who	O
doing	O
accordingly	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
she	O
was	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Offence	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Canes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Chain	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
Steal	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shimell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Function	O
Frock	O
belonging	O
to	O
2	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
3	O
Persons	O
who	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Dust-men	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
hung	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
and	O
the	O
Frock	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Ruffel	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
hanging	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
Window	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Shop-Keeper	O
swore	O
he	O
bought	O
'em	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Market	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Door	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
Abroad	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
bundl	O
'd	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
several	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
into	O
which	O
the	O
ran	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Baliffs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Covel	I-pers
alias	O
Burgess	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coach-Seats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Coach	O
being	O
just	O
set	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
each	O
a	O
Seat	O
under	O
their	O
Arms	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
took	O
two	O
Persons	O
as	O
described	O
with	O
the	O
Seats	O
,	O
who	O
letting	O
them	O
fall	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Persons	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
was	O
Hope	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
Covel	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Hope	O
positively	O
sworn	O
to	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Venner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
between	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Plaintiffs	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bastard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Defendants	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
in	O
Trinity-Term	O
,	O
anno	O
12	O
Anna	O
R.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
6.	O
Edward	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Streek	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
alias	O
Hales	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
D	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kembal	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fawcet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Charles	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
K	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bottomly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Boyard	I-pers
,	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Mark	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
,	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
,	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquire	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
Occasions	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
LOst	O
or	O
miscarried	O
from	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Thomas-Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
black	O
Japans	O
'd	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Figure	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
2	O
Wedding	O
Rings	O
;	O
the	O
Posy	O
of	O
one	O
was	O
,	O
Let	O
Virtue	O
be	O
your	O
Guide	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
no	O
Posy	O
,	O
but	O
marked	O
B	O
R	O
G	O
or	O
J	O
W.	O
Two	O
Burial	O
Rings	O
,	O
I	O
mark	O
'd	O
F	O
M	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Mark	O
forgot	O
:	O
With	O
3	O
other	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Angel	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
James	O
Rex	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Silver	O
Medals	O
of	O
Note	O
and	O
Value	O
.	O
A	O
crimson	O
Velvet	O
Purse	O
bound	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
a	O
Gold	O
Medal	O
of	O
Charles	O
I.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
of	O
James	O
I.	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
I.	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
a	O
double	O
Guinea	O
of	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
single	O
one	O
ditto	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
Pounds	O
of	O
fine	O
Silver	O
ones	O
:	O
Likewise	O
the	O
following	O
Linen	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
marked	O
W	O
G	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
2	O
large	O
Down	O
Pillows	O
,	O
2	O
small	O
ones	O
,	O
several	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
2	O
fine	O
Mechlin	O
Laced	O
Pinners	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
,	O
and	O
Laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
of	O
Value	O
.	O
Whoever	O
shall	O
bring	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
Pculterer	O
,	O
near	O
Smithfield-bars	O
,	O
shall	O
receive	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
full	O
Proportion	O
for	O
any	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
:	O
And	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
shall	O
be	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
or	O
valued	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bearer	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
Edward	O
Crouch	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
as	O
above	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
Wallbrook	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
never	O
failing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
cures	O
the	O
GOUT	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
time	O
;	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
fallens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
,	O
and	O
Hypocondriacal	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
:	O
Faintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
,	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
,	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cur	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
.	O
Also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
them	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fitts	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Now	O
living	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Sheers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chambers-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Goodmans-fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
,	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
The	O
Vain	O
Prodigal	O
Life	O
and	O
Tragical	O
Penitent	O
Death	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hellier	I-pers
,	O
who	O
for	O
Murdering	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
was	O
executed	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
at	O
Westover	O
in	O
Charles	O
City	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Virginia	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Plantation	O
called	O
Hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
perpetrated	O
the	O
said	O
Murders	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Sam	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
head	O
Ally	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
