TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1715.	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ble	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Beasly	I-pers
John	B-pers
D	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Beresford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Strode	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ba	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Kairnes	I-pers
Just	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Brave	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Priddy	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
George	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clavents	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Garal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
drank	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
rode	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
into	O
Fleerstreet	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
siez	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
Witness	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Evening	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Powell	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
23	O
Guineas	O
into	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
8	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
She	O
said	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
Carbonet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barbamine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Meakins	O
keeping	O
the	O
Star-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Drawer	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
done	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Meakins	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
give	O
them	O
6	O
half	O
Guineas	O
for	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Money	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
other	O
Persons	O
take	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Star	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
where	O
the	O
Drawer	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
positively	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
whom	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
while	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
Business	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
were	O
bid	O
welcome	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
unsuspected	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Moid'ors	O
,	O
a	O
Double	O
Pistole	O
,	O
two	O
Half-Broad-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
in	O
Cateaton-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cloth	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bargain	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
where	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Witness	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
who	O
turning	O
some	O
Gold	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
against	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
among	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
his	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
had	O
their	O
Hands	O
busy	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
their	O
Actions	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
keep	O
their	O
Hands	O
off	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
their	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
telling	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
wanting	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
positively	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
cou	O
'd	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
They	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
ever	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Carbonet	O
and	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Moid'ers	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shale	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1711	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Shales	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
turning	O
out	O
a	O
Bag	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
thrust	O
their	O
Hands	O
into	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
half	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Moid'ors	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
none	O
could	O
take	O
'em	O
but	O
they	O
.	O
They	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
two	O
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
and	O
bought	O
3	O
Neckcloths	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
putting	O
out	O
his	O
Bag	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
Carbonel	O
some	O
Days	O
ago	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
knew	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
notice	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Carbonet	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Moid'ors	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nath	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
amongst	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Pieces	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
also	O
very	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Still	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
White	O
was	O
cheapening	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Still	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
mistrusted	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
gainst	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
White	O
laid	O
down	O
Money	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Parkhurst	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bridget	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Brides	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Pleura	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
both	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
next	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
Lewis	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
ye	O
?	O
But	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
Lewis	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
you	O
owe	O
me	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
others	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
naked	O
and	O
bleeding	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
.	O
Being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
(	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
being	O
first	O
taken	O
off	O
)	O
where	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
dress	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
in	O
Number	O
,	O
(	O
two	O
of	O
'em	O
mortal	O
)	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
.	O
One	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
disarm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Pleura	O
,	O
are	O
ye	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
?	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
by	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
imperfect	O
Man	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
past	O
;	O
which	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
who	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Lunatick	O
and	O
Whimsical	O
Things	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
within	O
that	O
Space	O
of	O
time	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Capacity	O
of	O
distinguishing	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
having	O
lately	O
transacted	O
some	O
Business	O
relating	O
to	O
his	O
Liberty	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Senses	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
Company	O
,	O
from	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Skeel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
John	B-pers
Clely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Drugget	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waggs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
on	O
Wig	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
selling	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
Tankard	O
of	O
wash	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
real	O
Silver	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Calf-Skins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Murhouse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
dress	O
'd	O
such	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
had	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
like	O
Number	O
of	O
such	O
Skins	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
lost	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Gold	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
in	O
his	O
Closet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
was	O
wanting	O
;	O
whereupon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Horasay	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lounds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
drinking	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
paid	O
honestly	O
for	O
his	O
Lodging	O
and	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Two	O
Nights	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Hornshy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
together	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Ale	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
accordingly	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Landlord	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
Hornshy	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
(	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Half-hang	O
'd	O
Smith	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
crime	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Longuet	I-pers
and	O
partners	B-pers
and	O
partners	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Warehouse	O
is	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
having	O
been	O
3	O
times	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
away	O
,	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
Thieves	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
accordingly	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Stock-lock	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
Door	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Padlock	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enter	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
missing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Rood-lane-end	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
the	O
Padlock	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
with	O
Tinder	O
and	O
Matches	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
thus	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
or	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
as	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Places	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
left	O
special	O
to	O
be	O
determin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Judges	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Shepard	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Proof	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Intention	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
order	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gilt	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
Church	O
of	O
St	O
Paul	O
in	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fringe	O
was	O
stoln	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Alter-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dean	O
's	O
Stall	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
25	O
of	O
Burnt-Silver	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Gilt	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Fringe	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
siez	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
some	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
among	O
the	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
from	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
which	O
making	O
it	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
casting	O
his	O
Eye	O
down	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coronets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Leeds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Chariot	O
driving	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
get	O
up	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
one	O
Coronet	O
,	O
and	O
unscrew	O
another	O
;	O
whereupon	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coronet	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Suit	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tresear	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
flower	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hillersden	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
Waggon	O
at	O
the	O
Swan-Inn	B-place
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Dog	O
under	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
saw	O
Martin	O
run	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
he	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
much	O
affecting	O
C	O
-	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
-	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Burgis	O
,	O
a	O
Pewterer	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
11	O
Plates	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
view	O
'em	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Bear	O
upon	O
'em	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
defaced	O
;	O
whereupon	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boldwin	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-Tavern	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
who	O
upon	O
this	O
Discovery	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
4	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Dish	O
more	O
,	O
defac	O
'd	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Harp-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
a	O
Market-price	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
under-hand	O
Dealing	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
's	O
House	O
near	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
huff	O
,	O
and	O
summon	O
'd	O
her	O
Master	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
for	O
her	O
Wages	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
selling	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	O
Cornwall	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Gibbons	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
several	O
Burglaries	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
became	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
112	O
Pound-weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Weight	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boit	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
swore	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Scales	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
24	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
and	O
Evans	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
Cornwall	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Proof	O
than	O
Gibbon	O
's	O
swearing	O
against	O
Evans	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Plates	O
,	O
12	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
;	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Aron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
40	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
either	O
in	O
this	O
or	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Indictment	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
bare	O
Oath	O
of	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
fraudulently	O
taking	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Scalton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Boutle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
400	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Rope	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Boutle	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
from	O
Wapping-Dock	B-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rowing	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Rope	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Poplin	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
then	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
form	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
thro	O
'	O
Round	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
drove	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Help	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Overlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Nortonfolgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
having	O
been	O
clean	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
hung	O
out	O
dry	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
bringing	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tisden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Valentine	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
King-street	O
Westminster	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
His	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
imperfect	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Stand	O
of	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Fellow	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
slipt	O
under	O
a	O
Crach-Pole	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
pursuing	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
,	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
running	O
and	O
crying	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
could	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
be	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Breest	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Can	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Anderson	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
fate	O
in	O
her	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pilts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
St.	O
Albans	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
Advice	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
he	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
buys	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
these	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
get	O
Six	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
steps	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stillington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Bushel	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fichler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Porsian	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Greno	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Journey-men	O
)	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
again	O
till	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Proof	O
enough	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquited	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
pair	O
of	O
Mill-nes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Governour	B-pers
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
New-River	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
as	O
a	O
Stragler	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Linnen	O
being	O
drying	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
Sheer	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
jump	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Young	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
an	O
Amethyll	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Fos	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
both	O
her	O
Servant	O
about	O
Two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
That	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
thought	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Sweet-heart	O
,	O
upon	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
but	O
said	O
before	O
from	O
his	O
Misteress	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
Enquiry	O
made	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
the	O
by	O
it	O
unless	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
amongst	O
Linnen	O
by	O
Mistake	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Frost	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
then	O
therein	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
's	O
Footman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Chambers	O
but	O
in	O
Inn	O
about	O
11	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
again	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chambers	O
with	O
the	O
Clocks	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Outer-Door	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
being	O
unscrew	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Screws	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Hand-Vice	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Inn	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Man	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stair-case	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
bring	O
down	O
what	O
he	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
involous	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rutherton	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Katterns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Witness	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
she	O
spent	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Strag-Breeches	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
is	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Matthew	O
's	O
Shop	O
is	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
(	O
being	O
Sunday	O
)	O
when	O
Matthews	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
his	O
Eyes	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
coming	O
;	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
a	O
Bag	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Snag	O
Breeches	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Girl	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Abeting	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
arrested	O
by	O
one	O
Exton	O
a	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
in	O
his	O
Spunging-house	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
together	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
Exton	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
denying	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
Prison-Rooms	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
that	O
Blandford	O
,	O
whose	O
Husband	O
is	O
Exton	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
Leeson	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Having	O
seen	O
a	O
Room	O
or	O
Two	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
known	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
another	O
;	O
which	O
Blandford	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Leeson	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
way	O
laughing	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Leeson	O
flung	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
force	O
himself	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Hand	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
to	O
her	O
Privy-parts	O
behind	O
,	O
did	O
by	O
force	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
all	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
when	O
Blandford	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
laughing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Captain	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Man	O
Midwife	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
grop	O
'd	O
her	O
well	O
;	O
Come	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
a	O
handsom	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
pretty	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
pretty	O
Child	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Injury	O
done	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
undone	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Damage	O
in	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
making	O
Inspection	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Scratch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parts	O
somewhat	O
red	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
Violence	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scratch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Inflamation	O
in	O
those	O
Parts	O
.	O
Leeson	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
is	O
his	O
Life	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Request	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
serveral	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
thrust	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
be	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
once	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
beliv	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
something	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
long	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
And	O
one	O
swore	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
Captain	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Man	O
Midwife	O
,	O
pray	O
feel	O
my	O
Body	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Stars	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
fond	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
grew	O
uneasie	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
him	O
going	O
,	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Midwives	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Damage	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
perceive	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Damage	O
by	O
a	O
Force	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
clapt	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
Leeson	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
twice	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
sound	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
swore	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
Husband	O
tax	O
her	O
with	O
clapping	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
brought	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
Dublin	O
College	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
and	O
elsewhere	O
.	O
Blandford	O
also	O
had	O
some	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
heard	O
,	O
May	O
call	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
amongst	O
whom	O
was	O
a	O
Minister	O
,	O
who	O
marry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
about	O
8	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
had	O
administer	O
'd	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
among	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
regular	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Costin	I-pers
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowles	O
Smocks	O
a	O
Lastring	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Bow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
imperfect	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Doily	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lench	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
6	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Doors	O
were	O
fall	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
were	O
found	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
Doily	O
was	O
stopt	O
selling	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mercy	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Red	O
Heifer	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Steer	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Bullocks	O
were	O
driven	O
from	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
Mr.	B-place
Mohun	I-place
's	I-place
Ground	I-place
in	O
Walworth	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
going	O
to	O
Peckham	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
credible	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Ship	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Business	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Pistol	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
altogether	O
groundless	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Barfleur	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
Wapping	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
keeping	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Skip	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
upon	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
it	O
cry	O
extremely	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strip	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
its	O
Mother	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
it	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
Child	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Button	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Buttons	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hollingsby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
wrong	O
laid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Yoxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joanna	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Yoxton	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Everett	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
24	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Roberts	B-pers
Sabre	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Yoxton	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
Charge	O
with	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
search	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
Mother	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
acquainted	O
at	O
Everett	O
's	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
came	O
while	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Iron	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Everett	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
to	O
that	O
wicked	O
Crime	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Jordan	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Cup	O
of	O
Everett	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Yoxton	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Everett	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Colt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Door	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
Fellow	O
prentice	O
threw	O
his	O
Hat	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boots	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hayden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Montague	B-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
swore	O
,	O
her	O
Winston	O
,	O
who	O
getting	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
against	O
Hayden	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hadley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Arthur	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Misunderstanding	O
between	O
'em	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Things	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
foul	O
Language	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
interpos	O
'd	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
still	O
sav	O
'd	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Garden	O
to	O
the	O
Parlor	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
got	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
express	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
concern	O
for	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
sucking	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
doing	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
first	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
Difference	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
without	O
Provocation	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Parlor-window	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
let	O
his	O
Sword	O
fall	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Gun	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Confusion	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
by	O
that	O
blow	O
render	O
'd	O
him	O
infancible	O
how	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
carr	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
but	O
against	O
that	O
Witness	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
litigious	O
troublesome	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Pot	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
2	O
Salvers	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Croydon	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
carry	O
Things	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
-	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemister	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
Marriages	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Caltan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
No	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
74	O
Deal-Boards	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Boards	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
How	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
Necessity	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Lalam	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
full	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pierson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Town	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hurrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Hastler	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
goods	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
Line	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Butchelor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sail	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cloths	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
General	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
William	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Gane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dulier	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Thieves	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bundled	O
the	O
Clocks	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hawks	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Half-Guineas	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Murrant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Harthurst	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	B-pers
Harthurst	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Turky	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
8	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
Passage	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
thither	O
,	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
did	O
accordingly	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
observ	O
'd	O
some	O
Passages	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Troy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
4	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
they	O
said	O
drew	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
58	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pendrell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pendrell	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Pendrell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Locks	O
having	O
been	O
sometimes	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Board	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
hiding	O
it	O
under	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
Watkins	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
anybody	O
could	O
discover	O
the	O
Place	O
but	O
she	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
Howell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Sweet-heart	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
also	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
and	O
Parer	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
by	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
spend	O
Money	O
extravagantly	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Casman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Sailor	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
where	O
Casman	O
was	O
a	O
Passenger	O
from	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Callicoes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
run	O
to	O
avoid	O
Cullom	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
ashore	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
Demand	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
Carbonel	I-pers
,	O
B	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barbamino	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Perkhurst	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Frost	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Skip	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Yoxton	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
being	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
crav	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
:	O
but	O
a	O
Record	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
apear	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
obtain	O
'd	O
that	O
Benefit	O
in	O
a	O
like	O
Case	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Cushaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
him	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
23.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Skeal	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
W	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Doily	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepard	I-pers
,	O
Joanna	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winston	I-pers
,	O
F	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hosier	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
17.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowland	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Natt	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Busslew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pierson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hurrel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Skip	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
severally	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
to	O
be	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
KING-ABIGAIL	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Secret	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
She-Favourite	O
,	O
detected	O
and	O
applied	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Sermon	O
upon	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
And	O
Women	O
rule	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
Isa	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Deliver	O
'd	O
(	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
preach	O
'd	O
)	O
by	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Dunton	I-pers
,	O
Author	O
of	O
Queen	O
Robin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Sermon	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
Ox	O
-	O
and	O
Bull	O
-	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Popping	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
;	O
J.	O
Harrison	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
A.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
and	O
A.	O
Boulter	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
1715	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
)	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Tin-shop	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
Abroad	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
insallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
THE	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
abroad	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
that	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
parts	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
for	O
no	O
sooner	O
is	O
it	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Parts	O
griev	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
gives	O
immediate	O
Ease	O
,	O
and	O
removes	O
the	O
Cause	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wondeful	O
Success	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
safe	O
and	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Teeth	O
from	O
Rotting	O
or	O
Decaying	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
next	O
Door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Dog-Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bow-lane	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Tin-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Stock-Market	O
.	O
Liveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparible	O
Wash	O
to	O
beautify	O
the	O
Faces	O
;	O
which	O
far	O
excels	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
found	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-burn	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
and	O
render	O
as	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Young	O
it	O
keeps	O
always	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
:	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
from	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
five	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
Pomatums	O
,	O
White-Pots	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Snow	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
where-ever	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
;	O
she	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
Light	O
or	O
Dark	O
Brown	O
;	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
shapes	O
the	O
Eye	O
brows	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
Beautiful	O
;	O
she	O
hath	O
a	O
delicate	O
Paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red	O
Pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE-8th	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainment	O
:	O
Consisting	O
of	O
One	O
Thousand	O
and	O
One	O
Stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indian	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
Marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
avenge	O
himself	O
for	O
the	O
Disloyalty	O
of	O
his	O
first	O
Sultaness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
7	O
Vols	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
diverting	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	O
D'Anois	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Faires	O
,	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
A	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
A	O
Book	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
instructing	O
Youth	O
in	O
reading	O
.	O
With	O
Forry	O
Gurs	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
speak	O
in	O
publick	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
Lives	O
British	O
and	O
Foreign	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Great	O
Men	O
that	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Years	O
1711	O
and	O
12.	O
pr	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Secret	O
History	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Shewing	O
by	O
what	O
Steps	O
the	O
Clergy	O
ruined	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
that	O
Nation	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
Lydall	O
's	O
Tables	O
of	O
Simple	O
Interest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
,	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
Exactly	O
computed	O
to	O
the	O
1000th	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
also	O
Tables	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
per	O
Cent	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
exact	O
of	O
any	O
Extant	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Gardiner	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Directions	O
for	O
right	O
ordering	O
of	O
Fruit	O
Gardens	O
and	O
Kitchin	O
Gardens	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
London	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Gardiners	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
A	O
Complete	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Sacheverell	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Index	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
any	O
Particular	O
in	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Trial	O
may	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
Anna	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
House-keeper	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
6	O
Years	O
ago	O
being	O
so	O
injur	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Husband	O
with	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
broke	O
out	O
in	O
large	O
Blotches	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
great	O
Holes	O
in	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
infecting	O
my	O
Blood	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
dreadful	O
Symptoms	O
not	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
5	O
Years	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
constantly	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
Salve	O
for	O
5	O
Years	O
together	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
then	O
forever	O
other	O
eminent	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
Prescriptions	O
without	O
any	O
Benefit	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
despairing	O
of	O
a	O
Cure	O
,	O
having	O
wept	O
whole	O
Nights	O
and	O
Days	O
to	O
see	O
myself	O
so	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
take	O
of	O
the	O
Specifick	O
Remedy	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Edition	O
of	O
,	O
The	O
Practical	O
Schedule	O
of	O
the	O
Disease	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
given	O
Gratis	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
will	O
but	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Toy-shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
,	O
near	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
remov	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Putten	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
since	O
that	O
Day	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
there	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
only	O
4	O
times	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
thrown	O
away	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
my	O
Legs	O
are	O
well	O
,	O
my	O
Head	O
intirely	O
cur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
This	O
(	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Husband	O
)	O
I	O
own	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
further	O
satisfy	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
this	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
Anne	O
Awery	O
Witness	O
R.	O
Tosdale	O
,	O
House	O
Keeper	O
25	O
Years	O
within	O
4	O
Days	O
of	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Rod	O
lion	O
street	O
,	O
Holbourn	B-pers
,	O
R	B-pers
.	I-pers
Roberts	O
,	O
House-Keeper	O
10	O
Years	O
in	O
Lords	O
Chappel	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
have	O
been	O
presently	O
.	O
B.	O
LILBURN	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
lately	O
at	O
the	O
Bakehouse	O
in	O
Great	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
remov	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Street	O
,	O
two	O
Doors	O
above	O
the	O
3	O
Tun	O
Ter	O
,	O
up	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
and	O
sells	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
about	O
30	O
Years	O
)	O
the	O
Wase	O
for	O
making	O
away	O
Freches	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Warms	O
,	O
and	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
as	O
Fault	O
Shelling	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
the	O
from	O
all	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
some	O
Years	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
now	O
only	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
who	O
gives	O
Adivice	O
(	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Medicines	O
)	O
for	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Her	O
Antiscorbutick	O
,	O
Hysterick	O
,	O
and	O
Hand-Pills	O
,	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
Cancers	O
,	O
Kings-Evil	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
and	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
are	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Her	O
Elixes	O
for	O
Agues	O
,	O
Cholick	O
,	O
Gripes	O
,	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Cold	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
Looseness	O
,	O
is	O
one	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Vial	O
,	O
or	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
The	O
Girdles	O
for	O
curing	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
are	O
One	O
Shilling	O
and	O
Six	O
pence	O
each	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Help	O
for	O
all	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
,	O
or	O
Hurts	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.L	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head	O
Ally	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bay	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
)	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Barthalomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchange	O
.	O
