TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
1716	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Immins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sprint	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Humsreys	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmerr	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Upp	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
George	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ravenor	I-pers
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
James	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
an	O
Inquisition	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
charged	O
with	O
Gunpowder	O
and	O
Bullets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
returned	O
Ignoramus	O
John	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
)	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
shut	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
found	O
several	O
Watchmen	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
throw	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Windows	O
broke	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
scarce	O
4	O
Panes	O
whole	O
;	O
but	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Mischief	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
drove	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
read	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
People	O
advanced	O
with	O
great	O
Shouts	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
being	O
within	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
particular	O
or	O
general	O
Cry	O
used	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
however	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Mobber	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Tuckey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Balcony	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
1	O
a-Clock	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
advancing	O
from	O
Fleet-street	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	B-place
Door	O
hollowing	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
People	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
their	O
Cry	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
King	O
George	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
had	O
Sticks	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
push	O
'd	O
on	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Yards	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Distance	O
before	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
no	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fin	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Execution	O
.	O
And	O
Bill	O
stood	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Blunderbuss	O
did	O
the	O
Mischief	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
level	O
his	O
Piece	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
kept	O
Shop	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
sate	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
there	O
say	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
them	O
beat	O
against	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Voice	O
say	O
,	O
Come	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Roe-buck	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
1	O
a-Clock	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
she	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Butchers	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Barbers	O
(	O
whose	O
Door	O
was	O
beat	O
open	O
)	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
beat	O
against	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
no	O
Watch	O
nor	O
Constable	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Windows	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Stones	O
thrown	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
with	O
Sticks	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Mob	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Oath	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
advance	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
stock	O
still	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Yards	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
fin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fall	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
levelled	O
his	O
Piece	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
dropt	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Crowd	O
being	O
very	O
great	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Passage	O
into	O
a	O
fort	O
of	O
an	O
Ally	O
by	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Church-yard	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
went	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
against	O
her	O
and	O
frighted	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
under	O
an	O
uneasie	O
Conscience	O
,	O
as	O
fearing	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
that	O
Morning	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Windows	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
staid	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
about	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
some	O
Men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
a	O
Proclamation	O
with	O
three	O
Huzzus	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
out	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
discharg	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
some	O
Questions	O
concerning	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
their	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
Sticks	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Not	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
nothing	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
took	O
towards	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moultfier	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
overagainst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Stones	O
thrown	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
saw	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
against	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Roc-buck	O
,	O
walk	O
in	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Crowd	O
about	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
whole	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
as	O
some	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
broke	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
Gentleman	O
read	O
a	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
were	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
Sticks	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
advance	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Yards	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mug	O
house	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
back	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
retire	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Mob	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
nor	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
increased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
cry	O
King	O
George	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
High-Church	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
read	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
People	O
drove	O
down	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
forced	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
parted	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
on	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
deposed	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Boyles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
several	O
Watchmen	O
drew	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Rank	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
they	O
hiss	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
they	O
hiss	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
threw	O
Stones	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
once	O
before	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-Room	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
one	O
overs	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
suffer	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
having	O
Authority	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
enough	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
securing	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
threw	O
the	O
Stones	O
;	O
who	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
their	O
own	O
Windows	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Hour	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
sent	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Ale	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Constable	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
forbid	O
his	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hucks	O
offered	O
them	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
these	O
look	O
like	O
honest	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
Drink	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
made	O
them	O
return	O
that	O
also	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
Constable	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
that	O
Rout	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Constable	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Rout	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
your	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Constable	O
in	O
that	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
direct	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
some	O
Mischief	O
happened	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
togather	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
till	O
9	O
,	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
inclined	O
to	O
do	O
more	O
Mischief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deponent	O
ventured	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
reason	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
ruin	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
them	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
received	O
two	O
Knocks	O
by	O
Stones	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
bleed	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
struck	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Stone	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
an	O
armed	O
Mob	O
was	O
preparing	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
two	O
Expresses	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Townsend	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
armed	O
,	O
with	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Clubs	O
,	O
appeared	O
in	O
Fleetstrees	O
making	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
consulted	O
what	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
Security	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Advice	O
to	O
attack	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
joined	O
the	O
Mob	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
became	O
too	O
formidable	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
and	O
Hour	O
before	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
:	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
repulsed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
the	O
Mob	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Barricade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
as	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
Stones	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
discharge	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
encouraged	O
the	O
Mob	O
by	O
Connivance	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
(	O
Men	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
Children	O
)	O
began	O
to	O
show	O
their	O
Colours	O
,	O
by	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
and	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
their	O
Number	O
was	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
drove	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
which	O
served	O
but	O
to	O
encrease	O
their	O
Rage	O
and	O
Number	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
Stones	O
so	O
thick	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
also	O
armed	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
presented	O
their	O
Pieces	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
he	O
gone	O
,	O
true	O
a	O
Care	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
&	O
c.6	O
Minutes	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
they	O
were	O
pelted	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
take	O
no	O
Aim	O
;	O
the	O
Mob	O
still	O
advancing	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hollowing	O
out	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
fired	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
posted	O
himself	O
for	O
the	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
broke	O
into	O
it	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
beat	O
with	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Clubs	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
along	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
Guards	O
and	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tobias	B-pers
Cheesbrook	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
certainly	O
been	O
murdered	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
were	O
pulling	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
That	O
before	O
this	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Harm	O
offered	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
all	O
Night	O
for	O
its	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Society	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Swin	O
,	O
for	O
crying	O
out	O
King	O
George	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
civil	O
Manner	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
Persons	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Windows	O
and	O
untiled	O
the	O
Penthouse	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
files	O
upon	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
which	O
broke	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Heads	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
broke	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
the	O
Tiles	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
thrown	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
no	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
Swin	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Tiles	O
were	O
thrown	O
from	O
the	O
Penthouse	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
Cut	O
over	O
the	O
Nose	O
by	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Tile	O
from	O
the	O
swan	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
the	O
least	O
Provocation	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
returned	O
there	O
Tiles	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
their	O
Windows	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Mob	O
broke	O
their	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Fellow	O
whom	O
the	O
Mob	O
called	O
Vinegar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Mob	O
much	O
encreased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
No	O
Hannoverians	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
quite	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
repulsed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
keep	O
back	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
brandishing	O
it	O
and	O
bauling	O
out	O
,	O
Fall	O
on	O
,	O
brave	O
Boys	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
is	O
landed	O
with	O
20000	O
Men	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
they	O
had	O
released	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Mob	O
fell	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Barricade	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
heard	O
great	O
clattering	O
and	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
below	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
more	O
speedy	O
Destruction	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Mob	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
there	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
therefore	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Consequence	O
.	O
Whilst	O
he	O
was	O
observing	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
and	O
read	O
a	O
Proclamation	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
huzza	O
'd	O
for	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Huzza	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
huzza	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
advanc	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
sought	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
beat	O
at	O
last	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Mob	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
No	O
Hannoverians	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
louder	O
than	O
ever	O
,	O
with	O
Sticks	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
universal	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
lean	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
held	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
two	O
Hands	O
like	O
a	O
Quarter-staff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob-fling	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Bricks	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
whilst	O
others	O
advanc	O
'd	O
with	O
Sticks	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harbottle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
near	O
the	O
Rose-Inn	O
at	O
Holbourn	O
bridge	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
Men	O
past	O
by	O
him	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
hollowing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
attack	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
trac	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nicholls	O
's	O
a	O
Soap-boiler	O
by	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
Sticks	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
Braziers	O
near	O
Adams	O
's	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
more	O
Sticks	O
given	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
Boys	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
Sticks	O
enough	O
now	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
having	O
arm	O
'd	O
themselves	O
with	O
Clubs	O
to	O
their	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
away	O
their	O
small	O
Sticks	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Salisbury-court	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
they	O
press	O
'd	O
forward	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
beat	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
;	O
but	O
growing	O
stronger	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Charge	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Shout	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Mug	O
House	O
and	O
hear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
,	O
Have	O
a	O
Care	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Piece	O
fired	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
throwing	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Dr.	O
John	O
De	O
la	O
Caste	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
through	O
the	O
Mob	O
into	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Provision	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Townsend	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
his	O
Lordship	O
of	O
their	O
Danger	O
,	O
and	O
blamed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
not	O
doing	O
so	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
small	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
Warning-gun	O
for	O
the	O
Mob	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
;	O
for	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
with	O
great	O
Fury	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
behind	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sexton	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
had	O
the	O
Cruelty	O
to	O
turn	O
a	O
Mastiss	O
loose	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
Defence	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
under	O
a	O
necessity	O
of	O
killing	O
the	O
Dog	O
and	O
him	O
too	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
off	O
:	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Monday-Night	O
before	O
this	O
Action	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
their	O
was	O
a	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
thought	O
incouraged	O
and	O
encreas	O
'd	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
by	O
taking	O
no	O
Care	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
ling	O
Stones	O
to	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
threw	O
there	O
just	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Action	O
done	O
in	O
their	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
Stones	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Baskets	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
Constable	O
this	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
some	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Johnson	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
battered	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
understand	O
them	O
(	O
being	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
)	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Duty	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Mob	O
there	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
about	O
Noon	O
coming	O
from	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
breaking	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gutting	O
and	O
pulling	O
Things	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
say	O
,	O
just	O
thus	O
will	O
we	O
pull	O
King	O
George	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Then	O
Dr.	O
De	O
ls	O
Coste	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
more	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
and	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
too	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Berwick	O
,	O
was	O
landed	O
with	O
20000	O
Men	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Friday-Night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
Chairman	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mob	O
threatned	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
down	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Messenger	O
to	O
the	O
Loyal	O
Society	O
in	O
Tavistock-street	O
,	O
desiring	O
their	O
Company	O
and	O
Assistance	O
if	O
Need	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
very	O
readily	O
and	O
disperst	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Harp	O
and	O
Fiddle	O
,	O
playing	O
The	O
King	O
shall	O
enjoy	O
his	O
own	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Chairman	O
of	O
that	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
well	O
now	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Orders	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
President	O
generally	O
enters	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
profound	O
Silence	O
is	O
made	O
,	O
they	O
always	O
begin	O
a	O
hearty	O
Mug	O
to	O
the	O
Health	O
and	O
Prosperity	O
of	O
His	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
King	O
GEORGE	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
to	O
their	O
Royal	O
Highnesses	O
the	O
Prince	O
and	O
Princess	O
of	O
Wales	O
and	O
their	O
Issue	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
;	O
a	O
third	O
to	O
the	O
Glorious	O
and	O
Immortal	O
Memory	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
or	O
never	O
miss	O
a	O
fourth	O
to	O
the	O
Prosperity	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
sometimes	O
with	O
a	O
supplement	O
,	O
as	O
wishing	O
she	O
may	O
never	O
want	O
Power	O
nor	O
Inclination	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
encourage	O
all	O
Protectants	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
without	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
are	O
inclined	O
to	O
stay	O
longer	O
,	O
they	O
fill	O
up	O
the	O
Time	O
with	O
other	O
Loyal	O
Healths	O
of	O
lesser	O
Note	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Chairman	O
or	O
President	O
shall	O
think	O
proper	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
to	O
the	O
Confusion	O
or	O
Damnation	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
or	O
Thing	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Enemies	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
and	O
theirs	O
have	O
falsly	O
given	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carleton	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
court	O
full	O
of	O
Mob	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Passage	O
by	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Wall	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turning	O
himself	O
about	O
saw	O
two	O
Parties	O
engaging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
making	O
a	O
Longe	O
at	O
the	O
Mob	O
with	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
fixed	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
broke	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retire	O
,	O
bearing	O
down	O
upon	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Torrent	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
at	O
their	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
Instant	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Piece	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
to	O
his	O
thinking	O
)	O
was	O
advancing	O
to	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
to	O
close	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
particularly	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
starting	O
and	O
heaving	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
helped	O
to	O
convey	O
him	O
into	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
violent	O
Noise	O
of	O
Boards	O
breaking	O
and	O
crashing	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
think	O
it	O
high	O
Time	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paul	B-pers
Burdeau	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
violent	O
Mob	O
affaulting	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Constables	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
need	O
of	O
their	O
Assistance	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
Constables	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
just	O
by	O
there	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Call	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
Duty	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
walkt	O
about	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
to	O
observe	O
what	O
passed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Fellow	O
say	O
,	O
Damn	O
that	O
Granadier	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
him	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Fun	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
replied	O
,	O
Damn	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
some	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
that	O
Person	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Daniel	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Luke	B-pers
Whitson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Salisbury-Court	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Consultation	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
which	O
served	O
but	O
to	O
increase	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
great	O
Shouts	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
knock	O
down	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Mob	O
pressed	O
forwards	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
their	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fire	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
Law	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
Justice	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
Reason	O
on	O
your	O
side	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
his	O
Stick	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
and	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
Action	O
,	O
till	O
past	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Mob	O
was	O
numerous	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stones	O
thrown	O
in	O
great	O
Plenty	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
wounded	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
be	O
dre	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Boys	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
was	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
would	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Fellow	O
bring	O
out	O
three	O
Bottles	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
kneel	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Swan	O
Door	O
near	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
hollowed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Swan	O
hollowed	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
Engagement	O
between	O
the	O
Mob	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
took	O
some	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
throw	O
a	O
Stone	O
at	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
his	O
two	O
Fists	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
:	O
He	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
called	O
him	O
Vinegar	O
,	O
some	O
Little	O
Daniel	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
destroy	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
they	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
in	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Fellow	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
three	O
Bottles	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
;	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
standing	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
And	O
lastly	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Badcock	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
informed	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
desired	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Riot	O
or	O
Disorder	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Constable	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
being	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
who	O
replied	O
,	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Breach	O
of	O
it	O
themselves	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
done	O
nothing	O
that	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
just	O
Offence	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Clatter	O
against	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
another	O
Constable	O
,	O
one	O
Johnston	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
desired	O
likewise	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
and	O
disperse	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
promising	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
about	O
20	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
replied	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
People	O
threw	O
the	O
Stones	O
themselves	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
knew	O
himself	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
being	O
shut	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
fling	O
any	O
out	O
.	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
that	O
Ward	O
;	O
the	O
Mob	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
in	O
their	O
very	O
sight	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
heard	O
this	O
Constable	O
say	O
the	O
House	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pulled	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Bustle	O
and	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
at	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Windows	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wounded	O
;	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
threw	O
a	O
Stone	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
resoned	O
their	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
Substance	O
and	O
Worth	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thinking	O
it	O
needless	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
The	O
Recorder	O
having	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considered	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
Cassie	O
and	O
Carnegy	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
condemn	O
'd	O
Rebels	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
it	O
Felony	O
without	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
to	O
demolish	O
,	O
or	O
begin	O
to	O
demolish	O
,	O
any	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
none	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
but	O
Purchase	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Door	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
Stones	O
and	O
Bricks	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
cried	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
all	O
the	O
Presbyterians	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Delander	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
rescued	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gott	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Love	O
helping	O
to	O
break	O
down	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
That	O
Purchase	O
and	O
Bean	O
were	O
also	O
there	O
hurling	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
Stones	O
and	O
Sticks	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Purchase	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Stick	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gott	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Purchase	O
throw	O
a	O
Stick	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Love	O
was	O
assisting	O
in	O
throwing	O
a	O
Rope	O
over	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
they	O
drew	O
it	O
first	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
loosened	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
,	O
him	O
climb	O
up	O
the	O
Rope	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Sign	O
.	O
Bean	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gott	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Bean	O
break	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
Sticks	O
thrown	O
up	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Michael	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
break	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
laboured	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
extraordinary	O
industrious	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
the	O
Destruction	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
pulling	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
employing	O
himself	O
every	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
purpose	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
the	O
Guards	O
came	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Price	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Prices	O
,	O
Purchase	O
and	O
Love	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
Bean	O
in	O
the	O
Rio	O
,	O
plendering	O
and	O
destroying	O
the	O
Mug	B-place
house	I-place
and	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
Love	O
swarmed	O
up	O
the	O
Rope	O
almost	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
is	O
order	O
to	O
sway	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Prices	O
were	O
employed	O
chiefly	O
within	O
Doors	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
Household	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Purchase	O
in	O
compleating	O
the	O
Ruine	O
of	O
those	O
brought	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
Bottles	O
and	O
Sticks	O
,	O
bawling	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
.	O
No	O
Hannoverian	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
Love	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Rope	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
falling	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
climbed	O
up	O
the	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
with	O
Pickaxes	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hasell	I-pers
junior	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Bean	O
running	O
with	O
great	O
Joy	O
from	O
Fleet-street	O
towards	O
Ludgate-hill	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
that	O
accompanied	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Cart	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Patters	O
Door	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
Bean	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
returned	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
Letters	O
R.R.E	O
.	O
upon	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
it	O
by	O
those	O
Letters	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
Sign	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
Bean	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
so	O
high	O
as	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carleton	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bean	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Return	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
from	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Sign	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Heat	O
,	O
running	O
with	O
it	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
greatest	O
Joy	O
and	O
Triumph	O
imaginable	O
,	O
towards	O
Fleet-Disch	O
;	O
which	O
sarprized	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cassie	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carnegy	O
,	O
two	O
Rebel	O
Prisoners	O
now	O
condemned	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
confined	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Luke	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
pull	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Force	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
whole	O
Front	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
beat	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Joy	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Love	O
stamp	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
break	O
them	O
,	O
especially	O
a	O
Coffee-Pot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
No	O
Hannoverian	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
Purchase	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Michael	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
cry	O
,	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
pull	O
down	O
this	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
pull	O
King	O
George	O
from	O
the	O
Throne	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Purchase	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
2	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Love	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Rope	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
called	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Temple	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
silly	O
,	O
ignorant	O
fellow	O
;	O
and	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
brewing	O
.	O
Bean	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
full	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Sign	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
Evidence	O
against	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
concerned	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Tuscan	O
Crown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
Dollar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
10	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wenham	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
several	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sims	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
leading	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Sight	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Defence	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Indigo	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
4	O
d	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
appeared	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
by	O
the	B-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
35	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Astill	I-pers
and	O
Atkinson	B-pers
Sugby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wilson	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
Confederate	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
concern	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wilson	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Colour	O
for	O
charging	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
Ingram	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Ingram	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
match	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
hide	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Cloths	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Callicoes	O
not	O
liking	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Servant	O
(	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Callico	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
)	O
for	O
some	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
not	O
being	O
soon	O
enough	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
grew	O
impatient	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
called	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
bought	O
some	O
Holland	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
attempting	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philipps	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
51	O
.	O
11	O
s	O
6d	O
.	O
which	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Gun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
some	O
jostle	O
or	O
Blow	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
'em	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
,	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
in	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
run	O
,	O
nevertheless	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wallbank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Basket-woman	O
that	O
plied	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
imploy	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Meat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bakers	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
busy	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Mugg	O
off	O
a	O
Shelf	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
Milk	O
,	O
which	O
running	O
about	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
only	O
crying	O
,	O
My	O
Mugg	O
and	O
my	O
Milk	O
,	O
my	O
Mugg	O
and	O
my	O
Milk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
time	O
enough	O
understood	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
about	O
3	O
weeks	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
Butcher	O
who	O
imploy	O
'd	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
committed	O
this	O
Felony	O
,	O
knew	O
her	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Butcher	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
imploy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
swore	O
he	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Mugg	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
upon	O
that	O
Occasion	O
:	O
Notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Mugg	O
not	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
not	O
properly	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mullineur	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
d	O
up	O
the	O
Sa	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
reaching	O
at	O
a	O
Wigg	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
Compassion	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Romley	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Entry	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revett	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Yards	O
at	O
Blue	O
Bays	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Bags	O
,	O
some	O
Linnen	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
on	I-place
London	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
packt	O
upon	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
which	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
they	O
learnt	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
unloaded	O
at	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
l	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Horse	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Bury	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
R	O
only	O
helping	O
to	O
unload	O
:	O
Wherefore	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
their	O
Bu	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
evers	O
often	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
and	O
cheat	O
the	O
Boys	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
for	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Moons	O
they	O
inform	O
'd	O
themselves	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
where	O
Bury	O
lodg	O
'd	O
.	O
Robinson	O
is	O
unloading	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
cut	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
defi	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
respled	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
them	O
when	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Upon	O
Trial	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
Boy	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
Blame	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
upon	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
on	I-place
London-Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sagathie	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leveridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
proved	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Camley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
empty	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
22	O
Bushels	O
of	O
value	O
39s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
swore	O
it	O
very	O
positively	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
good	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rumney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
Vintrey	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Spirits	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Cakes	O
of	O
Ginger-bread	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Niel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
fair	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Watches	O
to	O
send	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Father	O
he	O
said	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
(	O
calling	O
him	O
Captain	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
to	O
lay	O
some	O
Watches	O
before	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
examine	O
them	O
against	O
his	O
Arrival	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
expected	O
every	O
Moment	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
none	O
of	O
those	O
said	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
again	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Nail	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
applying	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Description	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
particularly	O
famous	O
for	O
Facts	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
upon	O
this	O
Wild	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
all	O
his	O
other	O
Troubles	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
Wild	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
several	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
knew	O
him	O
best	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Watches	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
and	O
not	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
However	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
Service	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Swithins	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Laskinby	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
very	O
intimate	O
dear	O
Friends	O
;	O
never	O
happy	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
continually	O
falling	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Red-Lion-Square	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Fallings-out	O
and	O
Reconcilements	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
common	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
minded	O
by	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
It	O
happened	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
who	O
urged	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
occasioned	O
their	O
last	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
high	O
Words	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
replied	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
some	O
these	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
fight	O
a	O
better	O
Man	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
Thus	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
an	O
Ozhen	O
Stick	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
light	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
be	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
robat	O
Fighting	O
was	O
afterwards	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
together	O
till	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
parted	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Wine	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
yet	O
sober	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
41	O
1.	O
at	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
Note	O
he	O
h	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
off	O
their	O
Demands	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Nagg	O
's	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
honourably	O
by	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
replying	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
passed	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
on	O
Fish-street	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Knowles	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
London-Stone	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowles	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
to	O
themselves	O
they	O
grew	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
Time	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
stop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
up	O
his	O
Seats	O
the	O
Business	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
much	O
wounded	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Hilt	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
very	O
furiously	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
hisled	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
mapled	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
fault	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
died	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
considering	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
Blood	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
cool	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Wisman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
in	O
Coleman	B-place
street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hankerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitebeak	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
considering	O
the	O
Value	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Callico	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Thimble	O
6d	O
.	O
1	O
Common	O
Prayer-Book	O
,	O
36	O
and	O
49	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhallows	I-place
on	I-place
London	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Meazy	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Healing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Healing	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Waters	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
a	O
more	O
convenient	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
Bible	O
without	O
drinking	O
his	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Book	O
at	O
a	O
Book-binder	O
's	O
in	O
Duck-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
9	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
fair	O
Price	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
(	O
2	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
more	O
Books	O
to	O
sell	O
)	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Healing	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
valued	O
much	O
above	O
the	O
common	O
Price	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
Graveschurch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burrell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Grance-church	B-place
street	I-place
about	O
1	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
either	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
immediately	O
lost	O
,	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
Fits	O
and	O
gather	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
whilst	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
always	O
near	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
their	O
Pockets	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Confession	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tidman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Doubt	O
in	O
the	O
clear	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pewterer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Finch	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assisting	O
in	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Phillis	B-pers
Delpeck	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
Upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Winter-time	O
use	O
to	O
do	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Queen	O
of	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
one	O
Night	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
whilst	O
a	O
Man	O
not	O
yet	O
known	O
;	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
Person	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Pox	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Nurses	O
of	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hospital	O
swore	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
more	O
afflicted	O
with	O
that	O
Disease	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
so	O
young	O
a	O
Child	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bennet	I-place
Grace-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
sworn	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Story	O
appear	O
'd	O
likely	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Copman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Henry	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
William	B-pers
Burkitt	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
(	O
Burkitt	O
)	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
hearing	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
also	O
marry	O
Mr.	O
Pollard	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
they	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
sold	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
being	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
they	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Women	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
near	O
Newgate	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
they	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowk	I-pers
alias	O
Bowden	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
offering	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Spurs	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
as	O
Silver	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
Martha	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Slate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Slate	O
were	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
with	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
Major	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
26	O
Guineas,1	O
Broad-piece	O
and	O
11	O
Moydores	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Church-Lane	B-place
(	O
a	O
most	O
notorious	O
Place	O
)	O
and	O
Darby	O
and	O
Rogers	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Dykes	O
and	O
Slate	O
and	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
into	O
some	O
Ren	O
where	O
they	O
bound	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
anci	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Way	O
out	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Rents	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Gold	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
d	O
Indictment	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
alone	O
to	O
one	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
(	O
since	O
executed	O
)	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Rings	O
which	O
he	O
very	O
much	O
valued	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
two	O
Guiness	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Pritchard	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Rum	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
stupid	O
Fellow	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
the	O
tary	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
;	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Pritchard	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Rents	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
M	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Cl	O
Lane	O
and	O
child	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
ly	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
same	O
others	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
said	O
by	O
throwing	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
Abuses	O
,	O
had	O
almost	O
frighted	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
happily	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Relief	O
and	O
sav	O
'd	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
made	O
herself	O
as	O
Evidence	O
in	O
this	O
Matter	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Robbery	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
lt	O
her	O
Fellow-Women	O
's	O
Share	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
by	O
Agreement	O
among	O
there	O
themselves	O
,	O
whoever	O
makes	O
a	O
Boo	O
to	O
divide	O
it	O
i	O
manner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
agreed	O
Dykes	O
was	O
not	O
prsent	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
;	O
nor	O
was	O
they	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
Bolton	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Darby	O
,	O
Dykes	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Slate	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Darby	O
,	O
Slate	O
,	O
and	O
Lawson	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Dykes	O
and	O
Bolton	O
were	O
acquitted	O
[	O
Slate	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Darby	O
,	O
Dykes	O
,	O
Rogers	O
,	O
Lawson	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wisler	I-pers
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Rents	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
against	O
Flood	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
pass	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
but	O
Darby	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
more	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Flood	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Radcliff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
45	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Morphew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
unaccountable	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
in	O
that	O
Kind	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hinde	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
36	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skellan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
at	O
Market	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
Servants	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Grounds	O
,	O
where	O
sometimes	O
afterwards	O
he	O
plowed	O
them	O
up	O
wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
no	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brailsford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
plain	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Stuff-Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pattins	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
and	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sciffars	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stennet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Mismanagement	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
and	O
triffling	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Potten	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
Order	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
the	O
Orders	O
of	O
the	O
Lords	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
for	O
taking	O
off	O
R	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
two	O
R	O
's	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Muster-Roll	O
of	O
the	O
Enterprize	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
in	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Saphire	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
himself	O
acquainted	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Admiralty-Office	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Busines	O
of	O
that	O
Office	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
lawful	O
Manner	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
persuaded	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
suddled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
many	O
Repolses	O
,	O
to	O
copy	O
out	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
his	O
drawing	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
conformable	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Lords	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
off	O
and	O
R	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
burnt	O
his	O
Original	O
,	O
and	O
engag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
with	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
Names	O
,	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
about	O
40	O
l	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elisha	O
Johns	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
R	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
forfeited	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
another	O
R	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Means	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
the	O
Clerk	O
(	O
who	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
)	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
lose	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
ruin	O
him	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
by	O
informing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
to	O
his	O
Measures	O
;	O
and	O
thus	O
by	O
Threats	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
Fears	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
break	O
thro	O
'	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
so	O
Slavish	O
a	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
above	O
1000/	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
's	O
Money	O
by	O
these	O
counterfeited	O
Orders	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
both	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Leatherton	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
7	O
Burglaries	O
and	O
Felonies	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
5	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
Mills	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Depositions	O
were	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hadley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Fellow-	O
servant	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pitchfork	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
1	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
One	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
last	O
February	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Esq	O
;	O
Caser	O
's	O
about	O
selling	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
contented	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
yet	O
from	O
Richard	O
Davis	O
;	O
But	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
too	O
since	O
she	O
spoke	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
found	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Dung	O
headless	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
(	O
one	O
Bisbop	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
missing	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Answer	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Livery	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
fetcht	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
another	O
;	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Dung	O
yet	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
rot	O
.	O
That	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Wheelbarrow	O
off	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Human	O
Skull	O
,	O
which	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
Terror	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Richard	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
pickt	O
clean	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Bone	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Hogs	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
With	O
this	O
Surprize	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
Richard	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Skull	O
upon	O
yonder	O
's	O
Dunghill	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
replied	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
found	O
the	O
Body	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
Livery	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Buckles	O
in	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
wear	O
Silver	O
ones	O
,	O
not	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Two	O
Women	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
remarkable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stript	O
off	O
the	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
which	O
were	O
upon	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
confirmed	O
much	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
missing	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
skull	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
Trial	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
stung	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
sensible	O
Remorse	O
of	O
his	O
crying	O
Guilt	O
,	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
look	O
his	O
Judge	O
nor	O
Jury	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
often	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
mov	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Sin	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
East	I-place
Bedford	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
1s.4	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Wild	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
haunted	O
the	O
Bushes	O
and	O
wild	O
Places	O
about	O
Kingston	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
a	O
Field-Gate	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Morton	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Kingston	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Mare	O
's	O
Bridle	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
Club	O
demanded	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Aspect	O
so	O
terrible	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
very	O
Thought	O
of	O
him	O
have	O
ever	O
since	O
made	O
her	O
tremble	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
the	O
16	O
d.	O
damning	O
her	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
followed	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
her	O
Mare	O
soal	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
durst	O
never	O
come	O
from	O
Market	O
alone	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
always	O
about	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
well	O
mounted	O
,	O
another	O
Evening	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
with	O
all	O
their	O
Speed	O
to	O
avoid	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
stifly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
depending	O
only	O
upon	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
Satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gualter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Moring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
a	O
Dust-basket	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
Sets	O
of	O
China	O
,	O
12	O
Silver-hasted	O
Knives	O
,	O
1	O
dozen	O
of	O
Table	O
cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
notorious	O
for	O
such	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Shepherd	O
impeach	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
proved	O
them	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
so	O
.	O
[	O
Allen	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Dunn	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Corny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Aug	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Evans	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Lame	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
;	O
who	O
demanded	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Wife	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
sign	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
Pickle	O
your	O
House	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
clean	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
fell	O
to	O
tumbling	O
his	O
Goods	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
might	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
nothing	O
fit	O
for	O
their	O
Purpose	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Spectacles	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
also	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
Goods	O
a	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
those	O
above	O
mentioned	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
seeing	O
them	O
with	O
each	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
their	O
Apron	O
,	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
