TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th,7th	O
,	O
and	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June,1717	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Montague	O
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Duman	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justies	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Court	I-pers
John	B-pers
Player	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
John	B-pers
Body	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Jof	B-pers
.	I-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
Natha	B-pers
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Exon	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Bruce	B-pers
Randel	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hicler	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Hector	B-pers
Machenzy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Beatknife	I-pers
George	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
Avon	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whiton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Skull	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ralph	B-pers
Barwood	I-pers
and	O
Gregory	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lock.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Overman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
stairs-head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
smiling	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
smile	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
perceiving	O
her	O
mistake	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
notice	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Rogues	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
or	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Kenny	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Workmen	O
)	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
out-cry	O
,	O
ran	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
seize	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
king	O
swore	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
be	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
touch	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
wounding	O
him	O
and	O
knocking	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
William	O
Kenny	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seizing	O
Freeman	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
struggled	O
together	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
snapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Picklock-keys	O
,	O
a	O
Betty	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
two	O
Bullets	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
so	O
behaved	O
themselves	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
appeared	O
to	O
their	O
reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Field	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Chalk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
.	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Emerald	O
Ring	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.2	O
Towels	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Francia	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Kath	O
Field	O
being	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Servant	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Field	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
in	O
her	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Emerald	O
Ring	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Katharine	O
Field	O
.	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
Ring	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
The	O
Towels	O
and	O
2	O
Plates	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Chalk	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Towels	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
Katharine	O
Field	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Shift	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
assist	O
Field	O
sometimes	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
Chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Plates	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
presence	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
probability	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val.6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
safer	O
keeping	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
her	O
over-care	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
val.15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
they	O
were	O
stollen	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
her	O
she	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Isaak	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
meets	O
four	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
immediately	O
stabbed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
cutting	O
through	O
the	O
folds	O
of	O
his	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
entring	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
they	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
save	O
them	O
,	O
received	O
another	O
stab	O
about	O
4	O
inches	O
deep	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
save	O
his	O
Hat	O
but	O
lost	O
his	O
Wig	O
;	O
whereupon	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
nigh	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
made	O
toward	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Jones	O
running	O
away	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
to	O
other	O
Watchmen	O
for	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Another	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Hosier-Lane	O
end	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
first	O
have	O
one	O
knock	O
at	O
his	O
Knapper	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
seeing	O
Ely	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
not	O
taking	O
him	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
securing	O
Jones	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
Secur	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
bloody	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
wherewith	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
stabbed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
against	O
Ely	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Arthur	B-pers
Key	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.3	O
Silver	O
Castors	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
,	O
3	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
161.	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stephens	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
secure	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
gone	O
when	O
she	O
rose	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Tho	O
Mills	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Evens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisadoes	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Glass	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Jones	O
who	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Evans	O
entred	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
Street-door	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
Jones	O
:	O
then	O
entring	O
a	O
Parlour	O
where	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
fast	O
asleep	O
.	O
himself	O
stood	O
over	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Evans	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
Baskets	O
;	O
then	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Plate	O
into	O
Bags	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Deborah	O
Stent	O
for	O
73	O
l.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
confirm	O
'd	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Common	O
Hunt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Coppers	O
and	O
an	O
Alembick	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
Tho	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
Tiles	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Coppers	O
were	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
fetching	O
them	O
away	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Jone	O
Revel	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lolly	B-pers
Arris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
val	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Coral	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.4	O
Gold	O
Rings,23	O
s	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baldock	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lidyard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
pretending	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
of	O
400	O
Tun	O
laden	O
with	O
Iron	O
and	O
Timber	O
from	O
Rotterdam	O
consign	O
'd	O
to	O
three	O
Merchants	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
enertain	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
after	O
Dinner	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
sleepy	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
and	O
was	O
accordingly	O
conducted	O
to	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
instead	O
of	O
lying	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
he	O
broke-open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
by	O
chance	O
taken	O
at	O
Depeford	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
Newgate	O
but	O
learn	O
'd	O
Roguery	O
enough	O
to	O
cook	O
up	O
a	O
Newgate	O
Defence	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Goods	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
upon	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Regard	O
to	O
it	O
than	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
serve	O
Clois	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
did	O
Cain	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Leith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
1/2	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
val.6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
stole	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Chair-man	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
curtains	O
were	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Sedan	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Seat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Masters	O
Coach	O
,	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
seat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
waking	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Cushion	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
and	O
stumbled	O
over	O
it	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Old	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews-Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Morgan	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
few	O
nights	O
before	O
seen	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
engaged	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bob	O
ken	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
a	O
house	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
)	O
whereupon	O
they	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
fath	O
and	O
took	O
3	O
Hats	O
that	O
hung	O
on	O
pegs	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
pleased	O
with	O
their	O
Success	O
,	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
attempt	O
to	O
steal	O
Mugs	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
:	O
but	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
wrung	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
ever	O
seen	O
his	O
old	O
Companion	O
Evans	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wadsworth	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
gowns	O
,	O
they	O
dogged	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Wadsworth	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Hambleton	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigail	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Pits	I-pers
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Fenchurch-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
knocked	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
stood	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
till	O
some	O
body	O
came	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
hugging	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
urged	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
for	O
her	O
advantage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
indeed	O
been	O
a	O
naughty	O
boy	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
bitting	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taking	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
mad	O
man	O
,	O
ran	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
into	O
a	O
Paltry-cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
43	O
yards	O
of	O
Poplin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Canlet	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
having	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Poplin	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Threadneedle-Street	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
like	O
a	O
Merchant	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
Yes	O
;	O
th	O
en	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
pence	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
serch	O
him	O
6	O
bottles	O
of	O
Wine.3	O
of	O
White	O
and	O
3	O
of	O
Red	O
;	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
trouble	O
some	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Poplin	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
hold	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
hold	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
strict	O
charge	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
neither	O
Stuff	O
nor	O
Man	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
inquiry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Poplin	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
some	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
insisting	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
used	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
depending	O
pretty	O
much	O
upon	O
the	O
Lad	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Writing-desk	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.3	O
Shop-books	O
;	O
val.20s.5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.12s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
val.1	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rocknel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
street-door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
while	O
a	O
person	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
serch	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Candle	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
into	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
,	O
the	O
Desk	O
and	O
Books	O
gone	O
.	O
Jane	O
Smallwead	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
small	O
Box	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Freedom	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
about	O
29	O
l.6	O
s.	O
)	O
bidding	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
to	O
keep	O
;	O
and	O
George	O
Clark	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Glenester	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
Oath	O
in	O
Court	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
and	O
George	O
Clark	O
had	O
a	O
prejudice	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
Smallwood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
Jane	O
Smallwood	O
threaten	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
Smallwood	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
and	O
Clark	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
Company-Keepers	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Smallwood	O
was	O
such	O
an	O
Adorer	O
of	O
the	O
Tallboy	O
Clark	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
if	O
an	O
Angel	O
should	O
descend	O
from	O
Heaven	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
prefer	O
Clark	O
before	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Starkey	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
sent	O
out	O
his	O
Servant-maid	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
locking	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
tampering	O
with	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
stepped	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Key	O
turn	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
hastily	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
walking	O
off	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
assisting	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
stollen	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
followed	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Seller	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Connyers	I-pers
,	O
or	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Murden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
alias	O
Fashion	B-pers
of	O
Chelsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Moise	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
34	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val.34	O
s	O
and	O
other	O
Milinary	O
Ware	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
brick	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
digged	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Parlour-window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
,	O
the	O
Gate-keeper	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
clapping	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
felt	O
the	O
Glove	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
true	O
Account	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
them	O
being	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Depsford	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Ratcliff	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Bundle	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Direction	O
upon	O
a	O
paper	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Mrs.	O
Moise	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
likewise	O
when	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
which	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
her	O
Counter	O
Cloth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
5	O
days	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Draws	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
doing	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fordam	I-pers
.	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	O
Hammond	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
Aprons	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
18	O
Periwigs	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Stalls	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
out	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
it	O
then	O
growing	O
light	O
,	O
the	O
Beef	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
carrying	O
off	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
.	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Berryman	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
hurry	O
of	O
Coaches	O
and	O
Carts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
likewise	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
killed	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Eunuch	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Callico	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
purse,1	O
d.	O
and	O
40	O
s.6	O
d	O
in	O
money	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
postern	O
at	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
under	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turning	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
porch	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
she	O
persuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reuse	O
.	O
Mr.Reuse	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
locking	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
Masters	O
side	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
.	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
middle	O
porch	O
into	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
several	O
persons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Whitmash	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
saw	O
some	O
Persons	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Cloths	O
dropping	O
some	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
following	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
some	O
persons	O
sent	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
and	O
so	O
missed	O
apprehending	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawk	I-pers
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Godwin	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blewcoat	B-pers
Jemmy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Snubnosed	B-pers
Jemmy	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
;	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wethered	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
he	O
employed	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Wethered	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Burieigh	I-pers
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
Money	O
and	O
Silk	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Godfrey	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Picklock-key	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Desk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
hard	O
by	O
while	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
threatning	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
quickly	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
him	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.Burieigh	O
(	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
William	O
Burleigh	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
whereas	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
also	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Thomes	O
Wethered	O
as	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Gloucester	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
before	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Badrick	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
Letters	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
Deposnions	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
;	O
alledged	O
that	O
not	O
only	O
by	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
other	O
cases	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
so	O
demeaned	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
having	O
accused	O
her	O
Son	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
shoar	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Letitia	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
val.20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Ruby	O
,	O
val	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wise	O
deposed	O
,	O
her	O
Room	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Letitia	O
White	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
there	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
Jobn	B-pers
Hendon	I-pers
Brother-in-law	O
to	O
Letitia	O
White	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
That	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
2	O
Locks	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
36	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
it	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
himself	O
had	O
the	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
in	O
Bernards-Inn	B-place
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Harris	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Ann	O
Steed	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Moulding	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
almost	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
running	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
enquiting	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
.	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
Harris	O
give	O
a	O
Hum	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Steed	O
notice	O
of	O
somebody	O
coming	O
)	O
he	O
seized	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	O
Steed	O
dropped	O
an	O
Iron	O
.	O
Chissel	O
upon	O
his	O
seizing	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
shelter	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
Rain	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
Ann	O
Steed	O
,	O
she	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
using	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cloak	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
revenge	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Chissel	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Frock	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Chissel	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
However	O
these	O
pretences	O
did	O
not	O
hinder	O
the	O
Jury	O
from	O
finding	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
Soap	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
over-persuaded	O
by	O
another	O
woman	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
follow	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
doors	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
opening	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
loose	O
Life	O
,	O
examined	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
gave	O
him	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
promising	O
her	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
while	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
this	O
Plea	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Dram-cup	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ken	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pendry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
and	O
a	O
Periwig	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
tripped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
Outcry	O
he	O
made	O
toward	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
toward	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
halted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Chair-man	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Chair-man	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berryman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	B-place
out	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
to	O
turn	O
his	O
Dray	O
drawn	O
by	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dray	O
ran	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breech	O
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
ran	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
;	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
crush	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
spoured	O
out	O
like	O
as	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
Carelesness	O
and	O
hafty	O
turning	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
only	O
be	O
Spectators	O
of	O
that	O
dismal	O
Sight	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
the	O
poor	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
hard	O
of	O
Hearing	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
body	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Zachary	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Jew	O
)	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
having	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
change	O
and	O
he	O
changed	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
before	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
her	O
hands	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
replyed	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
13	O
s.6	O
d.	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
Master	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
Change	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
not	O
having	O
Silver	O
enough	O
,	O
thought	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
changed	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
Master	O
neverthess	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
change	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
spend	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
private	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
off	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Beger	O
's	O
,	O
buying	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
upon	O
his	O
knee	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
walking	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
immediately	O
he	O
knocked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
quarters	O
,	O
having	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
sick	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
wet	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
his	O
knee	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
fit	O
;	O
them	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
sold	O
no	O
better	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
sold	O
no	O
Solder	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
force	O
got	O
down	O
when	O
he	O
knocked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
not	O
gone	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
from	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
l	O
am	O
bere	O
;	O
she	O
goes	O
up	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
his	O
Dear	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
liked	O
to	O
fit	O
there	O
better	O
,	O
being	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
airy	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
forced	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
rescued	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
pine	O
of	O
Sider	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
mighty	O
struggling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
i	O
'll	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
whereupon	O
fearing	O
he	O
would	O
hurt	O
her	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
disputing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
kicked	O
him	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
calling	O
him	O
names	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
wounded	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Penknife	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
recover	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
flung	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
master	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
flew	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Devil	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Devil	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
Devi	O
should	O
carry	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
names	O
in	O
his	O
language	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
English	O
Dogs	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
tongue	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbing	O
him	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Several	O
persons	O
apeared	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
this	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Relation	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
,	O
her	O
Parents	O
upon	O
his	O
request	O
let	O
her	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
,	O
honest	O
Girl	O
and	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
therefore	O
appearing	O
a'prosecution	O
malicious	O
and	O
vilainous	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Liecester	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
him	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
running	O
a	O
Truck	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Truck	O
threw	O
him	O
suddenly	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cart	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
sudden	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
alias	O
Old	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val.48	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Socks	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bob	O
ken	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
House	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
)	O
so	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stens	I-pers
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
Hang	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
made	O
himself	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
and	O
always	O
came	O
off	O
for	O
all	O
their	O
Evidences	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
now	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
alias	O
Browne	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Bag	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
61.3	O
Coats,3	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Meswin	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Row	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
5	O
Dowlas	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val.18	O
s.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Industry	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
villanous	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Sen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
wooden	O
Boxes	O
containing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Boxes	O
into	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
Hill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	B-place
Tavern	I-place
for	O
2	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Red	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
White	O
that	O
he	O
for	O
the	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Mark	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Husband	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Smith	O
)	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Mill	O
at	O
Bromly	B-place
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Stepney	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Dirch	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
excuse	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20	O
of	O
January	O
1715	O
.	O
and	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val.24	O
s.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Year	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
entrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Fellow-servant	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Masters	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
to	O
keep	O
in	O
Secrecy	O
,	O
swearing	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bible	O
not	O
to	O
divulge	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Butcher	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
to	O
convert	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
(	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Cole	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
pilser	O
and	O
purloin	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
resided	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
proved	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Suit	O
in	O
Law	O
depending	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
Marshal	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
for	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Fidelity	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
near	O
the	B-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.73	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Twenty-shilling	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chase	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Barber	O
rented	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	O
Bethel	O
,	O
Seafaring	O
Men	O
,	O
likewise	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
John	O
Hawks	O
and	O
Matthew	O
Bethel	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
East	O
Ham	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
lay	O
that	O
night	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
That	O
hearing	O
that	O
Hawks	O
and	O
Bethel	O
were	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
got	O
them	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assisting	O
her	O
in	O
their	O
apprehension	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
Wigs	O
also	O
(	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
not	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
but	O
hearing	O
some	O
things	O
relating	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
more	O
expensive	O
rate	O
than	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
Money	O
more	O
plenty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
about	O
buying	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Considerable	O
value	O
,	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
pretty	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
certainly	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
again	O
in	O
8	O
days	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
satisfie	O
for	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
70	O
l.	O
upon	O
a	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
,	O
Shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Attorney	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
notice	O
was	O
without	O
Seal	O
and	O
this	O
made	O
her	O
the	O
more	O
suspicious	O
of	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
certainly	O
have	O
her	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
8	O
days	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
a	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
Letter	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
signifying	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
directed	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
near	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
stopped	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Plate	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
a	O
scrap	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
Sara	B-pers
Long	I-pers
's	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
Who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Long	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
keeping	O
the	O
Porter	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
said	O
positively	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Letter	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
the	O
Porter	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
undone	O
;	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Book	O
to	O
reckon	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
some	O
accounts	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
confirmation	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
circumstances	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
swore	O
positively	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
called	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Griffin	O
Tavern-door	O
in	O
Leaderball	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
hasre	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
sent	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
talked	O
with	O
John	O
Morrice	O
the	O
Portor	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
trouble	O
in	O
Mind	O
in	O
swearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
either	O
knowing	O
or	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
falsely	O
,	O
wishing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
compell	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
John	O
Morrice	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
so	O
troublesome	O
an	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
detected	O
a	O
Rogue	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
also	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
tender-spirited	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
Villany	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
produced	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
Money	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
contriving	O
,	O
counselling	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
in	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Post-boy	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
Strawberry	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
;	O
4	O
Mails	O
val.8	O
l.	O
and	O
50	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
Holiday	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
performed	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
his	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Allegation	O
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
fulfilled	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
his	O
Pardon	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Court	O
accepted	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Legal	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Whereupon	O
William	O
Holiday	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
him	O
first	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Williams	O
and	O
Chessey	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
recommended	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
stout	O
Fellows	O
,	O
fit	O
to	O
undertake	O
any	O
bold	O
Enterprize	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
projected	O
the	O
robbing	O
of	O
the	O
Bost-boy	O
,	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
procure	O
horses	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Design	O
in	O
execution	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
likewise	O
he	O
would	O
borrow	O
Pistols	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
them	O
Bags	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Letters	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
6	O
Guineas	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Chessey	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
who	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Mary	O
Holiday	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Smith	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
direct	O
her	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Smith	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
underst	O
,	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
her	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
dressed	O
himself	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Chessey	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Portes	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
was	O
angry	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
sent	O
home	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
to	O
seed	O
the	O
Horses	O
home	O
,	O
left	O
by	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
betray	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
no	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
scandalous	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
would	O
soon	O
be	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
Chessey	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
an	O
like	O
frighted	O
men	O
,	O
busie	O
in	O
opening	O
Letters	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
Smith	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Williams	O
reply	O
'd	O
Why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
Williams	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
A	O
-	O
him	O
!	O
What	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
put	O
us	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
now	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
her	O
,	O
taken	O
the	O
Mail	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Consequence	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Advantage	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
5	O
or	O
6000	O
l.	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
uneasy	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
need	O
you	O
be	O
uneasy	O
?	O
You	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
.	O
She	O
depos	O
'd	O
likewise	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
preposed	O
they	O
should	O
carry	O
the	O
Letters	O
into	O
some	O
empty	O
House	O
to	O
open	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
attend	O
that	O
Day	O
because	O
he	O
most	O
attend	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
look	O
upon	O
a	O
Note	O
which	O
she	O
describ	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Chequer-Note	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Paper	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
likewise	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
that	O
too	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Holliday	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Holiday	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
one	O
in	O
every	O
place	O
to	O
swear	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
related	O
to	O
Evidence	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
Evidences	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
entirely	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Holliday	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
and	O
had	O
Evidence	O
at	O
hand	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
draw	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Westminister-Hall	O
at	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
an	O
Improvement	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Persons	O
were	O
not	O
produced	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
hired	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
Improbability	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
engage	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Design	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
fact	O
by	O
some	O
Adversaries	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
suing	O
as	O
Creditor	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
statute	O
of	O
Bankruptcy	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Little	I-pers
;	O
not	O
was	O
he	O
destitude	O
of	O
Evidences	O
who	O
deposed	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
making	O
that	O
appear	O
planfible	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
being	O
thus	O
intricated	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Creditors	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Little	I-pers
of	O
their	O
Mony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
try	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ricard	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hiller	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
(	O
commonly	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Evidence	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Lieutenant	O
Governour	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
defrauding	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
18	O
l.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
Store-keeper	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Henry	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
of	O
40	O
l.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
making	O
him	O
a	O
Searcher	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Customs	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
Tryal	O
was	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Nath	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Applebee	I-pers
,	O
Printers	O
of	O
the	O
Weekly	O
Journals	O
,	O
were	O
summon	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
reprimanded	O
for	O
presuming	O
to	O
print	O
Abstracts	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayley	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
like	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
for	O
such	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
be	O
proceeded	O
against	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,8	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
alias	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
alias	O
Skull	O
Dean	O
,	O
Gregory	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Eunuch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Connyers	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
alias	O
Old	O
Harry	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,11	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tew	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Berryman	I-pers
,	O
Letice	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Lolly	B-pers
Arris	I-pers
,	O
B	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	O
Hammond	O
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,9	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
6	O
s.8	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Connyers	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannel	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKs	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
is	O
Lombard	O
Sccoet	O
,	O
near	O
Stock	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuative	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Medications	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Christian	O
's	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Eraf	O
,	O
now	O
render	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Gaines	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Warrew	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	O
D.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Clarlton	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Athnetick	O
made	O
case	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinet	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
4th	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Feremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
;	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
Use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
lage	O
in	O
Cours	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samual	O
The	O
while	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
30	O
Copper-Plates	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Protestant	O
on	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
main	O
Principles	O
of	O
Religion	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Diffenters	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Articles	O
and	O
Homilies	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England,8	O
c.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Micheal	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Jordeine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetic	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Sabtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Daodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
facts	O
of	O
Sopersicies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Gloss	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
,	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Guaging	O
of	O
all	O
forts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
forts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Basie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity.8	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
THE	O
most	O
excellent	O
BALSAMICK	O
WATER	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
greatest	O
Preservative	O
of	O
Health	O
in	O
Nature	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
50	O
Years	O
Study	O
of	O
Physick	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
needs	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
in	O
its	O
Commendation	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
recommend	O
it	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Interest	O
in	O
making	O
of	O
it	O
Publick	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
general	O
Good	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
die	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
(	O
like	O
the	O
English	O
Quack	O
)	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
cures	O
all	O
Distempers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
infalbibly	O
keeps	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
defends	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
infections	O
Airs	O
and	O
distempers	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
3	O
Spoonfuls	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Pinc	O
of	O
warm	O
Ale	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Liquid	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
or	O
Sex	O
soever	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
Consinement	O
or	O
Hinderance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
printed	O
Directions	O
given	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
prevents	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
and	O
cures	O
them	O
it	O
not	O
too	O
far	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
relieves	O
the	O
Tiffick	O
and	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breat	O
;	O
cures	O
in	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
it	O
all	O
ctions	O
,	O
and	O
intallibly	O
all	O
forts	O
or	O
Warms	O
in	O
Young	O
or	O
Old	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Yellow	O
and	O
Black	O
dice	O
,	O
pecty	O
,	O
ltch	O
,	O
and	O
Scald	O
Heads	O
.	O
It	O
certainly	O
eradicates	O
that	O
reigning	O
Distemper	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
;	O
chears	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Appetite	O
.	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
all	O
Child-bearing	O
Women	O
,	O
it	O
preserving	O
the	O
Insant	O
from	O
those	O
Infirmitics	O
that	O
Children	O
are	O
generally	O
affected	O
with	O
,	O
par	O
the	O
whole	O
Mass	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
renders	O
the	O
Skin	O
beautiful	O
and	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
causes	O
easy	O
Delivery	O
.	O
Likewise	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
Sea-faring	O
Men	O
that	O
Trade	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
or	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
Countries	O
where	O
Fevers	O
or	O
the	O
Plagne	O
are	O
infections	O
.	O
When	O
all	O
other	O
Remedies	O
fail	O
,	O
this	O
excellent	O
Balsastick	O
Water	O
drives	O
out	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
or	O
Measles	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Stomach	O
or	O
Throat	O
,	O
preventing	O
that	O
Soreness	O
which	O
generally	O
accompanies	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
in	O
that	O
Distemper	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
prevents	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
infections	O
Distemper	O
,	O
from	O
Spreading	O
in	O
a	O
Family	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
excellent	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
after	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
,	O
far	O
exceeding	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
it	O
discharges	O
the	O
Body	O
from	O
the	O
Imparity	O
of	O
bad	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanses	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
Scorbutick	O
Spots	O
,	O
Scane	O
,	O
oritoyls	O
,	O
by	O
bathing	O
outwardly	O
;	O
and	O
cures	O
all	O
Old	O
Sures	O
and	O
Green	O
Wounds	O
,	O
by	O
washing	O
the	O
Place	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
fore	O
Mouths	O
caused	O
by	O
inward	O
Heat	O
or	O
Canker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
causing	O
them	O
to	O
pas	O
.	O
and	O
evacuate	O
whatever	O
Humours	O
offend	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
is	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
half	O
Pint	O
Bottles	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
at	O
large	O
for	O
the	O
Taking	O
and	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
close	O
Stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
retains	O
its	O
Virtue	O
in	O
all	O
Climates	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
older	O
it	O
grows	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
It	O
generally	O
gives	O
one	O
Stool	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
off	O
by	O
Urine	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsa	O
Water	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Counterseits	O
,	O
is	O
sold	O
only	O
at	O
Mr.	O
ker	O
's	O
,	O
Book-seller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
a	O
Lin	O
and	O
Dagger	O
.	O
Perform	O
'd	O
by	O
HENDRICK	O
VANDOR	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
here	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
times	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
gives	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occation	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-Makers	O
,	O
near	O
Excter	O
Excharge	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bast	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Subarbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
I	O
Testify	O
that	O
my	O
Child	O
was	O
so	O
troubled	O
with	O
Fifts	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
hard	O
Breeding	O
of	O
its	O
Teeth	O
,	O
that	O
its	O
Life	O
was	O
desair	O
'd	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
only	O
wearing	O
the	O
Celebrated	O
NECKLACE	O
recommended	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
for	O
Children	O
's	O
Teeth	O
,	O
it	O
presently	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
its	O
Life	O
,	O
never	O
having	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
One	O
Fit	O
after	O
the	O
Necklace	O
was	O
bung	O
about	O
its	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
worn	O
the	O
Necklace	O
now	O
about	O
9	O
Months	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
should	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
other	O
Children	O
.	O
Job	O
Hodkinson	O
,	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Flower	B-pers
Pot	I-pers
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
in	O
the	O
Lower	O
Street	O
in	O
lstington	O
.	O
This	O
Admirable	O
Anodyne	O
NECKLACE	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
Directions	O
in	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
for	O
wearing	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
Only	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
this	O
Necklace	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Key	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
a	O
Toyshop	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
At	O
which	O
Places	O
is	O
given	O
Gratis	O
,	O
The	O
19th	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
Secrets	O
Injuries	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitations	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
,	O
and	O
Mercury	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Philosophical	O
ESSAY	O
,	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Society	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
admirable	O
Necklace	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenoar	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Back	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
old	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lame.1717	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
