TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
JULY,1717	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencoe	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Bezaleel	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Merryweather	I-pers
William	B-pers
Marsland	I-pers
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
East	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Nightingal	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cossey	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tant	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
George	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kinch	I-pers
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ann	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Damask	O
Tabie-Cloths	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
val.7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Bennet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
within	O
his	O
Study	O
at	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
coming	O
out	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
covered	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
beg	O
some	O
Small	O
Beer	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
thinking	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
bold	O
Beggar	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
into	O
his	O
Study	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
her	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Pocket	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
full	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
to	O
be	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
down	O
in	O
an	O
Entry	O
between	O
the	O
Study	O
and	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
under	O
his	O
Feet	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
was	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Study	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
Shavings	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Workmen	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Fact	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
22	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Shoes	O
away	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
having	O
several	O
times	O
missed	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Intimations	O
given	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
some	O
Difficulty	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
owned	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.1	O
Hat	O
,	O
val.3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Holms	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
and	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Time	O
specified	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Act	O
of	O
Indemnity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shakleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
4	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
bringing	O
him	O
a	O
Pattern	O
to	O
match	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
difficult	O
in	O
the	O
matching	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Shalloon	O
she	O
bought	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
convey	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
under	O
her	O
Clothes	O
and	O
suffer	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
they	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Shalloon	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
Knew	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
infinuating	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Contrivance	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
Reward	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
appeared	O
so	O
little	O
Probability	O
in	O
this	O
Pretence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
by	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,1	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
black	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Seager	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Hood	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
Fellow-Traders	O
in	O
Iniquity	O
,	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
slender	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.1	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
val.6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
bent	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Pretence	O
did	O
him	O
that	O
Service	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Measure	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Four	O
Pence	O
Halfpenny	O
in	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
the	O
same	O
Days	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
feil	O
a	O
Brass-Candlestick	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
while	O
his	O
Servant	O
was	O
calling	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
Measure	O
to	O
bulge	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Halfpence	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Colcot	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
late	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
stollen	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Minn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted-Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.9	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
one	O
Pair	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Shortness	O
of	O
his	O
Memory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
14	O
Pound	O
of	O
Solder	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Solder	O
to	O
one	O
Orrel	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
depending	O
on	O
the	O
single	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wetherbone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Michael	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Matthew	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
having	O
stollen	O
3	O
Wiggs	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
good	O
,	O
where	O
spying	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
unbolted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Family	O
had	O
not	O
bolted	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Barker	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
Gammon	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
to	O
watch	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
to	O
surprize	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
Gardiner	O
's	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.1	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.1	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
28	O
the	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
the	O
Sashes	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
gotten	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
accordingly	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
one	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
China	O
Bason	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
brush	O
'd	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
James	O
Evans	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Ann	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Moidores,4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
one	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
recommended	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Servant	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	O
Dunn	O
;	O
That	O
coming	O
about	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
set	O
her	O
to	O
dusting	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
;	O
That	O
about	O
11	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
her	O
out	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Half-pennyworth	O
of	O
Currants	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
had	O
been	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
furnished	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Ann	O
Dunn	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
good	O
and	O
honest	O
Servant	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Recommendation	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
spent	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
raise	O
10	O
l.	O
by	O
nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
signified	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Injury	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
such	O
Offer	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
seeming	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
Wife	O
Blood	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
great	O
Hurt	O
on	O
her	O
Belly	O
near	O
her	O
Navel	O
by	O
a	O
Coach-pole	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
permit	O
none	O
to	O
bleed	O
her	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Wigs	O
were	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Shop	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
while	O
the	O
Servant	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
look	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
leaving	O
Word	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Star	O
Inn	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Master	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
thither	O
to	O
bleed	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
deposed	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Star	O
Inn	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Trick	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
found	O
the	O
Wiggs	O
were	O
stollen	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Servant	O
describing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Wiggs	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
nevertheless	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Flower-pot	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Flower-Pot	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
and	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
some	O
Rags	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Flower-pot	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
:	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
fortunate	O
in	O
buying	O
such	O
good	O
Bargains	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
lucky	O
to	O
escape	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
alias	O
Cobler	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
in	O
September	O
last	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.2	O
Leather	O
Jacks	O
tipped	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
by	O
lifting	O
up	O
a	O
Sash	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Hats	O
and	O
Gloves	O
from	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Jacks	O
were	O
stollen	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
to	O
corroborate	O
Evans	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
single	O
Felony	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replyed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
sick	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
vomit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
immedietely	O
after	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
missing	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took'em	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
so	O
sick	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
own	O
from	O
other	O
Peoples	O
,	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
enough	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Sturmey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
10	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beachfield	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hasle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard-Infant	O
,	O
by	O
drowning	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
seeing	O
some	O
suspicious	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
Delivery	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
searched	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Child	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
Tokens	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Matter	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
pressing	O
her	O
more	O
closely	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Copper	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
in	O
a	O
Copper	O
wherein	O
was	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Pails	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pails	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Copper	O
.	O
A	O
Midwife	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
;	O
That	O
examining	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
its	O
Birth	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
spread	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
lean	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
asleep	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Quaker	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
lay	O
about	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
down	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
Marks	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
of	O
its	O
having	O
been	O
hurt	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
blackishCircle	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Mouth	O
(	O
which	O
a	O
Midwife	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
was	O
usual	O
to	O
such	O
Infants	O
,	O
tho'dying	O
by	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
better	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
clandestine	O
Births	O
and	O
concealing	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Bastard-Children	O
,	O
which	O
enacted	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
concealing	O
the	O
Birth	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
Bastard-Children	O
should	O
make	O
the	O
Mothers	O
deem	O
'd	O
the	O
Murtherers	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Reach	O
of	O
this	O
Act	O
,	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Conception	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
,	O
who	O
died	O
same	O
time	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Wingate	O
at	O
Enfield	O
Church	O
.	O
And	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Wingate	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
expressed	O
his	O
Concern	O
in	O
leaving	O
her	O
six	O
Weeks	O
gone	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Tho'in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sister	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
ever	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Evidence	O
prevailing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
deemed	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
affected	O
by	O
that	O
Statute	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
then	O
turning	O
on	O
another	O
Hinge	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Business	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
murthered	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
neither	O
perceived	O
it	O
to	O
stir	O
nor	O
heard	O
it	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
she	O
provided	O
for	O
her	O
Delivery	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
deposed	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
three	O
Months	O
since	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Nurse	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Months	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
July	O
or	O
beginning	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
chief	O
Stress	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
then	O
being	O
whether	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
murthered	O
by	O
her	O
before	O
putting	O
into	O
the	O
Copper	O
,	O
or	O
alive	O
when	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Evidences	O
generally	O
agreed	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
visible	O
Tokens	O
of	O
any	O
Violence	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Infant	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
the	O
Judge	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
alive	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
testified	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
its	O
being	O
opened	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Water	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
Opinion	O
on	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Opinion	O
,	O
deposing	O
upon	O
Oath	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
no	O
human	O
Body	O
could	O
be	O
drowned	O
without	O
receiving	O
some	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Water	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
the	O
Child	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
alive	O
when	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Copper	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
thus	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
either	O
murthered	O
the	O
Infant	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
so	O
unaccountably	O
inhuman	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
but	O
little	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Lapparelle	I-pers
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	B-place
near	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Ax	I-place
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
hugg	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
pointed	O
to	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
she	O
was	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
missed	O
that	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
therefore	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
found	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Pockets	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chintz	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
a	O
Sarsenet-Hood	O
,	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
dress	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
she	O
perceived	O
something	O
to	O
move	O
the	O
Bedcloaths	O
;	O
so	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
unlock	O
'd	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
searching	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
over	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
before	O
mention	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
moved	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Places	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
till	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
behind	O
some	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
found	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Sarsenet-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Madam	O
Hadley	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
hide	O
herself	O
from	O
some	O
Officers	O
she	O
saw	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
arrested	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
indeed	O
appeared	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Madam	O
Hadley	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Plimouth	O
,	O
or	O
somewhere	O
by	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
escape	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tennier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Stamford	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Motley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
provided	O
by	O
his	O
Gang	O
with	O
a	O
Ladder	O
and	O
Rope	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
her	O
Casement-Window	O
when	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
Bar	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
interrupt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stollen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Window	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Rope	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Motley	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Shirts	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Court	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
testified	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shirts	O
and	O
10	O
s.6	O
d.	O
but	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
skreen	O
'd	O
her	O
Daughter	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
an	O
adulterous	O
manner	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Motley	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
ruined	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
thrown	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
with	O
a	O
sham	O
Action	O
,	O
kept	O
him	O
there	O
16	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
they	O
knew	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
60	O
l.	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Motley	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
all	O
away	O
and	O
ruined	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
left	O
6	O
good	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
he	O
carried	O
away	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
amply	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
this	O
privately	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
Scores	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	O
Motley	O
had	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
beaten	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Motley	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
but	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
own	O
Bed	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Others	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
most	O
abused	O
that	O
any	O
Man	O
was	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
courted	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
had	O
refused	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
had	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
send	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
detained	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
Proof	O
sufficient	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
alias	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mathers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
9	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.4	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	O
Thompson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
near	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
Twopence	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Tavern	O
hard	O
by	O
(	O
the	O
Name	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
Sixpence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
deliver	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
his	O
young	O
Mistress	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
hold	O
his	O
Linnen	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
carrying	O
the	O
Ring	O
upon	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
Way	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
over	O
against	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
took	O
his	O
Linnen	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunder	I-pers
's	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
along	O
seeing	O
the	O
Boy	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
Linnen	O
,	O
espied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seised	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Linnen	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
then	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Lucia	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cossoy	O
Chariot-Seats	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
espied	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Footman	O
,	O
who	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Footman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
leaving	O
one	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
throwing	O
down	O
the	O
Seat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
he	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
instead	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
unhappy	O
Mistake	O
is	O
like	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
an	O
ill-favour	O
'd	O
Dance	O
after	O
the	O
Cart	O
's	O
Arse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ashbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Justice	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
lurking	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
Cow	O
Yard	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
suspecting	O
them	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Landry-yard	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
from	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
Notice	O
sent	O
a	O
Servant	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Hay-stack	O
,	O
finding	O
themselves	O
pursued	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-stack	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pond	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
27	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.36	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rebow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
Footboy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Footman	O
to	O
Sir	O
Isaac	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
another	O
Cabinet	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
supposed	O
about	O
half	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Cabinet	O
and	O
Chest	O
he	O
took	O
about	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
Silk	O
and	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
.	O
Sir	O
Isaac	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
near	O
Colchester	O
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
sending	O
him	O
word	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Thieves	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Chimney	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
Footboy	O
he	O
disclos	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
had	O
again	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
it	O
partly	O
on	O
Robert	O
Brown	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
as	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
excuse	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sugar-dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rebow	I-pers
in	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
by	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Edminton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
13	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
This	O
did	O
not	O
excuse	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Aleworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Maribone	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.6	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
coming	O
within	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Herbert	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
one	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
probable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cassels	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
pleaded	O
a	O
Boy	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Distress	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
something	O
for	O
her	O
pains	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Scyas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
val.20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
a	O
Woman	O
bid	O
her	O
stay	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
suffice	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
three	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
Six	O
Napkins	O
,	O
val.6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Labbatosh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
four	O
Persons	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Dean-street	B-place
going	O
into	O
Tybourn	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Santeloe	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	O
Santeloe	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Person	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
the	O
principal	O
Criminal	O
on	O
whom	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
thinking	O
fit	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
his	O
single	O
Testimony	O
,	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Buttolph	O
's	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
alive	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
commonly	B-pers
known	I-pers
by	I-pers
the	I-pers
Name	I-pers
of	I-pers
Evidence	I-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
or	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
stiles	O
himself	O
)	O
Colonel	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
not	O
try	O
'd	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
expected	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
notorious	O
Cheats	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
is	O
continued	O
in	O
Newgate	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
contriving	O
and	O
abetting	O
Williams	O
and	O
Chessey	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
this	O
Sessions	O
for	O
a	O
Forgery	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
several	O
material	O
Evidences	O
for	O
him	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
them	O
,	O
desiring	O
therefore	O
his	O
Tryal	O
might	O
be	O
deferred	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
knowing	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Forgery	O
,	O
had	O
come	O
twice	O
from	O
Salisbury	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
considerable	O
Charge	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Evidences	O
ready	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bringing	O
Proof	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
material	O
Evidence	O
was	O
in	O
Town	O
but	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
serv	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
the	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Expenses	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
in	O
attending	O
two	O
Sessions	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
satisfactory	O
Bail	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
Tryals	O
were	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
seeing	O
through	O
the	O
Shuffle	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
trick	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
trick	O
'd	O
himself	O
the	O
next	O
way	O
into	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Panton	B-pers
the	I-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
uttering	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
light	O
Gaineas	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
filed	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Tryal	O
suspended	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
Surrey	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,4	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
alias	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
James	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ann	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,3	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Lucia	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,11	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Minn	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ashbrook	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Scias	I-pers
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By-Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
keep	O
and	O
drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
publish	O
'd	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
John	O
Way	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Sutton	O
,	O
More	O
Molineux	O
,	O
Cha	O
.	O
Barnard	O
,	O
J	O
.	O
Idle	O
.	O
Allow	O
'd	O
and	O
approv	O
'd	O
by	O
Cowper	O
,	O
C.	O
Parker	O
,	O
P.	O
King	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Bury	O
,	O
Note	O
,	O
These	O
Orders	O
,	O
By-Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinance	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
Force	O
the	O
Four	O
and	O
Twentieth	O
Day	O
of	O
June,1717	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
4th	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Christian	O
's	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Erasmus	O
,	O
now	O
render	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
Funerals	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Guines	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Charlton	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
;	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
Use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
lage	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
30	O
Copper-Plates	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Protestant	O
Union	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
main	O
Principles	O
of	O
Religion	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Articles	O
and	O
Homilies	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Ec	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Jordaine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Superficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Guaging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity.8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Ingenious	O
and	O
Useful	O
Art	O
of	O
writing	O
Short	O
hand	O
.	O
Containing	O
Twenty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
(	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life-time	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Scholars	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
Characters	O
and	O
Contractions	O
used	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
and	O
Directions	O
explaining	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Whereunto	O
are	O
added	O
Law-terms	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Discourses	O
as	O
on	O
War	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Binds	O
,	O
Beasts	O
,	O
Fruits	O
,	O
Vermin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Omega	O
:	O
A	O
Poem	O
on	O
the	O
Last	O
judgement	O
.	O
In	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
d.	O
WE	O
Charles	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keep	O
the	O
Derby	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
White-horse-yard	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
do	O
hereby	O
affirm	O
,	O
that	O
our	O
Child	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
its	O
Teeth	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
and	O
expected	O
in	O
Sorrow	O
and	O
Tears	O
)	O
ready	O
to	O
expire	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
ANODINE	O
NECKLACE	O
,	O
Recommended	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
,	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Key	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
about	O
its	O
Neck	O
:	O
It	O
had	O
not	O
wore	O
it	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
his	O
Feet	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
great	O
Amazement	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
ever	O
since	O
so	O
visibly	O
recover	O
'd	O
and	O
thriv	O
'd	O
that	O
thro	O
'	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
brave	O
healthy	O
lusty	O
Boy	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
satisfy	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
desires	O
it	O
.	O
July	O
16,1717	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
comeat	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
gives	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-Makers	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
THE	O
most	O
excellent	O
BALSAMICK	O
WATER	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
greatest	O
Preservative	O
of	O
Health	O
in	O
Nature	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
50	O
Years	O
Study	O
of	O
Physick	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
needs	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
in	O
its	O
Commendation	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
recommend	O
it	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Interest	O
in	O
making	O
of	O
it	O
Publick	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
general	O
Good	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
die	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
(	O
like	O
the	O
English	O
Quack	O
)	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
cures	O
all	O
Distempers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
infallibly	O
keeps	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
defends	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
infections	O
Airs	O
and	O
distempers	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
3	O
Spoonfuls	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
warm	O
Ale	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Liquid	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
or	O
Sex	O
soever	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
Consinement	O
or	O
Hinderance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
printed	O
Directions	O
given	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
prevents	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
and	O
cures	O
them	O
if	O
not	O
too	O
far	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
relieves	O
she	O
Tissick	O
and	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breath	O
;	O
cures	O
Ulcers	O
in	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
it	O
opens	O
all	O
Obstructions	O
,	O
and	O
infallibly	O
destroys	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Worms	O
in	O
Young	O
or	O
Old	O
.	O
It	O
cares	O
the	O
Yellow	O
and	O
Black	O
Jaundice	O
,	O
Leprosy	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
and	O
Scald	O
Heads	O
.	O
It	O
certainly	O
eradicates	O
that	O
reigning	O
Distemper	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
;	O
chears	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Appetite	O
.	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
all	O
Child-bearing	O
Women	O
,	O
it	O
preserving	O
the	O
Infant	O
from	O
those	O
Infirmities	O
that	O
Children	O
are	O
generally	O
afflicted	O
with	O
,	O
purifies	O
the	O
whole	O
Mass	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
renders	O
the	O
Skin	O
beautiful	O
and	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
causes	O
easy	O
Delivery	O
.	O
Likewise	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
Sea-faring	O
Men	O
that	O
Trade	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
or	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
Countries	O
where	O
Fevers	O
or	O
the	O
Piague	O
are	O
infections	O
.	O
When	O
all	O
other	O
Remedies	O
fail	O
,	O
this	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
drives	O
out	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
or	O
Measles	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Stomach	O
or	O
Throat	O
,	O
preventing	O
that	O
Soreness	O
which	O
generally	O
accompanies	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
in	O
that	O
Distemper	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
prevents	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
infections	O
Distemper	O
,	O
from	O
spreading	O
in	O
a	O
Family	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
excellent	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
after	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
,	O
far	O
exceeding	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
it	O
discharges	O
the	O
Body	O
from	O
the	O
Impurity	O
of	O
bad	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanses	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
Scorbutick	O
Spots	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
or	O
Boyls	O
,	O
by	O
bathing	O
outwardly	O
;	O
and	O
cures	O
all	O
Old	O
Sores	O
and	O
Green	O
Wounds	O
,	O
by	O
washing	O
the	O
Place	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
sore	O
Mouths	O
caused	O
by	O
inward	O
Heat	O
or	O
Canker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
causing	O
them	O
to	O
pass	O
and	O
evacuate	O
whatever	O
Humours	O
offend	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
is	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
half	O
Pint	O
Bottles	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
at	O
large	O
for	O
the	O
Taking	O
and	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
close	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
retains	O
its	O
Virtue	O
in	O
all	O
Climates	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
older	O
it	O
grows	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
It	O
generally	O
gives	O
one	O
Stool	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
off	O
by	O
Urine	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Counterfeits	O
,	O
is	O
sold	O
only	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
's	O
,	O
Book-seller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lambord-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
a	O
Liew	O
and	O
Dagger	O
.	O
Perform	O
'd	O
by	O
HENDRICK	O
VANDOR	O
.	O
