TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th,12th,13th	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September,1717	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
John	B-pers
Willmott	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Upp	I-pers
George	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Frye	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Millward	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hulst	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Beckinton	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Illford	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ravenor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Mattley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Charlwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bretridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Herns	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Hannah	B-pers
Pinion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
half	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.2	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
5	O
s.4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stollen	O
the	O
Goods	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallaince	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Altho	O
'	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
snatched	O
off	O
his	O
Wig	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turning	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
up	O
Nicholas-lane	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
Nicholas-lane	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
but	O
he	O
:	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
perhaps	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
might	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
Farringdon	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
7	O
s.3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yerbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
came	O
in	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
Anthony	O
Waldron	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
him	O
Assertion	O
,	O
and	O
Waldron	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Repute	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hutchinson	O
only	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Yerbury	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
London	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
died	O
at	O
Oxford	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Relations	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
him	O
his	O
Livery	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Yerbury	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yerbury	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
be	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
however	O
denied	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Panting	I-pers
alias	O
Panton	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsly	O
and	O
deceitfully	O
uttering	O
110	O
light	O
Guineas	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
fired	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
in	O
Lombard	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
succinctly	O
opened	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
the	O
infinite	O
Detriment	O
that	O
such	O
Diminution	O
of	O
the	O
Coin	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
supported	O
their	O
Charge	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edes	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Guineas	O
paid	O
in	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
some	O
few	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
light	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
filed	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Order	O
to	O
his	O
Servants	O
when	O
any	O
Stranger	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
in	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
Care	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
filed	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
303	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
new	O
some	O
old	O
,	O
desiring	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Smith	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Guineas	O
having	O
been	O
told	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Shovel	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sorted	O
them	O
took	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
rubbing	O
his	O
Finger	O
over	O
the	O
Edges	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
some	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
like	O
fine	O
Filings	O
come	O
off	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Particles	O
to	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Board	O
where	O
the	O
Guineas	O
lay	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
weighed	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
110	O
of	O
the	O
303	O
to	O
be	O
light	O
,	O
wanting	O
about	O
18	O
d.	O
per	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
Note	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
who	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Guineas	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
John	O
Smith	O
a	O
Clothier	O
living	O
at	O
Beesely	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
Reply	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
Money	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
light	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
filed	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
must	O
detain	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
and	O
Satisfaction	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
Guineas	O
.	O
He	O
giving	O
him	O
some	O
unsatisfactory	O
and	O
evasive	O
Answers	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
detain	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
charge	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
did	O
consent	O
to	O
stay	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
a	O
Porter	O
might	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
send	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
Message	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
permit	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
that	O
could	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinkley	O
the	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
interrogated	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
paid	O
in	O
300	O
and	O
odd	O
Pound	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
mention	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
light	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
Guinea	O
should	O
weigh	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
weigh	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
asking	O
him	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
Questions	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
nothing	O
but	O
trifling	O
Answers	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shunks	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Edes	O
's	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
dejected	O
,	O
and	O
trembled	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
mention	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
home	O
a	O
Porter	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
advisable	O
to	O
defer	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
should	O
think	O
they	O
would	O
probably	O
take	O
no	O
farther	O
Notice	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
deferred	O
the	O
Search	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
,	O
when	O
taking	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
Officer	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
small	O
Appearance	O
,	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
below	O
Stairs	O
were	O
kept	O
shutt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
Lad	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
talking	O
with	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
seem	O
'd	O
unwilling	O
on	O
let	O
them	O
come	O
in	O
till	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
Opposition	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
must	O
use	O
Violence	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
entring	O
found	O
the	O
Furniture	O
within	O
meaner	O
than	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
amount	O
of	O
the	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Furniture	O
in	O
their	O
Opinion	O
not	O
to	O
exceed	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
l.	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Loom	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lad	O
puddling	O
about	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
expected	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Workshop	O
they	O
espy	O
'd	O
a	O
Door	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
opened	O
;	O
the	O
Brother	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
whereupon	O
setting	O
his	O
,	O
Foot	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
and	O
dusty	O
,	O
land	O
some	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
lying	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Furniture	O
exactly	O
answerable	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
sorry	O
old	O
torn	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Trunk	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
Trunk	O
might	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Brother	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
they	O
replied	O
then	O
they	O
must	O
break	O
it	O
upon	O
;	O
where	O
upon	O
he	O
fetched	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
this	O
Trunk	O
in	O
one	O
Parcel	O
was	O
93	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
193	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
187	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
then	O
searching	O
about	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
some	O
old	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
feeling	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
felt	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
346	O
Guineas	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
filed	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
all	O
these	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Guineas	O
were	O
fresh	O
new	O
Guineas	O
,	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
or	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
Weights	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Grains	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
other	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
appear	O
among	O
some	O
Dust	O
something	O
to	O
shine	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
some	O
fine	O
Filings	O
of	O
Gold	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
likewise	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
his	O
depending	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
on	O
in	O
Forma	O
pauperis	O
.	O
These	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
generally	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Officer	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkley	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Satisfaction	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
very	O
evasively	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
various	O
Persons	O
in	O
small	O
Sums	O
as	O
5	O
or	O
10	O
l.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
Employments	O
,	O
sometimes	O
as	O
a	O
Weaver	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
as	O
a	O
Solicitor	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Stock-jobbing	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
they	O
suspecting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
some	O
Accomplices	O
who	O
had	O
furnished	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
file	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
promised	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edes	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
inform	O
himself	O
who	O
this	O
John	O
Smith	O
was	O
at	O
Beesely	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
and	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Letters	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
The	O
Import	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
very	O
diligent	O
Inquiry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
there	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Repute	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
mean	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
rated	O
4	O
d.	O
per	O
Month	O
to	O
the	O
Poor	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
body	O
or	O
another	O
to	O
answer	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
had	O
obtained	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
make	O
Distress	O
,	O
did	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
distrain	O
for	O
15	O
s.2	O
d.	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
found	O
not	O
Movables	O
worth	O
their	O
taking	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
resolving	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Loom	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
muster	O
'd	O
up	O
10s	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
engaged	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Others	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Trade	O
he	O
carried	O
on	O
was	O
very	O
inconsiderable	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
necessitous	O
,	O
being	O
always	O
very	O
pressing	O
for	O
his	O
Rent	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
Quarter-day	O
was	O
past	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
deposed	O
that	O
tended	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
reputed	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
mean	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
probable	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
Accomplices	O
who	O
had	O
supplied	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
either	O
to	O
diminish	O
or	O
utter	O
,	O
or	O
both	O
.	O
This	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeaveor	O
'd	O
to	O
obviate	O
by	O
producing	O
Witnesses	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
by	O
this	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
consequently	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
scraping	O
together	O
for	O
this	O
15	O
to	O
16	O
Years	O
by	O
working	O
hard	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
racking	O
his	O
Brains	O
and	O
starving	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
urging	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
put	O
away	O
false	O
Money	O
unknowingly	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
some	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
about	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
ago	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
and	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
Cloth	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
here	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
that	O
worked	O
Journey-work	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
traded	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Repute	O
of	O
a	O
Mony	O
'd	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
Money	O
upon	O
Pawns	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
weekly	O
Payments	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
discounted	O
Notes	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
100	O
l.	O
upon	O
Security	O
,	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
again	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
:	O
and	O
another	O
particularly	O
testified	O
,	O
that	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
since	O
he	O
'	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Purchase	O
for	O
him	O
worth	O
5,6	O
or	O
700	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
showed	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Houses	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
fair-dealing	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
frugal	O
and	O
saving	O
,	O
making	O
Advantages	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
every	O
way	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
contenting	O
himself	O
with	O
bare	O
Necessaries	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
Things	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
.	O
T	O
o	O
which	O
the	O
Council	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
produced	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
John	O
Smith	O
a	O
Clothier	O
of	O
Beesely	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
who	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
303	O
Guineas	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Messieurs	O
Green	O
and	O
Edes	O
;	O
that	O
an	O
honest	O
fair-dealing	O
Man	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
such	O
Falsifications	O
in	O
paying	O
his	O
own	O
Money	O
into	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
yet	O
made	O
no	O
Proof	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
inasmuch	O
as	O
excepting	O
the	O
100	O
l.	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Notes	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
discounted	O
,	O
were	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sums	O
themselves	O
but	O
small	O
,	O
and	O
together	O
amounting	O
to	O
no	O
Sum	O
comparable	O
with	O
1100	O
l.	O
which	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
Gold	O
.	O
They	O
observed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
boarded	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
new	O
Guineas	O
,	O
sit	O
for	O
filing	O
:	O
They	O
observed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
any	O
considerable	O
Dealings	O
in	O
this	O
Trade	O
,	O
whereby	O
to	O
procure	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
produce	O
'd	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
dealing	O
in	O
Stocks	O
,	O
Exchequer-Notes	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
relating	O
to	O
Publick	O
Credit	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
his	O
having	O
bought	O
or	O
sold	O
one	O
single	O
Exchequer-Bill	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
in	O
Pawns	O
,	O
they	O
observed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
deposed	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
Pawns	O
(	O
except	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat,3	O
or	O
4	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
aforesaid	O
)	O
nor	O
no	O
Books	O
of	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Dealings	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Occupations	O
.	O
They	O
likewise	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Action	O
of	O
uttering	O
the	O
Guineas	O
was	O
very	O
unlike	O
an	O
Old	O
Gripe	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Council	O
had	O
been	O
labouring	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
no	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
Convetous	O
in	O
improving	O
Money	O
would	O
pay	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
single	O
Goldsmith	O
upon	O
his	O
bare	O
Note	O
which	O
allows	O
no	O
Interest	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
may	O
for	O
it	O
have	O
Exchequer	O
Notes	O
on	O
Parliament	O
Security	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
which	O
bear	O
Interest	O
.	O
They	O
observed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Persons	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
leave	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
as	O
470	O
l.	O
so	O
carelesly	O
as	O
in	O
old	O
Clouts	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
They	O
observed	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
.	O
Mayor	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
weigh	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
yet	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Scales	O
and	O
Weights	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
highly	O
probable	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Money	O
he	O
was	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
from	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
fraudulent	O
and	O
pernicious	O
Intent	O
and	O
Porpose	O
:	O
and	O
however	O
,	O
were	O
it	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
Suspicion	O
was	O
the	O
stronger	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
when	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
honest	O
Intent	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
in	O
paying	O
them	O
to	O
Messieurs	O
Green	O
and	O
Edes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Consultation	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Matthews	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgkin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
nevertheless	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Higson	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Work-shop	O
where	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
shewing	O
him	O
a	O
Repeating	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
it	O
strike	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
to	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hayns	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
val.15	O
s.	O
from	O
Jacob	B-pers
Coler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-lane	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
behind	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
12	O
pewter	O
Dishes,28	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
upon	O
Ann	O
Wright	O
.	O
N	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Neeland	I-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
had	O
something	O
likewise	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
laying	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
appeared	O
probable	O
;	O
wheneupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	O
Wright	O
pleaded	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
val.3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Proctor	I-pers
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Webberlin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
Francis	B-pers
Blaks	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Webberlin	O
came	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
comes	O
Linn	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
a	O
Coach-maker	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
one	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
one	O
in	O
Sight	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
Linn	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
following	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
calling	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Webberlin	O
was	O
,	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
first	O
dropped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Webberlin	O
denied	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
he	O
knew	O
Linn	O
.	O
Linn	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Webberlin	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
that	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Webberlin	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Wig	O
and	O
Gloves	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
the	O
better	O
Appearance	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Sign	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
move	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Webberlin	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Linn	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Suspicion	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
against	O
Webberlin	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
34	O
s.	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
Money	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
staying	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
seeming	O
uneasy	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
carry	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
Davis	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Davis	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Callico	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
five	O
Pieces	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
she	O
missed	O
one	O
Piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
entertaining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
in	O
doing	O
some	O
Business	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Clothes	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
her	O
Rags	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Snelling	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Sept	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
a	O
Trap-door	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ridge	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
got	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
surrender	O
himself	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Hands	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
Chimney	O
and	O
jumped	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
some	O
Goods	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
took	O
the	O
Parcel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
immediately	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Duffell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Sept	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Duffell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amy	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Isabel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
by	O
force	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
dropped	O
them	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
ran	O
in	O
pursuit	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
story	O
being	O
grown	O
too	O
common	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
4	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cellar	O
underneath	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
over	O
him	O
and	O
hugg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
This	O
Circumstance	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
his	O
dear	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
kissing	O
and	O
hugging	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shropshire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Corral	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fledam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Cockball	I-pers
the	O
21st	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complaining	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
and	O
lent	O
her	O
Clothes	O
to	O
wear	O
;	O
she	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Money	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Carriers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Corral	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
drop	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Carriers	O
.	O
The	O
Corral	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes,20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Col.	O
Floyer	B-pers
's	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
near	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
in	O
an	O
Entry	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
offering	O
him	O
two	O
Pence	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
Tavern	O
to	O
bid	O
them	O
send	O
4	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Bundle	O
to	O
hold	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
turning	O
back	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Bundle	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
crying	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Persons	O
that	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Whitehall-bridge	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Horrocks	I-pers
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
twelve	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Row	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Outcry	O
ran	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Abraham	O
Devicq	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Sept	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
walking	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	O
it	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
having	O
their	O
Pockets	O
pick	O
'd	O
like	O
wise	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
noised	O
on	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
6	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Exchange	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
for	O
all	O
his	O
pretence	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half,4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
troublesom	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
another	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
leaving	O
her	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
hang	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
gave	O
very	O
great	O
Cause	O
of	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Men	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
nor	O
whether	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
or	O
they	O
him	O
:	O
several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
drunk	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
lost	O
his	O
Memory	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
said	O
or	O
did	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet	O
street	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
following	O
him	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Foot	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
the	O
pulled	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
clapping	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Watch	O
hanging	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
nevertheless	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Santeloe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
only	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
stumble	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
alias	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Grariff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
doz	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
likewise	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Frocks	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
desiring	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
would	O
needs	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
Civility	O
;	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Frocks	O
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dermee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	O
de	O
la	O
Force	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Pate	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
their	O
Rounds	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
at	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
apprehended	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
Instruments	O
about	O
them	O
for	O
such	O
Designs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
trifling	O
Excuses	O
for	O
their	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
;	O
a	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
a	O
Watchman	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
the	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examined	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
Christening	O
her	O
Sisters	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
finding	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
alleged	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
carry	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abel	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Forder	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
with	O
their	O
Lanthorns	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
happened	O
to	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Criminals	O
that	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
gotten	O
out	O
of	O
New-prison	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
had	O
enter	O
'd	O
himself	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Ferret	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ferrer	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
brought	O
back	O
and	O
searched	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
telling	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
and	O
threatning	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
thorough	O
search	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
as	O
she	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ellikar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Boustel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
block	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Block	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
Hayes	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Purse	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Whip	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
a	O
Canvass	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
l	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Wickham	O
Market	O
about	O
7	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
in	O
Hayes	B-place
Parish	O
three	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Grey	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Black	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
damning	O
him	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
alight	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Saddle	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Horse	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rode	O
away	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
positively	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
rifled	O
him	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
,	O
that	O
lived	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
ride	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
drink	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
his	O
Ale	O
and	O
smoak	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
on	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
Men	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
staying	O
there	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
Horse	O
,	O
espied	O
three	O
Men	O
such	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
described	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Gate	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
through	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
finding	O
the	O
Gate	O
shut	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
giving	O
Nichols	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bridle	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
dismounted	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Whip	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
likewise	O
a	O
Hanger	O
at	O
his	O
Girdle	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
a	O
Scabbard	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wig	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charged	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
House	O
were	O
likewise	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Scroggs	O
at	O
a	O
Town	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
they	O
undertook	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
they	O
threatned	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
stir	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
considerable	O
distance	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Whip	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hadlived	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
at	O
Knight	O
's	O
Bridge	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Inn	O
there	O
(	O
and	O
as	O
one	O
said	O
used	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Liquorments	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
now	O
his	O
Father	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
being	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
an	O
Estate	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
collecting	O
her	O
Rents	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
committed	O
any	O
such	O
irregularity	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
thus	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
intimated	O
to	O
the	O
Recorder	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
well	O
behaved	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
surprized	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
verily	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
requested	O
the	O
Recorder	O
to	O
represent	O
the	O
Case	O
accordingly	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
:	O
To	O
whom	O
the	O
Recorder	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
requested	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calamanco	O
val.30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
match	O
a	O
Pattern	O
of	O
Calimanco	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Piece	O
under	O
her	O
dinghood	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
ancient	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
appeared	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
lived	O
very	O
credibly	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
had	O
wherewithal	O
to	O
live	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
times	O
she	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
behave	O
herself	O
very	O
odly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knights	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Copper-pots	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.12	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
val.40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
License	O
for	O
selling	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
general	O
Release	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
his	O
Wife	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
She	O
fear	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
setting	O
down	O
the	O
Pots	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
over	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
their	O
Apprehension	O
his	O
and	O
Release	O
found	O
in	O
Smith	O
's	O
Pocket	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
Wright	O
had	O
given	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
confesed	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Smith	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
and	O
Release	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
last	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
val.5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Cassel	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
17	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Reb	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
Ferry	O
,	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Tide	O
,	O
he	O
frightened	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Boats	O
came	O
toward	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
frightened	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
ashore	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val.6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Rody	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
not	O
owning	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
but	O
saying	O
as	O
a	O
Relation	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
Parents	O
lived	O
at	O
Dartford	B-pers
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
Drink	O
for	O
50	O
s	O
,	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
conversation	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
not	O
thinking	O
himself	O
safe	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
where	O
Watermen	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
indeed	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
of	O
East	B-place
Bedford	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
20	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
being	O
sick	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
went	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enquired	O
of	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Waggon	O
?	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
some	O
Discourse	O
,	O
he	O
claiming	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Townswoman	O
,	O
he	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Bush	O
,	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
Waggoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
big-bellyed	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
her	O
Self	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
Importunity	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
also	O
Bush	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Waggon	O
going	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
walked	O
four	O
Miles	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Bellsound	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
Bush	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
left	O
them	O
two	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
his	O
Waggon	O
to	O
Stains	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
growing	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Lane	O
this	O
side	O
Stains	O
,	O
three	O
Miles	O
long	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Foot-path	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
overjoyed	O
that	O
she	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sober	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Townsman	O
too	O
.	O
But	O
having	O
walked	O
a	O
pretty	O
Way	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
put	O
his	O
Foot	O
before	O
her	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Hillock	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
lay	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Heels	O
higher	O
than	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
getting	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
lying	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
upon	O
hers	O
so	O
close	O
she	O
could	O
scarce	O
breathe	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
Christ	O
Jesus	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
injure	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
holding	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
that	O
Posture	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
or	O
Feet	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Stains	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
took	O
another	O
Road	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
injured	O
,	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
she	O
apply	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
had	O
Medicines	O
,	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Condition	O
eversince	O
,	O
was	O
So	O
now	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
was	O
intirely	O
ruined	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
like	O
to	O
recover	O
her	O
Health	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Doctor	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
served	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
swore	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
remaining	O
still	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
make	O
Complaint	O
of	O
such	O
Usage	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
her	O
Violence	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Excoration	O
in	O
the	O
Parts	O
mentioned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Medicine	O
,	O
accordingly	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
fainting	O
Fits	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
applied	O
proper	O
Remedies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
her	O
Illness	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
Heat	O
of	O
Urine	O
.	O
He	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
any	O
Injury	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
her	O
Cure	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Face	O
to	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Offers	O
made	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
5	O
l.	O
She	O
being	O
asked	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
this	O
Matter	O
known	O
first	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Salisbury	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Mother	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
distemper	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
supposing	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
after	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
walk	O
'd	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Inn	O
at	O
Stanes	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Mention	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
went	O
on	O
Foot	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Carrier	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Weather	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
might	O
probably	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Illness	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrad	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Colthurst	I-pers
of	O
Hesson	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
40	O
s.12	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
by	O
two	O
Men	O
who	O
clapped	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Prisner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Reasons	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Par	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Penalty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stretchbury	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hannaway	I-pers
and	O
Gaston	B-pers
Orm	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
her	O
Box	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rochet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Johnson	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
s.4	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Killingsworth	I-pers
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Demant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
150	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lazarus	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
they	O
deposed	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Lazarus	O
Joseph	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Gloucester	O
Sloop	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
a	O
Passenger	O
from	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
a	O
Bag	O
marked	O
S.	O
J.	O
with	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
this	O
Bag	O
on	O
shore	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Passengers	O
likewise	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Bag	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Jebone	O
carried	O
it	O
towards	O
the	O
Cook-Room	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
went	O
on	O
Shore	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
sailed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Dishonesty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
an	O
Apprenticeship	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
such	O
Goods	O
brought	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Ships	O
Crew	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
any	O
such	O
Bag	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
never	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
his	O
Mate	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
his	O
Steward	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pleaded	O
so	O
much	O
Poverty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
begged	O
his	O
Passage	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
old	O
Clothes	O
;	O
and	O
pleaded	O
so	O
great	O
Poverty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Six-pence	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Tide-Surveyor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
Parcel	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Merchandize	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
as	O
pays	O
20	O
l.	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
Duty	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Goods	O
enter	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Custom	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
that	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
that	O
Bulk	O
and	O
Weight	O
could	O
be	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
at	O
Noon	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
deposed	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Tide-Waiters	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
by	O
drowning	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ashtol	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
conveniency	O
of	O
lying	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Press	O
Bed	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Bed	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
granted	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Hours	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Bedside	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
taking	O
notice	O
that	O
her	O
Sheets	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
pickle	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
so	O
:	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
an	O
Answer	O
as	O
proper	O
as	O
the	O
Case	O
would	O
hear	O
without	O
telling	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
wash	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
But	O
suspecting	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Child	O
born	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
others	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
she	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
why	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
Because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
else	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
Shame	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
before	O
its	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
case	O
known	O
to	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Necessaries	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
confirm	O
'd	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
an	O
experinc	O
'd	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinions	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
four	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
since	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
Writ	O
to	O
arrest	O
one	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
having	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
secured	O
him	O
she	O
might	O
oblige	O
him	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matters	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Evidence	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
or	O
as	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
stiled	O
himself	O
Colonel	O
Fuller	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Cheating	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
18	O
l.5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Lieutenant	O
Governors	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
and	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
he	O
using	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
took	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
Trade	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
telling	O
,	O
him	O
be	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Man	O
be	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Store-keeper	O
's	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
60	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
for	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
furnish	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
for	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Deputation	O
and	O
such	O
incident	O
Charges	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
,	O
being	O
elevated	O
at	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
his	O
Preferment	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Money	O
in	O
order	O
thereunto	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
often	O
came	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
sometimes	O
with	O
one	O
Obstacle	O
and	O
sometimes	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
Money	O
would	O
remove	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
trick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
such	O
Pretences	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Mony	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
Notes	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
one	O
Note	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Note	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hoy-Man	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Steward	O
and	O
receive	O
of	O
him	O
151	O
l.	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entitled	O
to	O
a	O
Pardon	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
begun	O
before	O
the	O
Act	O
commenced	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Charges	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
he	O
might	O
lay	O
claim	O
to	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
poor	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
50	O
Farthings	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
asked	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
the	O
50	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
a	O
crocked	O
Pin	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
suffer	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
imposed	O
upon	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Cheating	O
Henry	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
of	O
40	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
using	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Tilt	O
Yard	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pity	O
he	O
should	O
spend	O
his	O
Time	O
in	O
filling	O
out	O
Dishes	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
such	O
a	O
liking	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
prefer	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Treasury	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Commissioner	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Land-Waiter	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
wheedled	O
him	O
under	O
this	O
Expectation	O
out	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
various	O
Times	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
making	O
the	O
same	O
Excuses	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
for	O
the	O
deferring	O
his	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
Place	O
;	O
one	O
time	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
till	O
Term	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
sworn	O
in	O
the	O
Treasury	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
another	O
Hinderance	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Estate	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
1000	O
l.	O
And	O
this	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
Limits	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
comply	O
with	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
by	O
paying	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Costs	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Tryal	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
denied	O
his	O
Pretences	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Money	O
lent	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
whenever	O
he	O
should	O
retrieve	O
his	O
Misfortunes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
likewise	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Notes	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bill	O
to	O
receive	O
150	O
l.	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Steward	O
(	O
in	O
Nubibu	O
)	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
other	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
unkind	O
Usage	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
contrived	O
to	O
defer	O
his	O
Tryal	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
spoke	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Townsend	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Walpole	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Great	O
Men	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
pernicious	O
Contrivance	O
indeed	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
so	O
;	O
out	O
however	O
since	O
these	O
Great	O
Men	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Persons	O
of	O
less	O
Figure	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
challenging	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Court	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
full	O
)	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Misdemeanor	O
likewise	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
108	O
Guineas,2	O
double	O
Doubloons,1	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
124	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodged	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
,	O
When	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	B-place
Inn	I-place
near	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Pillow	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
?	O
whereupon	O
he	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
booted	O
and	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stones	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
wanting	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Watch-pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Hostler	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
his	O
Boots	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
call	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
seemed	O
unwilling	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
disturb	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
them	O
without	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
leave	O
something	O
for	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
called	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
hear	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
he	O
starts	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
wondering	O
at	O
this	O
sudden	O
Motion	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Stones	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Stones	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Chamberlain	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Chamberlain	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
7	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
stay	O
2	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
he	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
admir	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
so	O
early	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
therefore	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
among	O
the	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
12	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Strings	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Purse	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket,124	O
l.10	O
s.	O
That	O
they	O
counted	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
wanted	O
just	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
12	O
Guineas	O
which	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
Sum	O
neither	O
more	O
nor	O
less	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
Days	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rochester	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
him	O
7	O
months	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
hearing	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
Inn	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
called	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
one	O
Alexander	B-pers
Darwent	I-pers
alias	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
habited	O
like	O
a	O
Country	O
Farmer	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s	O
upon	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
receipt	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hired	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Suspicion	O
was	O
heightened	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
one	O
Longstaff	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Norton	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
Newgate	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
hard	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
in	O
procuring	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
should	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
and	O
dated	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
payable	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
immediately	O
write	O
a	O
Receipt	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
to	O
penetrate	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
procure	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Shew	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
wrote	O
such	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Praemium	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
per	O
duem	O
during	O
the	O
Attendance	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
This	O
Note	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mackdonald	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
discharged	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
at	O
Ailsbury	O
by	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
Norton	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Contryvance	O
,	O
ordered	O
Mackdonald	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Redmayn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
intitled	O
,	O
The	O
Case	O
of	O
Sabisn	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
truly	O
stated	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Howell	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
be	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,15	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
C	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
alias	O
Matthews	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,8	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ellikar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shropshire	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
