TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1717	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LAWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
Gay	B-pers
St	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smythies	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Berrysford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Abreaham	B-pers
Brawn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cullwum	I-pers
John	B-pers
Seddom	I-pers
Herry	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
May	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Thursfield	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
London-Bridge	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
polling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
nevertheless	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Minnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lingwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
of	O
a	O
Stage-Coach	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
hinder	O
Wheel	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
some	O
Persons	O
making	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Customer	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
and	O
credited	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
missed	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
by	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
match	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Pound	O
of	O
Rhubarb	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pargiter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
seven	O
o-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
turning	O
her	O
Head	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lignum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gallop	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stollen	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
Botolph-Wharf	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stollen	O
it	O
by	O
asking	O
an	O
under	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Gate-way	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Thoroughfare	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
free	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Geoge	B-pers
Widgeon	I-pers
alias	O
Whale	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
1	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
.	O
while	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
gon	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
guest	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
owned	O
tho	O
Fact	O
,	O
promising	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Service	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
imbezzled	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
the	O
Proposal	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pretended	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
crediting	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
Fellow	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
his	O
Clothies	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Necessary	O
drove	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
wrong	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dam	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
he	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Spurs	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
upon	O
his	O
tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Acton	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grasscon	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Drugget	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Tenters	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
selling	O
it	O
here	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
in	O
Town	O
for	O
16	O
d.	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Withy	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Fountains	O
of	O
Lamps	O
of	O
the	O
Convex-Lights	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
and	O
Sir	O
Fisher	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Lamps	O
were	O
stollen	O
from	O
High-street	B-place
in	O
Mile-End-New-Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
High-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
neither	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Grimshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
brass	O
Pots	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
one	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
1716	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	O
Executed	O
last	O
March	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Casement	O
putting	O
a	O
Knife	O
between	O
the	O
Shutters	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
cutting	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
boring	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
a	O
Nailpiercer	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
,	O
>	O
15	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
House	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
giving	O
them	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
Frame	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
a	O
Storehouse	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
's	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
Frame	O
and	O
all	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Store-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
credit	O
to	O
the	O
Plea	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Change	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
telling	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
3	O
s.	O
wanting	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Brandy	O
containing	O
12	O
Gallons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Brandy	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
lying	O
near	O
St.	O
katherines	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Water-man	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Brandy	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
called	O
Sculler	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
ply	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Brandy	O
being	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Fleetwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
at	O
the	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
near	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coach	O
Cushions	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Philip	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Coach	O
standing	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cushions	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
brush	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cushions	O
were	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
honestly	O
so	O
lucky	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scone	I-pers
alias	O
....	B-pers
rick	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Carriers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scales-House	O
in	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
loading	O
their	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.Magnes	B-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Quaile	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Eles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
over	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
the	O
things	O
lying	O
in	O
Bundles	O
upon	O
the	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
Bundles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
alias	O
White	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
alias	O
Huss	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Calico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Windress	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Sailors	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
Wives	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lain	O
there	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Women	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Women	O
afterwards	O
rose	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
staid	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
near	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
Clothes	O
under	O
their	O
own	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
on	O
Riding-hoods	O
far	O
some	O
small	O
t	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
so	O
sent	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
of	O
till	O
it	O
fell	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Brother	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
Elizabeth	O
Storey	O
near	O
Clarkenwell	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Clothes	O
on	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knowing	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stollen	O
,	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
out	O
Mary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
had	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Clothes	O
on	O
likewise	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Storey	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
endeavored	O
to	O
clear	O
Scot	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
gave	O
the	O
Clothes	O
to	O
Scot	O
;	O
and	O
Scot	O
denied	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
:	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Barbey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
180	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dowlass	O
,	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
sorts	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
76	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
his	O
Pack	O
weighing	O
100	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
rest	O
upon	O
a	O
Rail	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Hooper	B-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
in	O
Goodmans-Fields	B-place
,	O
went	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
at	O
some	O
Houses	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
but	O
any	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
his	O
pack	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
most	O
diligent	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Bell-man	O
to	O
Cry	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
who	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
about	O
her	O
Waist	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Pack	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
Owner	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
two	O
Young	O
Fellows	O
2	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
had	O
it	O
seems	O
in	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
so	O
far	O
outliv	O
'd	O
her	O
Honesty	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Mabe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hatfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
herself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Fellow-Servants	O
to	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Ann	O
Mabe	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
Ill	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
some	O
time	O
above	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
answered	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Pan	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
warmed	O
her	O
Bed	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
suspecting	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
did	O
observe	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
fallen	O
in	O
her	O
Bulk	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
asking	O
her	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pressing	O
her	O
very	O
hard	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Miscarried	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
something	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Abortion	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
not	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
Ann	O
Mabe	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
acquainted	O
Sir	O
George	O
with	O
her	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Sir	O
George	O
gave	O
him	O
Orders	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Vaults	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
declar	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Sir	O
George	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
alive	O
had	O
due	O
Care	O
been	O
taken	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Violence	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Cheeks	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
little	O
pushed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tongue	O
lay	O
between	O
its	O
Gums	O
exerted	O
to	O
the	O
exterior	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hands	O
clenched	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
sent	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
confessed	O
that	O
Sir	O
George	O
's	O
former	O
Coachman	O
had	O
gotten	O
her	O
with	O
Child	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
several	O
Letters	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
near	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
the	O
Child	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
by	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
that	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
two	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
Delivered	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
tell	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Midwise	O
and	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Child	O
that	O
is	O
new	O
born	O
,	O
if	O
alive	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
World	O
with	O
its	O
Hands	O
expanded	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
if	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
its	O
Hands	O
clench	O
'd	O
.	O
Considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stamworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Parkhouse-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pocket-book	O
and	O
Seal	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Padington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
.	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Loves	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
near	O
Agmondesham	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Padington	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Padingson	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
an	O
Inn-keeper	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
Satisfaction	O
in	O
that	O
matter	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Sheep	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Love	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
144	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Hose	O
,	O
12	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
12	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
34	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
had	O
bought	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
packed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Lighter	O
at	O
Wiggin	O
's	O
Key	O
the	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
likewise	O
that	O
Daniel	B-pers
Love	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
so	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Love	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
Knives	O
,	O
Forks	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
also	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
some	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
an	O
Uncle	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Holland	O
Trader	O
that	O
then	O
lay	O
dead	O
at	O
Shed	O
Thomas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
the	O
Stockings	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
more	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
reson	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
sold	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
the	O
Merchant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sold	O
those	O
Stockings	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
Pair	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
perhaps	O
the	O
finest	O
ever	O
were	O
seen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
by	O
Daniel	O
Love	O
and	O
himself	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Love	O
called	O
Sculler	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ply	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
did	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
ail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Burleigh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
and	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
immediately	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
dealt	O
in	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Things	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
for	O
8	O
d.	O
But	O
she	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Guineas,2	O
Caralon	O
Bound-Pieces	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Eles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
Seven	O
Days	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
while	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Billingate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
receiving	O
some	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
four	O
Watermen	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
piece	O
to	O
apprehend	O
her	O
,	O
sending	O
his	O
Man	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
thereupon	O
got	O
down	O
to	O
Gravsend	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seized	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
near	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
E	O
-	O
had	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Rings	O
on	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
her	O
Necklace	O
on	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Clothes	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
likewise	O
Mary	O
Morrice	O
;	O
That	O
;	O
E	O
-	O
had	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
Double	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
she	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Morrice	O
had	O
five	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Morrice	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
24	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
herself	O
,	O
said	O
Morrice	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
;	O
E	O
--	O
--	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Morrice	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
E	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Morrice	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Eles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Darlington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Tortoise-Shell	O
Snuffbox	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Jackson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
were	O
going	O
alongFleetstreet	O
,	O
Women	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
who	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
on	O
Thompson	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
White-Fryars	B-place
near	O
Water-Lane	B-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
there	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
impudent	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
brought	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
demaning	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
with	O
Shilling	O
,	O
Thompson	O
demanded	O
23	O
s.	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
they	O
bullied	O
them	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
assaulted	O
them	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
coming	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tarvel	O
his	O
friend	O
deposed	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
they	O
dreamed	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
at	O
a	O
violent	O
Rate	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
in	O
beating	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
rod	O
hot	O
Poker	O
,	O
sting	O
upon	O
23	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
Murthered	O
they	O
last	O
took	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Darlington	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
the	O
Door	O
the	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
Darlington	O
interposed	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
while	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
Wench	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
and	O
were	O
up	O
Stairs	O
had	O
five	O
feggros	O
Drink	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
Jackson	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
and	O
gave	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlewomen	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
she	O
would	O
keep	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jackson	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Heart	O
and	O
take	O
there	O
was	O
23	O
s.	O
demanded	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Mistress	O
took	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea,2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	O
cock	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
buying	O
Meat	O
at	O
Newgate-Market	O
about	O
10	O
a-clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
And	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
Lucy	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Promiet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
S-	O
were	O
Fellow-Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Lacy	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
S	O
-	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
Haynes	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stollen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Derwentwater	I-pers
;	O
and	O
pleading	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
catch	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
was	O
introduced	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
regaled	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
him	O
at	O
Oxford	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Say	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a-clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Racket	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
his	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sat	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
overtaken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
shutting	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Goodmans-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lend	O
out	O
Money	O
upon	O
Pawns	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Persons	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovelock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Trained	O
Bands	O
last	O
Whitsuntide	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
as	O
be	O
dressed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
opened	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
lately	O
robbed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
near	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
examined	O
and	O
had	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Millard	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Diason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
said	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
be	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Levin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Levin	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
withdrew	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Sone	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Byard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gallimore	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
ten	O
Months	O
old	O
,	O
by	O
not	O
allowing	O
it	O
sufficient	O
Meat	O
,	O
Drink	O
and	O
due	O
Attendance	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
it	O
languish	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Parish-Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
five	O
young	O
Children	O
of	O
different	O
Ages	O
to	O
keep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
Twins	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Richard	O
Pugh	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
contracted	O
with	O
the	O
Father	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
for	O
good	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
and	O
had	O
Two	O
Twins	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Gallimore	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Condition	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
no	O
Account	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
Follow	O
'd	O
them	O
when	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Gallimore	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
afterwards	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
frequently	O
the	O
Children	O
crying	O
vehemently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
she	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
Gallimore	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
Gallimore	O
always	O
hector	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
threatned	O
her	O
,	O
forwarn	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
her	O
to	O
visit	O
them	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
five	O
Children	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Day	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
stay	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
a	O
drunknaing	O
,	O
and	O
use	O
the	O
Children	O
cruelly	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
Richard	O
Pugh	O
died	O
,	O
one	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
wrapped	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Rag	O
and	O
laid	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
any	O
violent	O
Methods	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Children	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
likewise	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
back	O
Parts	O
of	O
it	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
,	O
locking	O
like	O
an	O
Ox	O
Liver	O
parboil	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
ha	O
nd	O
,	O
she	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
produced	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
Gallimore	O
was	O
out	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
Victuals	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
feed	O
them	O
,	O
turn	O
them	O
dry	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
although	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
negligent	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
laid	O
for	O
Murther	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wiltron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
having	O
served	O
an	O
Appenticeship	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
Journey-man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
Notice	O
that	O
oftentimes	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
suppose	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Money-box	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Change	O
was	O
wanted	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
happening	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
finding	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Servant-Maid	O
,	O
she	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
replied	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
greater	O
Thief	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
than	O
she	O
,	O
naming	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
putting	O
the	O
Matter	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
times	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
for	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
also	O
done	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
intimating	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
Master	O
Warning	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
this	O
Accusation	O
was	O
fixed	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
alias	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
alias	O
Hugh	O
Roberts	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Polygamy	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
marrying	O
several	O
Wives	O
)	O
and	O
in	O
particular	O
for	O
marrying	O
Amy	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
marrying	O
Susanna	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
Amy	O
Parker	O
being	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
prov	O
'd	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
Cook	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Gracechurch-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Master	O
Carpenter	O
in	O
great	O
Business	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Gang	O
attending	O
who	O
personated	O
his	O
Workmen	O
whom	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Show	O
of	O
paying	O
them	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
personating	O
such	O
as	O
were	O
pressing	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
work	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Fleetditch	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
25	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
fine	O
Furniture	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
;	O
That	O
having	O
appointed	O
a	O
Day	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
Tavern	I-place
on	O
Ludgate	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
to	O
marry	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
refusing	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
Some	O
constraining	O
Methods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
She	O
proved	O
her	O
Marriage	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Things	O
packed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
then	O
got	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
Villainous	O
Tricks	O
he	O
had	O
plaid	O
in	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
Grace	O
to	O
disobey	O
his	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Wives	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
he	O
at	O
Liberty	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
an	O
Hundred	O
more	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
fourteen	O
Wives	O
who	O
were	O
Cook-Maids	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
his	O
Wives	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
standing	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Marriage	O
with	O
Amy	O
Parker	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
looselaid	O
,	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Lurch	O
and	O
so	O
that	O
Indictment	O
miscarried	O
likewise	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
well	O
appriz	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Villany	O
in	O
marrying	O
of	O
Women	O
and	O
getting	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
and	O
then	O
leaving	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
advised	O
the	O
Wives	O
to	O
provide	O
themselves	O
with	O
better	O
Evidence	O
,	O
till	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
secured	O
.	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Paleotti	I-pers
,	O
Esq	B-pers
;	I-pers
alias	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Marquess	I-pers
de	I-pers
Paleotti	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Niccolo	I-pers
alias	O
John	O
the	O
Italian	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
likewise	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
the	O
Evidences	O
gave	O
the	O
Accounts	O
following	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
(	O
Esq	O
;	O
Ballasis	O
)	O
Door	O
in	O
Lisle-Street	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Marquels	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pass	O
by	O
and	O
heard	O
Niccolo	O
say	O
,	O
Tous	O
les	O
Jours	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
passed	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
knocking	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pursue	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Servant	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Garde	O
,	O
Garde	O
,	O
Garde	O
,	O
near	O
ten	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Post	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walked	O
by	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
Stick	O
or	O
Sword	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Marquess	O
being	O
gone	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
Niccolo	O
never	O
spoke	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Marquess	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
Gerard-Street	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbridge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
positive	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
the	O
Marquess	O
and	O
Niccols	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
knocking	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Lights	O
reflecting	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
perfect	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
Marquess	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
postively	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
then	O
distinsguish	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Red	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
or	O
understand	O
English	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
sworn	O
.	O
told	O
the	O
Marquess	O
in	O
French	O
what	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
in	O
English	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
bid	O
him	O
ask	O
the	O
Marquess	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
any	O
Questions	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Scarlet	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
very	O
angrily	O
,	O
That	O
whatsoever	O
he	O
had	O
deposed	O
was	O
all	O
Lies	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Red	O
Coat	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
anon	O
disprove	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
knocking	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Mother	O
;	O
and	O
running	O
to	O
Lisle-street	B-place
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Stature	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
Stature	O
and	O
make	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
pretty	O
remarkable	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
)	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Marquess	O
:	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
,	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
the	O
Marquess	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
themselves	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
that	O
looked	O
into	O
Lisle-Street	O
,	O
Saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
pass	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
heard	O
the	O
Footman	O
cry	O
out	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Footman	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
near	O
the	O
Lady	O
Bellasis	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rucks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
(	O
Esq	O
;	O
Elmys	O
)	O
House	O
in	O
Lisle-Street	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
Out-cry	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
up	O
Stairs	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
groan	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Bellasis	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
pass	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
Shape	O
and	O
Stature	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Marquess	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
Niccolo	O
was	O
fallen	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
Lisle-Street	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
keeping	O
the	O
Coach-way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
either	O
a	O
Sword	O
or	O
Stick	O
under	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Red	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
along	O
hastily	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
several	O
times	O
looking	O
behind	O
him	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
Gerard-Street	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
his	O
Stature	O
and	O
Shape	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
Marquess	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
stepping	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
be	O
and	O
another	O
found	O
him	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
Wounds	O
;	O
and	O
examining	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
Papers	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
discover	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Marquess	O
de	O
Paleotti	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
one	O
Penny	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
living	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
kept	O
a	O
Sutler	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Marquess	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
been	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
Home	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
Supper	O
and	O
much	O
Attendance	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Room	O
illuminated	O
and	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Marquess	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
though	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
confirmed	O
what	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Marquess	O
's	O
Room	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Grandchild	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Marquess	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
Curtains	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Man	O
Niccols	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
some	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
she	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Bed	O
without	O
the	O
Bed	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Candle	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Fire	O
that	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
Light	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Marquess	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Marquess	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Man	O
Niccolo	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
just	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Belon	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Marquess	O
that	O
Niccolo	O
was	O
found	O
murthered	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
hurry	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
dress	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
his	O
Grey	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
fetched	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dressed	O
himself	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bilhop	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
's	O
(	O
very	O
probably	O
thinking	O
to	O
find	O
Sanctuary	O
in	O
the	O
Bishop	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
a	O
Church	O
or	O
Cloyster	O
in	O
Popish	O
Countries	O
)	O
where	O
it	O
seems	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
so	O
rudely	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Riot	O
.	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
's	O
;	O
which	O
Sword	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
Justice	O
Gors	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
four	O
Months	O
with	O
the	O
Marquess	O
as	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Marquess	O
that	O
Day	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
with	O
Niccolo	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
Scarlet	B-pers
Clothes	I-pers
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
Blue	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sword	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
any	O
other	O
Sword	O
but	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dubasamel	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
Marquess	O
de	O
Paleotti	O
,	O
be	O
discoursing	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Guard-Chamber	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
his	O
Servant	O
John	B-pers
Niccolo	I-pers
was	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Lady	O
and	O
supp	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
Nicccalo	O
waited	O
on	O
them	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
the	O
Lady	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
through	O
a	O
dark	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
Niccalo	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
almost	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
lost	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
by	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dubasamel	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Marquess	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
differ	O
'd	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Marquess	O
chased	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Haughty	O
Air	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
suffer	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
interrogated	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
he	O
?	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
kicking	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
7	O
Inches	O
deep	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
broad	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
penetrated	O
into	O
the	O
Left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
his	O
Lungs	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
satisfied	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
hollow	O
Blade	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Sword	O
as	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Marquess	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
having	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
sworn	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
)	O
pleaded	O
total	O
Innocence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	O
Niccalo	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Ill-will	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Cause	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
way	O
of	O
punishing	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
Martial	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Troop	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
owned	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
and	O
supped	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Niccalo	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
step	O
some	O
where	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
presently	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
without	O
Niccalo	O
's	O
putting	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Maid	O
that	O
Niccalo	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
He	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
suddenly	O
to	O
bed	O
without	O
Attendance	O
,	O
Light	O
,	O
Fire	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Bed	O
made	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fire	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
the	O
Maid	O
being	O
examined	O
again	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
Matter	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
the	O
Bed	O
wasnot	O
made	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Fire	O
that	O
gave	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Light	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
grew	O
unsatisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
affronting	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
frequently	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
excuse	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
Appearance	O
great	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Capacity	O
for	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
by	O
the	O
unhandsome	O
Carriage	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
frequent	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
they	O
had	O
appointed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
condescend	O
to	O
gratify	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
prevailed	O
with	O
a	O
Worthy	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
to	O
humour	O
the	O
Marquess	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Defence	O
following	O
.	O
That	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Niccalo	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
staid	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Sister	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Shrewsbury	O
sent	O
him	O
50	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Jewels	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
his	O
Man	O
Niccalo	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
somewhere	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
other	O
Questions	O
being	O
put	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
his	O
Man	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
well	O
knew	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
Niccalo	O
was	O
enquired	O
for	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
better	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
thus	O
he	O
contradicted	O
himself	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
and	O
his	O
Tryal	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
produce	O
Evidences	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
had	O
sufficient	O
Notice	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
fourteen	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lorrain	O
that	O
his	O
Tryal	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
his	O
Defence	O
being	O
trifling	O
and	O
contradictious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
A	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovelock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Millard	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
alias	O
Wright	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Marquess	I-pers
de	I-pers
Paleotti	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
17.	O
Francis	B-pers
Minnett	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hend	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Widgeon	I-pers
alias	O
Whale	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
S	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinburn	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
P	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Barby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Withy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fitegerald	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Oxton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
A	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lovelock	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Storey	O
and	O
Mary	O
Scott	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
A	O
-E	O
-	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovelock	I-pers
not	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Press	O
and	O
will	O
speedily	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Tryals	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
Forty	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
her	O
Murthers	O
,	O
High	O
Way	O
Robbing	O
,	O
Piracy	O
,	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
Foot-padding	O
,	O
Shop-lifting	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Fortune-stealing	O
,	O
Trepanning	O
,	O
Kidnapping	O
,	O
Forgery	O
,	O
Perjury	O
,	O
notorious	O
Frauds	O
and	O
Cheats	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
and	O
most	O
memorable	O
Exploits	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
of	O
those	O
Malefactors	O
.	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
,	O
Books	O
of	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Paul	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Wynes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
several	O
Ordinaries	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Even	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Printing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Line	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
And	O
particularly	O
these	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Lives	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
following	O
,	O
Of	O
Clot	O
.	O
Via	O
Lieutenant	O
Stern	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Botoski	O
the	O
Polendes	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Esquire	O
Thynne	O
;	O
Roger	B-pers
Congden	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Madam	O
Getiings	O
,	O
her	O
Child	O
and	O
Maid	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murtel	I-pers
,	O
or	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Pullien	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Jewlier	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
L	O
Grand	O
;	O
CreySimon	O
,	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartler	I-pers
;	O
Peter	B-pers
Dremani	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
Edmund	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Bulevant	O
;	O
Harman	B-pers
Stodrman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wakers	I-pers
his	O
Fellow	O
Prentice	O
;	O
Gerard	B-pers
Dromclius	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Berg	I-pers
and	O
Katherins	O
,	O
Van	B-pers
Berg	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norice	O
;	O
The	O
Brother	O
of	O
Gweester	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
the	O
Constable	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
;	O
Roger	B-pers
Lowen	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Loyd	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Morgidge	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Caps	O
;	O
Mayned	O
,	O
Brovins	O
and	O
Marsh	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Stocton	O
the	O
Victualler	O
:	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
remarkable	O
Murthers	O
.	O
Of	O
Highway	O
Men	O
,	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Claude	O
da	O
Vel	O
,	O
Old	O
Mh	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stency	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Sool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
notorious	O
Highway-Men	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Piracy	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
KM	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Culliford	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Cap	O
.	O
Guitter	O
and	O
73	O
of	O
his	O
Crew	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
Paper	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oldersham	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
Exchequer	O
Bills	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
coining	O
Dutch	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Fouder	O
,	O
Scanlen	O
,	O
Goff	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
GoldSmiths	O
in	O
Boswel	O
Court	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
for	O
absolving	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
of	O
her	O
Sins	O
:	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
notorious	O
Criminals	O
of	O
all	O
Kinds	O
,	O
too	O
many	O
to	O
inserted	O
here	O
;	O
which	O
Collection	O
is	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Present	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
at	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
printing	O
House	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryars	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
settling	O
first	O
in	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
flying	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
over	O
my	O
Body	O
,	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Swelling	O
and	O
inflamation	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
uncapable	O
of	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bed	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
has	O
continued	O
ever	O
sure	O
,	O
excepting	O
some	O
small	O
Intervals	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Adv	O
ice	O
of	O
several	O
eminent	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
the	O
various	O
removings	O
of	O
my	O
Distempers	O
,	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
Medicines	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Batholomew	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
Out	O
Patient	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Physicians	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
violent	O
GOUT	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
Ease	O
.	O
Having	O
thus	O
had	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
without	O
Success	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
hearken	O
to	O
every	O
bodies	O
Instructions	O
,	O
sending	O
for	O
and	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
Medicines	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
the	O
Expence	O
was	O
large	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
their	O
number	O
I	O
think	O
innumerable	O
,	O
which	O
only	O
added	O
to	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
not	O
hearing	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
so	O
violently	O
afflicted	O
as	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Being	O
in	O
this	O
miserable	O
Conditions	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
articurable	O
,	O
the	O
Gout	O
still	O
increasing	O
so	O
violently	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Joints	O
became	O
so	O
Knitted	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
render	O
'd	O
quite	O
unable	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
difficult	O
to	O
all	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
the	O
Anti-Arthritick	O
Medicines	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
RHEUMATISM	O
,	O
gives	O
gti	O
Up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Anodyne	O
.	O
NECKLACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
above	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Alteration	O
.	O
The	O
GOUT	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
Stomach	O
,	O
abaied	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Continuance	O
of	O
those	O
Remedies	O
I	O
still	O
grew	O
sensibly	O
better	O
every	O
Day	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
free	O
from	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
Suffress	O
in	O
my	O
Joints	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
and	O
Strength	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
This	O
Benefit	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
by	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
:	O
and	O
those	O
i	O
e.	O
inable	O
Remedies	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
great	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
published	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Irish	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
eay	O
to	O
testify	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Printing	O
House-street	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
.	O
Octob	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
1717	O
.	O
James	O
Davis	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
parker	O
as	O
its	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lomhard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
AESO	O
P	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Edvange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
ve	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Cts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
:	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
fine	O
paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Roles	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
,	O
800	O
.	O
price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuative	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
Warren	O
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
6th	O
Edit	O
.	O
price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
ST.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Jordaine	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
in	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplications	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Supersties	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Gauging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tons	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
matters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
800	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evel	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
came	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Paral	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwise	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-Makers	O
,	O
near	O
Emetr	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Straud	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
Since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
sutisly	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquint	O
the	O
Curious	O
,	O
THere	O
is	O
to	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Grocers	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Mgh	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
FleetStreet	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
Wonderful	O
Fire-Eater	O
:	O
Who	O
Eats	O
such	O
vast	O
quantities	O
of	O
combustible	O
Matters	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ashtvaisherth	O
all	O
Mankind	O
that	O
ever	O
betteld	O
him	O
:	O
His	O
Fellow	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
he	O
eats	O
Fire	O
and	O
Brimborn	O
like	O
Saltmander	O
,	O
and	O
follows	O
Flint-stones	O
like	O
an	O
Ostrich	O
:	O
With	O
divers	O
other	O
great	O
Curiocities	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Quarto	O
Bills	O
.	O
Prices	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
1s	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
1s	O
.	O
Note	O
the	O
Astronomical	O
and	O
MUSICAL-CLOCK	O
,	O
A	O
Piece	O
of	O
Art	O
not	O
yet	O
parall	O
'd	O
:	O
its	O
Performances	O
so	O
curious	O
,	O
is	O
Harmony	O
so	O
delightful	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
Variety	O
of	O
Parts	O
so	O
surprizing	O
,	O
as	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
conceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
but	O
those	O
that	O
see	O
in	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
.	O
was	O
never	O
shown	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
a	O
Seperate	O
Show	O
.	O
