TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th,15th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May,1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
;	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ruby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Overall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Took	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sheaf	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eaden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Josias	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
,	O
Besar	B-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Hector	B-pers
Mackensey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walkingham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiten	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
his	O
Hand-kerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Red-Cross	O
street	O
,	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Aylmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canister	O
of	O
Bohee	O
Tea	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
l.1	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Thare	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Row	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tea	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
within.a	O
few	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
exercising	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
his	O
Officer	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Gothard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
his	O
Spoon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
dony	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
several	O
Jews	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
not	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
dropt	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Spoon	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
cleaning	O
some	O
Spoons	O
above	O
Stairs	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
while	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
a	O
half-pennyworth	O
of	O
Peas	O
,	O
she	O
serv	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
Hungary	O
Water	O
behind	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
mist	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
intrusted	O
her	O
very	O
considerably	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
living	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
Hungary	O
Water	O
,	O
Chocolate	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
this	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
furbelow	O
'd	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
furbelow	O
'd	O
Apron	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
;	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Dolliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
she	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
furbelow	O
Apron	O
and	O
Scarf	O
next	O
her	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
;	O
but	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
one	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Highsham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Highsham	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
obserserv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
some	O
Gentlemens	O
Pockets	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clap	O
his	O
Hat	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
convey	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Hand-kerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle,2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
8s	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
merry	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
and	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	B-place
,	O
who	O
assaulted	O
him	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hair	O
and	O
beat	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Buckels	O
his	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
have	O
10	O
l.	O
next	O
Day	O
for	O
his	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
dead	O
Drunk	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
treated	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
have	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
for	O
his	O
Living	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
em	O
happy	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Story	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
declar	O
'd	O
it	O
so	O
freely	O
to	O
Strangers	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cooks	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
Maid	O
having	O
given	O
or	O
permitted	O
the	O
Dustman	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
Coals	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
and	O
not	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Cawdrey	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
Mistress	O
pardon	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
fetchMoney	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
some	O
Muslin	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Muslin	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
servent	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Pudding	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
Servants	O
with	O
robbing	O
of	O
her	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
given	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
her	O
Hand	O
for	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
stay	O
and	O
work	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Masters	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
one	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
intrusted	O
with	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
had	O
frequent	O
Opportunities	O
of	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Masters	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Honest	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
always	O
found	O
very	O
just	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
nor	O
claim	O
any	O
particular	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
in	O
Widegate	O
Alley	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
ask	O
'd	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Newgate	B-place
Street	I-place
about	O
a	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jostled	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
charged	O
her-with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
under	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
Just	O
by	O
and	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
denying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
coming	O
by	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
found	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
and	O
so	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
justle	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Chain	O
glisten	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
what	O
is	O
before	O
related	O
about	O
the	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
St.	O
Martins	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
needs	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Silk	O
Handker-chiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Fan	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
formerly	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
Favour	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
had	O
free	O
access	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
frequently	O
,	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
things	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
perswaded	O
her	O
that	O
or	O
Lodgers	O
must	O
take	O
them	O
particularly	O
the	O
Fan	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mother	O
's	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	O
Mitchel	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
another	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
then	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mary	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Drawer	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
7	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
;	O
bidding	O
them	O
give	O
'em	O
to	O
Mary	O
Mitchel	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Mistress	O
there	O
with	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
her	O
Mistress	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
that	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
Sister	O
had	O
a	O
Sweetheart	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
therefore	O
brought	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Choice	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
either	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
or	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
out	O
late	O
one	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
and	O
disguised	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
another	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
come	O
to	O
himself	O
perceived	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
him	O
unless	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
early	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
prevailed	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Loving	O
Fit	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
his	O
Tobacco-box	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Box	O
there	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
seeing	O
what	O
a	O
Condition	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Shillings	O
for	O
him	O
therefore	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Box	O
till	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Norton	B-place
Falgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slye	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
7	O
s.6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
consented	O
to	O
take	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Haynes	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
who	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
3	O
Half-Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
either	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
Stockings	O
when	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Haynes	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
Breeches	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
above-mentioned	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
till	O
taken	O
:	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
mist	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Robers	O
Watkins	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
Notesthat	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Breechs	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
cost	O
:	O
and	O
called	O
Haynes	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
any	O
body	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
fully	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
rate	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Servant	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
3	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
)	O
in	O
her	O
absence	O
:	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
de	O
alt	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
Pounds	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
poor	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Linnen	O
Aprons,4	O
Stall-Cloths	O
,	O
one	O
Sheet,2	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Steal	O
and	O
8	O
pound	O
of	O
Fat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Manning	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Slaughter-House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
12	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Laths	O
that	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Morgan	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
Wash	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Slaughter	O
House	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mannings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brutfield	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Rounds	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
he	O
met	O
and	O
challenged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Bundle	O
leapt	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
persued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
one	O
Dalton	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Manning	O
's	O
.	O
Dalton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Morgan	O
,	O
one	O
Foulstone	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Foulstone	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Morgan	O
staid	O
without	O
and	O
received	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mannings	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
told	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
receive	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
'em	O
.	O
Morgan	O
denyed	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Dalton	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Manning	O
denyed	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
intrusted	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
and	O
helpt	O
to	O
maintain	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Morgan	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Mackfossett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
The	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
74	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Mackfosset	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dyer	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Chare-Woman	O
about	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
Mackfosset	O
.	O
She	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Sick	O
like	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
)	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
4	O
Rolls	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
make	O
Money	O
of	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
his	O
Sister-in-Law	O
might	O
be	O
unkind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reach	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Jelousie	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
.	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Rolls	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Rachel	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
quilted	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Andrews	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Quilt	O
ready	O
works	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
unworkt	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
and	O
no	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
value	O
7	O
s.6	O
d.5	O
pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Garring	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
handed	O
him	O
along	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
fumbling	O
about	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Rings	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocke	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Newtoners-Lane	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
Picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
nor	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
nor	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Iron	O
Shot	O
value	O
10	O
s.250	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Rope	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gapt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
his	O
Ship	O
lying	O
at	O
Shadwell	B-place
Dock	I-place
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Boy	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beason	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
two	O
Coils	O
of	O
Rope	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
Captain	O
Harrison	O
's	O
Ship	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
acquainted	O
him	O
therewith	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Ropes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beason	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
thought	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
luck	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Ropes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
restor	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
;	O
and	O
considering	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
Board	O
had	O
told	O
his	O
Captain	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
actually	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welbraham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Sarsenet	O
Hood	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
dealt	O
in	O
Old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
clean	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
for	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
home	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Masters	O
Shoes	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Informers	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compar	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
take	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Rings	O
and	O
raise	O
some	O
Money	O
on	O
it	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Fees	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
(	O
her	O
own	O
Clothes	O
being	O
ragged	O
)	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Keys	O
behind	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Rings	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drawer	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
back	O
Room	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
Money-Drawer	O
from	O
the	O
Compter	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Eve	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Eve	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
Son	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Eve	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
Oath	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
not	O
for	O
she	O
World	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Eve	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
's	O
Face	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grist	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Eve	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Coat	O
and	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
wore	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
these	O
6	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
his	O
Health	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
not	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
till	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
where	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Warrants	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
Suspcion	O
only	O
,	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Eve	O
's	O
Oath	O
the	O
last	O
positive	O
on	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Oath	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
Acquited	O
him	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
License	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
in	O
dicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carryed	O
it	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
under	O
a	O
Billiard-Table	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Direction	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Honey-Flower-Water,2	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Orange	O
Flower-Water	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Honey	O
Oyl	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
trust	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Boufette	O
,	O
a	O
Cabbin-Bell	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Pulley	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
of	O
Captain	B-pers
Torway	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
aboard	O
the	O
said	O
Vessel	O
in	O
Mr.	B-place
Fowlers	I-place
Dock	I-place
at	O
Limus	B-place
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
life	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
and	O
lockt	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Storehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
One	O
Burden	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
also	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Great	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Boufette	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
whole	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Boufette	O
way	O
Jayners	O
Work	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
old	O
Stuff	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Joyner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
his	O
Dock	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
workt	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Foreman	O
,	O
and	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
his	O
Store-houses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
keep	O
safe	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Customary	O
that	O
when	O
a	O
Vessel	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Dock	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
that	O
nothing	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Dock	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
that	O
workt	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Vessel	O
were	O
only	O
as	O
Day	O
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pay	O
'd	O
them	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
taken	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
only	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Store-house	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cocket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Journey	O
Woman	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
a	O
Manteau-maker	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
per	O
Week	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
for	O
9	O
s.5	O
d.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
made	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mothers	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transporation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Callicoe	O
Coat	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gauden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Gauden	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Tuttle	O
Bride-well	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pot	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drank	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
staid	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Pot	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
in	O
two	O
Earthen-Ware-Women	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
borrowed	O
two	O
Shillings	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
them	O
to	O
both	O
Prosecutors	O
in	O
Bride	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
denyed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
call	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ilife	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wig	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
Rest	O
before	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Sarah	O
life	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
Hungerford	O
Market	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Herbs	O
and	O
Flowers	O
the	O
Gardeners	O
had	O
brought	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
dropt	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Hungerford	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
he	O
saw	O
another	O
Person	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
feized	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
perswaded	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
some	O
there	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
his	O
Tryal	O
last	O
Sessions	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Biily	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Summer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Wash	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
40	O
Guineas	O
at	O
3	O
times	O
through	O
Necessity	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Nails	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
wherein	O
the	O
Guineas	O
lay	O
were	O
drawn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
four	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Lawes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dispute	O
of	O
Property	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Felony	O
nor	O
Robbory	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
lest	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Remedy	O
by	O
Action	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
has	O
provided	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
incted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Coat	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
missing	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
a	O
Coat	O
to	O
him	O
answering	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Lod	O
gers	O
Coat	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
towards	O
Rent	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
out	O
right	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious-Prosecution	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
his	O
Attorney	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
enrag	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Bill	O
Taxt	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
clear	O
him	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
his	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
her	O
Father	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
a	O
Landress	O
at	O
Grays-Inn	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Crowder	O
deposed	O
that	O
Morris	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
might	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Crowder	O
confirmed	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
59	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
two	O
Indictments	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
before	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
Ignoramus	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb-Inn	B-place
near	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
ride	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
overtaking	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Purse	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
soft	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
from	O
Jonas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
alias	O
Cole	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mecklin-Lace	O
value	O
19	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cunningham	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
shop	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Mecklin-Lace	O
,	O
and	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Piece	O
and	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
for	O
a	O
Child-bed-suit	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
fetch	O
a	O
a	O
Pattern	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
by	O
and	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
see	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
Fans	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
showing	O
the	O
Fans	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Visier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Visier	I-pers
tho	O
'	O
taken	O
from	O
Lewis	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Temperance	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mims	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Morebeck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnights	O
same	O
the	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
stopt	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
Gown	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
,	O
but	O
wanting	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
other	O
of	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
proper	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wales	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
Copper	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
and	O
a	O
Clasp	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rigley	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Tompkings	I-pers
his	O
Mother	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rigley	O
took	O
the	O
Boy	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Stranger	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
Victuals	O
.	O
Nothing	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Boy	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Captain	O
Buckland	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
prov	O
'd	O
an	O
untoward	O
Boy	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
missing	O
his	O
Tankard	O
found	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
Jane	B-pers
Dewberry	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Newport	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
favourably	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
receiving	O
a	O
heavier	O
Sentence	O
hereafter	O
,	O
hoping	O
that	O
going	O
abroad	O
may	O
reclaim	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Conspiracy	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ralph	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
42	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrick	I-pers
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
some	O
Body	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
opened	O
his	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Harrich	O
rusht	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
dispute	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
or	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
demanded	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
Harrich	O
snatcht	O
the	O
2	O
Guines	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
Williams	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
clapping	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
it	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Shirt	O
sleeve	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Surprise	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
follow	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrich	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
sent	O
over	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
stirring	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Richard	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
opened	O
his	O
Door	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Brusht	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
;	O
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
staying	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
Harrich	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
Bugger	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
pence	O
already	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Promise	O
of	O
a	O
further	O
Reward	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
disgrace	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Roger	O
Williams	O
the	O
Father	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
well	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Estate	O
in	O
Herefordshire	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
being	O
engag	O
'd	O
for	O
others	O
was	O
reduc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
an	O
Undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
also	O
supported	O
by	O
Friends	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
Richard	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
no	O
Business	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
several	O
Legacies	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
as	O
50	O
l.100	O
l.	O
,	O
and	O
251.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
upon	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
waited	O
for	O
their	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Richard	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Margrove	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
and	O
John	O
Wood	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
)	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
them	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
swear	O
Sodomy	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
this	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
under	O
a	O
Terror	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
great-Fear	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
s.	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
contented	O
with	O
that	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
shame	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
give	O
them	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Golden-Square	B-place
,	O
where	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
another	O
Guinea	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Wood	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
using	O
some	O
unseemly	O
Expressions	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
here	O
(	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
)	O
they	O
said	O
further	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
them	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
another	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
urg	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
was	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
with	O
threats	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
violence	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
feat	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Robbing	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Margrove	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
Young-Man's-Coffee-House	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
spent	O
the	O
last	O
6	O
Months	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Anchor	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
at	O
Old	B-place
Ford	I-place
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
workt	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackeny	I-place
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Damask	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Strawcolour	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
Silver	O
Porringer,5	O
Silver	O
Spoons,15	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets,11	O
Holland	O
Shirts,11	O
China	O
Plates	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Hutchins	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Silk	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Yellow	O
Silk	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
China	O
Bason	O
,	O
Sugar	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Claude	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
57	O
pound	O
of	O
wrought	O
Turkey	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Door	O
next	O
his	O
Garden	O
was	O
barr	O
'd	O
,	O
bolted	O
and	O
lockt	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
found	O
it	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
Pannel	O
of	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
One	O
Chetwood	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
got	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Wall	O
about	O
12	O
o	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mary-Hutchins	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Curtains	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
Clifford	O
,	O
who	O
disposing	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
Hutchins	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Clapton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Broom	O
confest	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
Indictments	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
clear	O
'd	O
Hutchins	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
cut	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
since	O
the	O
disposal	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Broom	O
of	O
the	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
as	O
Accessory	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Seaman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Margaret	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Man	O
Will	O
.	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
some	O
Fruit	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
her	O
Fruit	O
but	O
to	O
lye	O
withother	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Husband	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
a	O
handsom	O
Man	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
lov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
believed	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
and	O
haled	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backward	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
he	O
lock	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
weak	O
,	O
being	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
,	O
Months	O
gone	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
miscarryed	O
within	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
her	O
Thighs	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
home	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
apprehened	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
immediately	O
complained	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Erwin	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Smart	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Erwin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lookt	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Standing	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
Fruit	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
trembling	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
presently	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
would	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Marks	O
on	O
her	O
Arms	O
and	O
Thighs	O
,	O
and	O
than	O
she	O
Miscarry	O
'd	O
about	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Elenoar	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Lodging	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Fruit	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
,	O
Oranges	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
bruises	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
her	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
forcibly	O
entred	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
fainted	O
away	O
and	O
had	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
15	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
Lee	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
him	O
formerly	O
with	O
Fruit	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
her	O
pretended	O
Marriage	O
was	O
grown	O
impudent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
forbid	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
Christmass	O
Isabella	B-pers
Seaman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister-in-Law	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Week	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
pulling	O
and	O
haling	O
and	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
heard	O
nothing	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Lee	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
since	O
Christmass	O
James	B-pers
Cookman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
once	O
when	O
Lee	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
impudent	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Coward	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
since	O
Christmass	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
layn	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
without	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roderick	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
before	O
Christmass	O
commanded	O
,	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fetch	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
Fruit	O
,	O
nor	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
since	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
whol	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
there	O
since	O
Christmas	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
Information	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
she	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
acquainted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
(	O
neither	O
Error	O
nor	O
Smart	O
)	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
Erwin	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
before	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Criminal	O
.	O
Ann	O
Lord	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
never	O
told	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Rape	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
affronted	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
from	O
12	O
to	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
4	O
to	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
she	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
hal	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
occasion	O
her	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Miscarriage	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
from	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
till	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
Sold	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
Lee	O
say	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
Miscarry	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
hired	O
two	O
to	O
have	O
prostituted	O
their	O
Bodies	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Fencing-School	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
that	O
he	O
expected	O
him	O
there	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
a	O
Fencing-Master	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
School	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
File	O
and	O
Fence	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
improve	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
Fencing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
File	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Fight	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
,	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
abusing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
teach	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assured	O
him	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
to	O
pacifie	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
Fight	O
or	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	B-place
near	O
Marybone	B-place
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
Sacrifice	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Fight	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
inquired	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Saying	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
dangerously	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Oxendon-Street	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
own	O
Wounds	O
drest	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
of	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Leg	O
of	O
about	O
two	O
Inches	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
neither	O
Quarrelsom	O
,	O
nor	O
given	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
obliging	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Comrades	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
rid	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Lumley	O
's	O
Regiment	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Troop	O
of	O
Horse	O
Grenadiers	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Quarrelsom	O
Man	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
Fight	O
for	O
Fighting	O
Sake	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
dangerous	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
several	O
Instances	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
for	O
Paper	O
and	O
Parchment	O
on	O
the	O
Fifth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
selling	O
Counterfeited	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
finding	O
that	O
their	O
Stamps	O
were	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
buy	O
up	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Aggressors	O
,	O
and	O
prevent	O
such	O
evil	O
Practices	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
double	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Barber	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Chancery	O
Office	O
under	O
his	O
Master	O
)	O
for	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
a	O
Quire	O
,	O
whereas	O
the	O
ordinary	O
Price	O
was	O
4	O
s	O
4	O
d.	O
Whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Sydeuham	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rolles	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
with	O
more	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
fully	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
selling	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Sack	O
and	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
One	O
Hundred	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
Stationer	O
that	O
died	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
and	O
several	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Office	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
uttering	O
Counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
;	O
but	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mercy	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
believed	O
in	O
their	O
Conscience	O
from	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,10	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Aylmore	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Margrove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Licence	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
J	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,15	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mims	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Adsey	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
alias	O
Bridgeway	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Launder	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lay	O
since	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Licence	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Ruth	B-pers
Licence	I-pers
Not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THE	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
Dr.	O
Povey	O
,	O
Operator	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
now	O
follows	O
the	O
same	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
Clean	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
in	O
Artificial	O
ones	O
so	O
easie	O
,	O
neat	O
and	O
slim	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
may	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
with	O
their	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
their	O
natural	O
ones	O
;	O
and	O
fells	O
all	O
his	O
Medicines	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
in	O
his	O
Life-time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Person	O
can	O
make	O
the	O
Right	O
besides	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
A	O
pleasant	O
Dentance	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
constantly	O
used	O
;	O
it	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
decaying	O
,	O
destroying	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
She	O
bath	O
a	O
Cephalick	O
which	O
certainly	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth	O
ach	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Times	O
beyond	O
any	O
Person	O
in	O
England	O
:	O
and	O
froms	O
selaing	O
Teeth	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Tooth	O
are	O
rotten	O
or	O
uneven	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
ol	O
Holes	O
or	O
B'ack	O
Specks	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
make	O
them	O
smooth	O
,	O
even	O
,	O
found	O
and	O
white	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
shall	O
distingalm	O
where	O
the	O
Deces	O
has	O
been	O
.	O
She	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Water	O
that	O
prevents	O
any	O
Rottenness	O
from	O
selaing	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
Impostimes	O
,	O
Cankera	O
or	O
dwellings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
fastess	O
toose	O
Teeth	O
;	O
which	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
and	O
others	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
above	O
mentioned	O
Preoparations	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
)	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
and	O
Dial	O
and	O
next	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Tin-shop	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Will	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
at	O
Reasonable	O
Rates	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmond	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.8	O
l.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
cantaining	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shewing	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stenhold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
.	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Pialms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B	O
s	O
Shenson	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
D.	O
Warner	O
,	O
land	O
other	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
contalning	O
their	O
Census	O
,	O
Medim	O
and	O
Bassas	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
AEsop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflection	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
usef	O
ul	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succiuct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing	O
Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
p	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
's	O
Pens	O
Desterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
ealiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Charcters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
non	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bostley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Jurses	O
:	O
setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
with	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Anther	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Grdinences	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
steep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney	O
Coacher	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Orivett	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
direct	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cores	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-2ly	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rhenmatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Auatomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
,	O
-3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self	O
,	O
A	O
buses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Horlad	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self	O
abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-	O
LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
