TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencowe	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Yerbury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Fruchard	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
about	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Baldwins	B-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
Boys	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
a	O
Brickbat	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
their	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
wavering	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
fly	O
off	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
spin	O
cut	O
three	O
several	O
ways	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
wisht	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
cure	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
Hospital	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Callum	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Horses	O
to	O
his	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
Lothbury	B-place
a	O
Boy	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Boy	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Pistols	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Holsters	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
rid	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Pistols	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
whom	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
crasy	O
sometimes	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Parteridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leighton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
she	O
searcht	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
pardon	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Satchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
and	O
10	O
Horn	O
Handle	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tranter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
broke	O
a	O
Board	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse-door	O
in	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
and	I-place
Falcon-Inn	I-place
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
stopt	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
first	O
of	O
one	O
Person	O
,	O
then	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
taken	O
on	O
them	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Dukes-place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
7	O
Napkins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Thomas	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Box	O
of	O
Clothes	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Fellow	O
go	O
along	O
Shoemaker-row	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
)	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
complain	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Dwelling	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Burglary	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cain	O
Chair	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Chair	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Sign	O
Irons	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Trivet	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain	O
Rod	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Enticing	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Haberdasher	O
,	O
of	O
6	O
ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Keal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Print	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seduced	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Hanging-Sword-Court	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
conducted	O
him	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
another	O
Quartern	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
(	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
6	O
Pence	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Guinea	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jesson	I-pers
and	O
Tabitha	O
Ellis	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
Honest	O
Woman	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
backward	O
by	O
his	O
Turnover	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Guinea	O
.	O
-	O
Nichols	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
stealing	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
along	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
slid	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Another	O
Watchman	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hands	O
round	O
her	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Tavern	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
or	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
6d	O
.	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
mentioned	O
was	O
then	O
sick	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Sallivation	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
as	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
along	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
alias	O
Low	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Simpson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Guineas	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
28l	O
.	O
wanting	O
6	O
d.	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Press	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
underneath	O
the	O
Clothes	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
there	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
they	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
served	O
the	O
Warrant	O
on	O
them	O
they	O
confest	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
l.	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
Husband	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
on	O
themselves	O
and	O
clear	O
'd	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
that	O
Doleman	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Simpson	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
Men	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Warrant	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
trembled	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Doleman	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
tremble	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
clear	O
them	O
if	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Simpson	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
her	O
receiving	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Doleman	O
owned	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
clear	O
'd	O
Simpson	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Confession	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Four	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
Livery	B-place
Stables	I-place
in	O
Finsbury	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nurst	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
he	O
mist	O
5	O
Spurs	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
other	O
pair	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
refused	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
Iron	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
sold	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
were	O
odd	O
Spurs	O
belonging	O
to	O
3	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
by	O
comparing	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
Fellows	O
.	O
The	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Wife	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Spurs	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Young	O
Spark	O
for	O
some	O
present	O
Money	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
she	O
thought	O
)	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
signed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
28	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Tompkins	O
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wickers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Morrice	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
near	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
13	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
having	O
carried	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Mad	O
or	O
Drunken	O
Fellow	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Wowan	O
and	O
used	O
some	O
ill	O
and	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Cecil	B-place
Street	I-place
they	O
met	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
damn	O
ye	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
some	O
Fun	O
;	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
have	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
going	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
:	O
they	O
demanded	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
and	O
my	O
Partner	O
said	O
be	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prick	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Breech	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
frighten	O
'd	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
Chairs	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
theirs	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
prevented	O
his	O
hurting	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Liver	O
Colour	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
knockt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Amber	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
lookt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Four	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Chairmen	O
with	O
their	O
Poles	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Offence	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
about	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
crying	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
drunk	O
,	O
kickt	O
a	O
Watchman	O
's	O
staff	O
and	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
on	O
met	O
the	O
Chair	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
Fun	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Watchman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
pacify	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Swords	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
on	O
Liver	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
sometime	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
or	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Beaufort	O
Buildings	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Gentlemens	O
Swords	O
were	O
also	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
said	O
G	O
--	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
let	O
us	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Killed	O
.	O
Goner	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
waked	O
with	O
the	O
Noise	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
saw	O
an	O
Empty	O
Chair	O
turn	O
'd	O
over	O
;	O
the	O
Chairman	O
with	O
Poles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
advance	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
said	O
let	O
there	O
be	O
no	O
Mischief	O
done	O
,	O
shook	O
Hands	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
drew	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Swords	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Wounds	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Suit	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
in	O
particular	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Swanstone	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Chair	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Partner	O
had	O
a	O
Blow	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Pole	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pusht	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
scracht	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Pole	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
their	O
Fair	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Glasses	O
and	O
Frame	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
frightened	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
done	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Duty	O
(	O
a	O
Watchman	O
)	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
preserve	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
him	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
and	O
believes	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Assistance	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Rigby	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
for	O
killing	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
MrCeley	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hands	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
wisht	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
for	O
Age	O
on	O
his	O
Account	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
there	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Spots	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Liver	O
colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asking	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Dirt	O
on	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Blood	O
,	O
not	O
Dirt	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
end	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
took	O
a	O
Staff	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
from	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Gray	O
Clothes	O
trimmed	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
beat	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
by	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
they	O
stopt	O
the	O
Chair	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
that	O
stopt	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Five	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
amongst	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
Wound	O
given	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Grey	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Andrew	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
found	O
two	O
Wounds	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
backward	O
through	O
the	O
Thorax	O
into	O
the	O
Liver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Captain	O
Bennet	B-pers
and	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rochforts	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
till	O
near	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
home	O
all	O
alone	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Beaufort	O
Buildings	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
dozen	O
Doors	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
by	O
accidentally	O
at	O
that	O
unhappy	O
time	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Captain	O
Bennet	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
supt	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rochforts	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
3	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
parting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Rochforts	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Celey	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
Celey	O
,	O
Cook	O
's	O
and	O
Jeffery	O
's	O
Company	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Cousin	O
's	O
till	O
after	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Celey	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
very	O
Fractious	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
togo	O
and	O
scower	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
Captain	O
Bennet	O
's	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Supping	O
at	O
his	O
Mistress	O
Rochforts	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
soberly	O
before	O
him	O
about	O
Hungerford-Market	O
all	O
alone	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Squabble	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Whitish	O
Clothes	O
with	O
Silver	O
Trimming	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
who	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
Northumberland-House	O
and	O
Hungerford-Market	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
faster	O
got	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Cecil	O
Street	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
White	O
Clothes	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
make	O
two	O
Stabs	O
at	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
up	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
one	O
Man	O
in	O
Light	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
two	O
Stabs	O
,	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Liver	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Southampton	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Whitish	O
clothes	O
with	O
Silver	O
Trimming	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Watchman	O
run	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
dropt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
my	O
Companion	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Grey	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
prickt	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Half-Moon-Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
bloody	O
above	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wiped	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
but	O
no	O
Blood	O
on	O
his	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maccey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
some	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
more	O
Blood	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
on	O
the	O
Palm	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
without	O
any	O
Resistance	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Scabbard	O
.	O
One	O
Dalton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Ekins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
crying	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
.	O
-	O
Fox	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
walking	O
faster	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Fray	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drop	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
knockt	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
Ekins	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
and	O
met	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Fray	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pomroy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Jeffereyes	O
(	O
who	O
absconds	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
Rake	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
.	O
Col.	O
Carpenter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
their	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Celey	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
Bloody	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
Langley	O
and	O
Rigby	O
Swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
another	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Well-behav	O
'd	O
,	O
Peaceable	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anguers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
31	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harefoot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Trefena	B-pers
Man	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Night	O
Cap	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
44s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Bellenger	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Trefena	B-pers
Man	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
through	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
carry	O
them	O
through	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
the	O
Centinel	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
snatcht	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pomroy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Sitting	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
next	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
Girl	O
(	O
Trefena	B-pers
Man	I-pers
)	O
came	O
up	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Murder	O
:	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Band	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
just	O
run	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
Ale-House	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
Heart	O
to	O
rob	O
so	O
innocent	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Learn	O
her	O
more	O
Wit	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
and	O
Goods	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
both	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Amos	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Spoon	O
from	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
and	O
Place	O
of	O
Abode	O
ingraved	O
thereon	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Spoon	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
one	O
Smith	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Caffoy	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
3	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
Fourth	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
cut	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
jumpt	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Seats	O
in	O
his	O
Apron.-Nightingal	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Seats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Tollet	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Ravish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Theodore	B-pers
Amion	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Dangerous	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
way	O
of	O
Recovery	O
,	O
having	O
overcome	O
all	O
the	O
Accidents	O
liable	O
to	O
Trepanning	O
;	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
15	O
Days	O
after	O
receiving	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
Work	O
and	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
died	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
Irregularity	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rotier	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
of	O
great	O
Cousequence	O
desired	O
that	O
another	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
cured	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Irregularity	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
Eat	O
and	O
Drink	O
what	O
was	O
forbid	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
threatned	O
him	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
loved	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
Common	O
Correction	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Respect	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
kind	O
usage	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
lived	O
very	O
well	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
setting	O
on	O
Fire	O
the	O
Reed-Loft	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
whereby	O
that	O
Loft	O
and	O
Ten	O
Houses	O
about	O
it	O
were	O
burnt	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Yatch	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Smoak	O
went	O
on	O
Shoar	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Reed-Loft	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Tickner	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
--	O
Holman	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Reed-Loft	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
one	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
set	O
all	O
Wapping	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
Two	O
others	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Persons	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
bigger	O
Fire	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
Reed-Loft	O
several	O
Nights	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
smoakt	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Loft	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pipe	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
waking	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Fire	O
all	O
about	O
his	O
Ears	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jetson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
.	O
a	O
Black	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Lucius	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barcock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Restoration	O
Gardens	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
detained	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Rain	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
offer	O
'd	O
their	O
Service	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
safe	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
Boat	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Waterside	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
Home	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
them	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
readily	O
agreed	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
got	O
safe	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
called	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
and	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
Punch	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
venture	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
so	O
late	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
provided	O
a	O
Bed	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
enquiring	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Wife	O
fetch	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
the	O
Key	O
being	O
Secur	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
)	O
was	O
breaking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
made	O
him	O
Drunk	O
with	O
Wine	O
and	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunford	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Travilian	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
alias	O
Hastings	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
19th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
forcibly	O
lead	O
away	O
Rachael	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
worth	O
about	O
1000	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Marry	O
and	O
deflower	O
the	O
said	O
Rachel	O
Rogers	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
;	O
contrary	O
to	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
Henry	O
7.	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Brown	O
,	O
Mary	O
Dunford	O
and	O
Mary	O
Travilian	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
:	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Campbell	O
alias	O
Hastings	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
against	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rachel	O
Rogers	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
set	O
forth	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Widow	O
betwixt	O
60	O
and	O
70	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
worth	O
near	O
20	O
or	O
30000	O
l.	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
that	O
Thompson	O
assumed	O
the	O
Habit	O
of	O
a	O
Clergy-man	O
.	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
obtained	O
access	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
using	O
to	O
lend	O
Money	O
out	O
at	O
Interest	O
,	O
Thompson	O
agrees	O
with	O
Campbell	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Ratcliff-high-way	B-place
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Interest	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
thither	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Campbell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
received	O
her	O
Interest	O
Money	O
Mrs.	O
Campbell	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
dine	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
willingly	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
Thompson	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
great	O
surprise	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
sleepy	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Nap	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
undrest	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
that	O
Brown	O
tied	O
her	O
Legs	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-Posts	O
,	O
and	O
Dunford	O
and	O
Travilian	O
held	O
her	O
Arms	O
.	O
while	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Carnal-Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Consent	O
;	O
who	O
afterwards	O
took	O
her	O
Keys	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Dwelling	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
and	O
took	O
possession	O
of	O
her	O
Treasure	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
they	O
called	O
Rachel	O
Rogers	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
objected	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Thompson	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
after	O
som	O
Dispute	O
between	O
the	O
Council	O
was	O
granted	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
lawfully	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
who	O
called	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mottram	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Clergy-man	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
last	O
obtain	O
'd	O
Mrs	O
Roger	O
's	O
Consent	O
to	O
be	O
Married	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Campbell	O
's	O
in	O
Ratcliff-high-way	O
,	O
to	O
perform	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
Married	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Campbell	O
's	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Force	O
offered	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
present	O
but	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
why	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
done	O
so	O
very	O
private	O
,	O
was	O
answered	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Town	O
talk	O
.	O
The	O
Marriage	O
being	O
thus	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
complaining	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
one	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
confest	O
to	O
others	O
and	O
a	O
Mid	O
wife	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
18	O
Weeks	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Midwife	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
amis	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Boy	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Child-Bed-Linnen	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Orwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
tearing	O
and	O
cutting	O
her	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Assaulted	O
by	O
a	O
Multitude	O
of	O
Weaver	O
s	O
in	O
Red-Lion-Fields	B-place
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	O
who	O
tore	O
,	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
threatned	O
her-with	O
vile	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
naked	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Fright	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tear	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knows	O
him	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
snatcht	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
peice	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tuckt	O
up	O
his	O
Apron	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Web	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
from	O
their	O
Rage	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
her	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
tore	O
it	O
off	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mob	O
Assault	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
tear	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
put	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
where	O
Thomas	O
Painter	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
New-River	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Crowd	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
jumpt	O
off	O
the	O
Causeway	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Trouble	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
Assault	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
nor	O
tear	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
New-River	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
jumping	O
off	O
the	O
Causeway	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Crowd	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
in	O
Painter	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
tearing	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
Causeway	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Callicoe	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
a	O
Fighting	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
see	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
came	O
into	O
Trouble	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Lazenby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
16	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
6	O
Sheets	O
,	O
5	O
Holland	O
Bands	O
,	O
4	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
6	O
Muslin	O
Cravats	O
,	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
4	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
(	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
)	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
11	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
his	O
Key	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
his	O
Door	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Best	O
(	O
who	O
died	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
and	O
Smith	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Executed	O
for	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
Best	O
and	O
Smith	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chambers	O
while	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Stone	O
into	O
the	O
Lock	O
to	O
prevent	O
surprise	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
off	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
Spent	O
amongst	O
them	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Downing	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
of	O
New-Inn	B-place
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Duroy	O
Coats	O
and	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Best	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
going	O
through	O
New-Inn	O
observed	O
some	O
Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Ladder	O
which	O
stood	O
there	O
would	O
reach	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Best	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
waited	O
below	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
their	O
Booty	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
Dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shop-Book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ealand	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
stood	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
and	O
kept	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
brought	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pettifer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Saunders	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Clout	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Forbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
washt	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
who	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordinly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
5	O
Aprons	O
,	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Pinner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
.	O
The	O
Muslin	O
Pinner	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
heard	O
by	O
several	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dustan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Prunelloes	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
1718	O
.	O
Captain	O
Haddock	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Discovery	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Haddock	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Pocock	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Prunelloes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
past	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
true	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Dampney	I-pers
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
turning	O
out	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
to	O
Stepney	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Dempsey	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
prevented	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
Man	O
's	O
getting	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Prunelloes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
Pocock	O
or	O
Dampney	O
till	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
's	O
House	O
at	O
Ryegate	O
from	O
March	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Houses	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Ryegate	O
in	O
March	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
Workmen	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Family	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
the	O
nearest	O
Sunday	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
up	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
that	O
space	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
Business	O
went	O
on	O
there	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
workt	O
hard	O
at	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
sometimes	O
under	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
undertook	O
Business	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
Stone	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Medal	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Barber	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
Box	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Husler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Seats	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
draw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
within	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Seats	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Blacksby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wiggs	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopper	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
picking	O
of	O
Pockets	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
to	O
the	O
Masquerade-House	B-place
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
David	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
another	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopper	I-pers
,	O
but	O
John	O
Wigg	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Ring	O
with	O
4	O
Keys	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nest	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Charity	B-pers
Land	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
's	O
Mother	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Marks	O
she	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Examin	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
strictly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
83d	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
an	O
Alms	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
her	O
)	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Flowers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
laid	O
herself	O
on	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
an	O
Oath	O
was	O
,	O
answered	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
for	O
some	O
Flowers	O
3	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Two	O
Sundays	O
and	O
a	O
Monday	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
complained	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
till	O
her	O
Mother	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Flowers	O
in	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
any	O
Body	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Mansuer	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
Sixteenth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	O
Chapman	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boughtonn	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
Mr.	O
White	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
applied	O
himself	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
borrow	O
200	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
under	O
Age	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Estate	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
who	O
lent	O
the	O
Money	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mowson	O
a	O
Scrivener	O
to	O
negotiate	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Poland-Street	B-place
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
at	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
Message	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
Message	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
White	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
White	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
back	O
just	O
after	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Beds	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
somebody	O
knock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
awak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Legs	O
of	O
two	O
Men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
clap	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
White	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
lowermost	O
Stair	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Sword	O
found	O
but	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
setting	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
which	O
lookt	O
into	O
Mansuer	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
Chapman	O
drinking	O
Wine	O
and	O
Playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
up	O
in	O
Brown	O
Clothes	O
lined	O
with	O
Green	O
(	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
whom	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
Mansuer	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
look	O
out	O
without	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
on	O
.	O
Mr.	O
H	O
dding	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Johnson	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
or	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
dead	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
towards	O
his	O
Right	O
side	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sword	O
through	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
in	O
Silver	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
full	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
were	O
at	O
Cards	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
suppose	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
lie	O
Dead	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Belt	O
but	O
no	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pint	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hilt	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
which	O
matcht	O
with	O
the	O
Point	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
Brown	O
Clothes	O
lined	O
with	O
Green	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Toffel	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
fetcht	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
you	O
have-challenged	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
draw	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
catcht	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
clashing	O
of	O
Sword	O
;	O
saw	O
Mansuer	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
without	O
his	O
Wig	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
that	O
went	O
down	O
first	O
was	O
in	O
Brown	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Drops	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Blood	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crudeson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
with	O
a	O
Point	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Blood	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
said	O
that	O
White	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
Mansuer	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
observed	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
Wounds	O
one	O
through	O
his	O
Body	O
which	O
went	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
Ribs	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
through	O
his	O
Heart	O
and	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
9th	O
Rib	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
;	O
one	O
cross	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
directly	O
cross	O
,	O
the	O
Back	O
Orifice	O
largest	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
judg	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
backward	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
was	O
stuck	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
broke	O
on	O
Purpose	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
Fighting	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believes	O
the	O
Moment	O
be	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
through	O
his	O
Heart	O
he	O
must	O
drop	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Purchas	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
Foot	O
wide	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Purpose	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
who	O
should	O
be	O
accountable	O
for	O
4	O
Tickets	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
few	O
Nights	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
Play	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Maid	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
importunate	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
streightened	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
Fortune	O
,	O
but	O
under	O
Age	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
procure	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
Occasions	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
received	O
from	O
his	O
Guardian	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Expectation	O
gladly	O
embraced	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
many	O
promises	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
performance	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
Sincerity	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Words	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Puffs	O
of	O
Wind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
no	O
longer	O
rely	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
make	O
Application	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
Person	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Poland-Street	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
writing	O
such	O
a	O
Letter	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
without	O
Reason	O
after	O
so	O
many	O
Disappointments	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Intention	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
began	O
to	O
offer	O
fresh	O
Insults	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
a	O
ridiculons	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
other	O
scurrilous	O
Names	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
finding	O
himself	O
obliged	O
to	O
Fight	O
,	O
or	O
suffer	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
sacrificed	O
,	O
desired	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
sorry	O
Rascal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
were	O
his	O
only	O
Protection	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
instantly	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
finding	O
that	O
the	O
Passion	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
appeased	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
violently	O
rusht	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Douglas	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
without	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
had	O
wrote	O
him	O
an	O
affronting	O
Letter	O
,	O
wherein	O
be	O
says	O
that	O
his	O
Words	O
are	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
be	O
rely	O
'd	O
on	O
than	O
Puffs	O
of	O
Wind	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Mansuer	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
understanding	O
by	O
them	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
again	O
presently	O
.	O
A	O
Maid	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
used	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
naming	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
gross	O
Affront	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Drawer	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Little	O
Wild-street	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
tell	O
his	O
Wife	O
or	O
Maid	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Sword	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
leave	O
Word	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
presently	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redbourn	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
if	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
presently	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Porter	O
brought	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
same	O
Directions	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Polandstreet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
by	O
the	O
Temple	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
call	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
do	O
himself	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
extended	O
,	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
lasted	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mahon	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
accounted	O
for	O
the	O
Wounds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shipton	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
examined	O
near	O
20	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Authors	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
who	O
agree	O
that	O
persons	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Wounds	O
in	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
even	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
some	O
while	O
they	O
have	O
gone	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Paces	O
,	O
some	O
longer	O
and	O
others	O
shorter	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Lungs	O
is	O
not	O
present	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broadhurst	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Universally	O
Beloved	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
University	O
of	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
quiet	O
and	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Mary	O
Chapman	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Roger	O
Mansuer	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
,	O
against	O
whom	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murder	O
was	O
found	O
for	O
killing	O
Charles	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Dollars	B-place
Island	I-place
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	B-place
of	I-place
Sweeden	I-place
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
whom	O
a	O
Special	O
Commission	O
was	O
issued	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
several	O
material	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
that	O
Cafe	O
are	O
now	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Fleet	O
under	O
the	O
Command	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Baltick	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Commission	O
and	O
Tryal	O
was	O
Adjourned	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
alias	O
Low	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Simpson	O
,	O
Morrice	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Lazenby	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
3.	O
Frances	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Mansuer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
Lucius	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pettifer	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Husler	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Blacksby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Nelson	O
Mary	O
James	O
alias	O
Simpson	O
,	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
