TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1721	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
Eman	O
.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
Pater	O
Noster	O
Row	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jeneur	O
,	O
against	O
St	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Back	O
Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
17	O
Decemb	O
.	O
1720	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bar	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
JusticeKing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
JusticeEyre	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Mountague	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forfeit	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Allin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beamisse	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fincb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Bossel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
27	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fellowes	I-pers
Bart	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Hole	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
4	O
persons	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Crane-Rope	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wicker	O
Basket	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
2	O
Dinity	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
pecks	O
of	O
Apples	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9	O
h	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Bath	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Basket	O
from	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
crying	O
out	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
no	O
stab	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
stab	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Belley	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
Knife	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
strike	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Washfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Baptist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Weights	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
hearing	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
Phillips	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
finding	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Drawer	O
clammy	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
plainly	O
perceived	O
Birdlime	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
remembred	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
7	O
Sixpences	O
into	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
wiped	O
the	O
Holes	O
clean	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
dropt	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
Dram	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
set	O
her	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
and	O
her	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
was	O
gone	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
mist	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
marked	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
as	O
to	O
screen	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
work	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
into	O
his	O
Drawers	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
drew	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
4	O
Shillings	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
markt	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
another	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
markt	O
,	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Eye	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
owned	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
to	O
buy	O
Bread	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
intirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
alias	O
Powel	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Letter	O
Case	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithin	I-place
at	I-place
London	I-place
Stone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Phillis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Hatch	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
gone	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Braithwait	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Mug	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Canon	B-place
Street	I-place
.	O
The	O
Mug	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
as	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
)	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanour	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Martel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
new	O
fronting	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
to	O
get	O
further	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Ladder	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
Lodging	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
(	O
as	O
before	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
Five	O
Pound	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Clouts	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
36s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Latch	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
2	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
confes	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
had	O
Pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisner	O
in	O
Excuse	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
committed	O
any	O
Crime	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
alias	O
Hoskins	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell-Metal	O
Mortar	O
of	O
103	O
pound	O
weight	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Abraham	O
stole	O
the	O
Mortar	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
moved	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
Abraham	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elton	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
jumpt	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
retaken	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mortar	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
Elton	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Abraham	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
Elson	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Abraham	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
workt	O
Pockets	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Portress	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Goods	O
gon	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
Lace	O
Head	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Red	O
Cows	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Bullock	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Codner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Books	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Gustavus	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
3	O
Books	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
6	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Evidence	O
observing	O
the	O
Titles	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
them	O
which	O
Booksellers	O
generally	O
past	O
for	O
the	O
ready	O
sincing	O
out	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Books	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Favour	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Books	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
wore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
indiposed	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Simpsom	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
that	O
the	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
for	O
Two	O
Months	O
before	O
this	O
matter	O
happen	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
good	O
Man	O
before	O
,	O
His	O
Master	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forcd	O
for	O
2	O
Months	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
to	O
employ	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
however	O
,	O
and	O
imployed	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
little	O
matters	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
his	O
Disorder	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
Honest	O
having	O
entrusted	O
him	O
frequently	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Case	O
,	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
fames	O
Burstal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
freely	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Foster-Lane-end	B-place
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
always	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
Jonathon	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
that	O
Watch	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1719	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
formerly	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Lord	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
by	O
Place	O
and	O
woul	O
d	O
lay	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Blue	O
Cloak	O
to	O
lay	O
her	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
our	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
since	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
lay	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
called	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
taking	O
her	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Creech	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
pieces	O
of	O
China	O
and	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Tiking	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Creech	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
brought	O
the	O
Key	O
up	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
;	O
that	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
immediately	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Tiking	O
hid	O
at	O
length	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
ript	O
his	O
own	O
Bed	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Mr.Jones	O
confirmed	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
it	O
beforehand	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
expectation	O
of	O
Favour	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
Tiking	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Tiking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
in	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Broker	O
would	O
lend	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
15	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
take	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
having	O
sav	O
'd	O
up	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tiking	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Burglary	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
Bermudas	O
Straw	O
Hats	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Collins	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Anthony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Collins	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Anthony	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Vlevet	O
Hood	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Linten	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	O
How	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
181	O
yards	O
of	O
Tillers	O
,	O
value	O
to	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
Servant	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Tillets	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
directed	O
in	O
large	O
Letters	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Ratford	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
those	O
Goods	O
were	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Ratford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Ratford	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
at	O
Stocks	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
rested	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ratford	O
gone	O
by	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
the	O
whilst	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
accordingly	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
there	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
Coach	O
and	O
drove	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
sometime	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
King	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
Tillers	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
who	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
those	O
Tillers	O
of	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Tiller	O
Painter	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
;	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
not	O
doubting	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
acquainted	O
before	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
)	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
selling	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
Stamp	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
there	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
two	O
Boys	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
Whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Marsal	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
some	O
Friends	O
made	O
diligent	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
an	O
obstinate	O
Resistance	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
confest	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Marshal	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lauter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkershief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Abbat	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
afterwards	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Names	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Richard	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
about	O
to	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
William	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
over	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
who	O
pusht	O
himself	O
against	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
Violence	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
them	O
keep	O
off	O
.	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
Pickpockets	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
them	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Myer	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
past	O
through	O
Cheapside	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Voice	O
say	O
,	O
Keep	O
off	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
pick	O
any	O
pocket	O
?	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
Wil	O
.	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
recourse	O
to	O
his	O
Cane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Will	O
.	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
Dog	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
Jostled	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
fell	O
a	O
Caining	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
they	O
pay	O
their	O
Fine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smithfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feburary	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Corless	I-pers
;	O
and	O
3	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Thread	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	O
Corless	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whilst	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Boy	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Settle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
perceiving	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
to	O
hang	O
down	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Katherine	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Seals	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Furoy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Homston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
shirt	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Long	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
Ellis	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
LLoyd	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
a	O
Neck	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
4	O
Books	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Clark	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sells	O
Coals	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
Leather	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
d	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
Gardens	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
with	O
the	O
Bible	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Clothes	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
in	O
Lambs	O
Conduit	O
Fields	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Megan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Halls	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Halls	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
their	O
Apprentice	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Snuff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Porter	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
fear	O
his	O
Master	O
should	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ann	O
de	O
la	O
Fountain	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handle	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Huets	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
imployed	O
as	O
a	O
Charewoman	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
work	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
also	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
behind	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Compter	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
preparing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bath	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spurs	O
Her	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Buttons	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Dickinson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sending	O
her	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
she	O
staid	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
a	O
Beast	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Buttons	O
and	O
Buckles	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pouncer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
with	O
an	O
Oyster	O
Woman	O
,	O
Drank	O
freely	O
and	O
left	O
29	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
he	O
Hand	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pouncer	I-pers
put	O
her	O
upon	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Excuse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crocket	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
reaching	O
the	O
Church-Yard-Wall	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Corporal	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
coming	O
by	O
accidentally	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Howd	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landlord	O
)	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
getting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Bed	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
(	O
or	O
do	O
)	O
any	O
Mischief	O
;	O
that	O
with	O
much	O
adoe	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
undrest	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Breeches	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Pound	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
advised	O
his	O
Landlord	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
found	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
who	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
Four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
saved	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pay	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Captain	O
and	O
others	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Friendship	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Belam	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Internt	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Shirt	O
and	O
1	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Handerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
Lines	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
Mrs	O
Benn	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Business	O
there	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
by	O
one	O
who	O
accidentally	O
came	O
for	O
an	O
empty	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Oats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Fitzwicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Tench	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Well-Boat	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Fish	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mistress	O
bought	O
6	O
Tench	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
or	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Westmoreland	I-pers
.	O
Edward	O
Lawrence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Ropes	O
which	O
bound	O
the	O
Hay	O
where	O
cut	O
while	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Marshes	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hay	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Honer	O
's	O
Stable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Honer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
Coult	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
)	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
His	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Hay	O
was	O
owned	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Honer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bound	O
up	O
the	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
particular	O
make	O
of	O
the	O
Bands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
the	O
Hay	O
it	O
being	O
bright	O
and	O
Brown	O
(	O
some	O
Mow-burnt	O
)	O
mix	O
'd	O
together	O
John	O
Ivans	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Ivans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
with	O
two	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
from	O
the	O
Marshes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Quartern	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
,	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
1	O
Quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
a	O
Dinity	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Hoopt	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Hosborough	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Richins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
)	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
when	O
to	O
her	O
great	O
surprise	O
the	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
his	O
Wife	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
under	O
some	O
Holley-Trees	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Quartern	O
Pot	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
Pails	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Holleys	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Quartern	O
Pot	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
by	O
a	O
special	O
Commission	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
33	O
Hen	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Chap.23	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Certain	O
Island	O
near	O
the	O
Dahlers	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Sweden	B-place
in	O
parts	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
did	O
Murder	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
Bignell	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
upon	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
his	O
Breast	O
above	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Clement	O
Courland	O
Master	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ships	O
the	O
Worcester	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1719	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bignell	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
First	O
Lieutenant	O
Mr.	O
Cannon	O
(	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ely	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
first	O
Mate	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Dess	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Papers	O
drawn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
them	O
(	O
which	O
Papers	O
were	O
for	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
the	O
Deceesed	O
's	O
Share	O
of	O
a	O
Prime	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
on	O
the	O
Coast	O
of	O
Scotland	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
another	O
time	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
no	O
longer	O
be	O
make	O
a	O
property	O
of	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
refuse	O
to	O
sign	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
Husst	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
his	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
)	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
26th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
heard	O
several	O
abusive	O
Words	O
pass	O
between	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
from	O
Capt	O
.	O
Boyle	O
(	O
the	O
Commander	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
)	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
be	O
might	O
walk	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
before	O
Noon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
Boat	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Shore	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
himself	O
Justice	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
were	O
best	O
let	O
alone	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
defer	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
conse	O
quence	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
light	O
of	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Mates	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
leave	O
for	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
Shore	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
(	O
being	O
Sunday	O
the	O
27th	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
arose	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
gon-a-Shore	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
Boat	O
came	O
aboard	O
with	O
the	O
Corps	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
several	O
Wounds	O
some	O
clear	O
through	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
some	O
Questions	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
were	O
very	O
great	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
both	O
Money	O
and	O
Necessaties	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
give	O
Foul	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
Quarrelsome	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
ill	O
Language	O
be	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behaved	O
himself	O
all	O
along	O
very	O
Civilly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Surgeon	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
the	O
Worcester	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Mate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
1719	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
Papers	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sign	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Times	O
and	O
Seasons	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
be	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Property	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deseased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
being	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
huss	O
'd	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
also	O
came	O
and	O
walked	O
)	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Servant	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
turns	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
began	O
to	O
reproach	O
each	O
other	O
with	O
normal	O
Obligations	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
greatly	O
favour	O
'd	O
in	O
being	O
admitted	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
to	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
Lieutenants	O
aboard	O
other	O
Ships	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
this	O
and	O
received	O
as	O
many	O
Favours	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
officer	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
insist	O
upon	O
Privileges	O
but	O
what	O
are	O
we	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
ashore	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Charles	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
and	O
you	O
are	O
Edward	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
be	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
like	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
but	O
Scold	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
after	O
wards	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
mitigate	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
advising	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
used	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
Drink	O
is	O
no	O
Excuse	O
for	O
Rudeness	O
;	O
he	O
sha	O
n't	O
lye	O
in	O
my	O
Cabbin	O
any	O
longer	O
nor	O
will	O
I	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
challenged	O
me	O
;	O
nor	O
will	O
I	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
huss	O
'd	O
into	O
Compliance	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
walking	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
the	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
Mr	O
Weston	O
(	O
the	O
Second	O
Lieutenant	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Can	O
of	O
Elip	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
,	O
but	O
Capt.Boyle	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
on	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
do	O
himself	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
thereby	O
making	O
an	O
Uriah	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Challenged	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
whole	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
him	O
Justice	O
he	O
would	O
post	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Coward	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
Difference	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Protection	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
himself	O
Justice	O
let	O
the	O
Consequence	O
be	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
Morrow	O
was	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
Child	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
morrow	O
is	O
my	O
Birth-Day	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
30	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
and	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
my	O
Death	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
Life	O
so	O
left	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
he	O
hoped	O
that	O
would	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
reply	O
'd	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
will	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Mischief	O
that	O
might	O
arise	O
from	O
the	O
aforementioned	O
Dispute	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
Paper	O
and	O
prevent	O
the	O
mischief	O
which	O
might	O
otherwise	O
ensue	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
spent	O
his	O
Breach	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
consistent	O
with	O
his	O
Honour	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
sign	O
himself	O
a	O
Coward	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
huss	O
'd	O
and	O
bully	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Compliance	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
his	O
Principles	O
were	O
as	O
honest	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
Wrong	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nor	O
any	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Paper	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
used	O
him	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
forgive	O
him	O
nor	O
Drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
sit	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
6	O
o	O
,	O
Clock	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
8	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
whereof	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
under	O
the	O
Armpit	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
judged	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
aboard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drest	O
a	O
Wound	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Ely	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
aboard	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
might	O
have	O
prevented	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
serviceable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
used	O
to	O
jangle	O
with	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
once	O
threatened	O
to	O
Cane	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
meet	O
him	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
reply	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
served	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Well-behaved	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
(	O
Midshipman	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ask	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
hasty	O
for	O
his	O
signing	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
signing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
time	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Property	O
of	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Challenged	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
the	O
Boat	O
is	O
now	O
boisting	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
ashore	O
with	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Officer	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
post	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
will	O
talk	O
and	O
Chatter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Sick	O
Men	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
my	O
Captain	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
Capt	O
.	O
Boyle	O
's	O
come	O
aboard	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
(	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
first	O
Mate	O
)	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Morning	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
No	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
Boat	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
1719	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
a	O
Cann	O
of	O
Elip	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
Door	O
and	O
having	O
just	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Boat	O
was	O
lower	O
'd	O
and	O
Mann	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
the	O
Cox-swain	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
as	O
much	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
of	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
That	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
presently	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Coxswain	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
his	O
Cost	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Boat	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bignell	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Boat	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
ashore	O
again	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
second	O
Lieutenant	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Wiston	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
voluntarily	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
(	O
and	O
pointed	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wiston	O
's	O
Cabbin-Door	O
)	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Navis	I-pers
(	O
Coxswain	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1719	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Man	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
put	O
him	O
ashore	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
island	O
which	O
the	O
Ship	O
lay	O
against	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
him	O
ashore	O
be	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
give	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
walking	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Message	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
ashore	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
to	O
his	O
Sorrow	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
red	O
Bays	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
came	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
row	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
Deceased	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
mind	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
naked	O
Breasted	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Boats	O
Crew	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Pistols	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
shook	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
Answer	O
he	O
made	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
we	O
shall	O
decide	O
this	O
matter	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
Pistol	O
Cartridges	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
take	O
his	O
Choice	O
of	O
the	O
Pistols	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Left	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Pistols	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stooping	O
upon	O
some	O
Occasion	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
with	O
it	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
leapt	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
over	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
got	O
out	O
his	O
Sword	O
made	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Passes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Sword	O
faulter	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
continued	O
pushing	O
at	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Legs	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Evidence	O
called	O
the	O
Boat	O
's	O
Crew	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
Villian	O
hath	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Knaves	I-pers
,	O
Rowed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ashore	O
and	O
saw	O
what	O
past	O
there	O
)	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
striking	O
the	O
Deceased	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Stabbing	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
The	O
Villian	O
hath	O
Kill	O
'd	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Sword	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Caxman	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
no	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
(	O
Second	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
)	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
tell	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
lov	O
'd	O
Fighting	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
enough	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
quarrel	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Officer	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Captain	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
when	O
assured	O
the	O
Captain	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
for	O
his	O
Health	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Island	O
he	O
readily	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
the	O
Pistol	O
Cartridges	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Spit	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
Villain	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Money	O
when	O
at	O
Sheernesse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
foul	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Quarrelsome	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
challenge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Officer	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
had	O
bent	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
gave	O
Armouror	O
to	O
straighten	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
view	O
of	O
fighting	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
that	O
Sword	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Good	O
Humour	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
made	O
up	O
several	O
Quarrels	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Young	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Boat	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
at	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
before	O
Four	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
asking	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
on	O
Shore	O
for	O
his	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
Birth	O
Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Symonds	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
relating	O
to	O
a	O
Prize	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Coast	O
of	O
Scotland	O
bound	O
from	O
Rotterdam	O
to	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
concerning	O
that	O
Affair	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
condemn	O
'd	O
as	O
Prize	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
applying	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
assign	O
over	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
the	O
Rogues	O
and	O
ill	O
Names	O
imaginable	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Foul	O
Mouth	O
'd	O
,	O
censurious	O
Man	O
as	O
ever	O
God	O
put	O
Gut	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
to	O
Capt	O
Boyle	O
,	O
abused	O
his	O
Friends	O
that	O
Fed	O
and	O
Clothed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Body	O
else	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
wore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shirts	O
and	O
borrowed	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ingratiated	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Sailors	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
against	O
the	O
Officers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
second	O
Lieutenant	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Gibraltor	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
Months	O
,	O
while	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
first	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
affronted	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
on	O
Board	O
;	O
struck	O
and	O
kickt	O
him	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Discharge	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
challenge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
replyed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
better	O
than	O
to	O
fight	O
his	O
Superior	O
Officer	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
(	O
Armourer	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Weston	O
brought	O
a	O
Sword	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
streighten	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
dent	O
in	O
the	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
File	O
to	O
smooth	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
Sharpen	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Sword	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
18	O
Wounds	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
was	O
Mortal	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
2	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
Three	O
Inches	O
and	O
half	O
deep	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Four	O
inches	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
stood	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
others	O
afterward	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
made	O
some	O
Resistance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
foul-mouth	O
,	O
malicious	O
,	O
quarrelsom	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
which	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Four	O
or	O
Five	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
impartial	O
hearing	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boice	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Bags	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
thrust	O
into	O
a	O
Truss	O
of	O
Hay	O
in	O
the	O
Hayloft	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
he	O
had	O
dug	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
in	O
another	O
Stable	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Vaults	O
till	O
all	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
himself	O
out	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	O
any	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
Sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Othrinton	B-pers
Wratham	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1080	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sailcloth	O
,	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Lacey	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mannel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
after	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hides	O
Warehouse	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
observed	O
some	O
Boards	O
loose	O
that	O
cover	O
'd	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confest	O
10	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Wratham	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boards	O
and	O
Lacey	O
another	O
;	O
their	O
several	O
Confessions	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Williams	O
Hodge	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lacey	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Cornish	O
Mount	O
at	O
Ratstaff	O
Cross	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
earn	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
remove	O
some	O
Goods	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
Judgment	O
being	O
executed	O
on	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Barge	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Barge	O
lay	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
-	O
Lacey	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Cornish	O
Mount	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
earn	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
other	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Lacey	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
Wratham	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
16	O
Guineas	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lever	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Wratham	O
13	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Wratham	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
and	O
Lacey	O
as	O
Accessory	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Divine	I-pers
Durvine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniosly	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tweeds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felouiously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Stuff	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
3	O
Stuff	O
Basis	O
of	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Delaver	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Halliwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
about	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
ask	O
no	O
Questions	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
wanted	O
more	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
he	O
would	O
Mob	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
in	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
so	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Neckcloth	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
beckon	O
'd	O
to	O
2	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Savoy	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
once	O
before	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
into	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
People	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Somebody	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
held	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
confirmed	O
their	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
owning	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
and	O
promised	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
40	O
s.	O
Cole	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
in	O
Fester-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
keep	O
him	O
without	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
him	O
afterwards	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Evidence	O
to	O
corroborate	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Maccopney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Bucknel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Comb	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hand	O
kerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
double	O
Clout	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
the	O
twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Asop	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Bestock	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roebottom	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ramlett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roman	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Field	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
3	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Lace	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ockendon	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
(	O
about	O
Sixteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Youth	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Age	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
charged	O
with	O
Gunpowder	O
and	O
small	O
Shot	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Arm	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
killing	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
by	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Fowling	O
together	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
Shot	O
at	O
a	O
Bird	O
in	O
a	O
Tree	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
not	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
understood	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
his	O
shooting	O
at	O
the	O
Bird	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rather	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
25	O
Foot	O
distance	O
between	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
when	O
he	O
Shot	O
off	O
his	O
Gun	O
and	O
that	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
no	O
scattering	O
Shot	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Clothes	O
were	O
burnt	O
with	O
the	O
Flash	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gun	O
being	O
heard	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
observed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
own	O
Gun	O
which	O
shot	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Cheston	O
of	O
Hadley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
with	O
Four	O
Horses	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mother	O
and	O
Sister	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
between	B-place
Potters	I-place
Bar	I-place
and	I-place
Barnet	I-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
a	O
Light	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
Purses	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Watches	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sister	O
gave	O
him	O
their	O
Purses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
,	O
Sister	O
and	O
Coachman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Who	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Tristrum	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Coxed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
by	O
entring	O
into	O
a	O
Confederacy	O
and	O
combining	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
their	O
Prices	O
to	O
excessive	O
Rates	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
,	O
Edward	O
6	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
Club	O
at	O
the	O
Pied	B-place
Bull	I-place
near	O
Bridewell	B-place
,	O
(	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
the	O
Journeymen	O
's	O
Club	O
)	O
where	O
they	O
summon	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
young	O
Journeymen	O
to	O
meet	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
raise	O
their	O
Prices	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Paper	O
Printed	O
of	O
what	O
Prices	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Curriers	O
Company	O
summond	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
made	O
them	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
any	O
ways	O
agrieved	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Clerk	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
Stature	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
By	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
own	O
Oaths	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
their	O
By	O
Laws	O
only	O
as	O
Bugbears	O
;	O
deliver	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
of	O
the	O
Prices	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
abide	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
Meetings	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Prices	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
William	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Sunderland	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
requiring	O
him	O
to	O
Subscribe	O
for	O
a	O
Book	O
entitled	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Illustrious	O
and	O
Royal	O
House	O
of	O
Hanover	O
under	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
Paper	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Earl	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
his	O
Nephew	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Earl	O
's	O
Brother	O
's	O
or	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Son	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Spencer	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Family	O
too	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
imposed	O
upon	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
had	O
no	O
Brother	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Conner	O
(	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Sheriff	O
Billers	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Trick	O
and	O
got	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
impudently	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
twice	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Fined	O
,	O
and	O
Imprisoned	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
reclaim	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
Fined	O
him	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
Three	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
Othrinton	B-pers
Wrathan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
5.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Furoy	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ramlett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Codner	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
22.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Washfield	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Num	I-pers
alias	O
Powel	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
alias	O
Hoskins	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Oates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
Ellis	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
alias	O
Lewis	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boice	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Ann	O
de	O
la	O
Fountain	O
,	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Fined	I-pers
5	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
they	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Tristram	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Coxed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
William	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
Fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Just	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Christian	O
Housholders	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Family	O
Worship	O
,	O
undertaken	O
upon	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Cursed	O
Family	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
short	O
Tract	O
shewing	O
the	O
pernicious	O
Influence	O
of	O
Prayerless	O
Houses	O
upon	O
this	O
Church	O
and	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	B-pers
Risley	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
10	O
d.	O
Printed	O
for	O
R.	O
Ford	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Oldfields	O
Discourse	O
on	O
the	O
Trinity	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Arche	O
's	O
Sermon	O
Preach	O
'd	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
Wells	O
,	O
August	O
1	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
Sermon	O
of	O
Readiness	O
for	O
the	O
Coming	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
Remarks	O
on	O
Dr.	O
Gale	O
's	O
Letter	O
of	O
Infant-Baptism	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
ROBERT	O
WHITLEDGE	O
AT	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ave	O
Marie	O
lane	O
,	O
selleth	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
,	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Three	O
New	O
Large	O
Folio	O
Bibles	O
,	O
Printed	O
at	O
Oxford	O
:	O
The	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Books	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Start	O
's	O
Cutts	O
Van	O
der	O
Cachte	O
's	O
best	O
Cutts	O
,	O
or	O
painted	O
Cutts	O
,	O
(	O
rul	O
'd	O
or	O
unrul	O
'd	O
)	O
or	O
without	O
;	O
Bound	O
in	O
Shaggreen	O
,	O
with	O
Silver	O
Work	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Manner	O
of	O
Binding	O
,	O
neat	O
pocket	O
Bibles	O
with	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
Concordance	O
:	O
Books	O
of	O
D	O
tion	O
,	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
History	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
,	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Charity	O
(	O
and	O
other	O
)	O
Schools	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
Large	O
,	O
Books	O
of	O
H	O
,	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Letter-Cases	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
and	O
Retale	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Also	O
W	O
Bibles	O
Common-Prayers	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
A.	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
Spelling	O
Book	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
more	O
easy	O
and	O
regular	O
Method	O
of	O
teaching	O
to	O
Spell	O
,	O
Read	O
and	O
Write	O
true	O
English	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Urmston	I-pers
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
The	O
8th	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
useful	O
Additions	O
and	O
Alterations	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Child	O
may	O
be	O
taught	O
to	O
read	O
English	O
perfectly	O
by	O
this	O
Book	O
alone	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
unnecessary	O
Charge	O
of	O
other	O
Books	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Vocabulary	O
,	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
;	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
new	O
Method	O
proper	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Learner	O
with	O
Things	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Pure	O
Latin	O
Words	O
,	O
adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
26	O
pictures	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
The	O
4th	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
,	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Grammar	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shadwell	I-pers
's	O
five	O
new	O
Plays	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
lately	O
acted	O
at	O
the	O
Theater	O
Royal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Hasty	O
Wedding	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Intrieguing	O
Squire	O
,	O
a	O
Comedy	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
S	O
Prince	O
,	O
a	O
Comedy	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Rotherick	O
O	O
Connor	O
,	O
King	O
of	O
Connaught	O
,	O
a	O
Tragedy	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Plotting	O
Lovers	O
,	O
or	O
Dismal	O
Squire	O
,	O
a	O
Farce	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Irish	O
Hospitality	O
,	O
or	O
Vertue	O
Rewarded	O
,	O
a	O
Comedy	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmond	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
Christian	O
Monitor	O
,	O
containing	O
an	O
Earnest	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
:	O
With	O
some	O
Directions	O
in	O
order	O
thereto	O
.	O
Written	O
in	O
a	O
plain	O
and	O
easie	O
Stile	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
but	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
concerning	O
the	O
Excellency	O
and	O
Usefulness	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Prayer	O
.	O
Preached	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Beveridge	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
(	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
St.	O
Asaph	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Opening	O
of	O
the	O
Parish-Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Peter	O
's	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
The	O
Twenty-fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
price	O
3	O
d.	O
but	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Sacramental	O
Covenanting	O
with	O
Christ	O
:	O
Shewing	O
the	O
Ungodly	O
their	O
Contempt	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Covenant	O
.	O
And	O
calling	O
them	O
(	O
not	O
to	O
a	O
Profanation	O
of	O
this	O
Holy	O
Ordinance	O
,	O
but	O
)	O
to	O
an	O
Understanding	O
,	O
Serious	O
,	O
Entire	O
Dedication	O
of	O
themselves	O
to	O
God	O
in	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Covenant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Believing	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
J.	O
Rawlet	B-pers
,	O
B.	B-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Monitor	O
.	O
