TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terniner	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
Octob	O
.	O
1720	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lassoone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Marriner	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Halloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Coultson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bedall	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pashley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgower	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fowlis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thewlis	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prime	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Country	O
Lodgins	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bibbin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
but	O
designed	O
to	O
have	O
fetcht	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
Church	I-place
a	O
Gentleman	O
ask	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Husbands	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
through	O
Cornhill	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Church	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
so	O
quick	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
Bag	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
and	O
Cassock	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lukes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Small	O
Coal	O
Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
who	O
laid	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
,	O
)	O
that	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
Sack	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lombard-Street	O
to	O
Threadneedle-Street	O
,	O
where	O
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
crying	O
out	O
Thieves	O
)	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Small	O
Coal	O
Boy	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy	B-pers
Shop	I-pers
next	O
the	O
Bulk	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Threadneedle-Street	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Small	O
Coal	O
Boy	O
(	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
now	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
Horse	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Lombard-Street	O
end	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
.	O
who	O
being	O
then	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Change	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Bulk	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
to	O
Threadneedle-Street	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fellowes	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Schingle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
set	O
his	O
Foot	O
before	O
him	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
and	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
jostled	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
hurt	O
and	O
bruised	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
yet	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
lighting	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
two	O
Gentlewomen	O
along	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
between	O
them	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jostle	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Three	O
others	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
also	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tompion	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Tompion	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Cole	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Temple-Stairs	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Two	O
Pence	O
to	O
Pepper-Alley	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
room	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Tompion	O
sat	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
the	O
Purse	O
of	O
Guineas	O
were	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
rusling	O
about	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
thought	O
might	O
be	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
their	O
Hoops	O
incommoding	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
to	O
Dowgate	O
,	O
Ann	O
Tompion	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
.	O
we	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
Writings	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
without	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
wo	O
n't	O
hinder	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
but	O
call	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Oars	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
landed	O
at	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
feeling	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Waterman	O
mist	O
her	O
Purse	O
of	O
Guineas	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Tuly-Street	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
immediately	O
to	O
Pepper-Alley	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
the	O
Waterman	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
served	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
if	O
be	O
knew	O
any	O
Thief	O
Taker	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Black-Fryers	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
(	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
)	O
Mr	O
Murrel	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Black	O
and	O
White	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
;	O
where	O
telling	O
her	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Fat	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Smiling	O
Countenance	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Two	O
Tail	O
'd	O
wig	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Red	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Locket	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
Bobs	O
in	O
her	O
Ears	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
within	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
went	O
again	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
lent	O
her	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
9	O
Moidores	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
Profit	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brandon	O
's	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
11	O
Guineas	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bladen	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
Stairs	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
landed	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
swore	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
Tuly-Street	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Black-Fryers	O
and	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murrels	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	O
Stairs	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Waterman	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
seeming	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Note	O
there	O
promising	O
a	O
Reward	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
appear	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
who	O
could	O
produce	O
him	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
Rotherhith	O
(	O
where	O
they	O
Live	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Still-Yard	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bladen	O
's	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Bladen	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Mariner	O
and	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Dealings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
confirmed	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Moidores	O
and	O
her	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Waterman	O
(	O
Roberts	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murrel	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
past	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Murrel	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
taker	O
,	O
confirmed	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
swore	O
before	O
relating	O
to	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
who	O
invited	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
for	O
a	O
Thief-Taker	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Thief-Taker	O
himself	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
whither	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
have	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secure	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
gave	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tompion	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
confirmed	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
telling	O
her	O
Story	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
for	O
she	O
(	O
Ann	O
Tompion	O
)	O
was	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
ingenious	O
Pick-Pocket	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Borrowing	O
a	O
Sword	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
one	O
Woman	O
washing	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
another	O
washing	O
her	O
Feet	O
.	O
That	O
sometime	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
again	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
(	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Tompion	O
her	O
Husband	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
readily	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Sword	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
Devil	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Tompion	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
(	O
though	O
conceal	O
'd	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
)	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
she	O
met	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mrs.	O
Tompion	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Gown	O
of	O
her	O
Husbands	O
on	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
Mrs	O
Cole	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cooks	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Tompion	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
several	O
Disappointments	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
who	O
owed	O
her	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Croydon	O
Fair	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
whether	O
she	O
said	O
11	O
Guineas	O
or	O
13	O
;	O
nor	O
whether	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
received	O
it	O
that	O
Day	O
or	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tompion	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
in	O
Black	O
and	O
White	O
Court	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
House	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Croydon	O
Fair	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Linnet	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
craydans	O
Fair	O
from	O
11	O
till	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stay	O
there	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
arrested	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
but	O
clear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
Writings	O
for	O
her	O
safety	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
till	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Tompkins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Tompion	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
(	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
Day	O
till	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Facey	O
paid	O
him	O
13	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
That	O
though	O
be	O
workt	O
above	O
Stairs	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
often	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
Light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
constantly	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gooseman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Croydon	O
Fair	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
wore	O
that	O
Day	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murrels	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
a	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
used	O
some	O
Invectives	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Grudge	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Benchior	O
Higgins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Murrels	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Murrel	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Spleen	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
for	O
them	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
Men	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Tompion	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Old	O
fashion	O
Silver	O
,	O
6	O
Silver	O
Button	O
's	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Magick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
William	O
Reynolds	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
in	O
Trust	O
for	O
her	O
Nephew	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eves	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Mothers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
she	O
mist	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eaves	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Recorder	O
's	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
a	O
Shutter	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
a	O
Tankard	O
in	O
6	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
that	O
Day	O
was	O
Sevennight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Weaver	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Eves	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
how	O
her	O
Mistress	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
again	O
betimes	O
on	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Confusion	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Owen	O
)	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
search	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Old	O
Fashion	O
Silver	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Socket	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
a	O
Tankard	O
for	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
bid	O
the	O
Constable	O
move	O
a	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
without	O
the	O
Lid	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
weighed	O
18	O
Ounces	O
without	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Eves	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
for	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Lid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
askt	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
search	O
Mr.	O
Reynold	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
pulled	O
our	O
a	O
small	O
Drawer	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Glass	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
Rings	O
and	O
Trifles	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Old	O
Fashion	O
Silver	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
Mugg	O
,	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
Press	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Shutter	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
there	O
without	O
the	O
Lid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
the	O
Lid	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
lately	O
,	O
the	O
Pin	O
looking	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
filed	O
within	O
3	O
Days	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
above	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
which	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
G	O
M	O
M	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eves	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
also	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
and	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Eves	O
at	O
the	O
Market	O
price	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
7	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
18	O
s.	O
value	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Old	O
Plate	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Owen	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
Eves	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Eves	O
put	O
the	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
how	O
much	O
Silver	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
then	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Glasses	O
in	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drest	O
very	O
clean	O
and	O
tight	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Hood	O
or	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
White	O
Apron	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
Father	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
something	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
fair	O
Character	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Dealings	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
Ounce	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
Solder	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
more	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
,	O
Brother	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eggleton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Assistants	O
of	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
pitcht	O
on	O
for	O
particular	O
Matters	O
in	O
Assays	O
and	O
valuing	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
Judgment	O
and	O
Honesty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
workt	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
always	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
5	O
l.	O
per	O
Ounce	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
by	O
buying	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
consdering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
William	O
Reynold	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Elizabeth	O
Eves	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
at	I-place
Quern	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hankerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tilliard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Conduit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Cheapside	B-place
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Fruit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pickpockets	O
followed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
haste	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
therewith	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rushing	O
by	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Vellom	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Change	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
Mr	O
,	O
Levit	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Crowd	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
much	O
Searching	O
and	O
Stir	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
in	O
a	O
Black	O
Coat	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
Genteely	O
Drest	O
in	O
Brown	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Levit	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
;	O
that	O
be	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
round	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Crowd	O
gathering	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
Keepers	O
refuse	O
them	O
at	O
their	O
Peril	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
searched	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Black	O
Clothes	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
using	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
the	O
Clothes	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
Old	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Poore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Winckworth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
against	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
in	O
Fleet-Street	B-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Burying	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisner	O
jostle	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Hankerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
Prisner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Andrews	B-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwing	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ravenal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Purdew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
.	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Carolus	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gaudin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Cripplegate	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saluted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Countryman	O
?	O
Wo	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
towards	O
Islington	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
in	O
Golden	B-place
Lane	I-place
she	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
there	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Backside	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
Ordinary	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
had	O
Pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
(	O
worth	O
7	O
l.	O
)	O
to	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
Shilling	O
till	O
he	O
redeemed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
there	O
while	O
he	O
opened	O
and	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
they	O
'd	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
her	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Bobs	O
for	O
her	O
Ears	O
and	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
good	O
Clothes	O
on	O
then	O
though	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
Grab	O
when	O
he	O
drank	O
the	O
Brandy	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
told	O
them	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
went	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
just	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
their	O
directions	O
they	O
followed	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
poor	O
Garret	O
wherein	O
were	O
a	O
few	O
Flocks	O
and	O
Rags	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
lookt	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
owed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
those	O
Clothes	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
Gold	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Baine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coffering	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
And	O
Jane	O
Baine	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
Knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
alone	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
between	O
10	O
to	O
11	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Allen	O
came	O
and	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
short	O
Apron	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
at	O
a	O
Gold-Smith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
for	O
15d	O
.	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Apron	O
to	O
Baine	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
two	O
Notes	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
again	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
Allen	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Notes	O
down	O
the	O
Grates	O
on	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
Confes	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
15d	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Jane	O
Baine	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
James	O
Allen	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Withall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harris	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
24	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
Brass	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Gore	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dilley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Dilley	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
fast	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
that	O
they	O
set	O
up	O
till	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Scullery	O
and	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Cat	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
knockt	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
or	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
her	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Airy	I-pers
.	O
Rebecca	O
Airy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
5	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
again	O
till	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Gown	O
which	O
she	O
might	O
make	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
wore	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
brought	O
in	O
some	O
Plates	O
and	O
two	O
Sauce-Pans	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
staid	O
out	O
all	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
20th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
their	O
Landlady	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
James	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
safe	O
the	O
Back-side	O
the	O
Buildings	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
Green-house	O
open	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
2	O
quarrels	O
of	O
Glass	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
wrencht	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dacres	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Airy	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
nearest	O
Constable	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
Airy	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
make	O
things	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
Dilley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabath	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Perrey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Mobb	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brewinton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Seats	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Octob	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
for	O
entertaining	O
them	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Barnard	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
out	O
his	O
Coach	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
with	O
4	O
Seats	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
two	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
two	O
Seats	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Feathers	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
John	O
Andrews	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
Coach	O
by	O
King-street	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Seats	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Pizza	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
himself	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
William	B-pers
Lewellin	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
accordingly	O
.	O
William	O
Lewellin	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
caught	O
him	O
and	O
Speed	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
got	O
out	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Speed	O
took	O
the	O
Seats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Brewinton	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
(	O
Griffiths	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackham	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
under	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
wet	O
Night	O
)	O
he	O
saw	O
Lewellin	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
go	O
out	O
after	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
watcht	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
observing	O
,	O
Speed	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
about	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
Lewellin	O
to	O
Prison	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
Three	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Griffith	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Newtoners	O
Lane	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Seats	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
Matt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Feathers	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
leapt	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
carried	O
Lewellin	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
ingenious	O
Confession	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Confession	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Griffiths	O
House	O
in	O
Newtoners	O
Lane	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Seats	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
Griffiths	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Three	O
Men	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Shag	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Feathers	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
and	O
1	O
Sack	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach-House	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
5	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Shepherd	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Lining	O
and	O
Seats	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
.	O
searcht	O
several	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
[	O
several	O
words	O
unclear	O
]	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
that	O
Whitlock	O
and	O
Sibley	O
[	O
several	O
words	O
unclear	O
]	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
[	O
several	O
words	O
unclear	O
]	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
[	O
several	O
words	O
unclear	O
]	O
drink	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
cald	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
Garnets	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Three	B-place
Crains	I-place
in	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Granger	O
's	O
Bosom	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
others	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
but	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
round	O
Granger	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Steal	O
Box	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
Stones	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
after	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
(	O
except	O
5	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
)	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
Granger	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Jewels	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
lookt	O
round	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
take	O
the	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
Granger	O
's	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
same	O
small	O
Stones	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisners	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Star-Tavern	O
in	O
Coleman-Street	O
,	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
Ring	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
That	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
Granger	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Lawson	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Granger	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Cheltenham	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Innocent	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cheltenham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Ride	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
over	O
Finchley-Common	B-place
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Dickinson	O
rode	O
very	O
hard	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
against	O
him	O
with	O
such	O
Fury	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
he	O
fell	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
tore	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
Eyes	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Dickinson	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
--	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
Stand	O
and	O
Deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innocent	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
a	O
Shaise	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
rid	O
after	O
Dickinson	O
toward	O
the	O
Shaise	O
,	O
who	O
riding	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
rise	O
and	O
mount	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
disintangle	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
be	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
charged	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Browns-Well-House	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
swore	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
keep	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
proper	O
Officer	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
High	O
Way	O
Men	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Dickinson	O
clapt	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
it	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innocent	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
neither	O
;	O
that	O
Dickinson	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
drove	O
away	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
(	O
who	O
in	O
this	O
for	O
surprise	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Brown's-Well-House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innocent	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shaise	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cheltenham	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
coming	O
softly	O
down	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cheltenham	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
Pocket	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
loaded	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Intent	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Pistols	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
l	O
for	O
each	O
Offence	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
his	O
Fines	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Windell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Globe	I-place
in	O
Hungerford-Market	B-place
and	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
no	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Cart	O
load	O
at	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lockt	O
and	O
barr	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Window	O
of	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
next	O
the	O
Waterside	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
barr	O
'd	O
;	O
whereopon	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
guard	O
that	O
Window	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
Webb	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
while	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
waited	O
there	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Bolt	O
shoot	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Windell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
shewed	O
him	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
his	O
Drink	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Brandy	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
made	O
safe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
answering	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
was	O
seized	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
taking	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
2	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Mobb	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not-being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
of	O
St.Andrews	B-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
5	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
along	O
Kingsgate-Street	B-place
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
over	O
head	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seeing	O
of	O
him	O
run	O
,	O
mist	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
thus	O
he	O
finding	O
himself	O
pursued	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Stop	O
,	O
then	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
thrown	O
over	O
some	O
Rails	O
just	O
where	O
he	O
stopt	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
near	O
her	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
re-taken	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
rather	O
privately	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Jumps	O
value	O
50	O
s.and	O
3	O
Stomachers	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Sykes	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Jumps	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Sykes	O
followed	O
her	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
dropt	O
the	O
3	O
Stomachers	O
in	O
her	O
Flight	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Fee-Lane	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Jumps	O
to	O
fit	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
Shop	O
had	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
one	O
pair	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
were	O
his	O
also	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Jumps	O
and	O
3	O
Stomchers	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Callimancoe	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Riding	O
hood	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
(	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
her	O
Inner	O
Door	O
was	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Latch	O
for	O
the	O
Convenience	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
9	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
Notice	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
commited	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
William	O
Field	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
outer	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
inner	O
Door	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
Eliz	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knows	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
condemned	O
before	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
several	O
,	O
convicted	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Field	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glassford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Fellow-Prentices	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
kept	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Firth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
Stayes	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
4	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
144	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Seats	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Roberts	O
Diggs	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
make	O
Room	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
some	O
Timber	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Seats	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
when	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
gone	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
1	O
Seat	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Seats	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hellom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Lawn	O
Sheet	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Hoiland	O
Shirt	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Caldicut	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Blue	O
Apron	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
plainly	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Burglaries	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Sattin	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mohair	O
28	O
s.	O
47	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
6	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Burdet	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tiking	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gronas	I-pers
and	O
Gladwell	B-pers
Peyton	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Gladwell	O
Peyton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
3	O
Months	O
upon	O
Liking	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
another	O
Master	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
flush	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
himself	O
lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
often	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillip	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
Broker	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Mohair	O
,	O
Damask	O
,	O
Camblet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
that	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
10	O
l.	O
24	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
served	O
the	O
Warrant	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Piece	O
Broker	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
.	O
who	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
several	O
Particulars	O
and	O
the	O
Prices	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fortune	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
his	O
Signing	O
the	O
Paper	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
greatly	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Matthews	O
against	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
Halves	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
got	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawned	O
her	O
Coat	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
another	O
Crown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pacify	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Matthews	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
remained	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grasett	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Westall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susanah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Thursday	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
:	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Enfield	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Delforce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
Effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
before	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Cause	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
inticing	O
Robert	B-pers
Austen	I-pers
a	O
Black	O
Smith	O
to	O
go	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
to	O
exercise	O
his	O
Trade	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
withoutAldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Membry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Striking	O
,	O
Beating	O
,	O
and	O
Kicking	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Striking	O
,	O
Beating	O
and	O
Kicking	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Tower	B-place
Hill	I-place
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
as	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Distress	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
the	O
Deceased	O
near	O
the	O
small	O
of	O
her	O
Back	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Get	O
up	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
Run	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
kickt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
very	O
bright	O
;	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Dyer	O
in	O
Tower	O
street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tilsley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
kicking	O
and	O
striking	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
bidding	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
he	O
served	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Yellow	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Rag	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Williams	B-pers
Day	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
Corroborated	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Farril	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Nags-Head-Alehose	O
that	O
Night	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
blamed	O
the	O
Officers	O
for	O
suffering	O
such	O
loose	O
Cattle	O
to	O
lye	O
about	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
knockt	O
one	O
down	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bitch	O
he	O
kickt	O
down	O
and	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gideon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Overseers	O
brought	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
at	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
at	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
Bruises	O
on	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
Shoe	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Hip	O
every	O
where	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
smoak	O
a	O
Pipe	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Voice	O
cry	O
Capt	O
.	O
Membry	O
.	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Black	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
disperse	O
themselves	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
set	O
his	O
Foot	O
in	O
the	O
Breech	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
run	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
good	O
for	O
your	O
Health	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ruart	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
People	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Women	O
Drunk	O
or	O
Dead	O
in	O
Thames	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
poor	O
ragged	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Stones	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
next	O
Morning	O
lying	O
among	O
the	O
Stones	O
on	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Williams	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
such	O
a	O
Girl	O
from	O
Thames	O
Street	O
to	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
chargeable	O
to	O
their	O
Parish	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Black	O
Gown	O
,	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Leather	O
Bodice	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sam	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Evidences	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
for	O
the	O
reasons	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
dark	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
clean	O
Shift	O
,	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
he	O
believes	O
)	O
a	O
Yellow	O
Stomacher	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Urquehart	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
lying	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
with	O
some	O
Straw	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stone	O
under	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Captain	O
Membry	B-pers
that	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
kickt	O
her	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
washt	O
,	O
a	O
clean	O
Smock	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
examined	O
her	O
Body	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Hurt	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
Scratch	O
(	O
like	O
one	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Pin	O
)	O
on	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
be	O
went	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
Bruises	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
settling	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Glenn	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
(	O
the	O
Overseer	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
was	O
starved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
in	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
stript	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Bruise	O
or	O
Tumour	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
usual	O
after	O
Death	O
by	O
the	O
setling	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
Overseer	O
and	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Giril	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Trundley	I-pers
on	O
Wednesday	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Trundley	O
hitting	O
her	O
self	O
against	O
an	O
Iron	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
by	O
(	O
who	O
taking	O
them	O
for	O
Boys	O
)	O
kickt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
run	O
you	O
Dog	O
run	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
Ann	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Keys	O
at	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
that	O
Day	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
Ann	O
Trundley	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
Ann	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
Ague	O
,	O
and	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
died	O
with	O
a	O
Parish	O
Nurse	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
4	O
first	O
Evidences	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Girls	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
great	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Worth	O
to	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Compassion	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
Cruelty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belsenger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Martha	O
Gilbert	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
being	O
much	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Headache	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
laid	O
herself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
Force	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
what	O
Resistance	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
from	O
her	O
Mouth	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
fetching	O
of	O
Drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
a	O
Bussle	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coats	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flew	O
at	O
her	O
and	O
scratcht	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
strugling	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sued	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
Bitches	O
if	O
you	O
Prosecute	O
me	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
you	O
pickt	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
attempted	O
her	O
formerly	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
leap	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
to	O
avoid	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Woolley	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Britton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
damage	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Shift	O
at	O
their	O
Request	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
shew	O
of	O
Virginity	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Conversation	O
with	O
Man	O
till	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
Force	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Winny	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
bid	O
him	O
hush	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
easy	O
.	O
A	O
Girl	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
Pots	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Ye	O
old	O
Surfeit	O
here	O
are	O
none	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
prickt	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
Winny	O
took	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
Farthing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
they	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
Three	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
One	O
Penny	O
more	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
shall	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Winny	O
's	O
Child	O
was	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
naughty	O
Girl	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
she	O
askt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
another	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
huncht	O
and	O
gam	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Meadowes	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
2	O
Midwives	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
Man	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Shift	O
on	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
her	O
Virginity	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Woman	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Midwives	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
:	O
and	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
called	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Winny	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
Civil	O
,	O
Honest	O
and	O
Industrious	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
alias	O
Fellowes	B-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Tompion	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Withall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Delforce	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
2	O
Richard	B-pers
Trantrum	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lucius	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
both	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
19.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flory	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brewinton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Glassford	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Firth	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hellom	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Huwes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sussanah	O
Martin	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Fowlis	O
,	O
Alias	O
Thewlis	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Hewton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Fined	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
each	O
Offence	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
his	O
Fines	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tompion	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edward	O
Parker	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
Christian	O
Monitor	O
,	O
containing	O
an	O
Earnest	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
;	O
With	O
some	O
Directions	O
in	O
order	O
thereto	O
.	O
Written	O
in	O
a	O
plain	O
and	O
easie	O
stile	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
but	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
concerning	O
the	O
Excellency	O
and	O
Usefulness	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Prayer	O
.	O
Preached	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Beveridge	I-pers
,	O
D	O
:	O
D.	O
(	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
St.	O
Asaph	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Opening	O
of	O
the	O
Parish-Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Peter	O
's	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
168	O
l.	O
The	O
Twenty-fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
but	O
20	O
s.	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Sacramental	O
Covenanting	O
with	O
Christ	O
:	O
shewing	O
the	O
Ungodly	O
their	O
Contempt	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Covenant	O
.	O
And	O
calling	O
them	O
(	O
not	O
to	O
a	O
Profanation	O
of	O
this	O
Holy	O
Ordinance	O
,	O
but	O
)	O
to	O
an	O
Understanding	O
,	O
Serious	O
,	O
Entire	O
Dedication	O
of	O
themselves	O
to	O
God	O
in	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Covenant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Believing	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
J.	O
Rawlet	O
P.	O
D.	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Christan	O
Monitor	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
.	O
price	O
3	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cares	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvey-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
