TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROGEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortesceu	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bugby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Speckman	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Drybutter	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lassoon	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Selfe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Marriner	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Halloway	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Attlee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Charlewood	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10.	O
an	O
Apron	O
21.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
.	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
lookt	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Sword	O
Blades	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Vaughan	O
(	O
another	O
of	O
his	O
Journeymen	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Vaughan	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Vaughan	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enticed	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Head	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Damask	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bodham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
this	O
Servant	O
and	O
workt	O
by	O
the	O
Day	O
for	O
him	O
5	O
Years	O
:	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
losing	O
her	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
excuse	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
time	O
limited	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
)	O
the	O
Court	O
respited	O
her	O
Sentence	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
Ann	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Clopper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
in	I-place
Coloman-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Grown	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
The	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
persuading	O
and	O
abetting	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
Sweetman	O
and	O
Clopper	O
confest	O
when	O
apprehended	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Hinton	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Barbara	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Crowders-Well-Alley	O
in	O
Hinton	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
Hinton	O
as	O
Accessory	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
And	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
found	O
Sweetman	O
and	O
Clopper	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Feloney	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game-Cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Cock	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shed	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Matcht	O
it	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
another	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
which	O
Match	O
he	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Cock	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
sent	O
him	O
into	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
to	O
Fetch	O
the	O
Cock	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
But	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
he	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
alias	O
Dye	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Botolph	B-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sarfenet-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lace	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Trench	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Norton	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
CreedChurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holcrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquited	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bierdsly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
within	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
committing	O
a	O
Wilful	O
Perjury	O
by	O
making	O
two	O
Affidavits	O
,	O
one	O
whereof	O
contradicted	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pervert	O
Justice	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
reciting	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Affidavits	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sattin	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
2	O
Sattin	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shams	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hallis	I-pers
,	O
where	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Shams	O
to	O
Hallis	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Twiddy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Charewoman	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mantle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Church	O
one	O
Sunday	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	B-place
's	I-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Bible	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
presently	O
missing	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chints	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brion	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Gosling	O
's	O
to	O
Drink	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
John	O
Gosling	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
give	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
he	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Pleasant	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Katherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Moseley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
being	O
searching	O
the	O
Vault	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
felt	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Bottom	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stilborn	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Skin	O
off	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
well	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
askt	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
soure	O
Beer	O
had	O
Gript	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Katharine	O
Davis	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
's	O
Head	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Blood	O
at	O
its	O
Nose	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
of	O
a	O
Stilborn	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stilborn	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
provision	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
desired	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Sister	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
Necessaries	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
born	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
replyed	O
the	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
unlockt	O
her	O
Trunk	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
take	O
the	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dufour	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
watcht	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Stationer	O
's	O
Door	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Arm	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dunkley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
for	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Coach	O
running	O
by	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
was	O
scuffling	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
accidentally	O
going	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Reddit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hanesley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
wrapping	O
and	O
smothering	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Scott	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
another	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Wigg	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
cry	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Month	O
to	O
go	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
without	O
seeing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wigg	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Scott	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
her	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	O
Scott	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
wrapt	O
up	O
at	O
length	O
in	O
a	O
clean	O
Apron	O
by	O
her	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
believes	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
lookt	O
fair	O
and	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
grown	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
Linnen	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
made	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Month	O
longer	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Alexander	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
viewed	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
saw	O
no	O
Hurt	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
grown	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jabes	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
Gent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
the	O
Maid	O
how	O
the	O
Water	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
River	O
Company	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
Pipe	O
and	O
Cock	O
where	O
it	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Cistern	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
and	O
3	O
Spoons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
perceiving	O
,	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Scure	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Pipe	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Water	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
it	O
did	O
:	O
holding	O
his	O
Hand	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
seized	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Clerks	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
they	O
searcht	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Haresnape	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bembrick	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
a	O
China	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
29	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Bembrick	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confest	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Haresnape	O
(	O
Bembrick	O
's	O
Mother	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
and	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
Bembrick	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Temperance	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Glascock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Temperance	O
Walker	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Glascock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
out	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Howel	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
and	O
her	O
self	O
broke	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
described	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
exactly	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Account	O
)	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
believed	O
to	O
Temperance	O
Walker	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Howel	O
6	O
Years	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Howel	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Howel	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Katherine	O
Browne	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Browne	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
.	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
Katherine	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
a	O
Key	O
and	O
Chissel	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
workt	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Owen	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Yearly	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
had	O
some	O
markt	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Till	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
searcht	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
markt	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
markt	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
searching	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Angier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Murrock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belchier	I-pers
,	O
who	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Shorts	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
left	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
she	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
another	O
Habit	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Cucumber	B-place
Alley	I-place
in	O
Princes	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
complaining	O
that	O
the	O
Guard	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
hurt	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Belchier	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
picking	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
6	O
pence	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
after	O
wards	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Whores	O
Wages	O
and	O
Hackney	O
Horse	O
Hire	O
were	O
always	O
paid	O
beforehand	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
yet	O
trick	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
changed	O
their	O
Riding	O
Hoods	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
ran	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
kept	O
it	O
there	O
5	O
Days	O
,	O
then	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
arrested	O
Belchier	O
for	O
Money	O
she	O
owed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Officer	O
she	O
employed	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Officer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Arrest	O
Belchier	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Suit	O
;	O
who	O
then	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
swearing	O
one	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
Ten	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Holland-Shirts	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimancoe	O
and	O
4	O
Hats	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Farley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
owned	O
when	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
and	O
Coral	O
,	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
told	O
his	O
Wife	O
that	O
she	O
wondred	O
she	O
would	O
keep	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Place	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
missing	O
some	O
Childbed-Linnen	O
and	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
made	O
search	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Confest	O
the	O
Chain	O
and	O
Coral	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Winwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Susanna	B-pers
Lemondey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
22	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merthe	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Messe	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mason	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
Great	O
Britain	O
without	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Cause	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Euphian	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Euphian	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
Quilt	O
,	O
3	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Essex	B-pers
Ewens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
3	O
Razors	O
and	O
a	O
Glass	O
Eye	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Booth	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Booth	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
40	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
Shifts	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Cap	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
Apron	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Tatney	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
look	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
her	O
Trunk	O
broke	O
and	O
her	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
;	O
That	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
they	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Murfey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scurrier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
called	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
Shifts	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Silk	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Decrasto	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Lilbourn	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Syrupsell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Steal	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
Granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
stole	O
by	O
Katharine	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
from	O
George	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mountainy	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hart	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Leaky	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
)	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
rose	O
sooner	O
than	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
opened	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
the	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
again	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Honourable	I-pers
the	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Londonderry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Servant	O
lay	O
(	O
over	O
the	O
Coach-House	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
with	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
GERTRUDE	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
;	O
and	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Makepeace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hellingdon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Azariah	B-pers
Folgamb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
above	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
Makepeace	O
swears	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
he	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
ill.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
askt	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
ill	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
hurt	O
in	O
a	O
civil	O
Reproof	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replyd	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Reproof	O
out	O
of	O
Friendship	O
,	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
Ridicule	O
behind	O
one	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
were	O
reconciled	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Accession	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
Firing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Money	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
one	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Word	O
Solution	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
properly	O
spoke	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Ears	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
Scabbard	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
calling	O
of	O
him	O
Puppy	O
;	O
and	O
referr	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
decide	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
next	O
,	O
who	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turnd	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
D	O
--	O
n	O
you	O
Draw	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Beds	O
Feet	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Morrow	O
Mr.	O
Calf-sticker	O
,	O
you	O
drew	O
your	O
Sword	O
last	O
Night	O
on	O
three	O
Calves	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
rise	O
and	O
Fight	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
remained	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
Folgamb	O
,	O
who	O
fought	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
left	O
over	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Sword	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
on	O
this	O
Evidence	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
about	O
him	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Friendship	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
many	O
Favours	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
penceable	O
Temper	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
washt	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
Folgamb	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pritchet	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Chequer-Inn	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
Night	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Dispute	O
about	O
the	O
Word	O
Solution	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
Puppey	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
parted	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Tap-House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
had	O
to	O
their	O
Quarters	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
rose	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Sword	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
said	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Tap-House	O
over	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lent	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Peaceable	O
and	O
Quiet	O
Deportment	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Fielding	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behaved	O
himself	O
bravely	O
at	O
Dunblane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
through	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
his	O
Troop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Peaceable	O
and	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
so	O
Quarrelsom	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
dismist	O
.	O
Quartermaster	O
Bowls	B-pers
gave	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
out	O
late	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Round-House	O
rather	O
than	O
disturb	O
the	O
Family	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
lie	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
accordingly	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ginn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
De	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
entrusted	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Hats	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
both	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
enter	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
enterd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Coultis	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hottlestone	I-pers
alias	O
Mason	B-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
Hanging-Sword-Alley	B-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
Coultis	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
nor	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Coultis	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Note	O
where	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Joannah	O
Hower	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
two	O
Whores	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
two	O
great	O
ugly	O
Whores	O
.	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
handsome	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
vext	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
asking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Thief-	O
Taker	O
following	O
him	O
to	O
extort	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
whilst	O
she	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Note	O
where	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
might	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
courteous	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
parted	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
them	O
Good-Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Mackowen	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Walk	O
between	O
the	O
Mall	O
and	O
the	O
Road	O
about	O
the	O
first	O
Bench	O
near	O
Whitehall	B-place
,	O
one	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Casey	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
drinking	O
in	O
Theiving-Lane	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
also	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
throtle	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Neccloth	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Casey	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
they	O
'd	O
swear	O
Buggery	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
did	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
Casey	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
Stampt	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
D	O
--	O
n	O
you	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
and	O
wounded	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Rib	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Sentry	O
in	O
the	O
Cock-pit	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
another	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
Mackowen	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Longueville	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Park	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
he	O
saw	O
3	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
to	O
avoid	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
Mackowen	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Sentry	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mackowen	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
and	O
Mackowen	O
made	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mackowen	O
it	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
off	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
cryed	O
our	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sentry	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
surrendered	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
the	O
Sentry	O
.	O
That	O
Mackowen	O
had	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
Mackowen	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Sentry	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
Heals	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
there	O
,	O
Bloody	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
Mackowen	O
with	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Mackowen	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Casey	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Soldier	O
and	O
a	O
Shoe-cleaner	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
.	O
That	O
before	O
the	O
Sentry	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
told	O
this	O
Evidence	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
Murdered	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
.	O
-	O
Montgomery	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Longueville	O
's	O
Assistance	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
dodg	O
'd	O
by	O
Mackowen	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Bugger	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
he	O
threatned	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
Murder	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Longueville	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
Heals	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
,	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
Mackowen	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
owned	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
peached	O
Casey	O
.	O
-	O
Hall	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
with	O
Mackowen	O
at	O
Chairing-Cross	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
Mackowen	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Casey	O
's	O
Voice	O
.	O
Another	O
corroborated	O
Hall	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Casey	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Charewoman	O
at	O
Mr.Vickar	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Casey	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
from	O
%	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.Vicker	O
hearing	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
that	O
Casey	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
lookt	O
in	O
the	O
Almanack	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
testifie	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
occasion	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
where	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
now	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Holland	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
Three	O
Days	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vicker	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Watt	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Casey	O
staggering	O
by	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
after	O
the	O
Watch	O
went	O
12	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
said	O
because	O
he	O
mounted	O
the	O
Guard	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Casey	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Cellar	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Watchman	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Cellar	O
and	O
Casey	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
Swinney	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
Casey	O
was	O
in	O
Trouble	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Mackowen	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Park	O
with	O
Hall	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
Casey	O
,	O
one	O
Carefoot	O
and	O
a	O
Shoe-cleaner	O
beating	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Casey	O
tell	O
Carefoot	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Carefoot	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
Accidently	O
.	O
And	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
that	O
workt	O
hard	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
Mackowen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Casey	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Gregory	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cork-Skrew	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Park	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Skrew	O
and	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
searcht	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
they	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
Casey	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
since	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
lost	O
was	O
so	O
trifling	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
while	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
not	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Casey	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
Robbery	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
told	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
bound	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Tourton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
before	O
that	O
Casey	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cork-skrew	O
of	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broadpiece	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Brownsworth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Brownsworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	B-place
the	I-place
Turnpike	I-place
and	I-place
Islington	I-place
by	O
3	O
Persons	O
;	O
that	O
2	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
was	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Spurs	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
from	O
Barridge	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
going	O
to	O
Cambridge	O
Heath	O
)	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Brownsworth	O
described	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Spurs	O
cut	O
from	O
his	O
Boots	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Spurs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spurs	O
were	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
Boots	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Unfortunate	O
Man	O
,	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Symbol	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
within	B-place
300	I-place
Yards	I-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
by	O
3	O
Foot-Pads	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
cry	O
'd	O
knock	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
held	O
their	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
Burridge	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
described	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
had	O
his	O
Spurs	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Burridge	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Shaw	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
knew	O
Wigley	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
Burridge	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
acquainted	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Burridge	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
lined	O
with	O
Steel	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
this	O
Evidence	O
abroad	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Conyers	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
askt	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
rob	O
a	O
Coach	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Spurs	O
were	O
lined	O
with	O
Steel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
in	O
Burridge	O
,	O
who	O
Courted	O
one	O
he	O
advised	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
her	O
Brother	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Poppin	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
7	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
at	O
Variance	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
part	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
(	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Body	O
but	O
her	O
Children	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Camberwell	O
to	O
work	O
next	O
Day	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
assist	O
him	O
with	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
remembred	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
she	O
set	O
down	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
for	O
Capt.Busbey	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
what	O
she	O
sold	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
this	O
Servant	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Accompt	O
for	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
Accompt	O
being	O
lookt	O
into	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cross	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Margent	O
of	O
an	O
Almanack	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Seventh	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Page	O
was	O
writ	O
Eight	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
George	O
Alley	O
,	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
strange	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
her	O
Brother	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
Name	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
's	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
Called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Weymer	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
Portugal	O
called	O
Moidores	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
27	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
intending	O
thereby	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Westley	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Widow	O
Holmes	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Moidore	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
that	O
Day	O
Week	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
Moidore	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
counterfeit	O
:	O
that	O
Holmes	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Reeve	O
;	O
that	O
searching	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
they	O
found	O
five	O
False	O
Moidores	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Piece	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
Aqua-fortis	O
,	O
Quicksilver	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
That	O
Cooper	O
owned	O
the	O
Moidores	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Reeves	O
had	O
those	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Moidores	O
of	O
Reeve	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Drink	O
,	O
sometimes	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
changing	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
2	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Westley	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Holmes	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
from	O
Reeve	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
em	O
to	O
Reeve	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
she	O
to	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
clear	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
16	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Holmes	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
several	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sparks	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
searcht	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tools	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
2	O
Dies	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
Quicksilver	O
,	O
Flatted	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Vice	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
for	O
Coining	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bellasis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Westley	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
try	O
if	O
a	O
Moidore	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
Weigh	O
'd	O
and	O
Toucht	O
it	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Graver	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
Silver	O
underneath	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
5	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
his	O
Graver	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
true	O
Moidores	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
sealed	O
over	O
with	O
Gold	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
bore	O
the	O
Touch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
Aquafortis	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bore	O
that	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
owned	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Reeve	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
16	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Reeve	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
of	O
a	O
Captain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bembridge	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
5	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Silver	O
Crusade	O
and	O
a	O
Moidores	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Moidores	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Essay	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
false	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Silver	O
Plated	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
fine	O
Silver	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
6	O
s.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
he	O
bought	O
once	O
29	O
Ounces	O
,	O
and	O
twice	O
30	O
Ounces	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
's	O
heavier	O
than	O
Common	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
180	O
Ounces	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Ounce	O
would	O
make	O
3	O
of	O
those	O
Counterfeit	O
Moidores	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Cooper	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sometimes	O
bought	O
fine	O
flatted	O
Gold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
wide	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Whim	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
deposed	O
that	O
Cooper	O
bought	O
fine	O
Beaten	O
Gold	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
some	O
thicker	O
,	O
some	O
thinner	O
;	O
he	O
believes	O
about	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
Worth	O
since	O
last	O
March	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Reeve	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
ready	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
Gold	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
near	O
the	O
quantity	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
guess	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Gold-beater	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
:	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Harpum	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Cooper	O
told	O
him	O
Harpum	O
used	O
it	O
for	O
Clock-Cases	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
false	O
Moidore	O
of'em	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bowman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
age	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
an	O
Ingot	O
of	O
Silver	O
about	O
a	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
broad	O
as	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
abroad	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
apprehended	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
fine	O
Silver	O
because	O
it	O
bent	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
how	O
he	O
ventur	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
said	O
another	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Cooper	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Wool-pack	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
Press	O
to	O
strike	O
off	O
Watch-Keys	O
and	O
Middles	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
formerly	O
make	O
a	O
Press	O
for	O
one	O
Buntin	O
for	O
Watch-Keys	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
one	O
for	O
Cooper	O
,	O
only	O
discourst	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
one	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
for	O
Coining	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
that	O
Press	O
of	O
Buntin	O
's	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Workmen	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
use	O
in	O
Coining	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
these	O
Moidores	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
without	O
a	O
press	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Silver	O
used	O
in	O
them	O
was	O
15	O
Penniweight	O
better	O
than	O
Standard	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Cooper	O
proposed	O
to	O
Marry	O
Reeve	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
ingenious	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
learn	O
her	O
to	O
Coin	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
himself	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wear	O
a	O
long	O
Wig	O
and	O
Sword	O
in	O
3	O
Years	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
there	O
Iron	O
Ladles	O
,	O
White	O
Filings	O
and	O
Yellow	O
Filings	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
down	O
once	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
Garret	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
one	O
time	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
when	O
this	O
Discourse	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Cooper	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
Ned	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
all	O
my	O
Affairs	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Reeve	O
;	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
sometimes	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
how	O
long	O
this	O
was	O
ago	O
,	O
said	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
Ned	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
cast	O
,	O
Reeve	O
can	O
Gild	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
put	O
em	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
be	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
put	O
the	O
Danger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
Death	O
to	O
Coin	O
English	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Death	O
to	O
Coin	O
Foreign	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Scandal	O
of	O
a	O
Pillory	O
would	O
soon	O
blow	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
askt	O
when	O
this	O
Discourse	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
Pillory	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smaile	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Reeve	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Cooper	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harpum	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
only	O
laught	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
Gilded	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Cooper	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harpums	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
large	O
Dealings	O
with	O
for	O
Watches	O
and	O
fine	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Norway	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Tools	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
the	O
common	O
Tools	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Ash	O
swore	O
out	O
of	O
Mialice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
take	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harpum	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
sorts	O
,	O
some	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
with	O
Crosses	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sessioms	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Gold	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Table	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
Crosses	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
as	O
Owen	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkey	O
being	O
askt	O
by	O
Cooper	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
Harpum	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Brother	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Robert	B-pers
Harpum	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
with	O
50	O
false	O
Moidores	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Cooper	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
17	O
Moidores	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
or	O
Watches	O
,	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
Coining	O
without	O
others	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
Evening	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
Fine	O
Silver	O
publickly	O
and	O
bend	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Norway	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hariss	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
instructed	O
Mrs.	O
Reeve	O
in	O
Watch	O
Gilding	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
workt	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
non	O
bad	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Tools	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
they	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
Gild	O
without	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
use	O
the	O
finest	O
Gold	O
for	O
Gilding	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Watchmakers	O
and	O
Gilder	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
large	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
lately	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
them	O
honestly	O
in	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
Gild	O
without	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
Quicksilver	O
and	O
Aquafortis	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
slatted	O
Gold	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Garret	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
they	O
buy	O
at	O
Capt	O
.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reading	O
the	O
Newspaper	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Raven	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
wherein	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
was	O
mentioned	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
(	O
who	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Box	O
)	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Holland	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Cooper	O
)	O
cheated	O
him	O
in	O
Spanish	O
Wool	O
they	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
him	O
Hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smart	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Cooper	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
Sutton	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
Graved	O
Watches	O
for	O
Cooper	O
,	O
who	O
paid	O
him	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ash	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
base	O
Character	O
.	O
Job	O
Harris	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
House	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
Reeves	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
Trade	O
frequently	O
,	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
lockt	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
might	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
deposed	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
called	O
several	O
others	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
another	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
4.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Merth	I-pers
alias	O
Mess	O
alias	O
Mason	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
1.	O
William	B-pers
Makepeace	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
was	O
also	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Capital	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
her	O
Sentence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Judgement	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
whose	O
Offences	O
were	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
said	O
Date	O
,	O
were	O
respited	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
Ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
8.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clopper	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulden	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
alias	O
Howel	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mountainy	I-pers
.	O
Found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
19.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Baker	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Twiddy	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Haresnape	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bembrick	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Owen	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
Published	O
by	O
William	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Owen	O
's	O
Works	O
in	O
polio	O
.	O
Containing	O
several	O
scarce	O
and	O
valuable	O
Discourses	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
Declaration	O
of	O
the	O
Glorious	O
Mystery	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
Man	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Communion	O
with	O
God	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
Son	O
and	O
Holy	O
Ghost	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Indwelling	O
Sin	O
in	O
Believers	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
Temptations	O
.	O
The	O
Nature	O
and	O
Power	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Mortification	O
of	O
Sin	O
in	O
Believers	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Christ	O
:	O
The	O
Price	O
he	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
Purchase	O
he	O
made	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Display	O
of	O
Armianism	O
.	O
First	O
Published	O
in	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Life	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
Collected	O
together	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
perfixed	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Effigy	O
Curiously	O
Engraven	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
several	O
Learned	O
Divines	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
Doctor	O
's	O
and	O
other	O
Ministers	O
Effigies	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Single	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
William	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
by	O
J	O
Marshall	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
R	O
Ford	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Little	O
Brittain	O
,	O
and	O
E	O
Harrison	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
at	O
Edinburgh	O
in	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
at	O
Boston	O
in	O
New-England	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Bromfields	O
Pills	O
that	O
were	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
in	O
Play-yard	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
are	O
now	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
places	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
pain	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
