TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
:	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
1722.	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
STEWART	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Terbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Kelham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Oliver	B-pers
Bressington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Braithwait	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Predy	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Frome	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
Eleazer	B-pers
Maleroy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huddleston	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buckly	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Afflick	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
45	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Afflick	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Tewksbury	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
Square	O
,	O
walking	O
along	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Snuffers	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elias	B-pers
Ozier	I-pers
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
.	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bromly	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Ear	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languisht	O
till	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Boys	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
,	O
met	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
usual	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
Holidays	O
.	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Boys	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
which	O
Side	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belong	O
'd	O
)	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Boys	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
,	O
aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
at	O
their	O
Head	O
,	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
retreating	O
,	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Boys	O
rallied	O
their	O
Forces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Church	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
Gregg	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
carelesly	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sennit	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Church	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Captain	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
towards	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
his	O
aim	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
brusht	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Dumillion	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
shun	O
'd	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
but	O
recovering	O
his	O
ground	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Dumillion	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Ear	O
;	O
they	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
so	O
far	O
after	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Boys	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
Party	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Temple	O
Muscle	O
bruis	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Skull	O
fractur	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
depression	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
Blood	O
between	O
the	O
Skull	O
and	O
Dura	O
Mater	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
which	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
prevented	O
,	O
if	O
Care	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Apothecary	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
leaning	O
on	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Captain	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Boys	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
blow	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
.	O
Abigal	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
quiet	O
Lad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslanghter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
of	O
Harmonsworth	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Tho	O
.	O
Green	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pratly	I-pers
;	O
two	O
Mails	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
50	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
(	O
Hawkins	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Post-boy	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
near	O
the	O
Red	O
Horse	O
,	O
at	O
Slough	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
overtaken	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Ladbrook	I-pers
,	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
they	O
rode	O
in	O
company	O
to	O
Langly	O
broom	O
,	O
where	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Horse	O
,	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
rode	O
through	O
Colbrook	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
two	O
Men	O
followed	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Longford	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
their	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Wigs	O
and	O
Hats	O
pull	O
'd	O
forward	O
over	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
He	O
on	O
the	O
Chesnut	O
Horse	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
led	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
bringing	O
Ludbrook	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
Then	O
making	O
them	O
dismount	O
,	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
Chesnut	O
Horse	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
Lad	O
that	O
swore	O
against	O
Child	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Post-boy	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
rob	O
'd	O
yet	O
?	O
(	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
)	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
Why	O
then	O
you	O
must	O
pay	O
Beveridge	O
now	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
upon	O
somebody	O
for	O
poor	O
Child	O
's	O
sake	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
Ladbrook	O
's	O
Horse	O
loose	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
cut	O
his	O
Bridle	O
.	O
One	O
of'em	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
rode	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
bound	O
their	O
Hands	O
behind'em	O
,	O
ty'd'em	O
back	O
to	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
fasten'd'em	O
to	O
a	O
Tree	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
Ladbrook	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Gold	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
Ladbrook	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Ladbrook	O
with	O
strugling	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
Tree	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
tied	O
back	O
to	O
back	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Longford	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Ostler	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Gelding	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bags	O
cut	O
open	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
were	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Ladbrook	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Hawkins	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Simpson	O
till	O
last	O
August	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
consulted	O
together	O
to	O
rob	O
some	O
Mail	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
their	O
design	O
of	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Boar	O
Inn	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
Hawkins	O
on	O
a	O
tall	O
bay	O
or	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Simpson	O
on	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
or	O
Sorrel	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
on	O
a	O
dapple	O
Grey	O
;	O
they	O
crost	O
the	O
Water	O
at	O
Kew	O
Ferry	O
,	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Pigeons	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Post-house	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
loitered	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Post-house	O
at	O
Colbrook	O
:	O
where	O
they	O
supt	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Mail	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Langly	O
broom	O
about	O
midnight	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
dispatch	O
Simpson	O
alone	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
they	O
loiter	O
'd	O
till	O
his	O
return	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Post	O
Boy	O
and	O
a	O
Traveller	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Simpson	O
following	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
consulted	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
resolv	O
'd	O
that	O
Simpson	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
should	O
both	O
follow	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hawkins	O
should	O
watch	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
:	O
because	O
he	O
being	O
pretty	O
bulky	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
remarkable	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
then	O
chang	O
'd	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
Ladbrook	O
through	O
Colbrook	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Longford	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Simpson	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
Bridles	O
,	O
led	O
them	O
down	O
Harmonsworth	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
dismounted	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
Evidence	O
left	O
Simpson	O
to	O
bind	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Gelding	O
and	O
Mail	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Hawkins	O
waiting	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
rifled	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
selected	O
the	O
Bath	O
and	O
Bristol	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
rest	O
away	O
;	O
thence	O
they	O
rode	O
through	O
Kingston	O
and	O
Wansworth	O
,	O
and	O
riding	O
down	O
a	O
bye	O
Road	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
Bags	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
what	O
they	O
thought	O
proper	O
into	O
their	O
Pockets	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
Bags	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
over	O
a	O
hedge	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
their	O
way	O
through	O
Camberwell	O
,	O
came	O
along	O
Greenwich	O
Road	O
to	O
the	O
Hand	O
Inn	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
burnt	O
Wine	O
:	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
took	O
Coach	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
different	O
ways	O
to	O
Francis	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
House	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
suspicion	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
Wax	O
,	O
Paper	O
,	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
:	O
then	O
lockt	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
examined	O
their	O
Prize	O
:	O
and	O
reserving	O
only	O
the	O
Bank	O
bills	O
,	O
they	O
burnt	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
Notes	O
and	O
Letters	O
with	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
Three	O
20	O
l.	O
Bills	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
half	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
halves	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
each	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
equally	O
divided	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
made	O
this	O
same	O
Confession	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Carteret	O
Post	O
Master	O
General	O
:	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Green	O
Arbour	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Old	O
Baily	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Ostler	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Boar	O
in	O
Southwark	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Wilson	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
took	O
Horse	O
there	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
(	O
April	O
15th	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
Hawkins	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Wilson	O
a	O
Grey	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Simpson	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Mare	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
(	O
the	O
Post-house	O
)	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Wilson	O
drinking	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
Horse	O
back	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
Colbrook	O
Road	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Tapster	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
(	O
the	O
Post-house	O
)	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
3	O
Men	O
supt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rid	O
towards	O
Slough	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
their	O
Horses	O
were	O
a	O
Grey	O
,	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
or	O
Sorrel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bay	O
or	O
brown	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
Inn	O
in	O
Barnaby	O
street	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Wilson	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Inn	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Mare	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
ordered	O
them	O
2	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Beans	O
a	O
piece	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
what	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Weekly	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
7	O
Weeks	O
wages	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
)	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
him	O
altogether	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
:	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
kept	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Simpson	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
several	O
People	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Room	I-pers
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Green	O
Arbour	O
Court	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
be	O
frighted	O
but	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
who	O
were	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
overhearing	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Swore	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
Shoot	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Hawkin	O
's	O
brother	O
Mat	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
surrender	O
quietly	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
Wilsons	O
Information	O
;	O
why	O
then	O
(	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hawkins	O
)	O
we	O
are	O
dead	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
had	O
rather	O
lose	O
our	O
Lives	O
,	O
than	O
save	O
them	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
base	O
and	O
infamous	O
manner	O
as	O
that	O
Villain	O
Wilson	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
Comptroller	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Mail	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
10	O
Bags	O
wanting	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Bath	O
and	O
Bristol	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
all	O
brought	O
home	O
,	O
(	O
except	O
the	O
Bath	O
and	O
Bristol	O
,	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
Heath	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
objected	O
against	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
guilty	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
;	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
rode	O
out	O
with	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
when	O
Simpson	O
,	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
took	O
Horse	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Mother	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Bury	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
William	O
Fuller	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
April	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
Accounts	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
William	O
Fuller	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Hawkins	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Receipt	O
.	O
That	O
Hawkins	O
wrote	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
his	O
sight	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Fuller	O
)	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Ink	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
after	O
this	O
Note	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
Hawkins	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
likewise	O
taken	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
unluckily	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
reading	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Mail	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
compar	O
'd	O
his	O
Book	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
exactly	O
agreed	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Note	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
apparent	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Ink	O
as	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
wrote	O
withal	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
ever	O
they	O
lock	O
'd	O
themselves	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
,	O
Paper	O
,	O
Wax	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Wilson	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
Simpson	O
;	O
he	O
acquainting	O
Hawkins	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
Hawkins	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
comes	O
again	O
,	O
pray	O
deny	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
find	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Fellow	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
desire	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
further	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
soon	O
after	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
Wilson	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
Wilson	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
wronged	O
Simpson	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
hang	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Hawkins	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Brother	O
has	O
impeach	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stock	O
Jobber	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
Hawkins	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
South	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Bubbles	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
Hawkins	O
two	O
River	O
Douglasses	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
10	O
,	O
20	O
and	O
30	O
Guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
Hawkins	O
repaid	O
him	O
very	O
honourably	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
Living	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Years	O
ago	O
was	O
a	O
Livery	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Dennis	B-pers
Dutry	I-pers
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
traded	O
to	O
France	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
in	O
Wine	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
Simpson	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
Living	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Putney	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
remov	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Parents	O
to	O
Spalding	O
,	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
;	O
but	O
failing	O
there	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
himself	O
Under	O
Butler	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Castlemain	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr	O
Green	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Simpson	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
him	O
honestly	O
,	O
as	O
Footman	O
,	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Months	O
;	O
but	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
any	O
Service	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
nine	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
since	O
applied	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eiiet	I-pers
,	O
dying	O
at	O
Bawtry	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
four	O
Children	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
in	O
getting	O
in	O
her	O
Debts	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Sister	O
,	O
at	O
Sutton	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
-	O
Grubshaw	O
,	O
a	O
Fruiterer	O
,	O
and	O
assist	O
his	O
Clerk	O
in	O
getting	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
insisted	O
on	O
their	O
on	O
their	O
Innocence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
fortified	O
by	O
many	O
concurrent	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tilly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
Book	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
real	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
denied	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
upon	O
Examining	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
not	O
committed	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
in	O
April	O
1721.	O
which	O
being	O
before	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nut	I-pers
and	O
Joshua	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Children	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Rushton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
17	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halsted	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
an	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hendry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
colt	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
April	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Colt	O
from	O
Beconthorp	B-place
in	O
Norfolk	B-place
110	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Colt	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Stable	O
,	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Colt	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bred	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Ransom	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
him	O
the	O
Colt	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Colt	O
exactly	O
agree	O
with	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Colt	O
at	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
but	O
bringing	O
no	O
proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
l	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Littleboy	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Littleboy	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gelliman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
Peacock	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
often	O
importun	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
procure	O
him	O
two	O
of	O
Bull	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
Saxon	O
Laws	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
Peacock	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
William	O
Littleboy	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Black	B-place
Fryars	I-place
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
Peacock	O
's	O
Persuasions	O
and	O
Directions	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
two	O
Books	O
himself	O
to	O
William	O
Littleboy	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Bull	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Saxon	O
Laws	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Peacock	O
brought	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Set	O
of	O
Lesly	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
17	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
by	O
Peacock	O
's	O
further	O
importunity	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
Saxon	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Bull	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
White	O
Cross	O
Street	O
;	O
for	O
each	O
of	O
which	O
Books	O
,	O
Ball	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
worth	O
being	O
above	O
20	O
s.	O
apiece	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
left	O
one	O
Set	O
of	O
Lesly	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
(	O
value	O
2	O
Guineas	O
)	O
at	O
Peacock	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
Bell	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
afterwards	O
received	O
of	O
Bell	O
himself	O
12	O
s.for	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
Peacock	O
carry	O
two	O
Sets	O
more	O
of	O
Lesly	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Creed	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
left'em	O
for	O
Benjamin	O
Littleboy	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Peacock	O
brought	O
back	O
20	O
s.	O
William	O
Littleboy	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
Books	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
nor	O
paid	O
him	O
any	O
Money	O
.	O
Bell	O
said	O
,	O
Peacock	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
straits	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
sell	O
him	O
some	O
Books	O
a	O
Penny	O
worth	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Littleboy	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
three	O
of	O
Bed	O
's	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Histories	O
(	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
each	O
)	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Book	O
binder	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
;	O
but	O
Peacock	O
came	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had'em	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell'em	O
.	O
He	O
showed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Book	O
seller	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
25	O
s.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
peacock	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
Peacock	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
Saxun	O
Laws	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
9	O
s.	O
apiece	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
Two	O
Sets	O
of	O
Lesly	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
25	O
s.	O
each	O
Set	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
Three	O
of	O
Bull	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
apiece	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
3rd	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Peacock	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
dishonestly	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
spoil	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
Agua	O
Fortis	O
on	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Peruque	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Phillips	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
(	O
contrary	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
taking	O
force	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Douay	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
alias	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Job	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Weight	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Nighingal	O
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
,	O
were	O
stopt	O
.	O
Fowler	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Douay	O
,	O
pitching	O
the	O
Weight	O
on	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Hill	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
Douay	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Fowler	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Winwright	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Somerset	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
40	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
15	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
;	O
and	O
6	O
Sacks	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
and	O
himself	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Oats	O
out	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merit	I-pers
's	O
Lighter	O
,	O
at	O
Bear	B-place
key	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Quarter	O
,	O
to	O
Mark	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Hill	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
They	O
received	O
23	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
shared	O
among	O
themselves	O
.	O
Knight	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
in	O
Surry	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
evident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lazare	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Moidore	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Masters	O
were	O
Servant	O
s	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lazare	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke-maker	O
;	O
that	O
Masters	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Trunk	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
her	O
Aunts	O
,	O
in	O
Durham	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
6	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chimmey	O
Corner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
put	O
there	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
frightned	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
having	O
her	O
Pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
using	O
frequently	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
blam	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
they	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
spite	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Doe	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Eltham	O
,	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuft	O
Box	O
,	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Eltham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
ajar	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shaving	O
Hat	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
bullocking	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Riggins	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Jenning	O
's	O
Stable	O
.	O
His	O
Box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
his	O
Linnen	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
box	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Shirt	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Newcomb	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Berwick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Deborah	O
Berwick	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
under	O
John	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
's	O
,	O
an	O
Upholster	O
in	O
Brewer	B-place
Street	I-place
and	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
padlockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Padlock	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
emptied	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Padlock	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
Srair	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Cannon	O
,	O
in	O
Carnaby	O
Street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
absconded	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wild	O
and	O
Falkner	O
spited	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
'd	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mackfaston	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mackfuson	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
4	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
t	O
he	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
John	O
Freeman	O
's	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
in	O
Faulcon-Inn	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
be	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
'em	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Joseph	O
Bird	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ruffels	O
Harwich	O
Hoy	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
Duval	B-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
Bar	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
order	O
'd	O
ashore	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Boys	O
aboard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
the	O
Boys	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
pawn	O
'd	O
em	O
to	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold'em	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
to	O
Bulman	O
,	O
a	O
Slop	O
Seller	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Tankard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
towards	O
New	O
Crane	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
bear	O
him	O
company	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Pigeons	I-place
at	O
Execution	B-place
Dock	I-place
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
changing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
He	O
follow	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Marson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Varney	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Yard	O
wide	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stuffs	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennett	I-place
Fink	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonious	O
stealing	O
(	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
a	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
Compting	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cockfield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bought	O
'em	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
Pritchard	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
swore	O
the	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
being	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
(	O
Washerwoman	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
laying	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Children	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
before	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Smocks	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
wet	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
:	O
had	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
.	O
Burt	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Pawn	O
:	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Talmarsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoners	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bewly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
Daniel	O
Bewly	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
Clock	O
to	O
Captain	O
Robinson	O
's	O
in	O
Upperwell	O
Ally	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
standing	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
'd	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Penitent	B-place
Street	I-place
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
what	O
happened	O
afterwards	O
he	O
could	O
net	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
stunn	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
Falkner	O
knockt	O
the	O
Porter	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cheshire	B-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Perdue	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
both	O
kneeling	O
by	O
their	O
bed	O
side	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Arm	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neck	O
:	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
Landlady	O
this	O
Rogue	O
Cheshire	O
has	O
stuck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
Murder	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
G-D-	O
my	O
Blood	O
I	O
have	O
Actually	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Sober	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Bloody	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
pike	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
groaning	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
some	O
Geneva	O
and	O
Pepper	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
vomitted	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
for	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
brought	O
,	O
she	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shewed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
a	O
fresh	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Belly	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
Rogue	O
Cheshire	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sba	O
n't	O
rest	O
in	O
my	O
Grave	O
till	O
he	O
's	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
Drinking	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
Somerset-house	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
rusty	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
Drunk	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
home	O
Drunk	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
broke	O
down	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
believed	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
laid	O
this	O
here	O
to	O
Murder	O
me	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Guard	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Regimental	O
Doctor	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Wicked	O
Liver	O
:	O
a	O
desperate	O
and	O
abusive	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
drunk	O
every	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
Weak	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Bread	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masham	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
Customer	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
without	O
returning	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
accounting	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
pretending	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masham	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	O
Dawson	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
26	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2nd	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Judith	O
Rich	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
three	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
clapt	O
their	O
Hands	O
to	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Neckcloth	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
Glass	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Appleton	O
,	O
alias	O
Appleby	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
,	O
alias	O
Lee	O
.	O
(	O
both	O
hang	O
'd	O
since	O
)	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Roberts	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
Appleby	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
-	O
Partridge	O
,	O
a	O
Cook	O
,	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Jones	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
'em	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
that	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
buy	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
turned	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
a	O
Steel	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Glass	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Butterworth	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Charge	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bond	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Giblet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
breaking	O
them	O
asunder	O
,	O
sold	O
part	O
of'em	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Prat	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
was	O
snatched	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Lander	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lander	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
halves	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
alias	O
Brean	B-pers
of	O
Dowgate	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
120	O
Pound	O
of	O
Camels	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Rob	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
at	O
Robert	B-pers
Rositer	I-pers
's	O
a	O
Hatter	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Hair	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cross	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bradly	I-pers
.	O
Bradly	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
where	O
Cross	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
for	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Rositer	O
's	O
.	O
Rositer	O
being	O
apprehended	O
for	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
in	O
the	O
Downs	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
after	O
much	O
resistance	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hambleton	O
;	O
and	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Cross	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Hair	O
scattered	O
about	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Hambleton	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Cross	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Booty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
.	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Ann	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
Aged	O
five	O
Years	O
and	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
New	O
Street	O
,	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	O
Milton	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took'em	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
Ann	O
Milton	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
foul	O
Disease	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
complaining	O
of	O
her	O
illness	O
,	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
be	O
discovered	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Tobacconist	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
confest	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tweady	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Right	O
Jaw	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
issuing	O
from	O
a	O
Gun	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	O
Downing	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
a	O
Beef	O
Fork	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
laughing	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
'd	O
push	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
jesting	O
manner	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
struggled	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
parted'em	O
,	O
and	O
desir'd'em	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
playing	O
the	O
Fool	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Campry	I-pers
happening	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Firelock	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
sitting	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
Campry	O
's	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
laughing	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
accordingly	O
discharged	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
shot	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
sunk	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
shook	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
laught	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bleed	O
,	O
he	O
wrung	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
!	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ball	O
enter	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
Jaw	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Right	O
Ear	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
appearing	O
no	O
Malice	O
or	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
,	O
quiet	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Shewell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sheffield	B-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel	O
Screw	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Taps	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rea	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
the	O
Screw	O
Plate	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Screw	O
Plate	O
was	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
works	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Plate	O
himself	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Salver	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
54	O
l.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Bolonia	O
thrown	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
a	O
Canister	O
,	O
4	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Falwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Darbican	I-pers
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Trautum	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
Darbican	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Fallwells	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Glanisters	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Son	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
)	O
weighed	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
12	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
laced	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
laced	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
A	O
broad	O
Piece	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
and	O
being	O
accidentally	O
lockt	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Kitchen	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
alias	O
Floyd	B-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
)	O
on	O
Thursday	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
Johns	O
came	O
,	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
high	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Prats	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
break	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
slit	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
Bradshaw	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
beat	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
several	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
Watch	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
little	O
Cedar	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Townsend	O
coming	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
thrust	O
themselves	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Johns	O
taking	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
said	O
,	O
Child	O
I	O
am	O
high	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justices	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
'll	O
break	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
without	O
shewing	O
you	O
my	O
Authority	O
;	O
she	O
squauld	O
out	O
,	O
Bradshaw	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
Johns	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
Stair	O
head	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cedar	O
Chest	O
stood	O
:	O
she	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
Johns	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
Knife	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
or	O
break	O
her	O
Neck	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
Johns	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
(	O
a	O
girl	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Parlor	O
door	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
living	O
next	O
door	O
she	O
saw	O
Johns	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
and	O
say	O
;	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
Justice	O
Madam	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
cut	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
brought	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Perry	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Leckie	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Hereupon	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
Examined	O
on	O
that	O
point	O
:	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
and	O
visitors	O
use	O
to	O
Cry	O
out	O
Rogues	O
!	O
Whores	O
!	O
Thieves	O
!	O
Murder	O
.	O
Then	O
an	O
Officer	O
in	O
Court	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Mary	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Nightwalker	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
.	O
and	O
looking	O
wishfully	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
happening	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
a	O
Gouge	O
,	O
an	O
Auger	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
in	O
Marybon	B-place
Fields	I-place
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Toothacre	I-pers
.	O
Toothacre	O
bought'em	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
Grey	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
Tools	O
to	O
Grey	O
,	O
but	O
prov	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
long	O
before	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Grey	O
then	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
met	O
Nat	O
.	O
Glanister	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had'em	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
being	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
indicted	O
only	O
for	O
these	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Nat	O
.	O
Glanister	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloths	O
,	O
old	O
Glanister	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
own	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brean	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Booty	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hendry	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Newcomb	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Macfaston	I-pers
alias	O
Macsuson	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
5.	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Ozier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
last	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
1	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
19.	O
Bond	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Talmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tankard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Riggins	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Donay	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Winwright	I-pers
,	O
Natheniel	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
LEWIS	O
DOMINIQUE	O
CARTOUCHE	O
,	O
the	O
famous	O
French	O
Robber	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
broken	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
education	O
in	O
the	O
College	O
of	O
Jesuits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pranks	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
robberies	O
he	O
committed	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
Thief	O
taker	O
;	O
how	O
after	O
several	O
and	O
various	O
escapes	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
which	O
defy	O
'd	O
the	O
pub-lick	O
Justice	O
of	O
France	O
above	O
Seven	O
Years	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
relation	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
Also	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
bold	O
and	O
undaunted	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Confinement	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
a	O
Series	O
of	O
Adventures	O
and	O
Incidents	O
,	O
remarkable	O
,	O
entertaining	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
variety	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
just	O
arriv	O
'd	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
in	O
two	O
neat	O
Pocket	O
Volumes	O
with	O
Fourteen	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
.	O
THe	O
Life	O
and	O
strange	O
surprising	O
Adventures	O
of	O
ROBINS	O
O	O
N	O
C	O
R	O
U	O
S	O
O	O
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
who	O
28	O
Years	O
all	O
alone	O
in	O
an	O
uninhabited	O
island	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
America	O
near	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
River	O
Orinoquo	O
having	O
been	O
cast	O
ashore	O
by	O
shipwreck	O
wherein	O
all	O
the	O
Men	O
perished	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
strange	O
'	O
y	O
delivered	O
by	O
Pyrates	O
,	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
edition	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
W.	O
Taylor	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Black	O
Swan	O
in	O
Paternoster-Row	O
,	O
where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
Robinson	B-pers
Cruso	I-pers
's	O
serious	O
Refelections	O
,	O
viz	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
Solitude	O
how	O
uncapable	O
to	O
make	O
us	O
happy	O
,	O
and	O
unqualitied	O
to	O
a	O
Christian	B-pers
Life	I-pers
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
on	O
Honesty	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Honesty	O
,	O
of	O
Honesty	O
in	O
Promises	O
,	O
of	O
Relative	O
Honesty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Immorality	O
of	O
Converistion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Vulgar	O
Errors	O
of	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
on	O
the	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
Religion	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Listning	O
to	O
the	O
Voice	O
of	O
Providence	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
pro	O
ortion	O
between	O
the	O
Christian	O
and	O
Pagan	O
World	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
A	O
vision	O
of	O
the	O
Angelick	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
;	O
Wi.A	O
Common-wealth	O
Or	O
a	O
Teasury	O
of	O
Divine	O
,	O
Moral	O
,	O
Historical	O
,	O
and	O
Political	O
Admonitions	O
Similars	O
and	O
Sentences	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Schools	O
,	O
newly	O
corrected	O
and	O
enlarged	O
III	O
.	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
One	O
Thousand	O
and	O
One	O
stories	O
,	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indias	O
,	O
to	O
Divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
Avenge	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Dslalry	O
of	O
his	O
first	O
Sultaness	O
.	O
Containing	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
Manners	O
,	O
and	O
Religion	O
of	O
the	O
Eastern	O
Nations	O
,	O
than	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
any	O
Author	O
hitherto	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
parts	O
are	O
now	O
finish	O
'd	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
compleat	O
bound	O
,	O
i	O
.	O
6	O
Volumes	O
or	O
seperate	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Seignor	O
Roselli	O
,	O
adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
8mo.V	O
.	O
The	O
devil	O
on	O
two	O
stick	O
;	O
2	O
mo	O
,	O
VI	O
.	O
C.De	O
Amors	O
Novels	O
and	O
Tales	O
,	O
3.Vols	O
:	O
12mo	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
Love	O
Letters	O
from	O
a	O
Nobleman	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
parts	O
printed	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
8mo	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
Ovids	O
Art	O
of	O
Love	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
12mo	O
.	O
All	O
printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Taylor	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Black	O
Swan	O
in	O
Paternoster	O
Row	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
+++	O
An	O
intire	O
System	O
of	O
Arithmetic	O
:	O
or	O
Arithmetic	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
parts	O
Containing	O
Vulgar	O
,	O
Decimal	O
,	O
Duodecimal	O
Sexagerlineal	O
,	O
Political	O
,	O
Logarithmetical	O
,	O
Lineal	O
,	O
Instrumental	O
,	O
Algebraical	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Arithmetic	O
of	O
Negatives	O
,	O
and	O
Approximation	O
,	O
or	O
Converging	O
Series	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
Rules	O
New	O
,	O
curios	O
and	O
useful	O
mostly	O
accounted	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
Preface	O
,	O
the	O
Algebraic	O
paths	O
rendred	O
more	O
plain	O
and	O
care	O
than	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
,	O
by	O
Instructive	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
,	O
Literally	O
and	O
Numerically	O
in	O
a	O
method	O
new	O
solving	O
Equation	O
,	O
Simple	O
,	O
Quadratic	O
,	O
Cut	O
i	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
like	O
,	O
several	O
ways	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
proper	O
Places	O
of	O
this	O
Work	O
are	O
an	O
accurate	O
Table	O
of	O
Logerithms	O
,	O
to	O
10000.	O
and	O
Rules	O
to	O
find	O
those	O
to	O
100000000	O
,	O
and	O
natural	O
Numbers	O
to	O
such	O
Logarithms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
full	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Involution	O
,	O
Evolution	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Solution	O
of	O
all	O
Cases	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
are	O
24	O
large	O
:	O
and	O
Exquisite	O
Tables	O
(	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
valuation	O
of	O
Church	O
or	O
College-Leases	O
of	O
Land	O
)	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
those	O
of	O
Simple	O
Interest	O
and	O
Discount	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
method	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
Latter	O
and	O
the	O
present	O
worth	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
Days	O
,	O
also	O
multiple	O
Definitions	O
and	O
Explanations	O
of	O
Numbers	O
,	O
Quantities	O
,	O
and	O
Terms	O
used	O
in	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Arithmetic	O
in	O
Alphabetical	O
Order	O
,	O
rendering	O
the	O
whole	O
more	O
Intelligible	O
and	O
the	O
earlier	O
Learned	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
measuration	O
of	O
more	O
Superficies	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
than	O
any	O
book	O
wrote	O
purposely	O
on	O
the	O
Subject	O
has	O
Fashioned	O
.	O
This	O
Treatise	O
for	O
Copiousness	O
and	O
Novelty	O
of	O
Matter	O
and	O
Method	O
,	O
far	O
exceeding	O
the	O
most	O
perfect	O
Arithmetic	O
extant	O
.	O
Necessary	O
for	O
all	O
who	O
wou	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
little	O
study	O
acquire	O
a	O
compleat	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Numbers	O
and	O
Species	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
make	O
any	O
considerable	O
Progres	O
in	O
the	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
By	O
Edward	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
+++The	O
Scripture	O
Consist	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Scripture	O
Sentences	O
showing	O
what	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
Know	O
,	O
Believe	O
,	O
and	O
Practice	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
our	O
Eternal	O
Happiness	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Parts	O
,	O
I	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
such	O
sentences	O
as	O
show	O
us	O
our	O
Duty	O
to	O
God	O
and	O
Man	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
Graces	O
and	O
Virtues	O
:	O
Where	O
the	O
same	O
are	O
commanded	O
in	O
Holy	O
Scripture	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Promises	O
incouraging	O
thereto	O
,	O
their	O
opposite	O
Vices	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Threatnings	O
annexed	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Scripture	O
,	O
proper	O
for	O
our	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Thanksgiving	O
,	O
before	O
at	O
and	O
after	O
receiving	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
Also	O
an	O
Appendix	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Material	O
Arguments	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Authors	O
concerning	O
the	O
Divine	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	O
Scriptures	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Miracles	O
and	O
Prophecies	O
by	O
and	O
the	O
Prophecies	O
and	O
Types	O
of	O
our	O
Blessed	O
Saviour	O
.	O
All	O
Scripture	O
is	O
given	O
by	O
Inspiration	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
Profitable	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
2	O
,	O
T.	O
m.	O
3	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Holy	O
Scripture	O
containeth	O
all	O
Things	O
necessary	O
to	O
Salvation	O
,	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
Art	O
VI	O
.	O
and	O
Hom	O
.	O
10	O
;	O
Printed	O
for	O
W.	O
Mears	O
wihtout	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
away	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
5th	O
Edition	O
of	O
a	O
Perswasive	O
to	O
a	O
Serious	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Death	O
and	O
Judgement	O
:	O
Concerning	O
several	O
considerations	O
and	O
Directions	O
in	O
order	O
therein	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Supplement	O
to	O
the	O
Christian	O
Minister	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brief	O
Appendix	O
concerning	O
two	O
Forms	O
of	O
Prayer	O
,	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Plegue	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brief	O
introduction	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
Price	O
4d	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
A	O
Discount	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
,	O
Price	O
3d	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Bishop	O
Williams	O
's	O
Exposition	O
of	O
Church	O
Catechism	O
,	O
Price	O
4d	O
:	O
IV	O
.	O
A	O
method	O
for	O
serving	O
God	O
,	O
in	O
private	O
for	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
week	O
;	O
Price	O
3d	O
.	O
V.	O
The	O
necessity	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
attending	O
the	O
publick	O
Worship	O
there	O
,	O
Price	O
3d	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
An	O
ordinary	O
day	O
well	O
spent	O
,	O
Price	O
1d	O
.	O
All	O
printed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
yard	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
is	O
only	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymst	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Bell	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy	O
Grass	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
A	O
help	O
to	O
Magistrates	O
,	O
and	O
Ministers	O
of	O
Justice	O
:	O
Also	O
a	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
and	O
Ward-Officers	O
.	O
Containing	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Plain	O
or	O
ethics	O
for	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
Clerks	O
.	O
3	O
Of	O
Grand	O
and	O
Petty	O
Juries	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
4	O
.	O
Penalties	O
upon	O
Forestallers	O
of	O
Markets	O
Fairs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
5	O
.	O
Some	O
Directions	O
to	O
Coroners	O
and	O
their	O
Inquests	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
Mayors	O
of	O
Towns	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Branches	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
a	O
High	O
Constable	O
,	O
Petty	O
Constable	O
,	O
Headborough	O
,	O
Tythingmen	O
,	O
Bailifs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
Church	O
wardens	O
and	O
Sidemen	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
the	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
Tollkeepers	O
and	O
Fair	O
keepers	O
.	O
11.	O
he	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
Surveyors	O
of	O
Highway	O
,	O
Scavengers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Office	O
and	O
Duty	O
of	O
Officers	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Cases	O
13	O
.	O
Observations	O
about	O
Games	O
and	O
Gaming-Houses	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Penalties	O
14	O
.	O
Of	O
laying	O
Wagers	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Cases	O
adju	O
'	O
g	O
'd	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
,	O
With	O
considerable	O
Amendments	O
,	O
and	O
Additions	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
those	O
cases	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
any	O
former	O
Impression	O
.	O
By	O
P.	O
S.	O
Gent	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Boddington	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Ball	O
in	O
Duck-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
The	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Moughon	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Clare	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
in	O
Ireland	O
on	O
Two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
falsly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Hundred	O
and	O
One	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
to	O
Cheat	O
the	O
Popish	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Clare	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
,	O
by	O
Colour	O
of	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Entitled	O
an	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
suppressing	O
Tories	O
,	O
Robbers	O
,	O
Rapperices	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
I.Of	O
The	O
Laws	O
of	O
CHANCE	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Method	O
of	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Hazaeds	O
of	O
GAME	O
,	O
Presn	O
'	O
y	O
demonstrated	O
and	O
applied	O
to	O
Games	O
a.	O
present	O
most	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
Which	O
may	O
be	O
extended	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
intricate	O
case	O
of	O
Chance	O
imaginable	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Uzziah	O
and	O
Jesham	O
,	O
a	O
Poem	O
:	O
Occason	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Revolution	O
in	O
65k	O
.	O
and	O
containing	O
impartial	O
and	O
instructive	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
distinction	O
of	O
both	O
Parties	O
who	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
memorable	O
Event	O
.	O
Oxuris	O
vera	O
suvelveus	O
Price	O
6d	O
.	O
III.The	O
Whole	O
Dury	O
of	O
a	O
Christian	O
both	O
in	O
Faith	O
and	O
Practice	O
Succinctly	O
explain	O
'd	O
in	O
familiar	O
Verse	O
:	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
,	O
with	O
exact	O
References	O
to	O
the	O
Text	O
of	O
Scripture	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
several	O
Answers	O
are	O
grounded	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
Catechism	O
of	O
HUGO	B-pers
GROTIUS	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
Three	O
Pence	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
Admontions	O
,	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
Inherit	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
short	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
old	O
Gleets	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cur	O
'd	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
PRACTICAL	O
SCHEME	O
,	O
the	O
Method	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
expos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
grose	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
derected	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cincar	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
M	I-pers
.D	O
.	O
Emerasti	O
?	O
credo	O
meturi	O
carchii	O
.	O
Quaras	O
quando	O
itarum	O
persa	O
iterumque	O
perira	O
Pussu	O
,	O
I	O
satics	O
fortus	O
!	O
Horat	O
.	O
Principus	O
asta	O
.	O
Ovid	O
Printed	O
for	O
.	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
J	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holburn	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
Cheap-side	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Written	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
Memorandum	O
.	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Cherwood	O
at	O
the	O
Cato's-Head	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
T	O
Edsin	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Arms	O
over-against	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
Price	O
5s	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
Benj	B-pers
Motte	I-pers
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwisk	O
Lane	O
,	O
Price	O
3d	O
.	O
