TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
1679	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
Committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
THe	O
first	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
one	O
Katherine	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornzie	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
almost	O
smothering	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
with	O
the	O
Bed-clothes	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
her	O
Servant-Maid	O
,	O
who	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
effecting	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
their	O
Candle	O
,	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blemish	O
in	O
his	O
Eye	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
secured	O
all	O
pursuit	O
,	O
they	O
Ransacked	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
14	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Plates	O
,	O
fourty	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Table-Linnen	O
,	O
Childbed-Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cloathes	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
rub	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
after	O
upon	O
another	O
exploit	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Gold	O
being	O
Committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
parties	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
without	O
pausing	O
,	O
singled	O
him	O
from	O
amongst	O
a	O
dozen	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
place	O
of	O
residence	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
therefore	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrian	B-pers
Scroop	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
Murther	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Kings-street	B-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
some	O
violent	O
Fudes	O
arose	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
observing	O
,	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
prevent	O
and	O
hinder	O
them	O
from	O
injuring	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
sothat	O
by	O
the	O
mediation	O
of	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
they	O
seemingly	O
were	O
pacifyed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
return	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
his	O
sorrow	O
for	O
some	O
unadvized	O
words	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
out	O
in	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
long	O
renewed	O
that	O
Friendship	O
,	O
ere	O
a	O
greater	O
contest	O
arose	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
threw	O
two	O
several	O
Tankards	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
later-hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
whereupon	O
in	O
great	O
disgust	O
he	O
leaves	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
deceased	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
run	O
him	O
in	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
entering	O
about	O
five	O
inches	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
mortal	O
,	O
yet	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
disarmed	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
to	O
part	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
caught	O
the	O
deceased	O
by	O
the	O
Nose	O
with	O
his	O
Teeth	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
acted	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
yet-Best	O
deceased	O
not	O
till	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
therefore	O
no	O
malice	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
a	O
Taylor	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
a	O
Servant-maid	O
in	O
York	B-place
buildings	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
about	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
snatching	O
a	O
bundle	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
containing	O
two	O
Aprons	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
betook	O
himself	O
to	O
flight	O
,	O
yet	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
closely	O
pursued	O
by	O
two	O
Porters	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
Court	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
swearing	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
withstanding	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spark	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Souch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
a	O
notorious	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
was	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
Cornhil	B-place
,	O
by	O
one	O
Nichols	B-pers
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
needs	O
fasten	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
repairing	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
searching	O
her	O
Placket	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
searching	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
thence	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
proper	O
Use	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
making	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
sheard	O
off	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Cully	O
having	O
some	O
mistrust	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
loss	O
;	O
and	O
runs	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
departed	O
new	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
bewail	O
his	O
folly	O
:	O
yet	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
pursute	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
,	O
returns	O
again	O
,	O
perhaps	O
for	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
contrary	O
to	O
her	O
expectation	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Abbot	O
lying	O
perdue	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Nichols	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
returned	O
from	O
the	O
pursute	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
to	O
debauch	O
her	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
antient	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Abbot	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Actually	O
married	O
to	O
two	O
several	O
Wives	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
further	O
examination	O
of	O
Witness	O
or	O
particulars	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castillian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
having	O
impeached	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
the	O
Chamber-dore	O
of	O
one	O
Luke	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
,	O
after	O
an	O
entrance	O
at	O
the	O
outward	O
Window	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
severally	O
Indicted	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
former	O
should	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
yet	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
himself	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
handfuls	O
of	O
monies	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
broaken	O
Drawers	O
;	O
his	O
Arguments	O
against	O
his	O
pretended	O
accomplice	O
,	O
were	O
so	O
simple	O
and	O
ineffectual	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
induced	O
to	O
credit	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
often	O
traping	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Youth	O
of	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Jones	O
was	O
cleared	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Castilian	O
found	O
Guilty	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Swiny	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
Baliffs	O
follower	O
,	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
the	O
circumstance	O
in	O
nature	O
thus	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Bailiffs	O
and	O
their	O
followers	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
Arrest	O
one	O
Harris	O
for	O
a	O
debt	O
of	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
;	O
due	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Timothy	B-pers
Pride	I-pers
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
Guard	O
him	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
important	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
accordingly	O
came	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
three	O
crossing	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
still	O
following	O
them	O
to	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
back	O
Gate	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
swore	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
in	O
manfully	O
defending	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
received	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
Brest	O
five	O
inches	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
died	O
,	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Deaths-wound	O
by	O
the	O
Brother	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
an	O
accomplice	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
and	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Broad-Gold	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seymore	I-pers
of	O
White-Chapple	B-place
;	O
at	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Goss	O
entering	O
at	O
the	O
Seller	O
Dore	O
,	O
which	O
accidentally	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
undiscovered	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
in	O
part	O
confess	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
yet	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
stoutly	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
circumstance	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
and	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barrel	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
twelve	O
penny	O
Ribon	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
tenn	O
shillings	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Millener	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
offered	O
to	O
depart	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stayed	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
,	O
and	O
compounded	O
ere	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
farther	O
dispute	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
trick	O
,	O
to	O
evalidate	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
proved	O
ineffectual	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Benison	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
,	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
being	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
stolen	O
one	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
of	O
died	O
Bays	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
proof	O
thereof	O
,	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
of	O
force	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
wherefore	O
he	O
being	O
indicted	O
as	O
the	O
principle	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
referred	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
indictment	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pettiford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
by	O
one	O
Wallis	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
Water	O
Lane	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
bare	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
;	O
vallued	O
at	O
about	O
five	O
pound	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
nor	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
neither	O
handled	O
nor	O
saw	O
,	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Smith	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Family	O
swore	O
so	O
resolutely	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
maliciously	O
laid	O
to	O
blast	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
so	O
discreet	O
as	O
to	O
diserne	O
it	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Richardson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
three	O
more	O
did	O
Felloniously	O
take	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
forced	O
and	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
of	O
New-Inn	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.Clements-Dean	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
a	O
Hair-cambler	O
Cloak	O
,	O
one	O
beaver	O
Hat	O
forty-six	O
Guinnies	O
six	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Five-shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
;	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
spreading	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Richardson	O
,	O
who	O
before	O
was	O
very	O
bare	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
being	O
observed	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Inn	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
whole	O
handfuls	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
question	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
manner	O
and	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
where	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
moneys	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
thrown	O
by	O
his	O
Confederates	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
accordingly	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
denied	O
what	O
ever	O
former	O
he	O
had	O
declared	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
what	O
moneys	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
one	O
Russel	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
,	O
his	O
Confession	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
also	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Fellonously	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Milliner	O
s	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martains-lane	I-place
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
tweenty	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
;	O
but	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
soon	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
afore	O
mentioned	O
parcel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taxed	O
,	O
pretended	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
ne	O
'	O
r	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
his	O
slight	O
excuses	O
would	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
prevail	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Confederate	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game-cock	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
valued	O
at	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
from	O
Deborah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
and	O
fellonionsly	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hen-roost	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
said	O
Cock	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Market-woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Woman	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
thereof	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Drate	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
guilty	O
for	O
felloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Stockings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howly	I-pers
likewise	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
pence	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chamber-pot	O
in	O
Finch-lane	B-place
:	O
as	O
also	O
William	O
Woodword	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Rye	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
In	O
all	O
eight	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
7	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Zouch	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castilian	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Swiny	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
:	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Sessions	O
did	O
conclude	O
for	O
the	O
Fellons	O
,	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
the	O
Jesuits	O
being	O
to	O
begin	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
