TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
particularly	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
and	O
Gondemnation	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Wigginton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wiggens	O
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
like	O
hath	O
scarce	O
been	O
heard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Washborne	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
follow	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Sedanmen	O
,	O
had	O
as	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
been	O
carrying	O
one	O
Captain	O
Lucy	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
Nortnumberland-House	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
they	O
Jostelled	O
the	O
deceased	O
against	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
struck	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Cain	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
they	O
undertook	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
Horses	O
,	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Horse-way	O
,	O
this	O
began	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
conflict	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
so	O
wounded	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
thirteen	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
heard	O
for	O
both	O
parties	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Alexander	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Chearing-Cross	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
keeping	O
a	O
Coffe-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Coffe	O
,	O
staying	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
innto	O
a	O
Chamber	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Fellow	O
called	O
little	O
Anthony	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Legisman	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
house	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
seven	O
other	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Peerl	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Meddal	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
nineteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
vallue	O
of	O
100	O
pounds	O
,	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
much	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
Prison	O
,	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
at	O
Supper	O
together	O
,	O
there	O
arose	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
caused	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Singing	O
a	O
Baudy	O
Song	O
under	O
a	O
Ladies	O
Window	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
aggravate	O
with	O
many	O
base	O
words	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desiring	O
to	O
avoid	O
farther	O
mischif	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
when	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
geting	O
from	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
standing	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
had	O
the	O
ill	O
hap	O
to	O
wound	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
self	O
Preservation	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
returned	O
it	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Le-Merry	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Burglary	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
refusing	O
to	O
Plead	O
,	O
the	O
Executioner	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
tie	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
being	O
perswaded	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
Plead	O
,	O
and	O
Pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
confederate	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Cast	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burgalary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
near	O
South-Town	B-place
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Watch	O
vallued	O
at	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
Three	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
supposed	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broak	O
open	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
and	O
getting	O
in	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
who	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
light	O
a	O
Candel	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloathes	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Bed	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
feeling	O
them	O
and	O
then	O
putting	O
out	O
the	O
Candel	O
they	O
departed	O
;	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Party	O
robed	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloathes	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
Lodged	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloathes	O
of	O
a	O
Traveller	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Erazmus	I-pers
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
vallue	O
of	O
5	O
pounds	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
THe	O
first	O
we	O
shall	O
here	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Peetly	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
Nephew	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Ramble	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
past	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Whetstones	O
Park	O
,	O
wheregoing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
they	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
dore	O
for	O
entrance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
pretending	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
admittance	O
;	O
which	O
so	O
far	O
transported	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
throw	O
lighted	O
Links	O
up	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
affirmed	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
Fire	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
foul	O
Linnen	O
that	O
was	O
now	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Musquet	O
charged	O
with	O
hail-Shot	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
up	O
great	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
whereat	O
Wildstreet	O
end	O
the	O
Watch	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
disarmed	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
discharged	O
his	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
,	O
in	O
five	O
hours	O
he	O
dyed	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledging	O
that	O
the	O
piece	O
went	O
off	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Wigington	I-pers
alias	O
Wiggens	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
whipping	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
Girl	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
she	O
having	O
in	O
some	O
nature	O
offended	O
her	O
,	O
either	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
mony	O
from	O
her	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
spoiled	O
some	O
work	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
proceeding	O
to	O
this	O
unusual	O
Cruelty	O
,	O
She	O
having	O
got	O
one	O
Sadler	O
a	O
Bayliffs	O
follower	O
,	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
whip	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
a	O
Cat	O
with	O
nine	O
tails	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
did	O
affirm	O
that	O
they	O
whipped	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
so	O
cruelly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
blood	O
flowed	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
abundance	O
,	O
yet	O
could	O
not	O
this	O
nor	O
the	O
Childs	O
lamentable	O
cries	O
retard	O
her	O
Cruelty	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
hinder	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
from	O
hearing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
as	O
't	O
is	O
said	O
stopped	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
continued	O
to	O
whip	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
founded	O
away	O
as	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
that	O
barbarous	O
usage	O
dyed	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Asistant	O
fled	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
S.	O
sepulchres	O
Parish	O
,	O
as	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
Silk	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
having	O
been	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Underthrop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
having	O
Two	O
Wives	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
lawfully	O
Married	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Toogood	I-pers
had	O
been	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
here	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
leaving	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
to	O
ramble	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
courted	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
so	O
far	O
prevailed	O
with	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
consent	O
to	O
Marriage	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Sarjeant	O
at	O
the	O
Mace	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Estate	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
In	O
Court	O
the	O
latter	O
Wife	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Marriage	O
being	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Silk	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Plate	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
being	O
apprehended	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
such	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Campaign	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Stuffs	O
to	O
the	O
vallue	O
of	O
40	O
shillings	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
her	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
she	O
alledged	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
being	O
not	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Magdaline	B-pers
Woof	I-pers
,	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
10	O
or	O
a	O
11	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
formerly	O
,	O
durst	O
not	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
interrupt	O
her	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
desperate	O
Inclination	O
to	O
mischief	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Blanch	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
tryed	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
of	O
10	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Mat	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
buying	O
her	O
Clothes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
;	O
who	O
no	O
sooner	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
without	O
any	O
difficulty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
This	O
Session	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
pleaded	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
for	O
killing	O
a	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
Sessions	O
since	O
in	O
Old-Pallace-Yard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
a	O
Jesuite	O
or	O
Popish-Priest	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Indictment	O
Read	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
making	O
many	O
great	O
apollogies	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Tryed	O
and	O
acquitted	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
prepared	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
defer	O
his	O
Tryal	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
9	O
persons	O
Received	O
Sentance	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
3	O
Men	O
and	O
6	O
women	O
,	O
10	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
concluded	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
