TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
For	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
,	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
especially	O
the	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Winnel	I-pers
for	O
Murdering	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeks	I-pers
Yeoman	O
of	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
persons	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
,	O
living	O
near	O
Rochester	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
about	O
4	O
pounds	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Salsbury	O
Court	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
had	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
and	O
having	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Robbed	O
his	O
said	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
several	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
broak	O
open	O
divers	O
Chests	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Courts	O
directing	O
that	O
although	O
the	O
Fellony	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
another	O
County	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
London	O
was	O
a	O
Fellony	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Ferdenando	I-pers
a	O
Dutch-man	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
about	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Froud	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
where	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
he	O
broak	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
or	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
several	O
Half-shirts	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mrs.	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
Dutch-man	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
allowed	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
requires	O
.	O
A	O
mixed	O
Jury	O
,	O
of	O
half	O
English	O
and	O
half	O
Dutch	O
,	O
he	O
pleading	O
by	O
an	O
interpreter	O
,	O
his	O
plea	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
set	O
upon	O
,	O
run	O
in	O
thither	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
security	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
allegation	O
proved	O
too	O
weak	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
cliping	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
the	O
indictment	O
specifing	O
40	O
Elizabeth	O
shillings	O
.	O
40	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
half-Crowns	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
in	O
Carter	O
Lane	O
London	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheeres	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
ClippingInstruments	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
known	O
to	O
give	O
several	O
people	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
clipped	O
monies	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
several	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
in	O
other	O
mens	O
Names	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
put	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
call	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
got	O
large	O
money	O
in	O
exchange	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Clipped	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Tools	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Hix	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
supposed	O
designed	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
monies	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
appertained	O
to	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
behalf	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
feared	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
lodged	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
Attached	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
to	O
the	O
no	O
small	O
wonder	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dudy	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Bagshot	B-place
on	O
the	O
10	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
45	O
shillings	O
in	O
moneys	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Swore	O
possitivly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
horse	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
several	O
came	O
in	O
upon	O
oath	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Horse	O
he	O
road	O
out	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
evidence	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
,	O
the	O
scene	O
was	O
altered	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
so	O
challenged	O
was	O
bought	O
at	O
Kettering	O
in	O
Northhampton	O
shire	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Buying	O
and	O
Selling	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
traced	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
space	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
let	O
or	O
hired	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
suspicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
which	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
deposed	O
upon	O
oath	O
that	O
the	O
horse	O
found	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
far	O
different	O
marks	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
that	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Witnisses	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
strengthen	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
six	O
pounds	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
book	O
with	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
it	O
bearing	O
that	O
date	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
like	O
wise	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeks	I-pers
a	O
Yeoman	O
of	O
the	O
Gaurd	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
they	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
in	O
a	O
Coffe-house	O
near	O
the	O
Maypolefell	O
to	O
quarryling	O
about	O
drinking	O
of	O
Healths	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
some	O
pause	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
reconciled	O
and	O
so	O
parted	O
,	O
passing	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
where	O
again	O
faling	O
at	O
varience	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
ere	O
they	O
drew	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
deceased	O
fled	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
to	O
avoid	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Mortal	O
wounds	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
afront	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
calling	O
him	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
against	O
which	O
they	O
only	O
drew	O
to	O
defend	O
their	O
own	O
lives	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
De	I-pers
Bule	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-man	O
living	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
some	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Silver	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Custom-house-wayter	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
came	O
to	O
Aid	O
and	O
Assist	O
one	O
that	O
seised	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
De	O
Bule	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
Robbed	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toply	I-pers
her	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
carryed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
learned	O
he	O
lesson	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
again	O
denyed	O
the	O
same	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
a	O
Charwoman	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Brunkard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Fellonously	O
entring	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
by	O
takeing	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Cagement	O
and	O
entring	O
,	O
conveyed	O
thence	O
Lenin	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
fellony	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
confess	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
evident	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
a	O
Souldier	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Penner	B-pers
being	O
his	O
fellow	O
Souldier	O
,	O
by	O
knocking	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Musqnet	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
quarrel	O
and	O
sufficient	O
provocations	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
One	O
Fulnum	B-pers
a	O
Dray-man	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
For	O
the	O
Killing	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
which	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Lane	O
with	O
a	O
loaded	O
Dray	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
Horses	O
which	O
were	O
somewhat	O
unruly	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Flung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
the	O
Dray	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
near	O
to	O
a	O
Stoan-cutters	O
Shop	O
a	O
stone	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
Foot	O
long	O
and	O
1	O
Square	O
,	O
stood	O
up	O
an	O
end	O
,	O
behind	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
Run	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Dray	O
coming	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
stone	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
crushed	O
her	O
immediatly	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
without	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
her	O
making	O
the	O
least	O
out-cry	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Dray	O
and	O
Person	O
being	O
seased	O
;	O
the	O
Crowners	O
Jury	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
found	O
it	O
special	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
exceeding	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
bind	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
the	O
Brewer	O
to	O
answer	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
steal	O
a	O
Coral	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
living	O
in	O
Holburn	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
greatly	O
deny	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Petitions	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Whittakar	I-pers
,	O
were	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
them	O
imparting	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
under	O
commitment	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
petitioned	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
once	O
more	O
besought	O
their	O
Lord-ships	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
Bailed	O
or	O
Proceeded	O
against	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Proviso	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
:	O
As	O
likewise	O
another	O
Petition	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilsons	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Eearl	O
of	O
Shaftsbury	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
under	O
a	O
commitment	O
of	O
Treason	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
4	O
former	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
formerly	O
had	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Courts	O
Jurisdiction	O
to	O
Bail	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
must	O
apply	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Bench	O
Court	O
in	O
Term	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
prosecution	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
releived	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
their	O
Commission	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
sat	O
being	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Goal-delivery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
Goal	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
relieve	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
now	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
Expressed	O
many	O
horrid	O
Treasons	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
uttered	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
against	O
his	O
sacred	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
endevouring	O
the	O
Subversion	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
the	O
Witnisses	O
that	O
were	O
Sworn	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbin	I-pers
,	O
Brian	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elaines	I-pers
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Denis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Macknamara	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ivy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Turbervil	I-pers
,	O
who	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Counsel	O
gave	O
their	O
evidence	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
examined	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
examination	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
about	O
4	O
hours	O
returned	O
the	O
Bill	O
Ignoramus	O
,	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
persons	O
Condemned	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Winnel	I-pers
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
for	O
Horse-stealing	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
font	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
.	O
