TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYAL	O
and	O
CONDEMNATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
which	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAILY	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
And	O
most	O
remarkably	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
Whipt	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
Death	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	O
.	O
MAjor	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Oglethorp	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Captain	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Guards	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Posts	O
,	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
a	O
Health	O
To	O
the	O
confusion	O
of	O
alldouble	O
Hearts	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
declare	O
themselves	O
as	O
they	O
meant	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
interpreting	O
to	O
be	O
meant	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
flew	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
very	O
gross	O
language	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Major	O
not	O
being	O
longer	O
able	O
to	O
endure	O
,	O
drew	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
suffered	O
to	O
hurt	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
heat	O
continued	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
met	O
by	O
Clarendine	B-place
house	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
drew	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
'ere	O
any	O
could	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
and	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
:	O
and	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
another	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
Dyed	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
no	O
wayes	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
former	O
Grudge	O
or	O
prepense	O
Malice	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
A	O
Bailiffs	O
follower	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Murdering	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Ratcliff	B-place
:	O
Which	O
Inhuman	O
Barbarity	O
was	O
acted	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
or	O
Inmate	O
to	O
one	O
Lattice	O
Wigington	O
,	O
a	O
Semptress	O
,	O
who	O
Instructed	O
Children	O
in	O
that	O
Mystery	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretented	O
,	O
having	O
wronged	O
her	O
of	O
some	O
trivial	O
Summ	O
of	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
5	O
pounds	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
help	O
give	O
her	O
Correction	O
,	O
who	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Child	O
by	O
the	O
Wrists	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
whip-cords	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
strip	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
hours	O
,	O
still	O
rubbing	O
the	O
Wounds	O
with	O
Salt	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
an	O
handkercher	O
,	O
lest	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
should	O
pity	O
her	O
out-Cry	O
for	O
the	O
hard	O
cruel	O
usage	O
:	O
In	O
three	O
dayes	O
she	O
dyed	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fled	O
:	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Two	O
more	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
1680.	O
stole	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
Fustian	O
Drawers	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
in	O
Little	B-place
Saint	I-place
Bartholmews	I-place
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
a	O
Sailer	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Eight	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
Spain	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Boat	O
:	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
that	O
being	O
Shipwracked	O
about	O
2	O
Leagues	O
from	O
Shore	O
,	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
and	O
Thirteen	O
men	O
more	O
putting	O
several	O
Baggs	O
of	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Long	O
Boat	O
,	O
stood	O
from	O
shore	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Confusion	O
this	O
Money	O
being	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
he	O
converted	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Use	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
demand	O
,	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Naples	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
comprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
preventing	O
lude	O
women	O
from	O
Murthering	O
their	O
Bastard	O
Children	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cranvil	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranvil	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
pounds	O
.	O
And	O
again	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
of	O
both	O
which	O
Robberies	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
except	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranvil	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
by	O
Law	O
to	O
comit	O
any	O
Felony	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
opening	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
of	O
Lincolns	B-place
Inn	I-place
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
Pick-locks	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
having	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Logans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laramore	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
20	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Button	O
sellers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
coming	O
to	O
cheapenButtons	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Buttons	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
departed	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
Yard	O
,	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fellony	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Alice	O
Turburg	O
,	O
vel	O
Turnpery	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
s	O
Childs	O
Neck	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
part	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
11	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
which	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
her	O
Grandfathers	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Harness	O
maker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
there	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
except	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
boot	O
the	O
foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
complained	O
not	O
of	O
till	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
known	O
whether	O
the	O
Girl	O
did	O
consent	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
nice	O
point	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mace	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
notorious	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
by	O
them	O
committed	O
about	O
2	O
years	O
since	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Vakeny	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
Mathes	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
discovered	O
them	O
,	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Ladder	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
entred	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
Farindines	O
and	O
Morenas	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
latter	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Long	O
lane	O
,	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Maid	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
Light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
when	O
watching	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
Lace	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
another	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
:	O
And	O
likewise	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
by	O
the	O
dexterous	O
way	O
of	O
Glimmering	O
,	O
or	O
pretending	O
to	O
Light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
received	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Ship	O
lying	O
at	O
Deptford	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Sea	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
Rugs	O
,	O
Blankets	O
andother	O
Furniture	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Peuter	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
of	O
Raysons	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
whole	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
were	O
stopt	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
:	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
being	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Head	O
,	O
upon	O
plain	O
prooff	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
Mistris	B-pers
,	O
as	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Woollen	O
and	O
Peuter	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
prooff	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Ariss	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
of	O
2	O
Mares	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	B-place
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Warwickshire	B-place
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
home	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Hugh	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
several	O
Treasonable	O
Expressions	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
He	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Brainford	I-place
to	O
light	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
by	O
his	O
chilliness	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
replyed	O
,	O
what	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bellasis	O
Gentlemen	O
?	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
ever	O
since	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
a	O
Muster-Master	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
30	O
or	O
40000	O
in	O
Pay	O
,	O
Expecting	O
Orders	O
every	O
day	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Protestants	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
quartered	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
:	O
And	O
his	O
Captaines	O
name	O
was	O
Mews	O
.	O
For	O
this	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
,	O
He	O
spake	O
but	O
in	O
jest	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
other	O
Discourse	O
:	O
And	O
feigned	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
half	O
distracted	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Edwards	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
reading	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
a	O
special	O
Plea	O
,	O
Signed	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Counsellor	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
stand	O
it	O
,	O
certaining	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
then	O
acquitted	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
Orders	O
from	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
summ	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sing	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
a	O
Secretary	O
to	O
Mother	O
Cellier	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
several	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow	B-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
,	O
and	O
for	O
disparaging	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Popish	O
Plot	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Presbyterian	O
Plot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
was	O
Murthered	O
by	O
the	O
Presbyterians	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
readiness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
deferred	O
for	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Its	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Pension	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
Coffee-houses	O
and	O
publick	O
Meetings	O
to	O
disparage	O
the	O
Discoverers	O
of	O
the	O
Plot	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
7	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
john	O
Sadler	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Abot	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Mader	I-pers
,	O
J.	O
Aris	O
and	O
Jo	O
.	O
Robertson	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stanes	O
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
five	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
1	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
And	O
8	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
.	O
