TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYAL	O
and	O
CONDEMNATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
Beginning	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
1681	O
.	O
Ending	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
:	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
Two	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
,	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
Quartred	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hindmash	I-pers
,	O
who	O
printed	O
and	O
published	O
the	O
Blasphemous	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Presbyterian	O
Pater	O
Noster	O
,	O
their	O
Creed	O
,	O
&	O
X	O
Commandments	O
.	O
CAptain	O
Randal	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
Bridle	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Whip	O
,	O
all	O
valued	O
at	O
7	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mead	B-pers
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Half	O
way	O
house	O
between	O
Deptford	B-place
and	O
Kent-street	B-place
;	O
The	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
Mead	O
coming	O
from	O
Greenwich	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
near	O
the	O
Half	O
way	O
house	O
;	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
and	O
Deliver	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
Pistol	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
being	O
much	O
surprised	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
them	O
by	O
setting	O
Spurs	O
to	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
being	O
well	O
mounted	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
although	O
it	O
missed	O
him	O
,	O
frighted	O
him	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
to	O
yield	O
to	O
their	O
Mercy	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
book	O
,	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
Inn	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
ordered	O
her	O
standing	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
kept	O
private	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
came	O
;	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
wounded	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
wounded	O
him	O
about	O
2	O
years	O
since	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
hadnothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
brought	O
her	O
thither	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Inn-keepers	O
proving	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
having	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Whip	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
other	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
another	O
County	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Tryed	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reycroft	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Crasbrook	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
,	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Lace	O
,	O
several	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
wearing	O
Appare1	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
pound	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shifts	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
about	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
Her	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Masters	O
Mother	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
diligent	O
in	O
her	O
Sons	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
tripped	O
in	O
her	O
Tale	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
received	O
their	O
Charge	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Worell	I-pers
being	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Steward	B-pers
of	O
New-Inn	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
who	O
lately	O
Deceased	O
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
40	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
Prosecuted	O
by	O
the	O
Administrator	O
of	O
the	O
defunct	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
three	O
handfuls	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
in	O
her	O
Coat	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
note	O
testifying	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
honest	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
altogether	O
judged	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
like	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Goss	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
since	O
,	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
one	O
Seragold	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
moneys	O
,	O
Seragold	B-pers
,	O
Swearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick't	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
that	O
Sum	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
down	O
Temple-Lane	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Evidence	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodged	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
Apprehended	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
mention	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Robbery	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
judg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
grounded	O
upon	O
that	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
notorious	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sharply	O
reprehended	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
Cast	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Broad-Cloth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
ere	O
he	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hindmarsh	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
a	O
Blasphemous	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
Entituled	O
The	O
Presbyterians	O
Pater	O
Noster	O
,	O
Creed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
10	O
.	O
Commandements	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Ship	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
Anchor	O
near	O
New	B-place
Crane	I-place
Stairs	I-place
,	I-place
over	I-place
against	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
on	O
Easter	O
munday	O
last	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Hatches	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Beds	O
wearing	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
appertaining	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
Graves-end	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
not	O
rightly	O
laid	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
particular	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Books	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
shillings	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cadman	I-pers
a	O
Bookseller	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
which	O
he	O
conveyed	O
away	O
whilst	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Books	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Bookseller	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
a	O
brandy	O
Cup	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
6	O
pounds	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Broomer	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
Indicted	O
only	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
6	O
gilded	O
Corals	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
Mary	O
Woolnoth	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
near	O
King-street	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
got	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
a	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
such	O
means	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
Pregnancy	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
discernible	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Delivered	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
put	O
her	O
Child	O
(	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
was	O
Still-Born	O
)	O
into	O
a	O
Desk	O
or	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
locking	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
about	O
her	O
ordinary	O
Work	O
,	O
but	O
seeming	O
more	O
faint	O
and	O
weak	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
began	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
bare	O
conceit	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Delivered	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Mid-wife	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
with	O
many	O
protestations	O
,	O
till	O
by	O
Promises	O
and	O
Threats	O
they	O
so	O
far	O
prevailed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Still-Born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Labour	O
did	O
call	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
but	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
high	O
Garret	O
could	O
not	O
he	O
heard	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodal	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Crofts	B-pers
a	O
Bricklayer	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Crofts	O
'	O
fell	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
that	O
within	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
having	O
spit	O
Blood	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
One	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
several	O
Notorious	O
Robberies	O
,	O
by	O
him	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Roads	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
once	O
Sentenced	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
and	O
Pardoned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
Plead	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Pardon	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
the	O
needless	O
trouble	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
in	O
a	O
special	O
Plea	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
General	O
had	O
since	O
demurr	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
confessing	O
himself	O
a	O
Priest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Orders	O
from	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
desiring	O
wholy	O
to	O
cast	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
since	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
Orders	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
a	O
Treatise	O
against	O
the	O
Popish	O
Doctrine	O
of	O
Deposing	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
convinced	O
about	O
30	O
Catholicks	O
of	O
the	O
unlawfulness	O
of	O
that	O
Tenent	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oaths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
6	O
Weeks	O
space	O
betwen	O
his	O
being	O
cleared	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
France	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
space	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
taken	O
the	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
and	O
Supremacy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
abjure	O
the	O
Realm	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
sickness	O
hindred	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
heartily	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
interceed	O
for	O
Mercy	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
Recorded	O
and	O
he	O
Ordered	O
back	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
de	I-pers
Bordas	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Stephen	O
Beaumont	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Merchant	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
30	O
Guineis	O
,	O
1	O
Cap	O
,	O
1	O
Coral	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
1	O
CornelianRing	O
,	O
1	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
500	O
ounces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
pound	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
by	O
his	O
Executor	O
:	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
gave	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
full	O
proof	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
side	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
there	O
were	O
8	O
persons	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Die	O
.	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
6	O
Women	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Randal	O
Dolson	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Bordas	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reycroft	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Murther	O
and	O
Fellony	O
;	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Dickason	I-pers
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
for	O
perverting	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
then	O
a	O
Condemned	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Protestant	O
to	O
the	O
Popish	O
Religion	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
his	O
Sentence	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
,	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
Quarter	O
'd	O
,	O
Nine	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
and	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Hindma-sh	O
being	O
Bailed	O
,	O
the	O
Sessions	O
ended	O
.	O
