TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
especially	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
and	O
Condemnation	O
of	O
that	O
notorious	O
Highway-man	O
Randolph	B-pers
Poulson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Dickison	I-pers
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
who	O
Received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
Drawn	O
and	O
Quartered	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
for	O
Murther	O
ANN	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
felloniously	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male-Infant	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
the	O
circumstances	O
thus	O
,	O
She	O
having	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
confessed	O
,	O
was	O
got	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
so	O
cuningly	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
suspect	O
her	O
till	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
without	O
help	O
,	O
when	O
wraping	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
She	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
rising	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
her	O
Mistris	O
finding	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
cause	O
;	O
whereupon	O
supspecting	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
uponinquiry	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
stoutly	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
still	O
Born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
.	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
,	O
this	O
being	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
;	O
her	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
finding	O
her	O
pains	O
come	O
fast	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
knocked	O
with	O
her	O
shoo	O
,	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
none	O
hear	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
lay	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
concealing	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
material	O
Point	O
of	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
reciting	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sibel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Hut	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Maid	O
of	O
about	O
Eighteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
Some	O
angry	O
words	O
rising	O
between	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
her	O
Mothers	O
part	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
such	O
bad	O
Language	O
as	O
provoked	O
her	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
thrown	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Kenel	O
,	O
to	O
tread	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnights	O
time	O
after	O
died	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sickly	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
no	O
bruses	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquited	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
Lace	O
,	O
Puter	O
,	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Deans	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty-Fourth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodall	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
John	B-pers
Crafts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Labourer	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Brick-layer	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
minding	O
his	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
neglected	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
employ	O
another	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
gon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
denying	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
any	O
;	O
having	O
passed	O
his	O
word	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
Lodged	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
three	O
Weeks	O
afterward	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Death	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
who	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
Condemned	O
for	O
Cliping	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
Pardon	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
several	O
Roberys	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
,	O
who	O
about	O
three	O
Sessions	O
's	O
since	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
Twenty-fifth	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
received	O
Orders	O
from	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
came	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
and	O
acted	O
as	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
whose	O
Trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
once	O
for	O
,	O
his	O
pretending	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Sessions	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
special	O
Plea	O
he	O
brought	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Kings	O
Attorny	O
General	O
made	O
a	O
demur	O
,	O
being	O
now	O
called	O
up	O
and	O
his	O
Indictment	O
read	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
desiring	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
Pardon	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
trouble	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
advised	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
full	O
intent	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
cleared	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
to	O
depart	O
the	O
Kindom	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
writtent	O
a	O
Book	O
touching	O
the	O
unlawfulness	O
of	O
Murthering	O
or	O
deposing	O
Princes	O
and	O
had	O
perswaded	O
very	O
many	O
Catholicks	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
and	O
Supremacie	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Favourable	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
himself	O
wholly	O
upon	O
their	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Du	I-pers
Boardas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
being	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
Stephen	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Marchant	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
or	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
valued	O
at	O
Four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Three	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
Thirty	O
Guinies	O
,	O
125	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
in	O
Moneys	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
,	O
she	O
had	O
conveyed	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Moneys	O
upon	O
the	O
Constables	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
she	O
aledged	O
that	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
time	O
and	O
brought	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
withstanding	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Star	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Robed	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Weller	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Fourteen	O
Shillings	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Napkins	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
an	O
Old	O
Womans	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
hod	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
Shifts	O
made	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
She	O
pleaded	O
a	O
Lodger	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
excuse	O
being	O
groundless	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Three	O
Shilling	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Dickison	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pervert	O
on	O
Martha	O
Cook	O
a	O
Convict	O
,	O
his	O
Indictment	O
being	O
grounded	O
upon	O
a	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
drawing	O
away	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Subjects	O
from	O
their	O
Allegiance	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
about	O
Three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
since	O
being	O
Condemned	O
for	O
Cliping	O
and	O
Coyning	O
,	O
and	O
remaining	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Two	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
her	O
fellow	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
embrace	O
the	O
Romish	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
yielding	O
to	O
their	O
proposition	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Priests	O
into	O
the	O
Press-yard	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
promise	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
Pardon	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
renounce	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
confessed	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
to	O
encourage	O
her	O
to	O
perservere	O
in	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
Embraced	O
,	O
oftentimes	O
brought	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
disclosing	O
to	O
on	O
Partridg	O
a	O
Presbyterian	O
Minister	O
,	O
he	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
who	O
acquainted	O
Captain	O
Richardson	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
Twenty-first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Proselite	O
,	O
was	O
seised	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Priest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
Portugal	O
Embassadour	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
commited	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
likewise	O
owned	O
himself	O
a	O
Priest	O
;	O
and	O
but	O
faintly	O
denied	O
the	O
pervertion	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Partridg	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
giving	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
satisfied	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
,	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
Quartered	O
as	O
a	O
Traitor	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
An	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Roman	I-pers
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wood	B-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
'	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
vallued	O
at	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
former	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
Mary	O
Snell	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Fellony	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
against	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wood	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Corrals	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
7	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
Robing	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Randol	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
kept	O
a	O
Lime-Wharf	O
near	O
the	O
Horse-Ferry	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Six	O
Pounds	O
,	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Whip	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
;	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
coming	O
from	O
Dedford	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
near	O
the	O
Halph-way-House	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turning	O
his	O
Mare	O
about	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
adjacent	O
Houses	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
firing	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
dismount	O
and	O
stand	O
to	O
their	O
Mercy	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
about	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Ribon	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
being	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
private	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
confession	O
during	O
his	O
Imprisonment	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Seaman	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Ship	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
over	O
against	O
Waping	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Sea-cloaths	O
,	O
Beds	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Rugs	O
,	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Ships	O
Crue	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
geting	O
on	O
Shoat	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
plead	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
his	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Sea-man	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
producing	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
nor	O
proving	O
the	O
Buying	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
6	O
Women	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Randolph	B-pers
Poulson	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Dickason	I-pers
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Beardos	I-pers
,	O
:	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rycroft	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
for	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
.	O
9	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
1	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
