TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYAL	O
and	O
CONDEMNATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
Beginning	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
1681	O
.	O
Ending	O
the	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Shaftsbury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Howard	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
of	O
Escreek	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
of	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
against	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
Black-fryers	O
.	O
ONE	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rumny	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
both	O
being	O
alive	O
at	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
Marrying	O
the	O
first	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
Lived	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
went	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
:	O
where	O
at	O
Boston	O
in	O
New-England	O
,	O
he	O
personating	O
a	O
Knight	O
of	O
that	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Name	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
Marryed	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
last	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Committing	O
that	O
Fellony	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
Inclination	O
,	O
Tempted	O
him	O
to	O
Marry	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
continual	O
Torment	O
to	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Indictments	O
read	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
)	O
to	O
their	O
Indictents	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Buckly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Clenchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
the	O
party	O
Killed	O
being	O
a	O
Baliffs	O
Follower	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
,	O
attending	O
a	O
Marshals	O
Court-Officer	O
,	O
to	O
Arrest	O
Richard	B-pers
Boil	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
having	O
some	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
they	O
Watchedfor	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
drawn	O
by	O
4	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
upon	O
a	O
single	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Pistols	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Baliffs	O
planting	O
themselves	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Arrest	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
observing	O
(	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
scufling	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
let	O
fly	O
a	O
Pistol	O
which	O
only	O
Grazed	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
his	O
Master	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
fired	O
another	O
,	O
loaden	O
with	O
two	O
Bullets	O
,	O
which	O
enterd	O
six	O
Inches	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
Cryed	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
I	O
am	O
Shot	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Killed	O
,	O
he	O
dyed	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Baliffs	O
carryed	O
off	O
their	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Writs	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
112	O
l.	O
the	O
Youth	O
alledged	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
holding	O
the	O
Pistol	O
up	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
it	O
unhappily	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fired	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
several	O
Threatning	O
Words	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
upon	O
Executing	O
the	O
Kings	O
Writ	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Cases	O
the	O
Law	O
can	O
not	O
allow	O
it	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Maidstone	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Moor	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Handcarcheifs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Coifs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
in	O
Corn-hill	B-place
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
denyal	O
,	O
she	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hawkson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
setting	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
Robing	O
Edward	B-pers
Bets	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Cradeck	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
near	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
peices	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
Mony	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
beat	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
confestd	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
Accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
in	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
three	O
Fellows	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Hawkson	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Sham	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
,	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidences	O
Swearing	O
point	O
blank	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hornsey	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
several	O
others	O
(	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
already	O
Executed	O
)	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Plate	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
coined	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
broad	O
peices	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
60	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
Barbarously	O
using	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
Wounding	O
,	O
Beating	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Miles	O
distant	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
Testimony	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Swearing	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
one	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Broad	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
during	O
his	O
being	O
above	O
stairs	O
and	O
felloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
1	O
Cloak	O
3	O
Perriwigs	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Perriwigs	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
offering	O
Composition	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
once	O
found	O
mercy	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guildy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Till	O
of	O
a	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
being	O
askd	O
,	O
a	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Estate	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
shrewd	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
,	O
three	O
notorious	O
Shop-lifts	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Flowered-silk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tryerwood	O
,	O
in	O
Corn-hill	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Silk	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
without	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
buying	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Servants	O
were	O
busy	O
,	O
they	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
Cheapned	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
their	O
Confederate	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
observed	O
by	O
an	O
Opposite	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
notice	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
they	O
persued	O
,	O
and	O
Apprehended	O
all	O
three	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
whose	O
Custody	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
Contradicted	O
by	O
some	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
them	O
Discoursing	O
together	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Fellony	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Petitions	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
;	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
Esebreek	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
presented	O
their	O
Petitions	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	O
Patince	O
Ward	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
sitting	O
on	O
Commission	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
In	O
which	O
were	O
contained	O
their	O
several	O
Prayers	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Committed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Crimes	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
prosecution	O
being	O
made	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
requested	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
either	O
speedily	O
proceeded	O
against	O
,	O
or	O
Bailed	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
now	O
Majesty	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
,	O
which	O
Petitions	O
were	O
read	O
by	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Motion	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Consideration	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
General	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Pettyt	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
alledging	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
Church-men	O
,	O
or	O
persons	O
fitly	O
qualified	O
to	O
serve	O
their	O
King	O
and	O
Country	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sheriffs	O
Answered	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
returned	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
men	O
of	O
candid	O
Reputations	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dismissed	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Court	O
on	O
Fryday	O
morning	O
next	O
,	O
till	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Sessions	O
was	O
Adjourned	O
.	O
The	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
according	O
to	O
Order	O
attending	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
General	O
made	O
his	O
Exceptions	O
against	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
being	O
observers	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
returned	O
at	O
the	O
Nomination	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Tertio	O
Henry	O
8.	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
debate	O
,	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
against	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledg	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
Black-fryers	O
.	O
Wherein	O
was	O
specified	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
Traiterously	O
Conspired	O
against	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
he	O
intending	O
to	O
depose	O
and	O
Murther	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
provided	O
Armour	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Habillaments	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
to	O
seize	O
upon	O
his	O
Majesty	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
the	O
Reading	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
desired	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dugdale	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
.	O
the	O
Two	O
Macnamarra	O
's	O
and	O
Sir	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jennings	O
alleaged	O
several	O
desperate	O
Treasons	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
seise	O
the	O
King	O
at	O
Oxford	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
unlese	O
he	O
would	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
Parliament	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
ready	O
thousands	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prepared	O
with	O
Armor	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
weight	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
received	O
the	O
Bill	O
;	O
after	O
Dinner	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
Ignoramus	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
presented	O
a	O
Petition	O
,	O
subscribed	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
whereas	O
they	O
were	O
informed	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Priests	O
and	O
Jesuites	O
that	O
lay	O
under	O
Sentence	O
of	O
condemnation	O
,	O
did	O
dayly	O
Plot	O
and	O
contrive	O
by	O
sundry	O
Means	O
to	O
work	O
out	O
their	O
Deliverance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
Commission	O
from	O
Rome	O
,	O
they	O
sate	O
and	O
consulted	O
the	O
Destruction	O
of	O
the	O
Protestants	O
,	O
by	O
forging	O
diversand	O
sundry	O
devices	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
wherefore	O
they	O
prayed	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
might	O
either	O
be	O
removed	O
far	O
from	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
means	O
taken	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
from	O
such	O
like	O
attempts	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
which	O
Petition	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
promising	O
to	O
acquaint	O
his	O
Majesty	O
with	O
their	O
Prayers	O
.	O
Motion	O
being	O
made	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
late	O
Speaker	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
might	O
be	O
bailed	O
by	O
reason	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
entred	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
worthy	O
Peers	O
offered	O
to	O
engage	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
nor	O
only	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
9	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
foreseeing	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Motion	O
,	O
had	O
consulted	O
the	O
Matter	O
and	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
Opinion	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Power	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
Lordship	O
:	O
The	O
Tower	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Limits	O
of	O
that	O
Commission	O
they	O
sat	O
by	O
:	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Term-time	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
removed	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-bench-Bar	O
and	O
there	O
relieved	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wallop	O
likewise	O
moved	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
Heward	O
but	O
was	O
answered	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
having	O
no	O
Prosecutions	O
entred	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
discharged	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
:	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Hethrington	O
stiled	O
the	O
Manager	O
of	O
the	O
Irish	O
Evidence	O
,	O
upon	O
Bail	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
at	O
large	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
9	O
condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Th	O
.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
Ro	O
.	O
Hawkson	B-pers
,	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
Buckly	B-pers
,	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
Richardson	O
,	O
J.	O
Plat	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roly	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wolf	I-pers
.	O
4	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
3	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
