TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
Of	O
several	O
Notorious	O
MALEFACTORS	O
:	O
TOGETHER	O
With	O
the	O
other	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
OF	O
GOALE-DELIVERY	O
,	O
Holden	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
MUNDAY	O
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
1681.	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
Nineteenth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
.	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-house	O
in	O
the	O
Old-baily	O
,	O
holden	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goale-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fulnum	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
he	O
coming	O
up	O
Sea-coal-lane	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
a	O
suddain	O
starting	O
from	O
the	O
mid-way	O
,	O
ran	O
the	O
Dray	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
whenas	O
the	O
party	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
secure	O
herself	O
behind	O
a	O
great	O
stone	O
that	O
stood	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
Masons	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
wheel	O
drove	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
crushed	O
her	O
to	O
death	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
speaking	O
very	O
favourably	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
side	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
used	O
his	O
utmost	O
endeavours	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
expressed	O
abundance	O
of	O
sorrow	O
upon	O
the	O
fight	O
of	O
that	O
unlucky	O
accident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
bind	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
to	O
be	O
holden	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
next	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Mason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Indicted	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Certiorari	O
to	O
remove	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pomfrets	I-pers
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
;	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
stayed	O
the	O
drinking	O
of	O
five	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
calling	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
brought	O
it	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
alleadged	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
not	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
contest	O
arising	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
bound	O
them	O
over	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
Price	O
offered	O
to	O
compound	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
half	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Bonds	O
for	O
the	O
residue	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
testimonies	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
laborious	O
and	O
industrious	O
men	O
,	O
were	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
a	O
woman	O
about	O
seventy	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Husbands	O
;	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
eighteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
having	O
spent	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
Indicted	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
took	O
pitty	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
Acquit	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Curral	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
above	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
though	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Robberies	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
Sentence	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
was	O
reprieved	O
after	O
Judgment	O
,	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
Condemned	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
Arrabella	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Misprision	O
of	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
away	O
false	O
Coin	O
,	O
knowing	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Convicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
five	O
pound	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
his	O
Master	B-pers
,	O
living	O
near	O
Rochester	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
askt	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
alleadged	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
:	O
but	O
having	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Francisco	B-pers
Ferdinando	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Wolnooth	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
coming	O
up	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
convey	O
himself	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
alleadged	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
;	O
whereupon	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
half	O
Forreigners	O
and	O
half	O
English	O
were	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
heating	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Winel	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Murthering	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Guards	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
Sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
meeting	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
happened	O
into	O
discourse	O
about	O
divers	O
affairs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
contest	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
perswasions	O
of	O
some	O
persons	O
present	O
,	O
those	O
feuds	O
were	O
seemingly	O
laid	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
departed	O
as	O
good	O
friends	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
they	O
again	O
falling	O
at	O
variance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
upon	O
pretence	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
justled	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
latter	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
,	O
drew	O
likewise	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
.	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
after	O
several	O
Passes	O
run	O
him	O
in	O
under	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wounds	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Chirurgeon	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
Wounds	O
,	O
declaring	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wounds	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
two	O
several	O
Swords	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
after	O
the	O
Murther	O
committed	O
betaking	O
themselves	O
to	O
flight	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Filing	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Forty	O
Elizabeth	O
shillings	O
,	O
Forty	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Forty	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
the	O
First	O
his	O
half-Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
Clipping	O
shears	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
put	O
Monies	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Lumbard-street	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
short	O
warnings	O
,	O
receiving	O
broad	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Clipped	O
,	O
having	O
put	O
out	O
in	O
other	O
mens	O
names	O
about	O
six	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
allowed	O
them	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
that	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Instruments	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Hix	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
trusted	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
an	O
Attachment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
in	O
strange	O
names	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fopling	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
fourth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
Twenty	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
testified	O
against	O
her	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentance	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
sat	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
the	O
two	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justices	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
other	O
Judges	O
present	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftesbury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
Escreck	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
upon	O
Commitments	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Prisoner	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
like	O
Commitment	O
,	O
were	O
tendred	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pemberton	O
publickly	O
read	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
tending	O
to	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
;	O
shewing	O
that	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Petitioners	O
having	O
been	O
Committed	O
for	O
the	O
heinous	O
Crime	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
the	O
Warrants	O
of	O
their	O
Commitments	O
appears	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
continued	O
Prisoners	O
without	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
prosecution	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
twice	O
Petitioned	O
that	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
or	O
Bailed	O
,	O
therefore	O
they	O
again	O
humbly	O
besought	O
their	O
Lordships	O
,	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Tenor	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
then	O
be	O
brought	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
intent	O
and	O
meaning	O
thereof	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Petitions	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
return	O
for	O
answer	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tower	O
was	O
a	O
Prison	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
Jurisdiction	O
of	O
thatCourt	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
again	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
to	O
relieve	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
Term	O
apply	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Kings-Bench	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
no	O
prosecution	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
there	O
receive	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
for	O
securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
his	O
Lordship	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
sate	O
only	O
by	O
a	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goale-delivery	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Goale	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
appearing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Mr.	O
North	O
,	O
Counsels	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
made	O
objections	O
against	O
the	O
returning	O
of	O
the	O
Pannel	O
:	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
were	O
returned	O
upon	O
a	O
Precept	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goale-delivery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Returns	O
were	O
usual	O
,	O
they	O
prayed	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
over	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
Sworn	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
Returned	O
at	O
the	O
nomination	O
of	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
sworn	O
Ministers	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
3	O
Hen	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
And	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
observers	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Laws	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
frequented	O
Conventicles	O
,	O
and	O
resort	O
not	O
to	O
their	O
respective	O
Parish-Churches	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
prayed	O
the	O
Pannel	O
might	O
be	O
reformed	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Objection	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Pilkinton	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
worthy	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
men	O
of	O
unspotted	O
Reputations	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
returned	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
nomination	O
of	O
no	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
certain	O
knowledge	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
substancial	O
Citizens	O
.	O
Then	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sollicitor	O
General	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
demanded	O
whether	O
they	O
resorted	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
satisfyed	O
in	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
good	O
Churchmen	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
two	O
amongst	O
them	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
scruple	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
positive	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
demand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Loggan	O
;	O
whereupon	O
(	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
debate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
3	O
Hen	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
)	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
gave	O
their	O
consents	O
to	O
the	O
racing	O
out	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
inserting	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
being	O
removed	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
from	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
County-Goale	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
was	O
prefered	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
Eighteenth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
and	O
at	O
sundry	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
had	O
spoke	O
divers	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
the	O
destruction	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Subversion	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
that	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
were	O
Bryan	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turbervile	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Macknamarra	I-pers
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Denis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corkine	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
many	O
of	O
which	O
Deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Rouse	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
although	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Parliament	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
holden	O
at	O
Oxford	O
would	O
be	O
but	O
short	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
several	O
Prorogations	O
and	O
Dissolutions	O
would	O
avail	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
England	O
had	O
yet	O
another	O
way	O
to	O
effect	O
their	O
designs	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
by	O
force	O
of	O
Arms	O
to	O
compel	O
his	O
Majesty	O
to	O
condescend	O
to	O
their	O
requests	O
;	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
think	O
not	O
fit	O
here	O
to	O
insert	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
had	O
been	O
publickly	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
withdrew	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
allowing	O
them	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
debate	O
of	O
the	O
Priviledges	O
and	O
usual	O
Customs	O
of	O
Grand-Juries	O
,	O
they	O
consented	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
over	O
again	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
ask	O
them	O
such	O
Questions	O
as	O
they	O
should	O
think	O
convenient	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
tedious	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Jurors	O
withdrew	O
to	O
debate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
held	O
a	O
private	O
consultation	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
answering	O
every	O
man	O
to	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
returned	O
the	O
Bill	O
IGNORAMUS	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
demanded	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
thought	O
the	O
words	O
expressed	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
Treasonable	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
declaring	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
scrupled	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
resolve	O
their	O
doubts	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
satisfied	O
in	O
their	O
CONSCIENCES	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
what	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
had	O
Sworn	O
.	O
The	O
Grand-Jury	O
for	O
London	O
presented	O
several	O
noted	O
Recusants	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Liberties	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Commendations	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
declaring	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
defect	O
in	O
former	O
Juries	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
altogether	O
slack	O
in	O
returning	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
within	O
this	O
great	O
City	O
,	O
few	O
or	O
none	O
had	O
been	O
Convicted	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Plot	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Pilkinton	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
their	O
Lordships	O
needed	O
not	O
doubt	O
the	O
diligence	O
of	O
this	O
Jury	O
in	O
finding	O
Bills	O
against	O
Recusants	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
Convicted	O
.	O
The	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Portland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Recusancy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
joyned	O
Issue	O
thereupon	O
,	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
were	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
of	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
who	O
Convicted	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
last	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
at	O
this	O
Sessions	O
seven	O
persons	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
six	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
and	O
three	O
women	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Winel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Cutter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
to	O
be	O
Whiped	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
