TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
1681.	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
8th	O
following	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Shaftsbury	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
Howard	O
of	O
Escrick	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Rouse	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
preferred	O
against	O
Stephen	O
Colledge	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
concerned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
and	O
whipped	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
on	O
the	O
Twentieth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
they	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	B-pers
s	O
Pocket	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Georges	I-place
Fields	I-place
:	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
another	O
County	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
laid	O
as	O
only	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
she	O
finding	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Thief	O
takers	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
promised	O
Reward	O
,	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
bring	O
several	O
Pick-pockets	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
those	O
she	O
suspected	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
were	O
brought	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
presently	O
remembred	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
one	O
of	O
themconveyed	O
15	O
pieces	O
under	O
the	O
Carpet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
her	O
look	O
,	O
perhaps	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
15	O
pieces	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
they	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
silent	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
These	O
their	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Gang	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
were	O
such	O
plain	O
proofs	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
latter	O
he	O
being	O
only	O
taken	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Roly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Silk	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Tryerwood	I-pers
a	O
Mercer	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
yards	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
standing	O
purdue	O
,	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Silk	O
being	O
missed	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
.	O
Upon	O
their	O
Tryals	O
they	O
strove	O
to	O
shift	O
it	O
off	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
she	O
that	O
stood	O
without	O
pretending	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
only	O
hired	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
notoriously	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Traders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Leaner	I-pers
a	O
Taylor	O
living	O
in	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Churchporch	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
youth	O
,	O
and	O
lately	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
by	O
excessive	O
beating	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
Sworn	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
many	O
times	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
bruses	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
youth	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
attested	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
afterwards	O
take	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hands	O
and	O
squlch	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgions	O
that	O
opened	O
him	O
,	O
likewise	O
affirmed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
corrupted	O
Blood	O
and	O
water	O
in	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
lived	O
about	O
Nine	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
some	O
times	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Nor	O
Gulty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Prichet	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
the	O
mony	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
ere	O
he	O
could	O
escape	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
Servant	O
to	O
Esq	O
;	O
B.	O
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
upon	O
his	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Chenchit	I-pers
a	O
Marshals	O
Bailiffs	O
Follower	O
.	O
The	O
Circumstances	O
according	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
being	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
before	O
his	O
Masters	O
Coach	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Holsters	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
man	O
stop	O
the	O
Coach-Horses	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
upon	O
what	O
occasion	O
,	O
charged	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
doing	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Riding	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
found	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
had	O
Seised	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
so	O
inraged	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Riding	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Horses	O
Bride	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
another	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
forced	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Bullets	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
screamed	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
but	O
spoke	O
not	O
after	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
put	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
unawares	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evinence	O
being	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rumny	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Lawfully	O
marryed	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
alleadging	O
she	O
that	O
Prhsecuted	O
him	O
whom	O
he	O
last	O
Marryed	O
at	O
Boston	O
in	O
New	O
England	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
offending	O
against	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Lascivious	O
and	O
wicked	O
practises	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
his	O
being	O
marryed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
by	O
sundry	O
means	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hawkson	I-pers
,	O
two	O
notorious	O
Foot-pads	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
Richardson	O
(	O
who	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
)	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
abont	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
set	O
upon	O
one	O
Edward	O
Betts	O
near	O
Newington	O
Butts	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Barbarously	O
used	O
him	O
,	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
pound	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
they	O
well	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
pleading	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
unadvisedly	O
drawn	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Robbery	O
intended	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
charge	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
1	O
Coat	O
,	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
pounds	O
in	O
Mony	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
Broadstreet	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Perukes	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
made	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
in	O
Plate	O
,	O
Cloths	O
and	O
monys	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
Witness	O
Swore	O
point	O
Blanck	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
made	O
several	O
flight	O
Excuses	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
(	O
after	O
some	O
Objection	O
made	O
against	O
Three	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
General	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
containing	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
against	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
,	O
which	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Court	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
contained	O
several	O
treasonable	O
practises	O
by	O
him	O
devised	O
and	O
maintained	O
to	O
destroy	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
as	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
levy	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
raise	O
rebellious	O
Arms	O
to	O
seise	O
upon	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
Depose	O
and	O
Murrher	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
Examined	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
names	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dugdale	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Bryan	O
Haynes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Macknamarow	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Macknamarow	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Gennings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
gave	O
Testimony	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
about	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Design	O
on	O
foot	O
to	O
seise	O
the	O
King	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
enterprize	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
end	O
he	O
had	O
prepared	O
himself	O
not	O
only	O
Weapons	O
but	O
Armour	O
,	O
as	O
Back	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Head	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
declared	O
several	O
other	O
treasonable	O
practices	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
promoted	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
all	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
accorded	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
They	O
after	O
four	O
hours	O
consult	O
,	O
and	O
Examining	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
overagain	O
in	O
private	O
returned	O
it	O
Iguoramus	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	I-pers
Escbrick	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Colledge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
Committed	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
:	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Petitions	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
either	O
to	O
be	O
Proceeded	O
against	O
or	O
Bailed	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
For	O
Securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
Closing	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
their	O
Counsel	O
moved	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Judges	O
Opinion	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
Bail	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
comprehended	O
within	O
the	O
Commission	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Hetheringtan	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Bail	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Sessions	O
were	O
9	O
persons	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
6	O
men	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
,	O
viz	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Buckly	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
,	O
Richardson	B-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hawkson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roly	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
.	O
3	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
4	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
to	O
be	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
concluded	O
.	O
