TOKEN	NE
An	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
TRYALS	O
OF	O
SEVERAL	O
Notorious	O
MALEFACTORS	O
.	O
For	O
Murders	O
,	O
Fellonyes	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
Holden	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
AND	O
GOALE-DELIVERY	O
,	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
16.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
17	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
other	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
.	O
But	O
specially	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
John	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crossman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Debate	O
held	O
about	O
sending	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
to	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Scilly	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
January	O
the	O
16	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Perfuming	O
Pots	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Comizary	I-pers
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
living	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
bringing	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidences	O
possitive	O
swearing	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Confederate	O
with	O
a	O
Servant	O
lately	O
living	O
at	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Bethels	I-pers
in	O
Cornhil	B-place
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
Rob	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
three	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
eighty	O
Guinies	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
standing	O
Cups	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
300	O
l.	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
committed	O
when	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
that	O
servant	O
excepted	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
herbeing	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
Confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
where	O
the	O
Treasure	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
having	O
two	O
ten	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Guinny	O
,	O
an	O
half	O
Guinny	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sworn	O
,	O
having	O
Confessed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
six	O
pound	O
,	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Morfield	B-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
three	B-place
Black	I-place
Birds	I-place
in	I-place
Warwick	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
bringing	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
testify	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
dissatisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Hens	O
and	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
(	O
as	O
some	O
suppose	O
to	O
compleat	O
the	O
Turky	O
Feast	O
lately	O
held	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
so	O
is	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
but	O
sowr	O
sawce	O
to	O
his	O
Hollow	O
Bits	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cundell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloak	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
Drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
over-sight	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
amongst	O
his	O
own	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crosman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
Murthering	O
John	B-pers
Bret	I-pers
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
thus	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
opposite	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Cup	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Young	O
man	O
at	O
Play	O
with	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Stick	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
he	O
disarmed	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Carving-Tool	O
that	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
that	O
Trade	O
)	O
she	O
struck	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
3	O
inches	O
deep	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
his	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
left	O
it	O
sticking	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
threw	O
another	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
saying	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
Hanged	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
her	O
saying	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pass	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
Youth	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
forgive	O
me	O
my	O
Sins	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
Die	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
no	O
sooner	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
expired	O
;	O
She	O
alledged	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
several	O
provoking	O
Words	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
swore	O
Treason	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
forcibly	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Albinus	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
searching	O
for	O
prohibited	O
Goods	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Silver	O
Sword	O
Hilts	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
4	O
l	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
been	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
good	O
luck	O
this	O
:	O
But	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
Ten	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
continue	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Ten	O
Commitments	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
and	O
other	O
Goals	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Misdemeanors	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
objected	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
Counterfeited	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Five	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
the	O
Kings	O
Seal	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Loyal	O
NAT	O
'S	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Doctor	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Poysoning	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Life-Guard	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
Doctor	O
keeping	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
as	O
his	O
Miss	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
per	O
annum	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Doctor	O
takes	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
kindness	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Mornings	O
Draught	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
fell	O
exceeding	O
Ill	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
up	O
black	O
matter	O
,	O
complaining	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
Poysoned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
continuing	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
4	O
days	O
,	O
Died	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
opened	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Potion	O
was	O
found	O
setled	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
about	O
20	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
half	O
French	O
and	O
half	O
English	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Courts	O
being	O
dissatisfied	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ashbott	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Cars	O
over	O
her	O
head	O
of	O
which	O
braise	O
she	O
instanly	O
dyed	O
,	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
brushed	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
falling	O
under	O
the	O
wheel	O
,	O
the	O
Cart	O
being	O
heavy	O
Laden	O
with	O
Dung	O
,	O
it	O
went	O
over	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Horses	O
could	O
be	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
coming	O
by	O
might	O
under	O
the	O
Carter	O
from	O
saving	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
wilfully	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horses	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Almoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
Danes	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Sellwood	I-pers
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cravat	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	O
;	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Carpet	O
and	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
perceived	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
conveniently	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
charging	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
having	O
three	O
Indictments	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
of	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
for	O
Murder	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
another	O
by	O
the	O
Corroner	O
upon	O
his	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
andDeposed	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
several	O
Taverns	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
some	O
what	O
overcome	O
with	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
hot	O
Words	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
ere	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
prevented	O
run	O
him	O
two	O
inches	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
in	O
three	O
days	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Committed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Gresham	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
Committed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Foot	O
Soldier	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
a	O
Life-Guard	O
man	O
,	O
at	O
Kings-Gate	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Chelsey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Life-Guard	O
man	O
pursued	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
Draw	O
to	O
Defend	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
likewise	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Lemore	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentlewomans	O
House	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
valued	O
at	O
23	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
laid	O
at	O
13	O
l.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
having	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
speaking	O
with	O
Monsieur	O
Moses	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
Lodged	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
departed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
search	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
positively	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bringing	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
French	O
People	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lately	O
fled	O
out	O
of	O
France	O
for	O
Religion	O
,	O
to	O
Testifie	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Descended	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
honestly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
,	O
a	O
Council	O
,	O
moved	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
,	O
That	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
might	O
be	O
Granted	O
for	O
sending	O
the	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
,	O
now	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Newgate	O
to	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Scily	O
alledging	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
fully	O
Waranted	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
having	O
already	O
received	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Order	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pemberton	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
matter	O
that	O
concerned	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Majesty	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
Reprieve	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Order	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
thither	O
they	O
must	O
send	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
being	O
awarded	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
no	O
further	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
could	O
be	O
granted	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Pilkington	O
stood	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Lordship	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
his	O
Majestys	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
he	O
desired	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Sheriff	O
might	O
be	O
Indemnified	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
moved	O
by	O
a	O
Councellor	O
sent	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
General	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Bills	O
of	O
Indictment	O
were	O
brought	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evidence	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
preferred	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Order	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
were	O
brought	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Clerk	O
should	O
wait	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Kings	O
name	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
used	O
against	O
any	O
person	O
contrary	O
to	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Pleasure	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
7	O
persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
1	O
Man	O
and	O
6	O
Women	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Bennet	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crosman	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
3	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
Fined	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
10	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
John	O
brought	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Warrant	O
for	O
staying	O
his	O
being	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
:	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Recuzancy	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
ended	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
,	O
