TOKEN	NE
A	O
Full	O
and	O
True	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
WHICH	O
BEGAN	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
June	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
,	O
June	O
2d	O
.	O
1682	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
Contained	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
many	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
for	O
Murders	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Misdemeanours	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
the	O
TRYAL	O
of	O
JANE	B-pers
KENT	I-pers
for	O
Witch-Craft	O
.	O
TOGETHER	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
those	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Whip	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
some	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
Violently	O
took	O
the	O
Lady	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
June	O
1st	O
,	O
1682	O
.	O
THis	O
Day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
holden	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Instant	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rome	I-pers
,	O
of	O
25	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
narrow	O
Lane	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
hurt	O
by	O
a	O
Coach	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
stood	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
door	O
way	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
her	O
Gang	O
,	O
Shoulder'dher	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
delivering	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Comrades	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
immediately	O
perceiving	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
noise	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proofs	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
by	O
her	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
seaven	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
from	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jason	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
;	O
She	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
living	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Spoons	O
which	O
were	O
judg	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
pounds	O
,	O
being	O
used	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
clean	O
,	O
when	O
as	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Pantry	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
alledged	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
conveyed	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
whether	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
naming	O
a	O
strange	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
Masters	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
one	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
testifie	O
her	O
Honesty	O
and	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
her	O
former	O
Services	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Littlemorth	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Theed	I-pers
her	O
Master	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaels	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Querry	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
four	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
four	O
Guinnies	O
,	O
three	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
made	O
inquiry	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
Court	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
expressing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sorrow	O
for	O
her	O
Wickedness	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
return	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
three	O
Shillings	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butchers	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
being	O
these	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Stall	O
in	O
Honey-Lane-Market	B-place
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Neck	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
question	O
the	O
Sweetness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
smell	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watching	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
Apron-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
Money	O
departed	O
;	O
but	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
doing	O
such	O
another	O
Exploit	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Innocence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
Robbed	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Matpellier	I-place
,	O
otherwise	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarfe	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
;	O
whereupon	O
(	O
having	O
well	O
learnt	O
his	O
Lesson	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Indictments	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
for	O
Ships	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Yeames	I-pers
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
Stole	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
gathered	O
up	O
some	O
Chips	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Bolt	O
;	O
then	O
being	O
demandedwhy	O
he	O
concealed	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
he	O
alledged	O
that	O
his	O
Breeches	O
being	O
Ragged	O
,	O
it	O
droped	O
into	O
them	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
silly	O
excuses	O
excused	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Pilferer	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
es	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
Coverleds	O
,	O
Carpets	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broakers	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutor	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Arglass	O
,	O
deceased	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Crelling	I-pers
his	O
Lords	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Pormantle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Gold	O
Pendilum	O
Watch	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
14	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
and	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
28	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
21	O
Guinnies	O
,	O
25	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Siver-Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Earls	O
House	O
in	O
Druery-Lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
past	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
committed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
Irish	O
Man	O
whom	O
he	O
named	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
Renched	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
the	O
Pormantle	O
,	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
20	O
Guinnies	O
,	O
which	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
again	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Woman	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
e	O
're	O
she	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
Excuse	O
prevailed	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
a	O
Life-Guard-Man	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Roundwaite	I-pers
,	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
appeared	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Field	B-place
near	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
equally	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
pausing	O
,	O
fought	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
seven	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walked	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
friendly	O
walk	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
indeed	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
kind	O
of	O
former	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Mans-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
about	O
60	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Witch-Craft	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
several	O
Diabolick	O
Arts	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
compassed	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chamblet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
5	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
first	O
Bewitched	O
his	O
Swine	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
having	O
bargained	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
Pigs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
her	O
without	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
his	O
Daughter	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
most	O
piteous	O
Condition	O
,	O
Swelling	O
all	O
over	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
whichwas	O
discoloured	O
after	O
a	O
strange	O
rate	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
Bewitched	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Dr.	O
Hainks	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
his	O
Wives	O
water	O
,	O
the	O
pairing	O
of	O
her	O
Nails	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
boyl	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Pipkin	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
Swore	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
voice	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
Screimed	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
Murdered	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
swelled	O
and	O
bloated	O
:	O
A	O
Woman	O
that	O
searched	O
her	O
likewise	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Teat	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
unusual	O
Holes	O
behind	O
her	O
ears	O
:	O
A	O
Coach-man	O
likewise	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
refusing	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
his	O
Coach	O
overthrew	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
pains-taker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Chistopher	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
a	O
Laundress	B-pers
that	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
door	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
Bolted	O
;	O
then	O
entering	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Laundress	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
an	O
Oath	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
betrayed	O
,	O
yet	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
kneel	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
discover	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
present	O
she	O
promised	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
shutting	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
a	O
Study	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
20	O
pounds	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Squire	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Silk	O
Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
above	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Kinthorne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Gilis	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
from	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Landlord	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
received	O
a	O
severe	O
Clack	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
or	O
age	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentlewomans	O
Pocket	O
in	O
Honey-Lane	O
,	O
of	O
9	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Vox	B-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
him	O
.	O
Captain	B-pers
Pursell	I-pers
who	O
was	O
lately	O
Committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
violently	O
forcing	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Selleger	I-pers
out	O
of	O
her	O
Coach	O
,	O
upon	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
,	O
petitioned	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
of	O
Bail	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
replyed	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Indictment	O
intended	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Fellony	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Petition	O
,	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
Tryed	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
replyed	O
,	O
If	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
ready	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Session	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Littleworth	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
John	B-pers
Spittle	I-pers
ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Fined	O
20	O
pounds	O
.	O
