TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
OF	O
THE	O
PRISONERS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
Holden	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1682	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
related	O
a	O
True	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Proceedings	O
:	O
But	O
more	O
particularly	O
,	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
who	O
killed	O
the	O
Taylor	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ninth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
THIS	O
day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
began	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
Persons	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felonies	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Crimes	O
;	O
whereof	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
were	O
these	O
that	O
follow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
a	O
Victualler	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
third	O
past	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
whichbeing	O
refused	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
well	O
tutor	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
said	O
:	O
Yet	O
it	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
of	O
another	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Full-pot	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Summerset	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Meal	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
near	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
reading	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Josias	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lived	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
;	O
but	O
whilst	O
the	O
Tapsters	O
were	O
busie	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
afterwards	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
Thief	O
takers	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
although	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
disowned	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
said	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Orbe	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
questioned	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
whereto	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Cole	O
yard	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
promising	O
Satisfaction	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
being	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Indictments	O
under	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Perren	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
,	O
of	O
four	O
Guinies	O
,	O
two	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
knot	O
;	O
which	O
appeared	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
person	O
robbed	O
coming	O
drunk	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
pretended	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
took	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
long	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
mind	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
rose	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
charged	O
Perren	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
as	O
strongly	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
the	O
Shoulder-knot	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
nor	O
Silver	O
.	O
Perren	O
alledged	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
was	O
likewise	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
appearing	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
Company	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warraine	I-pers
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
party	O
dead	O
being	O
abroad	O
on	O
May	O
29	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
within	B-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
received	O
so	O
many	O
Bruises	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
thereof	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lay	O
languishing	O
,	O
he	O
accused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
verily	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
naming	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
might	O
but	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
doubted	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Party	O
(	O
though	O
desired	O
)	O
refused	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Yet	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Little	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Cloak	O
lined	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Sute	O
,	O
an	O
Embroider	O
'd	O
Belt	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
conveyed	O
away	O
by	O
Water	O
,	O
hiring	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
notice	O
that	O
such	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Thief-taker	O
,	O
who	O
soon	O
described	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
stoutly	O
denied	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
yet	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
One	O
Edling	B-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
died	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Wound	O
he	O
received	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster-Abby-yard	B-place
,	O
being	O
there	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
three	O
persons	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
tried	O
and	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
fled	O
into	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Several	O
Chyrurgeons	O
give	O
it	O
upon	O
their	O
Oaths	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
died	O
of	O
that	O
Wound	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
its	O
festering	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
his	O
Arm	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
although	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
strongly	O
urged	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Council	O
)	O
protesting	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
his	O
Assertion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
cleared	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scroby	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Silver	O
tipp	O
'd	O
Razors	O
,	O
Scissars	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Eight	O
pounds	O
;	O
when	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
sell	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Razors	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
those	O
Razors	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
any	O
ways	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Murrell	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
large	O
upon	O
Bail	O
)	O
for	O
killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
near	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
by	O
running	O
his	O
Coach	O
over	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
neglect	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
meer	O
accident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Catling	I-pers
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Covent-garden	B-place
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
was	O
very	O
tedious	O
;	O
a	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
called	O
on	O
either	O
Side	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
;	O
That	O
Robert	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
the	O
Party	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Party	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
used	O
too	O
much	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
far	O
enraged	O
his	O
Jealousie	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
sent	O
for	O
Catling	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
intimated	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Design	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
most	O
commonly	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
Dod	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
deny	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
having	O
passed	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
hapned	O
to	O
meet	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
several	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
much	O
Discourse	O
hapning	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
Manhood	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
killed	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
fear	O
'd	O
no	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
so	O
be	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Dod	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
simple	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
it	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
WhereuponDod	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
Fence	O
against	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
on	O
,	O
making	O
Offers	O
and	O
Passes	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
though	O
many	O
were	O
of	O
opinion	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
:	O
He	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catling	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
breaking	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
fled	O
;	O
Catling	O
dying	O
before	O
the	O
Chyrurgeons	O
could	O
dress	O
his	O
Wound	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Parson	O
in	O
Dod	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
his	O
Haunts	O
were	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Mountague	I-pers
's	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Poultney	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Trial	O
for	O
killing	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
drew	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Passes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
having	O
wounded	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
disarmed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
Tavern	O
;	O
where	O
finding	O
his	O
Wound	O
desperate	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Chyrurgeon	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
asking	O
who	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
fairly	O
,	O
the	O
Cause	O
being	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
Posted	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Minister	O
to	O
pray	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
forgiven	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
,	O
died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
produced	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
attest	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Party	O
defunct	O
had	O
upon	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
about	O
his	O
Marrying	O
a	O
Lady	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
many	O
threatning	O
Letters	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
followed	O
him	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
notice	O
he	O
sought	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Arms	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
to	O
whose	O
Custody	O
Mr.	O
Poultney	O
surrendred	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
absconded	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrough	I-pers
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
five	O
Pots	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Emms	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Northern	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
as	O
Accessarie	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
three	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
:	O
First	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tats	I-pers
;	O
second	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Person	I-pers
;	O
and	O
thirdly	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Tats	I-pers
.	O
Of	O
two	O
of	O
which	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
Emms	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
Sarah	B-pers
Northern	I-pers
only	O
appearing	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
At	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
condemn	O
'd	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meriday	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Emms	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
.	O
Seven	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
One	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
One	O
Fined	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pursell	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Pounsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
taking	O
away	O
Mrs.	O
Sinderfield	O
,	O
were	O
Bailed	O
.	O
