TOKEN	NE
THE	O
True	O
Account	O
OF	O
THE	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Holden	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
:	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Feb.	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Instant	O
.	O
CONTAINING	O
THE	O
TRYALS	O
Of	O
several	O
Notorious	O
Murtherers	O
,	O
Fellons	O
,	O
and	O
Burglarers	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pie	I-pers
,	O
For	O
Killing	O
the	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Hungerford-Market	O
.	O
TOGETHER	O
,	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
were	O
Condemned	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Whip	O
'd	O
:	O
With	O
many	O
other	O
Passages	O
that	O
happened	O
during	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Session	O
.	O
ON	O
Fryday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
several	O
Criminals	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
Fellony	O
,	O
Burghlary	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Misdemeanours	O
,	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bayliffs	O
Follower	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Edward	B-pers
Green	I-pers
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Hungerford-Market	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
(	O
as	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Marshals-Court-Writ	O
to	O
Arrest	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
word	O
of	O
Arrest	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
catching	O
up	O
his	O
Cleaver	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
at	O
their	O
peril	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
blow	O
cut	O
his	O
Wrist	O
almost	O
through	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
then	O
making	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
cut	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
fingers	O
almost	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
having	O
his	O
Rapier	O
drawn	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
still	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
his	O
Cleaver	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Writ	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Maiden	B-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
offender	O
,	O
had	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
;	O
Viz	O
.	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
observed	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
(	O
as	O
't	O
is	O
supposed	O
)	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lay	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
their	O
opportunity	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
locking	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
departed	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denying	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
suppos	O
'd	O
that	O
some	O
one	O
else	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
lay	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Bunfield	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Watches	O
,	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Moneys	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
pounds	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
already	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Cocks	O
,	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Fowl	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
proof	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
,	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Victualler	O
in	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
40	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
in	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
absenting	O
himself	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
hired	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
4	O
pounds	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
(	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
caused	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
(	O
upon	O
notice	O
had	O
of	O
their	O
flight	O
)	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
over-taken	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
carryed	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
7	O
Guinneys	O
were	O
found	O
sticking	O
in	O
a	O
Penny	O
Loaf	O
which	O
the	O
Womans	O
Child	O
had	O
in	O
its	O
Pocket	O
;	O
being	O
examined	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
Friends	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mardelue	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
an	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
comming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
watched	O
his	O
opportunity	O
and	O
carryed	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
(	O
being	O
evidently	O
proved	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Coxhill	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Dowgate	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Dyars	O
Apprentice	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
lost	O
off	O
the	O
Float	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
of	O
Padington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Chairs	O
,	O
Table-Linnen	O
and	O
Sheets	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
alledged	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Daughter	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
bringing	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
lay	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
a	O
Commission	O
from	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Customes	O
,	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Denue	I-pers
for	O
prohibited	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
Stones	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Diamond	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Three	O
pounds	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
having	O
Two	O
Sessions	O
since	O
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Fellony	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
Evident	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
prefer	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Trespass	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Francis	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Five	O
pounds	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
As	O
likewise	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boile	I-pers
as	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boile	I-pers
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
Indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
his	O
Companion	O
stole	O
it	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Couley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Glascock	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
,	O
vi	O
et	O
Armis	O
of	O
two	O
Hoods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Robbery	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Oden	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Pewter	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Willit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
A	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
Thirteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Shop-lifting	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
that	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
Fifty	O
pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Seaven	O
or	O
Eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
Evidently	O
proved	O
that	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
opening	O
a	O
Trunk	O
or	O
Desk	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Moneys	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
being	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
above	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
took	O
pitty	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
consideration	O
set	O
her	O
by	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Husband	O
during	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
failing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
latter	O
Marriage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
this	O
morning	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
formerly	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
perswasions	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
who	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
for	O
the	O
Procuring	O
his	O
Pardon	O
for	O
Burning	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	O
Stile	O
,	O
brought	O
his	O
Pardon	O
and	O
pleaded	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
Gloves	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
an	O
out-Shed	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Bennits	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Accusers	O
before	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
great	O
pains	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
obedient	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
:	O
In	O
that	O
case	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
doom	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Sentence	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strict	O
order	O
given	O
that	O
he	O
be	O
Executed	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
A	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
was	O
Exhibited	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burghlary	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
against	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
both	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
formerly	O
.	O
Eleven	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
:	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
:	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
And	O
One	O
Fin	O
'd	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
as	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
.	O
