TOKEN	NE
An	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
TRYALS	O
OF	O
SEVERAL	O
Notorious	O
MALEFACTORS	O
:	O
For	O
Murders	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
,	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
23.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
25	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
other	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
are	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Tryal	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
the	O
Butcher	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
full	O
Relation	O
how	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
pressed	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Obstinacy	O
in	O
not	O
Pleading	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Broaker	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Try	O
him	O
;	O
His	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
as	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
people	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
Testimony	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Belzer	I-pers
was	O
put	O
to	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bever	O
Hats	O
from	O
a	O
Haberdasher	B-pers
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan.	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
being	O
a	O
Quaker	O
,	O
and	O
refusing	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Quakers	O
Recognizance	O
for	O
prosecution	O
estreated	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
was	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Rhods	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
prooff	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
:	O
Jane	B-pers
Bunt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fam	O
'd	O
shop-Lifter	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
silks	O
,	O
Ribboning	O
and	O
stuffs	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Husbands	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
Marriage	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
in	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
under	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
antient	O
Plea	O
,	O
usual	O
to	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
old	O
proficients	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Treebarfoot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Drinking	O
and	O
making	O
Love	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
by	O
reasonof	O
going	O
to	O
School	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
afterwards	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Two	O
persons	O
were	O
likewise	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
but	O
no	O
exact	O
Proof	O
being	O
made	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
and	O
Bryan	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Kings	O
Highway	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
Indicted	O
having	O
a	O
Writ	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
somewhat	O
roughly	O
used	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
Fellony	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shippe	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
:	O
His	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
person	O
Condemned	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
yesterday	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
morning	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
earnest	O
request	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
denials	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
two	O
Indictments	O
one	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Matt-Peller	O
,	O
alias	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
on	O
the	O
19	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Commitment	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Thieves	O
,	O
comming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
were	O
shewed	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Cubbord	O
stood	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Tankards	O
were	O
which	O
they	O
perceiving	O
,	O
Pickt	O
the	O
Lock	O
in	O
the	O
Servants	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
departed	O
with	O
their	O
Prize	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Tankards	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
possitively	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Danstelo	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
Rings	O
,	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
which	O
things	O
upon	O
search	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
of	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
Sessions	O
since	O
:	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Crime	O
upon	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
hanged	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
in	O
Vain	O
,	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
becomming	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
keeper	O
in	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
about	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
Robbed	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
several	O
silver	O
Seals	O
,	O
Rings	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
kild	O
the	O
Butcher	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
l.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Widdow	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
killed	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
whereupon	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Testimony	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
now	O
Tryed	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Bayliffs	O
Assistance	O
or	O
Follower	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
sum	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
yield	O
obedience	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
taking	O
up	O
his	O
Carver	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
offers	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
a	O
stroak	O
over	O
the	O
Wrist	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
strove	O
to	O
guard	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
Cut	O
the	O
Bone	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
drawing	O
his	O
Rapier	O
,	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
giving	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mardelve	I-pers
an	O
Outlandish	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
ignorant	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
to	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
which	O
being	O
made	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
was	O
Tryd	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alost	I-pers
,	O
living	O
at	O
Paddington	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
Theives	O
cut	O
a	O
Ladder	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
12	O
doors	O
,	O
took	O
Table	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Tenant	O
to	O
the	O
Party	O
Robbed	O
;	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Searched	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Goods	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
proving	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Victualing	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Feilds	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
Sold	O
to	O
a	O
Usurer	O
in	O
Cloth-fair	O
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
Swore	O
Treason	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
unwarrantable	O
taking	O
away	O
Goods	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
Uncustomed	O
or	O
prohibited	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
Sessions	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Stone-Buttons	O
,	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
French	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
stole	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
prized	O
at	O
three	O
pounds	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Party	O
Robbed	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
he	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
much	O
in	O
Justification	O
of	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
appearing	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Frying	O
pan	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
all	O
endeavours	O
were	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
at	O
least	O
two	O
hours	O
spent	O
,	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
obstinately	O
refused	O
it	O
unless	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
his	O
Accusers	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
Sentence	O
was	O
passed	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
pressed	O
by	O
ten	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
conform	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
recant	O
his	O
former	O
stubborn	O
obstinacy	O
.	O
This	O
Sessions	O
Mr.	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
Pleaded	O
his	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Esquire	O
Stiles	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
.	O
An	O
Indictment	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
Nat	B-pers
.	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
report	O
about	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
which	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
being	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Billa	O
vera	O
.	O
The	O
French	O
Doctor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Poysoning	O
one	O
Morgan	O
a	O
Life-guard	O
Man	O
,	O
appearing	O
upon	O
his	O
Reculicence	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
Threatning	O
such	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
bound	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
security	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
John	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Nine	O
persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
one	O
Repreived	O
before	O
Judgment	O
,	O
upon	O
Promise	O
to	O
make	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Four	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Andd	O
so	O
it	O
Concluded	O
.	O
