TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
Held	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
Instant	O
,	O
but	O
Especially	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
S.	O
Tufton	O
,	O
and	O
Joh	O
.	O
Culfant	O
.	O
LAurance	B-pers
Adington	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Page	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Little	B-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	O
which	O
upon	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
Broak-open	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
taken	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30l	O
.	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
a	O
pick	O
Lock	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
some	O
suspition	O
Arising	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
at	O
Lambeths	O
Marsh	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
entring	O
a	O
suspitious	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
a	O
pick-Lock	O
Key	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
suspition	O
Committed	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
one	O
Rose	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
deep	O
gone	O
to	O
be	O
recovered	O
,	O
though	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
being	O
as	O
Scandalous	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Committed	O
to	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
about	O
30s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
when	O
in	O
Court	O
upon	O
Oath	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
and	O
proffered	O
either	O
to	O
give	O
or	O
take	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
on	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green-Dragon-Tavern	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
Hug	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Mony	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
presently	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
wicked	O
Husband	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
rid	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
denying	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
Evident	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
convict	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sackvil	B-pers
Tufton	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
a	O
Captain	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Agrith	B-pers
Hasselwood	I-pers
,	O
in	B-place
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
to	O
be	O
Assisting	O
to	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
in	O
the	O
performance	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Russel	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
said	O
Lord	O
Russel	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
caused	O
his	O
stand	O
of	O
Pikes	O
to	O
charge	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
Throng	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
the	O
Companies	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Ring	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Bill-Men	O
of	O
the	O
Hamlets	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
unfortunately	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushing	O
with	O
his	O
Pike	O
or	O
leading	O
Staff	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
into	O
which	O
towards	O
the	O
Left-side	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Staff	O
entered	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cryed	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Dead	O
Man	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
Blood	O
at	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
those	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
to	O
Seize	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
Killed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
less	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Died	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
sworn	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
by	O
divers	O
witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
their	O
Assistance	O
had	O
Orders	O
not	O
to	O
Enter	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
keep	O
Guard	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
pressed	O
hard	O
upon	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
which	O
oblidged	O
them	O
to	O
charge	O
their	O
Pikes	O
for	O
the	O
keeping	O
their	O
Orders	O
clear	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Pikes	O
were	O
so	O
charged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wound	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
Right-side	O
of	O
the	O
Pikes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
probably	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pike	O
was	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
yard	O
shorter	O
than	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
all	O
likelihood	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
weakness	O
in	O
his	O
Arme	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
such	O
a	O
Thrust	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
not	O
Subject	O
to	O
passion	O
or	O
rash	O
Actions	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
Of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Neverson	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
4l	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Mock	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
parish	I-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
out	O
Coats	O
,	O
Cloakes	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
Alleadged	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
ways	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
better	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Garret-	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
will	O
rather	O
induce	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
believe	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Allegation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
for	O
Killing	O
Edward	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
New-Branford	I-place
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Town	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
Drinking	O
Healths	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Macarty	O
drew	O
about	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
flinging	O
a	O
Brandy-pot	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
parted	O
;	O
Soon	O
after	O
a	O
difference	O
happened	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
formers	O
taking	O
Macartys	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
being	O
seemingly	O
made	O
Friends	O
,	O
they	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
expectation	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
Fought	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
some	O
passes	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
he	O
Dyed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Mallice	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Parliament	O
Robe	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sail	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
alleadged	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
Hackney	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Alderman	O
's	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Story	O
appearing	O
Frivilous	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Wiliam	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Cloath	O
from	O
Oliver	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
doing	O
the	O
like	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Kemps	I-pers
,	O
both	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Midwinter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
six	O
Coats	O
,	O
four	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Parsons	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
have	O
delivered	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
whereupon	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
by	O
running	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
fell	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
neither	O
saw	O
it	O
nor	O
could	O
have	O
prevented	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
found	O
Chance-Medley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Augustine	B-pers
Harkinson	I-pers
and	O
Humphy	B-pers
Steech	I-pers
,	O
took	O
their	O
Tryals	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Campaign-Coat	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
producing	O
divers	O
to	O
attest	O
his	O
former	O
Honesty	O
and	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
Jurors	O
supposing	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
himself	O
not	O
positively	O
owning	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knowel	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
George	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
upon	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Drinking	O
together	O
many	O
hours	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
fell	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
both	O
pacified	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
drew	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
after	O
divers	O
passes	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
received	O
a	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
former	O
Mallice	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Whinyard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Killing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
R.	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
when	O
upon	O
evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins-Lane	I-place
Fought	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Whinyard	O
and	O
Lake	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Jaw-broken	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
within	O
4	O
days	O
he	O
Dyed	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Whinyard	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
acquitted	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
anyways	O
Aiding	O
or	O
Abbetting	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Culefant	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Printing	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
,	O
two	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Libels	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
Intituled	O
,	O
The	O
Second	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Growth	O
of	O
Popery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
The	O
Second	O
part	O
of	O
Ignoramus	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Coppy	O
,	O
Corrected	O
the	O
Proofs	O
,	O
and	O
Incouraged	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clinch	I-pers
in	O
Amen-Corner	B-place
,	O
the	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
before	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Wixel	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
and	O
a	O
Pinner	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Woodvil	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pette	O
Lacenary	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Lace	O
,	O
Tape	O
,	O
Parchment	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
at	O
Gunies	B-place
near	I-place
Bow-Bridge	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Knives	O
,	O
Swords	O
,	O
Canes	O
,	O
and	O
Whips	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20l	O
.	O
from	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Waradine	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins-Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
day	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Presented	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
purporting	O
that	O
seeing	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
committed	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
continued	O
there	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
prejudice	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
he	O
Humbly	O
besought	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Bench	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
Tryed	O
or	O
Bailed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
taking	O
the	O
benefit	O
thereof	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Prayer	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
over-stayed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Power	O
to	O
grant	O
his	O
Request	O
.	O
This	O
Sessions	O
five	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Parson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Marsh	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bird	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	O
Marshal	O
.	O
Five	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	O
Daniel	O
,	O
Gabriel	O
Whinyard	O
,	O
Jane	O
Wixel	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Norton	O
.	O
Four	O
ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
James	O
Hancock	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Curtis	O
,	O
Peter	O
Neverson	O
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	O
Adington	O
.	O
Two	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Robinson	O
and	O
William	O
Smith	O
.	O
And	O
Lastly	O
,	O
John	O
Culefant	O
was	O
Fined	O
Two	O
hundred	O
pound	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-end	O
,	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
the	O
Fine	O
be	O
payed	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
Ended	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
