TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
which	O
began	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
following	O
;	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
commiting	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Entered	O
according	O
to	O
ORDER	O
THE	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
holden	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baly	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Midlesex	O
,	O
which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
were	O
these	O
Peter	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
appearing	O
thus	O
.	O
Viz	O
.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
traviling	O
late	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
lonely	O
place	O
,	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
three	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
accomplices	O
,	O
who	O
carryed	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
riffled	O
them	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Frienged	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
latter	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
Sword	O
,	O
Belt	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Mony	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
robery	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
butnot	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
having	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaden	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
er	O
'	O
e	O
he	O
well	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
Cock	O
at	O
half	O
bent	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pistol	O
thereupon	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Bullet	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
malice	O
nor	O
any	O
colour	O
of	O
intention	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Chance	O
Medlie	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Leaden	O
half-hundred	O
weights	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Porril	I-pers
in	O
little	B-place
Alhollows	I-place
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Examination	O
confessed	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Puterer	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Beaver-Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Belt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Alhollows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
the	O
Sword	O
and	O
Belt	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
withal	O
aledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
no	O
ill	O
design	O
the	O
Fellony	O
being	O
apparent	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Castelport	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
from	O
an	O
unknown	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
a	O
Fellony	O
committed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Parkeson	I-pers
.	O
Viz	O
.	O
the	O
latter	O
having	O
stolen	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Campaign	O
Coat	O
,	O
Linen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
vallue	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
sold	O
the	O
same	O
or	O
diuers	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
under	O
rates	O
,	O
which	O
goods	O
so	O
sold	O
were	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
,	O
hid	O
amongst	O
several	O
rags	O
and	O
were	O
at	O
first	O
denyed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
whichbred	O
a	O
suspition	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
not	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
pleading	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
party	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
bring	O
several	O
to	O
testifie	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
purchase	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
convert	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
in	O
Morc-Lane	B-place
into	O
a	O
common	O
Baudy	O
house	O
,	O
suffering	O
Lude	O
Licentious	O
people	O
to	O
commit	O
carnal	O
wickedness	O
in	O
a	O
debauched	O
way	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
caught	O
her	O
husband	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
lude	O
woman	O
just	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Chamber	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
swore	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
new	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
distantplace	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
nought	O
with	O
the	O
womans	O
husband	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
finding	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
also	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
testifie	O
her	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
honest	O
industry	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
one	O
Act	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
render	O
her	O
liable	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
prevention	O
of	O
such	O
lude	O
Courses	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
keep	O
a	O
common	O
baudy	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
entetain	O
all	O
comers	O
and	O
goers	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
upon	O
giving	O
suretys	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
futer	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
his	O
wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
recusants	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
above	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
16	O
years	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
space	O
one	O
Month	O
repaired	O
to	O
their	O
Parish	O
Church	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
Church	O
or	O
Chaple	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
Divine	O
Service	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
appearing	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
that	O
if	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Goal	O
delivery	O
they	O
rendered	O
not	O
up	O
their	O
body	O
to	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
their	O
Lands	O
,	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Chatles	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
seized	O
to	O
the	O
behoof	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
as	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
has	O
provided	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tindal	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
near	O
to	O
the	B-place
Muse	I-place
on	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
the	O
deceased	O
haveing	O
information	O
given	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tindal	O
had	O
Spoak	O
scurilous	O
words	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
resolued	O
to	O
take	O
Satisfation	O
for	O
the	O
abuse	O
and	O
thereupon	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
perswasions	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
sword	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
draw	O
,	O
yet	O
here	O
fused	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
defended	O
himself	O
.	O
still	O
retiring	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
finding	O
himself	O
hard	O
pressed	O
and	O
his	O
Life	O
in	O
danger	O
he	O
drew	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
gard	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
passes	O
the	O
deceased	O
receiued	O
a	O
wound	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
pap	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
with	O
in	O
an	O
houer	O
space	O
he	O
died	O
but	O
no	O
mallice	O
appearing	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
for	O
the	O
preservation	O
of	O
his	O
one	O
Life	O
the	O
Jury	O
returned	O
their	O
verdict	O
see	O
defendendo	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
filds	I-place
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
servaut	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
serveral	O
rings	O
aprons	O
stockings	O
scarfs	O
hods	O
Linnen	O
&	O
c	O
:	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
tryal	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
Custodie	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
yet	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
not	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
nurst	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
pety	O
Larcenary	O
,	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
indictmet	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloak	O
at	O
Hampsted	B-place
on	O
the	O
13	O
instant	O
from	O
Philp	B-pers
Frond	I-pers
Esp	O
.	O
which	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
greatly	O
denying	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Stockery	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
valued	O
at	O
5.	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabat	B-pers
Shipton	I-pers
of	O
Clarkenwell	B-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
instant	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
posstiue	O
proof	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
finding	O
the	O
prisones	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
dore	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
drink	O
after	O
which	O
being	O
abovt	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
recning	O
found	O
his	O
mony	O
gon	O
but	O
she	O
soon	O
after	O
being	O
apprehhended	O
and	O
now	O
brought	O
up	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swere	O
positiuely	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lamber	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Horse-stealing	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
repreived	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Execu-	O
upon	O
his	O
former	O
Sentence	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
Goal	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
presentments	O
made	O
against	O
dissenting	O
Ministers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
dissenter	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Session	O
Peter	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lamber	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Horse-stealing	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
repreived	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Execu-	O
upon	O
his	O
former	O
Sentence	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
Goal	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
John	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
James	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susanah	O
Morgan	O
sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
whiped	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
