TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
following	O
;	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
Entered	O
according	O
to	O
ORDER	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
that	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
The	O
proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
&	O
wastcoat	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Allen	B-pers
Tuller	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryars	I-place
whereupon	O
it	O
was	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
her	O
Master	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
then	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
small	O
acquaintance	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
e	O
're	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
proof	O
appearing	O
to	O
confirme	O
what	O
she	O
Alledged	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
though	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
being	O
Likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Powis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
of	O
15	O
Pounds	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
a	O
kettle	O
,	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
spoons	O
peuter	O
plates	O
and	O
the	O
Like	O
on	O
the	O
7	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
of	O
Steptny	B-place
;	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
tryal	O
appearing	O
only	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pots	O
Lost	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
brazier	O
;	O
to	O
counter	O
ballance	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
pot	O
of	O
one	O
Jones	O
now	O
prisoner	O
in	O
new-gate	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Robery	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Market	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
trade	O
to	O
buy	O
things	O
at	O
second	O
hand	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
Mary	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mantu	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland-Sleeves	O
,	O
Porrengers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Webly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
supposed	O
now	O
be	O
her	O
confederate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
whose	O
custody	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
Permission	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistris	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Quarles	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Pette-Coat	O
,	O
Sleves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
her	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
now	O
hardly	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valued	O
at	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Palace-Yard	I-place
Westminster	B-place
,	O
to	O
which	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Womans	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
sworn	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
of	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
busie	O
below	O
stares	O
slid	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Balcony	O
and	O
Marched	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
but	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
bogled	O
in	O
her	O
Evidence	O
ere	O
she	O
would	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
court	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
tampered	O
with	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
the	O
better	O
know	O
him	O
Caused	O
hisgreat	O
Coat	O
to	O
be	O
pulled	O
off	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
those	O
the	O
person	O
wore	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
swore	O
him	O
possitively	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
no	O
way	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
once	O
before	O
pardoned	O
he	O
now	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
price	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Hertford-shire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
exposed	O
to	O
sail	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
fifty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
(	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
upon	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
,	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
for	O
thirty	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
and	O
Reputation	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
together	O
all	O
night	O
and	O
playing	O
at	O
Dice	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
mony	O
to	O
answer	O
his	O
loosing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
Cheat	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
offended	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
answer	O
it	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
breaking	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Lambs-Conduict	B-place
Field	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
fought	O
,	O
when	O
after	O
several	O
passes	O
Griffith	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
being	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
6	O
,	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
likewise	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
in	O
several	O
other	O
places	O
but	O
no	O
prepence	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Rosseston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Stephen	B-pers
Low	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
the	B-place
May-pole	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
quarrel	O
arising	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
taking	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
&	O
some	O
others	O
his	O
Companions	O
ware	O
abusing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
provocative	O
words	O
and	O
blows	O
passing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
Low	O
in	O
the	O
Brest	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
meeting	O
being	O
being	O
Accidental	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mischief	O
done	O
in	O
heat	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
but	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Beaver-Hat	O
valued	O
40	O
Shillings	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
Convicted	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bauts	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Haly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
,	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Cheap-side	B-place
,	O
of	O
6	O
twenty-shilling	O
pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
one	O
22	O
.	O
Shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
Barbary	O
piece	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
mony	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mathew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
past	O
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
three	O
Rings	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
16	O
.	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Mony	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
five	O
more	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drink	O
late	O
,	O
watched	O
their	O
oportunity	O
bound	O
the	O
Master	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
ever	O
else	O
they	O
layed	O
hands	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dores	O
,	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
departed	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Coply	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
grosly	O
abused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
all	O
the	O
intreaty	O
's	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Contrary	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
rest	O
satisfied	O
,	O
but	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
his	O
departure	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
would	O
oblige	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
conflict	O
Hern	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
within	O
an	O
hours	O
space	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
Richard	B-pers
Thacrell	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
tankard	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Indictments	O
under	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hugds	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
in	O
leadon-Hall-Street	O
who	O
upon	O
his	O
Araignment	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
it	O
was	O
Sworn	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
her	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
carrying	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
valued	O
at	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Stopt	O
though	O
upon	O
Search	O
the	O
said	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
conjectured	O
(	O
as	O
usual	O
it	O
is	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
receivers	O
at	O
hand	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
delivered	O
his	O
prize	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offendor	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
shooting	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
his	O
fellow	O
Soldier	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
(	O
as	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
)	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
set	O
Sentinel	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
an	O
other	O
Soldier	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
a	O
jesting	O
manner	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Rogue	O
Savage	O
lets	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
thinking	O
further	O
harm	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
Cocking	O
his	O
Piece	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
fired	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Bullet	O
entering	O
under	O
his	O
Short-Ribs	O
went	O
out	O
behind	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
within	O
two	O
hours	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
demanded	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
but	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
prevented	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
killing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
ought	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
such	O
frivolous	O
excuses	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
nor	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
took	O
his	O
Piece	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
Savage	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murther	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
likwise	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
a	O
Child	O
not	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
old	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
living	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Brandy	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
not	O
permitting	O
it	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
raling	O
and	O
abusing	O
her	O
after	O
a	O
gross	O
rate	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
she	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dores	O
but	O
not	O
satisfied	O
or	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
himself	O
)	O
fully	O
revenged	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
Endeavouring	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
missing	O
his	O
blow	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
purposely	O
is	O
uncertain	O
,	O
hit	O
the	O
Child	O
such	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
within	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
it	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
imagining	O
that	O
he	O
wilfully	O
struck	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Convent-Garden	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
of	O
an	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Throckmorton	I-pers
,	O
killed	O
by	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Stanier	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Stanier	O
being	O
fled	O
and	O
out-lawed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
were	O
these	O
house	O
the	O
deceased	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
somwhat	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
&	O
gave	O
several	O
abusive	O
words	O
to	O
Stanies	O
who	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rebulking	O
him	O
&	O
he	O
rufly	O
handling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Stanier	O
or	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
should	O
take	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
a	O
letter	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Stanier	O
at	O
the	O
Spring-Garden	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
fighting	O
Sir	O
William	O
was	O
slain	O
,	O
but	O
other	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Counter	O
ballancing	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
said	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Dukes-place	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Cliping	O
and	O
Coining	O
,	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
his	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
either	O
sort	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
yet	O
the	O
Actual	O
Coining	O
and	O
Cliping	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
upon	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
under	O
rates	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
,	O
were	O
6	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Viz	O
.	O
Henry	O
Conway	O
Hugh	O
Jones	O
,	O
Henry	O
Russeston	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Katharine	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
9	O
Ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mackril	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
Phillp	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
6	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentance	O
of	O
Death	O
;	O
Viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rigs	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
Robert	O
Savage	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lumbert	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
And	O
5	O
Sentanced	O
to	O
be	O
whiped	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
