TOKEN	NE
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
Of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
Which	O
Began	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
10	O
of	O
October	O
1683.	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
Where	O
divers	O
persons	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
HIGH-TREASON	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
Felony	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Misdemeanors	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Condemned	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
.	O
JOhn	B-pers
Derry	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
;	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
thus	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
working	O
together	O
(	O
being	O
Printer	O
s	O
by	O
Trade	O
)	O
upon	O
some	O
words	O
passing	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
Printers	O
Ball	O
,	O
drawing	O
blood	O
by	O
the	O
stroak	O
which	O
happening	O
on	O
the	O
27.	O
of	O
Joune	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
till	O
the	O
23	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
and	O
Chyrurgion	O
giving	O
Testimony	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
ways	O
occasioned	O
by	O
that	O
stroak	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paybody	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Horses	O
;	O
one	O
from	O
Sir	O
Adam	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tapin	I-pers
near	O
Darkin	B-place
in	I-place
Surry	I-place
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Sidny	B-pers
Vandelo	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Castor	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sidney	O
Vandelo	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
run	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
notorious	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
divers	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Lawful	O
and	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Maid-Servant	O
living	O
with	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
Clipping	O
divers	O
times	O
in	O
her	O
Closet	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
found	O
Clippings	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
Files	O
,	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
Aqua	O
Fortis	O
:	O
And	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Bond	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
Secrets	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
Clipped	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Convicted	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
divers	O
Instruments	O
and	O
some	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
were	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Against	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Malice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
in	O
Fine	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
received	O
he	O
Charge	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
10	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Horse	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
but	O
upon	O
refusing	O
to	O
toll	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
true	O
owner	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Thomas	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
ignorantly	O
upon	O
the	O
word	O
of	O
Parsons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
received	O
him	O
into	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Parsons	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
tryed	O
on	O
another	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Page	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
home	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Barrier	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ransden	I-pers
of	O
Chattam	B-place
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Dram-cups	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
50	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
for	O
London	O
by	O
water	O
,	O
his	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
givin	O
him	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
a	O
Legacy	O
of	O
15	O
pounds	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
found	O
tardy	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
long	O
laced	O
Scarf	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Haburley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
against	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Exchange	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
in	O
Foster-Lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
they	O
appeared	O
were	O
these	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watching	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
turned	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
snatched	O
the	O
Tankard	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
closely	O
pursued	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
alledged	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
mistook	O
he	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
permitted	O
the	O
Felon	O
to	O
escape	O
;	O
but	O
those	O
Allegations	O
being	O
confuted	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Stealing	O
and	O
Party	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Linsy	I-pers
at	O
Chelsy	B-place
,	O
of	O
Laced	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Mantles	O
,	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
what	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
a	O
Bakers	O
house	O
near	O
Newgate	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
former	O
Smith	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
tryed	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
although	O
he	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parliament	O
Robe	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
,	O
yet	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
since	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
allegation	O
rather	O
augmented	O
than	O
extenuated	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
John	O
Smith	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
William	O
Smith	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Piser	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Susan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
by	O
running	O
over	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
hinder	O
wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
turning	O
of	O
Russel	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
wilful	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Children	O
warning	O
to	O
stand	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coach	O
crossing	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
further	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
alighted	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
back	O
his	O
Coach	O
;	O
upon	O
directions	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
three	O
Indictments	O
;	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
ravishing	O
Sibila	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
about	O
eighty	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
secondly	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
a	O
Ring	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
thirdly	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
house	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
party	O
ravished	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
sayhe	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
as	O
she	O
alledged	O
,	O
he	O
blindfolded	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
pounds	O
;	O
which	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
commitment	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Suits	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Crown	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
upon	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
upbraided	O
the	O
latter	O
with	O
his	O
sitting	O
the	O
Wooden-Horse	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
calling	O
him	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
Answer	O
returned	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
fitting	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
but	O
other	O
words	O
arising	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
presently	O
and	O
fought	O
,	O
when	O
after	O
divers	O
Passes	O
,	O
Hilton	O
was	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
body	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bernard	B-pers
Dison	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
clipping	O
divers	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
living	O
with	O
an	O
Oyl-Man	O
in	O
Watling-street	B-place
,	O
had	O
been	O
observed	O
to	O
have	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
not	O
pertinent	O
to	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
above	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
searching	O
for	O
old	O
Rags	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
Clippings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therewith	O
acquainted	O
her	O
other	O
fellow-Servant	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
other	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
greatly	O
concerned	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
them	O
occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
Clipping	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mony	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hanks	I-pers
,	O
from	O
out	O
the	O
Cabin	O
of	O
his	O
Ship	O
lying	O
in	O
Billings-gate	B-place
Dock	I-place
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cabin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Bag	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bag	O
he	O
had	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Bag	O
afterwards	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fitz-James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ruth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
;	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
being	O
these	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Welsh	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
fact	O
committed	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
at	O
landing	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
's	O
promising	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
latter	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
nothing	O
further	O
was	O
attempted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fitz	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ruth	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Welsh	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
promise	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
begged	O
his	O
Pardon	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Welsh	O
afterwards	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
depart	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
which	O
he	O
seemed	O
shy	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
promise	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
Animosities	O
that	O
might	O
create	O
a	O
quarrel	O
were	O
laid	O
aside	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
drinking	O
diversGlasses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
drink	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ruth	O
began	O
to	O
pick	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
spoken	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
out	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
Words	O
to	O
arise	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
Glasses	O
of	O
Wine	O
were	O
thrown	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Action	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ruth	O
Run	O
Mr.	O
Welsh	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
But	O
a	O
seeming	O
Friendship	O
appearing	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fitz-James	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
actually	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Ruth	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fenchurch-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Drawer	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Tavern	O
,	O
they	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Three-pence	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
a	O
Company	O
that	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
Encounter	O
,	O
Harding	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
languishing	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Instant	O
,	O
died	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
fought	O
with	O
him	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
was	O
Jacob	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Standback	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
Two	O
Cups	O
,	O
Four	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
in	O
West-Smithfield	B-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Plate	O
,	O
upon	O
putting	O
out	O
Bills	O
,	O
was	O
discovered	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
Prisoner	O
owning	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitting	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
she	O
onely	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
Five	O
pound	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
Against	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
no	O
sooner	O
had	O
a	O
Tankard	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
alone	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
slipped	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
within	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
and	O
Committed	O
,	O
he	O
by	O
Letter	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Delevere	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Seventeen	O
Shillings	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Agriman	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carleton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
appeared	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
,	O
affronted	O
by	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
kept	O
Bullies	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bolger	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
to	O
vindicate	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
ere	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
words	O
passing	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Bolger	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Bolger	O
thereupon	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
broke	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Bolger	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Presbyterian	O
plot	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
Plot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
one	O
Owen	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Quarles	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elenor	B-pers
Price	I-pers
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
into	O
which	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
120	O
l.	O
as	O
also	O
two	O
Bonds	O
;	O
which	O
Robbery	O
Temple	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
Quarles	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Convicted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
and	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
divers	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Silver-dust	O
,	O
Shears	O
,	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
Running-pots	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
;	O
as	O
also	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
Silver	O
Filings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
newly	O
Clipped	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
in	O
conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Eglestone	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
in	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Crevat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Reynold	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
,	O
Four	O
Dissenting	O
Ministers	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
,	O
Whether	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
?	O
But	O
they	O
refusing	O
,	O
their	O
Refusals	O
were	O
Recorded	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Pramunire	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Petty	O
Jury	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
discharged	O
,	O
their	O
Tryals	O
were	O
deferred	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
tendered	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
words	O
mentioned	O
therein	O
,	O
Asserting	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Rightful	O
Title	O
to	O
these	O
Realms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Dominions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Pope	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
or	O
Jurisdiction	O
therein	O
,	O
he	O
bogled	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
proceed	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Re-manded	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
having	O
been	O
taken	O
about	O
Yorkshire	O
for	O
Rumbold	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Oath	O
tender	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
difficulty	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
This	O
Sessions	O
Eighteen	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
Sidny	O
Vandelo	O
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paybody	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greens	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Quarles	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Rutler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Hair	O
;	O
The	O
last	O
Two	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
Francis	O
Eglestone	O
was	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Crown	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Piser	I-pers
being	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Burning	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	B-pers
,	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
Valour	O
,	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
Wil	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Humph	O
.	O
Hygins	O
.	O
Six	O
were	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Delevert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peech	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
having	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
thereunto	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
was	O
awarded	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
during	O
his	O
Majesties	O
pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
Chattels	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
seized	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
a	O
hundred	O
Marks	O
,	O
sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
