TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1683/4	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
35th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1684.	O
the	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
Pannels	O
Returned	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
several	O
Juries	O
)	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
to	O
Trial	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Henry	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Doctors	B-place
Commons	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
sitting	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
opposition	O
run	O
Dickenson	O
through	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
's	O
Brother	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
of	O
a	O
Difference	O
had	O
hapned	O
between	O
them	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
false	O
Dice	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
,	O
Dickenson	O
alledged	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
wronged	O
at	O
Play	O
,	O
either	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
had	O
thereupon	O
reported	O
Scarlet	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Sharper	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
all	O
his	O
Friends	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
:	O
To	O
revenge	O
which	O
Reproach	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
to	O
Fight	O
and	O
Kill	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
produced	O
a	O
real	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
first	O
drew	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
disagreeing	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
circumstances	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Scarlet	O
himself	O
prayed	O
Judgment	O
:	O
But	O
an	O
Appeal	O
being	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
as	O
next	O
Heir	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
allowed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
thereupon	O
continued	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Valor	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Mony	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mincham	I-pers
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Fleet	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
of	O
about	O
Thirty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goldsmiths	O
Servant	O
Swore	O
it	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
telling	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bag	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
Valor	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
snatch't	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Servant	O
pursuing	O
him	O
speedily	O
,	O
overtook	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Point	O
Crevat	O
off	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
near	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
being	O
seized	O
whilst	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver-handled	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rolson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Twenty	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Shopkeeper	B-pers
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Stringer	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
pretending	O
to	O
Buy	O
Cloth	O
;	O
but	O
disliking	O
what	O
was	O
shewn	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
other	O
sorts	O
were	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
companions	O
therein	O
,	O
Stringer	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
and	O
Mistress	B-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bury	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
some	O
Drawers	O
,	O
steal	O
out	O
37	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
also	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Band	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
is	O
found	O
guilty	O
thereof	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Belshar	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harris	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harrison	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Foot-Pads	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harrow	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Napkin	O
,	O
a	O
Womans	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
from	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
With	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
:	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
by	O
four	O
foot-Pads	O
with	O
great	O
Clubs	O
,	O
who	O
unawares	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
White	O
knock't	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
bruised	O
his	O
head	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
made	O
their	O
escapes	O
:	O
But	O
many	O
Robberies	O
having	O
in	O
those	O
parts	O
been	O
committed	O
by	O
four	O
such	O
Club	O
men	O
,	O
some	O
Country-men	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Foot	O
steps	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Snow	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
useful	O
to	O
follow	O
a	O
track	O
;	O
they	O
traced	O
them	O
above	O
five	O
Miles	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
a	O
Hay-Rick	O
,	O
whereupon	O
striking	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
four	O
Foot	O
strolers	O
leaped	O
out	O
,	O
two	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
their	O
four	O
Clubs	O
with	O
the	O
Cloak	O
of	O
Mary	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coopers	O
Adz	O
.	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Hayrick	O
which	O
Adz	O
.	O
John	O
Belshar	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
behaved	O
themselves	O
very	O
rudely	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
hold	O
up	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
until	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
thereto	O
by	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
pretending	O
much	O
Innocency	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Lundey	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Blew	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
cloth	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Campaine	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Disne	B-pers
Rooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Lewis	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
a	O
Carpenter	O
as	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Work	O
;	O
somewhere	O
near	O
So-ho	O
;	O
It	O
proved	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Trial	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mountague	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
some	O
Treat	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mullinax	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
those	O
Women	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
provocation	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
Brian	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
Died	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
but	O
such	O
probable	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
such	O
Credit	O
thereto	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
find	O
Mr.	O
Mountague	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
in	O
Hungerford	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
or	O
near	O
thereto	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
casually	O
by	O
some	O
provocation	O
given	O
by	O
Young	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Red-Coat	O
Soldier	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
James	B-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
that	O
Lorrain	O
who	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
did	O
there	O
kick	O
Gregory	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
Gregory	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
Lorrain	O
followed	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
cutting	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
Kill	O
or	O
be	O
Killed	O
:	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
Gregory	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Plank	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Nine	O
Pound	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pulchers	I-place
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
his	O
Mother	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
his	O
Father-in-law	O
:	O
)	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
being	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
gift	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
:	O
Bernard	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Williams	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sydens	I-pers
;	O
also	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grayham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Grayham	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Aiders	O
,	O
Abetters	O
and	O
Comforters	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Grayhams	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
late	O
a	O
Drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Fulchers	O
Church	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grayham	I-pers
had	O
some	O
difference	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
upon	O
the	O
next	O
Stand	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
came	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sydens	I-pers
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
Candle	O
,	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
juncture	O
of	O
their	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
Sydens	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
suddenly	O
died	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Three	O
persons	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
:	O
And	O
by	O
circumstances	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
sweared	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
with	O
Fat	O
or	O
Grease	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Inches	O
next	O
the	O
point	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
wound	O
of	O
that	O
depth	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
Sydens	O
Belly	O
:	O
That	O
none	O
else	O
had	O
Swords	O
but	O
those	O
Three	O
.	O
Many	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Trial	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
exactly	O
herein	O
particularized	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Two	O
Grayham	O
's	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Claybord	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Claypole	O
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
effected	O
by	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
weeks	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
pretendeda	O
dislike	O
:	O
and	O
at	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Gown	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Pickpocket	O
)	O
was	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
now	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Ten	O
pound	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Ralphson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Non-conformist	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Writing	O
,	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
an	O
Unlawful	O
,	O
Malicious	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
,	O
Intituted	O
,	O
An	O
Apology	O
for	O
Gods	O
Worship	O
and	O
Worshippers	O
:	O
But	O
containing	O
most	O
Infamous	O
Reflections	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
and	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
City	O
Marshal	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
those	O
Books	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ralphson	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Messengers	O
found	O
about	O
Fourscore	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Printers	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Cater	O
,	O
a	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Ralphson	O
had	O
contracted	O
to	O
Bind	O
200	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Paymaster	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ralphson	O
then	O
prayed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
might	O
be	O
Read	O
in	O
Latin	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
accordingly	O
granted	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Judges	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
would	O
be	O
Councel	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
Points	O
of	O
Law	O
therein	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
retained	O
Councel	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
denied	O
in	O
Cases	O
of	O
Trespass	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Ralphson	O
continued	O
to	O
ask	O
several	O
unusual	O
Questions	O
:	O
As	O
by	O
what	O
Warrant	O
the	O
Marshal	O
came	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
?	O
Whether	O
they	O
could	O
Swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Publisher	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Written	O
,	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
Publlisht	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
void	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thing	O
not	O
attainable	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
:	O
Which	O
Questions	O
being	O
all	O
very	O
easily	O
Answered	O
.	O
He	O
yet	O
continued	O
to	O
use	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
admired	O
that	O
any	O
Protestant	O
Court	O
should	O
think	O
his	O
Book	O
a	O
Reflection	O
;	O
pretending	O
it	O
only	O
tended	O
to	O
disclaim	O
all	O
Jesuitical	O
Clangs	O
and	O
Cabals	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
detected	O
those	O
fallacies	O
:	O
and	O
discovered	O
that	O
the	O
word	O
Protestant	O
,	O
is	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Ill	O
Designs	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
none	O
were	O
True	O
Protestants	O
but	O
such	O
as	O
lived	O
in	O
contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Laws	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Ralphson	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Publishing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Writing	O
or	O
Printing	O
the	O
said	O
Libel	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
de	I-pers
Lawn	I-pers
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
School-master	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Writing	O
,	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
another	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Nonconformists	O
Plea	O
:	O
containing	O
very	O
great	O
reflections	O
against	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Church	O
Government	O
by	O
Law	O
established	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Offence	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Griffyth	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Griffin	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
four	O
Non-conformist	O
Minister	O
s	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
been	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
refusal	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
lawfully	O
tendred	O
in	O
open	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
observed	O
concerning	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Evasive	O
Defence	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
positively	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dillan	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Hester	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Sayre	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tooth	O
Picker	O
,	O
valued	O
4	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
Case	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth	O
picker	O
,	O
valued	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Thimble	O
,	O
valued	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
;	O
and	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sayre	I-pers
is	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Evidence	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
along	O
near	O
the	O
French	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Coats	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
wherein	O
were	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
hanging	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Dillan	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
violently	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
other	O
Evidence	O
was	O
also	O
given	O
,	O
which	O
cohered	O
there-with	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
so	O
apparent	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Tooker	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
chiefly	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
Spoon	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Horner	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
or	O
small	O
Salesman	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
Shop	O
about	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
a	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
lodg	O
a	O
considerable	O
distance	O
therefrom	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Shop	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
great	O
Coats	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Wrights	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Charter-House	O
Lane	O
,	O
which	O
Wright	O
he	O
first	O
apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
Fellony	O
;	O
and	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
continues	O
upon	O
Wright	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
acted	O
fairly	O
therein	O
;	O
by	O
reason	O
,	O
That	O
although	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
paid	O
but	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
was	O
Sworn	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
Thirty	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Francis	O
Jennings	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
onely	O
accompanied	O
Mary	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
who	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
albeit	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
in	O
Wright	O
's	O
House	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
her	O
honest	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
pains	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Jennings	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	O
Belshar	O
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Harris	O
,	O
alias	O
,	O
Harrison	O
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
herein	O
before	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
Convicted	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
other	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hornsey	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Helder	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Poulterers	O
Man	O
,	O
Two	O
Geldings	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
Turkies	O
,	O
Capons	O
,	O
Chickens	O
,	O
Larks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Fowls	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Two	O
several	O
Men	B-pers
,	O
who	O
intrusted	O
the	O
said	O
Helder	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
Also	O
they	O
dragged	O
Helder	O
into	O
a	O
Wood	O
,	O
Gagged	O
and	O
Bound	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Luteners-lane	O
near	O
Holborn	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
harbouring	O
the	O
said	O
Robbers	O
:	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hamper	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Belshar	I-pers
found	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Capons	O
being	O
roasting	O
for	O
their	O
Supper	O
.	O
The	O
Evidencewas	O
not	O
clear	O
against	O
Massey	O
,	O
though	O
much	O
suspected	O
:	O
These	O
Robberies	O
were	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
four	O
Foot	O
Pads	O
herein	O
before	O
mentioned	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Hay-reek	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
John	O
Belshar	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
these	O
last	O
Robberies	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Roger	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Clanshey	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Chamlet	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
seven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver-spoon	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
concerning	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Spoon	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
Proof	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
the	O
Peruke	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
defence	O
,	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
Holland	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Barber	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Coat	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Christmas	O
Holy-days	O
he	O
presumed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Peruke	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Pretence	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
herein	O
already	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
Convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Rolson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Tryed	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
probable	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Five	O
and	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip't	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ustick	I-pers
,	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
such	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
Sold	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
alledged	O
she	O
Bought	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Broker	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
full	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
worth	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
hapned	O
to	O
Buy	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Bennison	O
is	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
cheating	O
John	B-pers
Petteson	I-pers
of	O
Two	O
new	O
Beaver	O
Hats	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wa	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
harbouring	O
Pick	O
pockets	O
and	O
other	O
bad	O
people	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Matkelon	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Twisdill	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Monteth	I-pers
,	O
five	O
Scotch	O
men	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
Taylor	O
s	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
obstinately	O
refusing	O
the	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
or	O
Obedience	O
,	O
when	O
lawfully	O
tendred	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hanscomb	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
thereof	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
from	O
a	O
Fringe	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
revengeful	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
first	O
Indicted	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bawd	O
,	O
Williams	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
rough	O
Tallow	O
from	O
a	O
Tallow	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
s	O
Shop	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Hillam	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Tedman	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
was	O
thereof	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Which	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Eight	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jacob	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Plank	I-pers
(	O
or	O
Flank	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Belshar	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Dillan	I-pers
.	O
Seven	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
,	O
Claybord	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lundey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Valer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
:	O
Francis	B-pers
Clenshee	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hillam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Izabel	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
others	O
tho	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
were	O
set	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thinking	O
fit	O
further	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
their	O
Crimes	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scarles	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	B-pers
both	O
made	O
application	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Clergy	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
is	O
deferred	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
Appeals	O
are	O
brought	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Matkelon	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Twisdal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Monteth	I-pers
received	O
Sentence	O
as	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
Pramunire	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Ralphson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Delawne	I-pers
,	O
are	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
Pay	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
100	O
Marks	O
:	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behavior	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
so	O
many	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
part	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
Libels	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
either	O
Seized	O
by	O
the	O
Messenger	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
Burnt	O
by	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
common	O
Hangman	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
at	O
Exchange-time	O
.	O
The	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
served	O
at	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
discharged	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
Loyal	O
Presentment	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
Publisht	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
.	O
