TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
8th	O
.	O
and	O
9th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
Eighth	O
and	O
Ninth	O
days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1684	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
:	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Keywarden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dyton	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Humfry	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Ainger	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
Chr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawlet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
Gerald	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Crape	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Salesman	O
,	O
upon	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
proveing	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Gown	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Trick	O
put	O
upon	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
Salesman	O
forced	O
to	O
repay	O
them	O
the	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
also	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
forthwith	O
set	O
at	O
Liberty	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
Fees	O
:	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
accordingly	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Thief	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
whose	O
House	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
hired	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
their	O
Service	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
getting	O
up	O
early	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Swinfield	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
also	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
on	O
the	O
11.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
telling	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
lately	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
they	O
sending	O
to	O
inquire	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
hired	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
newly	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
Servant	O
(	O
it	O
appearing	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
gotten	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
whose	O
good	O
Name	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
manage	O
her	O
Deceit	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
hired	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
her	O
former	O
Service	O
,	O
stay	O
'd	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
running	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
early	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
Mr	O
Richard	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
bythe	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Pallard	I-pers
,	O
having	O
used	O
the	O
like	O
Artifice	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
,	O
by	O
assuming	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Servant-Maid	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
from	O
this	O
Service	O
also	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Swinfield	O
,	O
being	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
carried	O
to	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Porters	O
Book	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Carrier	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Markman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Coife	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Bodkin	O
.	O
a	O
silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
a	O
Paiste-board	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
:	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Markman	I-pers
swearing	O
against	O
him	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Somerset	O
House	O
to	O
White	O
Hart	O
Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
having	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
behind	O
her	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
White	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Chr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Markam	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
into	O
whose	O
House	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Winterton	I-pers
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Key	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
about	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hinchly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Guy	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
Key	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Dodwell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dodwell	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Mathew	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
about	O
nine	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Palace-Yard	I-place
at	O
Westminster	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Washing	O
and	O
Scowring	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
but	O
14	O
s.	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bents	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
received	O
for	O
scowring	O
the	O
Irons	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
-	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bent	O
her	O
self	O
made	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
hidden	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
being	O
gone	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
found	O
the	O
fore-door	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
then	O
forewarned	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
she	O
missing	O
32	O
l.	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
a	O
Girl	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Girl	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
take	O
a	O
Glove	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
:	O
but	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bent	O
himself	O
being	O
called	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
his	O
Wives	O
Hoard	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
thereout	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
likewise	O
producing	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
their	O
honest	O
Reputation	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
indiscreet	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Irish-man	O
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
three	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
stole	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bycott	I-pers
of	O
Sohoe-fields	B-place
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
Bycott	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
whose	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
Hours	O
before	O
,	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
in	O
two	O
several	O
Trunks	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
they	O
first	O
drank	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
sent	O
first	O
one	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
of	O
their	O
Companions	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Street-door	O
to	O
sing	O
a	O
Ballad	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
that	O
Noise	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
when	O
they	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Locks	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Trunk	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
this	O
Linch	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Combes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
Company	O
,	O
was	O
more	O
ingenuous	O
than	O
he	O
in	O
picking	O
of	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
apparent	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
,	O
Linch	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Vallance	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Pinner	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Throne	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Maid-Servant	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Amors	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Veasey	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
thus	O
;	O
That	O
this	O
Veasey	O
being	O
a	O
Kentish	O
Man	O
newly	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
lodging	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
Amors	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Country	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
desire	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
Veasey	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
up	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
against	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Amors	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
a	O
Vintner	O
:	O
without	B-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Daughter	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Year	O
old	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
many	O
Circumstances	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
first	O
the	O
Mother	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Abused	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
:	O
a	O
second	O
Witness	O
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Sick	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
put	O
clean	O
Linen	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
borrow	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
foul	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
it	O
found	O
some	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
dealing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
asked	O
the	O
Child	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
;	O
to	O
whomshe	O
answered	O
Thomas	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
asking	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
replied	O
yes	O
Aunt	O
5	O
times	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
also	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
forced	O
her	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
her	O
self	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
Thomas	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Chamber	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
lay	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
commonly	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rape	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Domingo-De-la-Sarda	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Merchant	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
to	O
Joan	B-pers
Kellam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
now	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Priscila	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
thereof	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
;	O
but	O
oblieged	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jeffryes	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
:	O
the	O
said	O
Yates	O
alledged	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
by	O
one	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
William	O
Jeffryes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
Jeffryes	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
(	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
recieved	O
his	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
)	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
Six	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
Snuff-Dish	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
Mustard-Box	O
,	O
Pepper-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Candle-Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
Fruit-Dish	O
and	O
Ladle	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
Silver	O
;	O
with	O
two	O
Sattin	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coghill	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Esq	O
;	O
Coghill	O
and	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
two	O
Maid-Servants	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
only	O
left	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
four	O
Men	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
opened	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
,	O
they	O
rushed	O
in	O
,	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
abuseing	O
the	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
Breaking	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Shaw	O
had	O
Imployed	O
one	O
Carr	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
Sell	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
which	O
Carr	O
being	O
questioned	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
produced	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
Shaw	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
further	O
enquiry	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
Stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Coghill	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
Shaw	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Bennets	I-place
Fink	I-place
London	O
,	O
into	O
whose	O
shop	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Drink	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cup	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
length	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
a	O
Portuguise	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Turqueno	I-pers
,	O
which	O
upon	O
hearing	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Partner	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	B-pers
Turqueno	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
left	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
hands	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Arnock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-woman	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philipin	I-pers
:	O
also	O
Anthony	B-pers
Tizier	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
with	O
Jane	O
Arnock	O
,	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
John	O
Philipin	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Jane	O
Arnock	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
using	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
supposed	O
she	O
had	O
gotten	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
observable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
his	O
glass	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
Theives	O
above	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Chest	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Windows	O
being	O
broken	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
evident	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
upon	O
apprehending	O
her	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
15	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Tizier	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
and	O
Mortack	B-pers
Downey	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Rich	O
.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
did	O
Kill	O
and	O
murder	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Pickadilly	B-place
:	O
likewise	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Fairbank	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fairbank	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
appeared	O
thus	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Woman	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
to	O
pass	O
,	O
selling	O
Ale	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Chandles	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
)	O
was	O
about	O
Ten	O
a-clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Lodger	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
over-head	O
found	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Legs	O
tyed	O
,	O
hanging	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
her	O
Neck	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
a	O
bloody	O
Handkerchief	O
found	O
near	O
her	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
thrust	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
forcibly	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Teeth	O
were	O
struck	O
in	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
thought	O
might	O
occasion	O
the	O
Blood	O
:	O
also	O
her	O
Chest	O
,	O
open	O
all	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
before	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Murder	O
committed	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
Tooley	O
's	O
Wife	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
Tooley	O
's	O
Wife	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up-stairs	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
hearkning	O
at	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
heard	O
them	O
telling	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
see	O
them	O
share	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
throw	O
Dice	O
for	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
;	O
that	O
Wise	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
gold	O
Buttons	O
over	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
Suit	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Tooley	O
gave	O
to	O
his	O
said	O
Wife	O
40	O
s.	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
indebted	O
1	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
receive	O
Beveridge	O
of	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
Neighbour	O
brought	O
another	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
found	O
Wise	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
on	O
a	O
Hair-Ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
have	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Widdow	O
Fairbank	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Tooley	O
,	O
seeing	O
to	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
new	O
Lodgings	O
whither	O
he	O
intended	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
meeting	O
with	O
Mortack	O
Downey	O
,	O
they	O
whispered	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
some	O
greater	O
Fear	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Tide-house	O
till	O
the	O
Boat	O
went	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Ostend	O
;	O
that	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
they	O
returned	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
still	O
disquieted	O
within	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
for	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Paris	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
dying	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Priest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Jones	O
and	O
Wise	O
,	O
did	O
commit	O
the	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Tooley	O
swearing	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Wise	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
Candle	O
whilst	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
full	O
Evidence	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
was	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
Downey	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Brocksbank	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Theodore	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
Theodore	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
home	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
prevailed	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
also	O
some	O
spoke	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Gatefield	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Buggs	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Revell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edmond	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Sureties	O
required	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cheshyre	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
half	O
a	O
firking	O
of	O
Sope	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
Tann	O
'd	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Strongwaters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
in	O
Aldersgatestreet	B-place
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
:	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
were	O
sat	O
by	O
to	O
be	O
Tried	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mongomery	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
Surrendred	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
Committed	O
for	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Squire	O
Norbourn	O
,	O
being	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
middle-Temple	O
London	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Council	O
,	O
Moved	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
in	O
regard	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Mongomery	O
had	O
lately	O
rendred	O
himself	O
.	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
not	O
prepared	O
;	O
desired	O
therefore	O
the	O
Trial	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
Granted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Five	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Arnock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
And	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
for	O
three	O
several	O
Felonies	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
Pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
and	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
One	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
.	O
One	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
set	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Sentenced	O
.	O
