TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1684	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Montegue	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Judges	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
tryed	O
before	O
them	O
(	O
and	O
Judgment	O
given	O
thereon	O
)	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
James	B-pers
Wolden	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Souldier	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Captain	O
)	O
having	O
been	O
retained	O
into	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
Retention	O
and	O
receiving	O
of	O
Wages	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
(	O
or	O
other	O
proper	O
Officer	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
)	O
did	O
withdraw	O
himself	O
and	O
depart	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Service	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
not	O
returning	O
untill	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
following	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
arrested	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
Ensign	O
,	O
and	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
were	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Retained	O
him	O
at	O
Dover	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
duely	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Wages	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
being	O
commanded	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
he	O
from	O
thence	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
for	O
that	O
first	O
Offence	O
before	O
a	O
Court	O
Marshal	O
,	O
upon	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
forgiven	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
run	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
re-taken	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Special	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
retained	O
into	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Wages	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
departed	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterward	O
retaken	O
in	O
London	O
:	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
determined	O
by	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
whither	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Felony	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
24	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Alamode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooth	I-pers
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Den	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
another	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pierce	I-pers
:	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Leneve	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
16	O
s.	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
12	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Farambrass	B-pers
Styth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mounsan	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Volor	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bason	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
18	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
pot	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candle-sticks	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
first	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
said	O
plate	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
:	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
her	O
Maid	O
Servants	O
and	O
one	O
Youth	O
,	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
Elizabeth	O
Volor	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
searching	O
further	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
tyed	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
presume	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
so	O
removed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Passage	O
was	O
clear	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denying	O
she	O
was	O
any	O
higher	O
than	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
thinking	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
further	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vos	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Caudle-Cup	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Olives	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
big	O
Girl	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
Warren	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
to	O
bring	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
under	O
her	O
Scarf	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecka	O
Basee	O
(	O
or	O
Basen	O
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black-silk	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Market	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
and	I-place
Mouth	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
followed	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
they	O
alledge	O
the	O
Lace	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
buy	O
at	O
her	O
Price	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Lace	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Knightly	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Womans	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
pair	O
of	O
Stayes	O
,	O
and	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
18	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
those	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
Knightly	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
lying	O
two	O
Stairs	O
above	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
by	O
him	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
however	O
acquitted	O
because	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
he	O
did	O
remove	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bampfield	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shuttle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
six	O
Dowlas	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
several	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
twelve	O
Night-Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
Pillowbere	O
,	O
two	O
double	O
Clouts	O
,	O
two	O
Calico	O
hoods	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
many	O
Circumstances	O
which	O
gave	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
their	O
flying	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
Custody	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
therefore	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
astriped	O
Gause	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
spotted	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Scarse	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
:	O
likewise	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
:	O
both	O
which	O
Felonies	O
,	O
were	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereof	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
not	O
weighing	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
her	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
minded	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Liege	O
People	O
,	O
falsly	O
and	O
feloniously	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
Make	O
,	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
twelve	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tinn	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
false	O
Metals	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Likeness	O
and	O
Similitude	O
of	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
like	O
counterfeit	O
Metal	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Likeness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Six-Pences	O
:	O
which	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
diverse	O
times	O
seen	O
her	O
make	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
by	O
melting	O
first	O
a	O
certain	O
Quantiy	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Metals	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
much	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
weighed	O
about	O
a	O
Pound	O
weight	O
)	O
in	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Porringer	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
Vessel	O
,	O
afterwards	O
pouring	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
when	O
hot	O
,	O
into	O
Moulds	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
which	O
fashioned	O
it	O
like	O
the	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-Pences	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Witnesses	O
likewise	O
confess	O
d	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
much	O
of	O
that	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
therefore	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Evidence	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Horse	O
standing	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Albans-street	I-place
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Woolen	O
from	O
the	O
Tenters	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cloath-worker	O
:	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
that	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
when	O
pursued	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
denied	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
Clooth	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
20	O
other	O
People	O
were	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
those	O
Fields	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
which	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
in	O
probability	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tibbolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
Butcher	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
coloured	O
Red	O
,	O
price	O
6	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Orlando	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Servants	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Knight	O
witnessed	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Cow	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Ground	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Skin	O
of	O
their	O
Masters	O
Cow	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
a	O
Tanner	O
,	O
which	O
Gibbons	O
alledgedhe	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tibbolds	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
Stanes	O
Market	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
that	O
see	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tibbolds	I-pers
,	O
kill	O
and	O
dress	O
a	O
Red	O
Cow	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
was	O
stoln	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
affirmed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
to	O
some	O
Market	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
passed	O
through	O
Sir	O
Orlando	O
Gee	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
a	O
Red	O
Cow	O
being	O
laid	O
,	O
Clark	O
raised	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
forwards	O
to	O
their	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Bull	O
,	O
with	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Sheep	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
see	O
them	O
kill	O
a	O
Red	O
Cow	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
themselves	O
both	O
denyed	O
it	O
.	O
Clark	O
said	O
the	O
Cow	O
was	O
drest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
Tibbolds	O
alledged	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
selling	O
him	O
half	O
this	O
Cow	O
,	O
saying	O
be	O
bought	O
her	O
at	O
Hamersmith	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
stay	O
and	O
help	O
dress	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
shares	O
:	O
Tibbolds	O
also	O
confest	O
the	O
selling	O
the	O
Skin	O
for	O
Clark	O
.	O
In	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
Clark	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Tibbolds	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Bastard-Child	O
,	O
by	O
smothering	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
Blankets	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
privately	O
delivered	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
locking	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Trunk	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
dead-born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
delivered	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
other	O
Woman	O
denying	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
along	O
denying	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
though	O
some	O
presumption	O
might	O
be	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
,	O
yet	O
her	O
concealing	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Woman	O
away	O
,	O
locking	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Trunck	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sufficient	O
to	O
kill	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Enos	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
living	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Katherines	I-place
Lane	I-place
near	I-place
Tower-Hill	I-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Enos	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
met	O
this	O
Jane	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Parkers	O
,	O
Enos	O
pretending	O
to	O
hire	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Tatnam	O
Court	O
,	O
having	O
Tillage	O
and	O
Pasture-ground	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
after	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Enos	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Norman	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
Taylor	O
being	O
a	O
Coach-man	O
who	O
brought	O
Wheeler	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
to	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
being	O
therein	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
carried	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Codde	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Peticoats	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Viccars	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
.	O
Codde	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Viccars	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
Vicarr	O
's	O
Wife	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
otherwise	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Right	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Right	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
lodging	O
at	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dyton	I-pers
s	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
took	O
their	O
Opportunity	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
Dyton	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
it	O
was	O
adjudged	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
properly	O
be	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Axtel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
about	O
ten	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Vintner	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
it	O
was	O
drawing	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
nimble	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
.	O
Also	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Axtel	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rymand	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Seth	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
Etlin	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Brandford	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Lambe	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
several	O
Men	O
to	O
him	O
unknown	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
putting	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
into	O
great	O
fear	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
particularly	O
suspecting	O
a	O
Maid-Servant	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
accessary	O
with	O
the	O
Robbers	O
and	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rymond	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
that	O
Parish	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Maids	O
Sweet	O
heart	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
frequented	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
might	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
accordingly	O
and	O
himself	O
made	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
Conscience	O
believed	O
Rymond	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
threatning	O
his	O
Life	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
afterwards	O
rifled	O
his	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Proportion	O
,	O
and	O
Hair	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
Rymond	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
till	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
gotten	O
in	O
his	O
Masters	O
Service	O
,	O
the	O
Keys	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
carried	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mistaken	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Papers	O
containing	O
fifteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
in	O
Gray's-Inn	B-place
Lane	I-place
:	O
albeit	O
positively	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
yet	O
other	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
appearing	O
for	O
Andrews	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
Testimony	O
rendring	O
it	O
very	O
possible	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrews	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Close	I-pers
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Trevers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Inn-keeper	O
at	O
Wood-green	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Tatenham	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
in	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
250	O
l.	O
which	O
they	O
effected	O
,	O
by	O
going	O
first	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
passing	O
towards	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
being	O
habited	O
as	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Inn-keeper	O
making	O
much	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
good	O
Guests	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
assoon	O
as	O
it	O
grew	O
dark	O
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Trevers	I-pers
lett	O
in	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
them	O
to	O
bind	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
for	O
comforting	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
harbouring	O
them	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
found	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
found	O
with	O
Mary	O
Kelley	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
the	O
pretended	O
Wife	O
of	O
Hugh	O
Kelley	O
Trevers	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
was	O
or	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Habit	O
of	O
of	O
a	O
Granadeer	O
The	O
three	O
Men	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
Trevers	O
unbolted	O
a	O
Back	O
door	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
companions	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
Mary	O
Kelley	O
is	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse	O
to	O
a	O
sick	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Isabel	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
did	O
make	O
Discovery	O
to	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
might	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
believed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Gilman	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
fled	O
)	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
was	O
accessory	O
thereto	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
albeit	O
she	O
privately	O
since	O
frequented	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
managed	O
,	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Proof	O
was	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Baxter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
containing	O
many	O
Ells	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Linnen	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
New	B-place
Fish	I-place
street	I-place
:	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
Draper	O
seeing	O
him	O
snatch	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
made	O
such	O
quick	O
Pursuit	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Dowlas	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
a	O
common	O
Excuse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Lace	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
by	O
snatching	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Lumbard-street	B-place
:	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Barker	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Composition	O
hath	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Butterman	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
pretending	O
himself	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Horn	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
he	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
away	O
a	O
Trunk	O
full	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
at	O
that	O
Tavern	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
cheated	O
her	O
thereof	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
known	O
amongst	O
the	O
Pick-Pocket	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Yorkshire	O
Kate	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
other	O
linnen	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Beam	O
and	O
a	O
Peck	O
Weight	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gander	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gandee	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Bridget	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ladbery	I-pers
,	O
robbed	O
John	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
the	O
said	O
Bridget	O
Sands	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
Gandee	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
suspected	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
also	O
been	O
formerly	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
having	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
Printing	O
a	O
seditions	O
Paper	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
Shall	O
I	O
,	O
Shall	O
I	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
is	O
sentenced	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Which	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Eight	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vos	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Close	I-pers
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Trevers	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gander	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gandee	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Seven	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leneeve	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Six	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Don	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Enos	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Codle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Axtel	I-pers
.	O
One	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
which	O
received	O
Sentence	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
sentenced	O
for	O
the	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Smith	O
;	O
upon	O
whom	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
having	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
Printing	O
a	O
seditions	O
Paper	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
Shall	O
I	O
,	O
Shall	O
I	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
is	O
sentenced	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Butterman	I-pers
is	O
sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Blew	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
caloured	O
his	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
5	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
