TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1683/4	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1684.	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Mountague	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
great	O
silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
silver	O
Candle	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Hamper	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
besides	O
44	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
Numbred	O
;	O
which	O
Felony	O
she	O
effected	O
by	O
hiring	O
her	O
self	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Powney	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Poultney	I-place
,	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
living	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
Michaelmass	O
last	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
following	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistris	O
being	O
gone	O
some	O
Journey	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
or	O
Chest	O
where	O
his	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
laid	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
thereof	O
,	O
fled	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
appearing	O
by	O
a	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Crimes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sorrel	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
,	O
living	O
at	O
a	O
Village	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
about	O
25	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
;	O
which	O
Gelding	O
the	O
said	O
Hills	O
leaving	O
in	O
his	O
said	O
stable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
arose	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
finding	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
immediately	O
hasted	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Market	O
day	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Rolph	O
leading	O
his	O
Gelding	O
about	O
the	O
Market	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
little	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Gelding	O
to	O
ride	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
restore	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Carebust	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
black	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
silk	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
being	O
left	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Country	O
Laceman	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Inn	O
in	O
Friday-street	B-place
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lace	O
Market	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
aTrunk	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
pickt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Cary	O
having	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Hostler	O
,	O
had	O
in	O
that	O
space	O
been	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Trunk	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
apprehended	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
afterwards	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rosse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
Purse	O
and	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
near	O
Pye-Corner	B-place
,	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
however	O
violently	O
snatcht	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
quick	O
pursuit	O
,	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
some	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
offered	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
on	O
pretence	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
:	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
being	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Hodskins	I-pers
,	O
hiring	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Sambroke	B-pers
in	O
Black-Friers	B-place
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
either	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
poverty	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
lay	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
small	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
relieve	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
being	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
one	O
laced	O
Crevat	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Mantle	O
,	O
15	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Damask	O
Table-Cloaths	O
,	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
one	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
diverse	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
drinking	O
together	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
parting	O
with	O
their	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
How	O
and	O
Jones	O
going	O
by	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
Jones	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
also	O
appearing	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
some	O
provocation	O
,	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
How	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pantreer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
rashly	O
driving	O
the	O
near	O
Wheels	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
over	O
the	O
said	O
Childs	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
pleading	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
extravagant	O
driving	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
full	O
speed	O
)	O
was	O
by	O
striving	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Fare	O
,	O
which	O
called	O
,	O
Coach	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Buzonne	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
,	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
also	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
very	O
hard	O
drinking	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
whispering	O
was	O
between	O
Symonds	O
and	O
Mead	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
doubtful	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
provocation	O
,	O
Symonds	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
Mead	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
first	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
and	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Symond	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
Mead	O
a	O
quarrelsom	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
conclusion	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Symonds	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
discourse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Marshfield	I-pers
,	O
living	O
near	O
Knights-bridge	B-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Marshfield	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
below	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
these	O
three	O
Fellows	O
cut	O
and	O
wounded	O
,	O
shooting	O
off	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
charged	O
with	O
Bullets	O
,	O
till	O
that	O
he	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
his	O
Son	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
fled	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
principally	O
the	O
leaving	O
his	O
Hat	O
behind	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
both	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
wear	O
,	O
Davis	O
having	O
been	O
their	O
Servant	O
formerly	O
,	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
personally	O
knew	O
Davis	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
disguise	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Patteson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kirk	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
six	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
his	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
diminishing	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
d.	O
The	O
most	O
material	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
Patteson	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
said	O
Landlady	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
connived	O
thereat	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
acted	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
procuring	O
her	O
broad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
changing	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
Clipt	O
;	O
their	O
manner	O
being	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
broad	O
Money	O
for	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
at	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
by	O
changing	O
their	O
clipt	O
Money	O
for	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
allowing	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
the	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
confessing	O
to	O
have	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
changed	O
away	O
great	O
Sums	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
Money	O
;	O
a	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
,	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
thereof	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
therefore	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
and	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Charlet	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
Branford	B-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
Twelve	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Mault	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
havebeen	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Mault	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
not	O
lockt	O
,	O
Charlet	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Landlady	O
was	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Oliver	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
25	O
s.	O
which	O
Cup	O
she	O
sold	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burchenall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
of	O
Totenham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sadler	O
in	O
London	O
produced	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
a	O
Maid	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Money-Box	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
quick	O
pursuit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Harpum	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
16	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Edward	O
the	O
Sixth	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
pieces	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
clipping	O
,	O
or	O
filling	O
away	O
Silver	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
d.	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
:	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Brazier	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Chelmesford-Goal	O
,	O
brought	O
from	O
thence	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
positively	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Harpum	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
Clip	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
also	O
seen	O
them	O
Clip	O
Money	O
,	O
melt	O
the	O
Clippings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
the	B-place
Swan	I-place
in	O
White-Fryers	B-place
.	O
He	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Edward	O
Harpum	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
said	O
Clippings	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
carried	O
such	O
melted	O
Silver	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
selling	O
him	O
sixteen	O
Ounces	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
The	O
Goldsmith	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
Peter	O
Brazier	O
had	O
two	O
several	O
times	O
brought	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
either	O
Harpum	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Harpum	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
dealings	O
with	O
Brazier	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
lending	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
never	O
restored	O
,	O
Harpum	O
threatned	O
to	O
Arrest	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
Evidence	O
in	O
revenge	O
,	O
for	O
threatning	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
also	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
conclusion	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Male-Infant	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
being	O
alive	O
,	O
did	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
,	O
[	O
filled	O
with	O
Urin	O
:	O
Excrements	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
filth	O
,	O
]	O
whereby	O
she	O
said	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
was	O
smothered	O
and	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
thereby	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
her	O
said	O
Infant	O
Bastard-Child	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
her	O
all	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
five	O
Months	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
did	O
by	O
that	O
illness	O
Miscarry	O
:	O
The	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
produced	O
one	O
Stafford	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
Wedlock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
circumstances	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rolston	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolridge	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
instant	O
February	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
by	O
him	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Mathias	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Twenty	O
Perukes	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
30	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Massey	O
having	O
a	O
Shop	O
under	O
St.	O
Bennet	O
Finck	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
commonly	O
at	O
Six	O
or	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
finding	O
it	O
open	O
at	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Massey	O
having	O
sometime	O
before	O
Christmass	O
turned	O
away	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Servant	O
;	O
Savage	O
,	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
and	O
Watt	O
,	O
meeting	O
his	O
said	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
direct	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
rob	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
bargained	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
10	O
s.	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
and	O
direct	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
late	O
Masters	O
shop	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Massey	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
accordingly	O
broken	O
up	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
Joan	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Perukes	O
about	O
her	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
made	O
discovery	O
where	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mathias	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Harding	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Nichols	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Wimes	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
effect	O
following	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
dined	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-head	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
it	O
also	O
hapned	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bushfield	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
watched	O
in	O
thither	O
by	O
some	O
Bailiffs	O
or	O
Marshals	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
imployed	O
to	O
Arrest	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
effect	O
which	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
Followers	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Tavern	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
John	O
Brown	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wimes	I-pers
,	O
two	O
other	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Officers	O
went	O
in	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
Wimes	O
,	O
through	O
mistake	O
,	O
runs	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
dined	O
,	O
and	O
rudely	O
seizing	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Bushfield	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
violence	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Wimes	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Parry	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
affirmed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
did	O
draw	O
it	O
and	O
pass	O
at	O
Wimes	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
his	O
death	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sword	O
being	O
out	O
;	O
in	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Gent	B-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Bridget	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Parkers-lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
quarrel	O
hapning	O
upon	O
the	O
Coachman	O
's	O
refusing	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
they	O
desired	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
place	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
further	O
:	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
the	O
Coachman	O
offered	O
them	O
very	O
great	O
provocation	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Testimony	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
several	O
worthy	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
had	O
been	O
always	O
accounted	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
acquitted	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
being	O
Indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Barbados	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
meeting	O
Katherine	B-pers
Guilford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asking	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Shore-ditch	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
show	O
her	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
led	O
her	O
the	O
furthest	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
hollow	O
way	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
Passengers	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
deliver	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
threatning	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
cut	O
and	O
otherwise	O
misuse	O
her	O
,	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
Four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
or	O
Four	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Katherine	O
Guilford	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
Seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
otherwise	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bringing	O
two	O
Clipt	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
Bread	O
and	O
other	O
Commodities	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
used	O
to	O
Clip	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Melting-Pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
such	O
like	O
Instruments	O
:	O
a	O
Warrant	O
being	O
therefore	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Implements	O
in	O
Conyers	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
and	O
Clippings	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Edward	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jane	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Parum	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Seth	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Vicar	O
of	O
Ely	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Brantford	I-place
;	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
being	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Loggins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Down	O
bed	O
and	O
Boulster	O
,	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
Fire-shovel	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Cardell	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
some	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
;	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
and	O
comforting	O
her	O
therein	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mary	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Aunt	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
mentioned	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
Paper	O
to	O
be	O
Convicted	O
)	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Williamson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
300	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
one	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
living	O
near	O
Gray's-Inn	B-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Servant	O
was	O
shutting	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Which	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Twelve	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
be	O
Drawn	O
upon	O
a	O
Hurdle	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
hang	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Neck	O
till	O
he	O
be	O
dead	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Patteson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
burnt	O
to	O
death	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Sickts	I-pers
,	O
Gerrard	O
Middleton	O
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barbados	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Amongst	O
which	O
Condemned	O
persons	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
Joan	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
being	O
thereupon	O
sworn	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
thereinto	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
to	O
be	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
Ten	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rolson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Buzoune	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Hodskins	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Logins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
;	O
Five	O
of	O
which	O
Ten	O
were	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Carehust	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Charlet	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Atlee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
.	O
One	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Burchenall	I-pers
.	O
